PHEEBS, CAN YOU HELP ME PICK OUT
AN ENGAGEMENT RING FOR MONICA?
I CAN'T FIGURE THIS OUT. IT'S SO HARD.
SHOULD I GET HER A TIFFANY CUT OR A PRINCESS CUT OR A... OW!
PAPER CUT!
NOW, HAVE YOU TOLD ANYONE ELSE?
NO. I DON'T WANT TO TELL ANYBODY ELSE
BECAUSE I DON'T WANT MONICA TO FIND OUT.
YOU TOLD ME.
WELL, THAT'S BECAUSE I TRUST YOU
AND YOU'RE ONE OF MY BEST FRIENDS
AND YOU WALKED IN ON ME
WHILE I WAS LOOKING AT RING BROCHURES.
YEAH, WELL, ONCE AGAIN, NOT KNOCKING PAYS OFF.
I ONLY WISH YOU HADN'T BEEN ON THE TOILET.
ME, TOO.
NOW, LET ME SEE.
IS THERE SUCH A THING AS A MONICA CUT?
BECAUSE THAT WOULD BE YOUR BEST BET.
HEY. HEY. HEY.
SO, CHANDLER, WANT TO GO
TO THE COFFEEHOUSE?
OH, ALL RIGHT.
YEAH, COFFEEHOUSE.
PERFECT. WE WERE JUST GOING
TO SEE IF YOU WANTED TO GO.
OH, WELL, WE DON'T BECAUSE WE GOT THE OTHER PLACE.
HOW RUDE.
OH, I'M SORRY.
GOOD.
ALTHOUGH, YOU KNOW, HE'S A PRIVATE GUY.
YOU KNOW, I WISH I COULD GET HIM
TO OPEN UP A LITTLE BIT, SHARE SOME FEELINGS.
THAT'S EASY.
YOU JUST HAVE TO THINK OF HIM
AS A JAR OF PICKLES THAT WON'T OPEN.
SO WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
I SHOULD RUN HIM UNDER SOME HOT WATER
AND BANG HIS HEAD AGAINST THE TABLE?
NO. THAT'S WHAT YOU DO
WHEN YOU WANT TO GET THE TRUTH OUT OF SOMEONE.
HI, HONEY. HI.
WATCH THIS.
OKAY.
HEY, PAUL. HI, PHOEBE.
SO, HOW ARE THINGS GOING WITH YOU?
CAN'T COMPLAIN.
LET'S GO. OKAY.
HEY! HI!
ROSS, GOOD TO SEE YOU, TOO.
HOW YOU DOING? GOOD. BYE.
OKAY, YOU TAKE CARE.
YEAH!
EW.
HEY, PHEEBS, WHAT WAS THE DEAL
WITH YOU AND CHANDLER BLOWING US OFF BEFORE?
YEAH, IT WAS SO WEIRD, HUH?
PHOEBE, WHY'D YOU DO IT?
I DIDN'T DO IT.
IT WAS CHANDLER.
HE'S... HE'S MAD AT YOU.
WHA...? WHY?
PLEASE. I THINK YOU KNOW WHY.
CAN'T THINK OF ANYTHING.
COME ON, ROSS.
YOU'RE A PALEONTOLOGIST.
DIG A LITTLE DEEPER.
WAIT A MINUTE.
IS IT BECAUSE JOEY AND I DIDN'T INVITE HIM
TO THAT KNICKS GAME A COUPLE OF WEEKS AGO?
DO YOU THINK THAT'S SOMETHING THAT HE'D BE MAD AT YOU FOR?
I GUESS IT COULD.
WELL, THEN, I THINK THAT'S IT.
WELL, IF HE'S ANGRY
HE REALLY SHOULDN'T JUST COVER IT UP.
I WISH HE WOULD JUST TELL ME THE TRUTH.
OH, IF THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT
THEN YOU REALLY SHOULD RUN HIM UNDER HOT WATER
AND BANG HIS HEAD AGAINST THE TABLE.
HONEY, I MADE A RESERVATION AT CHINA GARDEN.
IS THAT OKAY?
YEAH. NO, THAT'S GREAT.
BUT FIRST, WAIT. TALK TO ME, TALK TO ME.
TELL ME ABOUT YOUR DAY.
IT WAS FINE.
OKAY.
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING RIGHT NOW?
I'M THINKING THAT YOU ARE LOOKING REALLY FINE
IN THAT DRESS.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S GREAT, PAUL
BUT YOU KNOW, I WANT TO KNOW WHAT...
WOW! THOSE ARE REALLY GREAT.
I JUST WANT TO KNOW WHAT IS
BEHIND THIS STRONG, SILENT EXTERIOR.
YOU KNOW, THEY SAY THAT STILL WATERS RUN DEEP
AND I WANT TO SWIM IN YOURS.
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT HAVING SEX?
NO.
PAUL, I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT YOU.
YOU KNOW, LIKE YOUR CHILDHOOD.
TELL ME ABOUT YOUR CHILDHOOD.
NORMAL.
OKAY.
WELL, THEN HOW ABOUT PUBERTY? COME ON.
THAT'S ALWAYS A PAINFUL TIME.
YOU KNOW, YOUR FRIENDS INVITE YOU TO A SLUMBER PARTY
AND THEN THEY STICK YOUR HAND IN WARM WATER
WHILE YOU'RE SLEEPING
SO YOU PEEIN YOUR SLEEPING BAG?
NOPE. THAT NEVER HAPPENED TO ME.
WELL, YOU'RE LUCKY
YOU NEVER MET THAT BITCH SHARON MAJESKI.
ANYWAY, UM, THE REST OF YOUR LIFE.
YOU KNOW, ANY REGRETS?
NOPE.
ALL RIGHT, PAUL.
YOU KNOW, I'M NOT ASKING FOR A LOT HERE, OKAY?
JUST GIVE ME SOMETHING.
ANYTHING.
OKAY.
WHEN I WAS SIX YEARS OLD...
MM HMM.
I WANTED A BIG WHEEL.
AND, INSTEAD, MY PARENTS GOT ME
THIS LITTLE PLASTIC CHICKEN THAT YOU HOP AROUND ON.
IT WAS EMBARRASSING.
KIDS MADE FUN OF ME.
OH.
THAT WAS A PRETTY TOUGH YEAR.
THAT'S GREAT. SEE?
I ALREADY FEEL LIKE I KNOW YOU
A LITTLE BETTER.
THANK YOU.
OKAY. COME ON.
NOW WE CAN GO EAT.
LET'S GO.
IT WAS HORRIBLE.
THEY CALLED ME "CHICKEN BOY."
AND, IN FIFTH GRADE, I GOT INTO A FIGHT.
WELL, IT WASN'T REALLY A FIGHT.
RICHARD DARUMBULL BIT ME ON THE NOSE AND I FELL DOWN.
I STILL HAVE A LITTLE SCAR RIGHT HERE.
YOU CAN SEE IT.
YEAH. YEAH, I SEE THE SCAR.
LISTEN, PAUL, I THINK THIS IS REALLY GREAT
THAT, YOU KNOW, YOU'VE SHARED YOUR FEELINGS.
REALLY, IT'S BEAUTIFUL
BUT, UM, WHAT DO YOU SAY WE GO SHARE SOME FOOD?
OH, I COULDN'T EAT NOW.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
YOU LOVE THEIR KUNG PAO CHICKEN.
"CHICKEN"?
"CHICKEN BOY"!
I'M SORRY! I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO DO THIS.
NOTHING. THIS IS
THE NINE MILLIONTH RING STORE WE'VE BEEN TO
AND I CAN'T FIND THE PERFECT RING.
UGLY RING, UGLY RING, UGLY RING.
IT'S A BEAUTIFUL SELECTION.
OKAY, SO MAYBE YOU DON'T GET HER A RING.
MAYBE YOU DO SOMETHING DIFFERENT.
YOU KNOW, MAYBE YOU GET HER
AN ENGAGEMENT BRACELET, YOU KNOW?
OR AN ENGAGEMENT TIARA.
OH, AN ENGAGEMENT REVOLUTIONARY WAR MUSKET.
YOU KNOW, I'M SO GLAD I PICKED YOU TO HELP ME WITH THIS.
HUH?
CAN'T YOU JUST IMAGINE GETTING DOWN ON ONE KNEE
AND HANDING HER THIS GORGEOUS PIECE OF WEAPONRY?
YEAH, I'M GOING TO STICK WITH THE RING.
OH, THIS ONE'S NICE.
I LIKE THIS ONE.
SIR, UH, KIND SIR?
CAN I SEE THIS ONE?
THIS IS THE REASON YOU BROUGHT ME, OKAY?
I KNOW HOW TO HAGGLE
SO LET ME HANDLE THIS FROM HERE ON OUT.
CAN I HELP YOU? UH, YES.
I WOULD LIKE TO SEE THAT RING, PLEASE.
OR NOT. WHATEVER.
THIS RING IS FROM THE 1920S.
IT'S A 100 CARAT DIAMOND
WITH SAPPHIRES ON EITHER SIDE.
SIR, COULD I ASK YOU TO, UM...
COULD YOU HOLD OUT THAT RING AND ASK ME TO MARRY YOU?
OKAY.
WILL YOU MARRY ME?
OH, MY GOD. THAT'S IT.
THAT'S THE RING.
HOW MUCH IS IT?
CHANDLER, I WILL HANDLE THIS.
$8,600 DOLLARS.
WE WILL GIVE YOU TEN DOLLARS.
ARE YOU INTEREST ED IN THIS RING?
YES. YES, BUT I CAN ONLY PAY $8,000 DOLLARS.
OKAY. I CAN LET  IT GO FOR $8,000 DOLLARS.
WE STAND FIRM AT TEN DOLLARS.
HOW WOULD  YOU LIKE TO PAY?
UH, CREDIT CARD.
OH, NO. BUT I LENT MY CREDIT CARD TO JOEY.
OKAY, I'LL GO GET IT.
YOU GUARD THE RING.
WHY DID YOU GIVE YOUR CREDIT CARD TO JOEY?
I GAVE IT TO HIM TO BUY SOME KNICKS TICKETS.
THEN THE JERK DIDN'T EVEN INVITE ME TO THE GAME.
BUT I'M OVER IT. WHATEVER!
LISTEN, I'M SORRY ABOUT BEFORE.
DO YOU HAVE ANYTHING HERE FOR TEN DOLLARS?
UH, YES.
I HAVE THESE TWO
RATHER BEAUTIFUL FIVE DOLLAR BILLS.
I'LL GIVE YOU ONE DOLLAR FOR THEM.
HEY, REMEMBER HOW CHANDLER AND PHOEBE
BLEW US OFF YESTERDAY?
NO.
REMEMBER? YOU WERE EATING PIZZA.
YEAH.
OKAY.
WELL, APPARENTLY, CHANDLER'S ANGRY AT US
FOR NOT GETTING HIM A TICKET
TO THAT KNICKS GAME A COUPLE OF WEEKS AGO.
WE WERE SUPPOSED TO JUST GET HIM A TICKET?
THAT GUY IS ALWAYS MOOCHING OFF OF US.
RIGHT.
ANYWAY, I STILL THINK WE SHOULD TRY
TO PATCH THINGS UP.
YOU KNOW, LIKE, UH...
MAYBE WE CAN GET HIM TICKETS TO ANOTHER KNICKS GAME
AND INVITE HIM.
OH, WOW, THAT'S A GREAT IDEA.
AND I STILL HAVE HIS CREDIT CARD.
HERE YOU GO.
HEY, HEY, HEY. HOLD ON.
I GOT THIS ONE. HERE YOU GO.
YOU KNOW, I GOT TO TELL YOU.
SOMETIMES I DON'T GET CHANDLER.
YOU KNOW, ME AND HIM DO STUFF
ALL THE TIME WITHOUT YOU
AND YOU DON'T GET ALL UPSET.
ALL THE TIME?
ALL THE TIME.
I'M SORRY.
IT WAS REJECTED.
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
LET ME SEE THAT.
OH, THIS ONE'S MINE.
HERE YOU GO.
OH, MY GOD! OH, MY GOD!
STILL CRYING?
LIKE A LITTLE GIRL.
I KNOW, I KNOW, I KNOW.
THIS IS ALL MY FAULT.
I WANTED HIM TO OPEN UP.
BUT I DIDN'T KNOW THAT I WAS GOING TO UNLEASH
THIS WEEPY, CLINGY, MOIST MONSTER.
YOU KNOW, I ONLY KNOW OF TWO SUREFIRE WAYS
TO SHUT A MAN UP, AND ONE OF THEM IS SEX.
WHAT'S THE OTHER ONE?
I DON'T KNOW. I'VE NEVER HAD
TO USE THE OTHER ONE.
I'M JUST SAYING
YOU KNOW, IF WE'RE HAVING SEX, HE'S NOT GOING TO BE TALKING.
OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU'RE THE TALKER.
ANYWAY, UH, GREAT IDEA.
UM, I GOT TO GO TO THE STORE.
I TOLD HIM THAT I WOULD BUY HIM SOME MORE TISSUES.
OH, WE HAVE SOME HERE.
NO, YOU DON'T!
OKAY. UM, I'D ALSO LIKE TO TRY ON THE TIARA.
OH, YEAH. OKAY.
WOW. WHAT DO YOU THINK?
TOO MUCH?
A TAD.
THEN TAKE THE TIARA BACK
AND LET ME HOLD THE MUSKET AGAIN.
SOMETHING'S MISSING.
IT'S NOT...
OKAY. OH. LET ME SEE THE RING
THAT MY FRIEND PICKED OUT.
WHERE'S THE 1920s
PRINCESS CUT RING?
I JUST SOLD IT TO THAT GENTLEMAN.
OH, MY GOD!
WAIT! NO!
NO! WHAT?! HEY!
LET ME OUT!
NOW!
RACHEL?
NO.
HOW ARE YOU, PAUL?
OKAY.
CHANDLER...
DID YOUR DAD EVER HUG YOU?
NO.
DID HE HUG YOU?
NO, I...
IT'S JUST THAT... MY DAD NEVER DID.
I MISS MY DAD.
WELL, YOU CAN  SEE MY DAD IN VEGAS
KISSING OTHER DADS.
HEY, CHANDLER?
YEAH?
WOULD YOU...
WOULD YOU HUG ME?
I'M A LITTLE BUSY HERE, PAUL.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT MY DAD USED TO SAY.
OKAY, A QUICK ONE.
COME ON, HUG IT OUT.
HEY!
THERE YOU GO.
OKAY.
FIVE MORE SECONDS.
OKAY!
HEY.
JOEY!
WHAT, HEY, WHAT, HEY, WHAT... HEY.
HI. PAUL, IS IT?
DO YOU HAVE MY CREDIT CARD?
YEAH, IT'S IN MY... IN... IN MY POCKET.
MY BACK POCKET!
THANK GOD.
HEY, LISTEN, I GOT US TICKETS
TO A KNICKS GAME TONIGHT
OH, I CAN'T GO.
COME ON. IT'LL BE FUN.
ME, YOU AND ROSS... AND PAUL, PROBABLY.
LOOK, I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR THIS, OKAY?
I GOT TO GO.
WOW.
THAT WAS MEAN.
YEAH, I KNOW.
GET IN HERE.
YEAH.
CHANDLER
I FOUND THE PERFECT RING.
OH, THAT'S THAT'S PRETTY NICE
BUT I'M GOING TO GO WITH THE ONE I PICKED FIRST.
OH, WAKE UP, CHANDLER.
THE ONE YOU PICKED IS GONE.
IT'S OVER!
WHAT?
SOME GUY BOUGHT IT.
I'M SORRY.
I TRIED TO STOP IT, BUT THEY PUT ME IN JAIL.
THEY PUT YOU IN JAIL?
THE LITTLE JAIL BETWEEN THE DOORS.
PHOEBE, I ASKED YOU TO GUARD THE RING.
I KNOW. I'M SORRY.
BUT, YOU KNOW, THIS RING IS BETTER.
AND MONICA NEVER EVEN SAW THE OTHER RING.
YEAH, BUT WHEN HE PROPOSED TO ME WITH THE RING
PS. I GOT... GOOSE BUM
MAYBE IT WAS THE GUY.
IT WAS THE RING.
HEY, SO, UH, WAS HE EXCITED ABOUT THE TICKETS?
NO.
HE BLEW US OFF.
WHAT?
I KNOW!
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
CAN I TELL YOU SOMETHING?
I'M A LITTLE MAD AT HIM NOW.
ME, TOO.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
HE DIDN'T WANT TO TALK TO US ABOUT BEING ANGRY.
WELL, MAYBE WE DON'T TALK TO HIM AT ALL.
OOH...
FREEZE HIM OUT.
THAT'S RIGHT.
I LIKE IT.
EH? WE'LL SHOW HIM.
FROM NOW ON, IT'S GOING TO BE JOEY AND ROSS--
BEST FRIENDS.
OKAY.
WE'RE GOING TO BE THE NEW JOEY AND CHANDLER.
WHAT?
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
YOU THINK YOU AND CHANDLER
WERE CLOSER THAN ME AND CHANDLER?
HEY, HEY, HEY. DON'T GET ANGRY.
WE TURN ON EACH OTHER, HE WINS.
HI. I'M BACK. HEY, I HAVE
SO MUCH MORE TO TELL YOU.
I'VE WRITTEN IT ALL DOWN.
AH, THAT'S GREAT.
NO, ACTUALLY, THAT'S...
THAT'S GREAT.
THAT'S REALLY GREAT.
YOU YOU KNOW, I GOT TO TELL
WRITING
GETS ME, UH...
GETS ME KIND OF HOT.
WAIT, WAIT, LISTEN.
LISTEN TO THIS.
YOU KNOW WHAT I WANTED TO BE WHEN I WAS THAT AGE?
A LOVER?
SURFER.
OH, YEAH? SURFER?
I WANTED TO BE ONE WITH THE WAVES, YOU KNOW...
OKAY, HONEY, HOLD ON REAL QUICK.
HOLD ON A SECOND.
LET ME JUST, UH...
GET A LITTLE MORE COMFORTABLE HERE.
OH, WAIT. NOW, WAIT A SECOND.
THIS ISN'T TOO REVEALING, IS IT?
NO. "WHATEVER HAPPENED TO THAT LITTLE DUDE...
SO FULL OF DREAMS?"
I DON'T CARE ABOUT THE LITTLE DUDE!
I CAN'T... I CANNOT LISTEN TO ANY MORE OF THIS.
THE ONLY PERSON WHO WOULD WANT TO LISTEN
TO ANY MORE OF THIS IS A MENTAL HEALTH PROFESSIONAL
AND THAT IS ONLY BECAUSE THEY GET PAID $100 AN HOUR.
DO YOU KNOW HOW MUCH MONEY I COULD HAVE MADE
LISTENING TO YOU? $2,000 DOLLARS.
AND YOU KNOW WHEN I FIGURED THAT OUT?
WHILE YOU WERE TALKING.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE TRYING TO STIFLE ME
WHEN, JUST 14 HOURS AGO, WE FIGURED OUT THAT THAT IS EXACTLY
WHAT MY MOTHER WAS TRYING TO DO TO ME.
OH, I'M SORRY.
I... I... I DON'T MEAN... DIDN'T MEAN TO STIFLE YOU.
I... THIS IS ALL JUST A LITTLE OVERWHELMING.
OH, RACHEL.
I'M...
SO SORRY.
OH...
I DIDN'T MEAN TO OVERWHELM YOU.
IT'S JUST THAT... WHEN THOSE GATES OPENED
IT WAS HARD TO... HARD TO CLOSE THEM...
BUT THEY ARE CLOSED NOW, BELIEVE ME.
I'M SO GLAD.
I'M SO GLAD... YOU SHARED...
AND I'M GLAD THAT YOU'RE DONE.
SO WHAT DO YOU SAY WE, UM...
I'D REALLY LIKE THAT.
MM HMM.
THAT WAS...
SO GOOD.
OH... OH...
YUCK!
HEY. I CAN'T BELIEVE
I LET YOU TALK ME INTO BUYING
THIS STUPID, GUMBALL MACHINE LOOKING RING.
IT'S NOT A STUPID, GUMBALL MACHINE- LOOKING RING.
IT'S A BEAUTIFUL RING.
NO, IT'S NOT.
WHEN I LOOKED AT THE OTHER RING
I COULD SEE MONICA'S FACE WHEN I GAVE IT TO HER, YOU KNOW?
AND I COULD SEE HER SAYING, "YES."
WHEN I LOOK AT THIS RING, ALL I SEE IS A RING...
UNLESS I LOOK AT IT REALLY CLOSELY
AND THEN... I CAN SEE MY OWN EYE.
LOOK, THIS IS THE MOST IMPORTANT THING
I'M GOING TO DO IN MY LIFE.
I WANT TO MAKE SURE IT'S PERFECT.
OKAY, THERE MAY BE A WAY
THAT WE COULD GET THE OTHER RING BACK
BECAUSE I HEARD THE GUY TELL THE JEWELER
WHERE HE WAS GOING TO PROPOSE.
SO, MAYBE WE COULD GET HIM TO TRADE RINGS OR SOMETHING.
WE CAN'T DO THAT.
WELL, YOU CERTAINLY CAN'T GIVE HER
THAT STUPID GUMBALL RING.
ALL RIGHT, WHERE WAS HE GOING?
IT'S A RESTAURANT...
IT'S... RAINBOW SOMETHING.
RAINBOW ROOM? NOPE.
RAINBOW GRILL? NO.
SOMEWHERE OVER THE...?
L'ESPACE.
RAINBOW L'ESPACE.
NO, NO. JUST L'ESPACE.
I WOULD LOVE TO KNOW
HOW YOU GOT FROM RAINBOW TO L'ESPACE.
NO, YOU WOULDN'T.
YOU DON'T WANT TO GET IN HERE.
THERE HE IS.
OKAY, AND HE HASN'T PROPOSED YET
BECAUSE SHE HAS NO RING ON HER FINGER.
OD. WOW, YOU'RE GO
AFTER THIS, WE SHOULD SOLVE CRIMES.
YEAH.
OKAY, GO GO GO GET HIM.
OH, OKAY.
EXCUSE ME, SIR.
COULD YOU COME WITH ME, PLEASE?
YOU HAVE A PHONE CALL.
WHO IS IT?
IT IS YOUR OFFICE.
DO YOU KNOW WHO AT MY OFFICE?
JOHN.
OH, JOHN. GREAT.
HERE HE IS.
HI, HI.
OKAY, THERE WAS A SLIGHT MIX UP
AT THE JEWELRY STORE.
THE RING YOU'RE ABOUT TO PROPOSE WITH
WAS SUPPOSED TO BE HELD FOR ME.
SO, I'M GOING TO NEED TO HAVE THAT BACK...
BUT, IN EXCHANGE
I'M WILLING TO TRADE YOU
THIS BEAUTIFUL, MORE EXPENSIVE RING.
WOW.
I WOULD TRADE.
IT IS BEAUTIFUL
BUT I'M GOING TO USE THIS ONE.
NOW, IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME.
NO, NO, SEE, THIS IS MY FIANCEE
AND HER HEART WAS SET ON THAT RING.
YOU DON'T WANT TO BREAK HER HEART, NOW, DO YOU?
YEAH, DO YOU WANT TO BREAK A DYING WOMAN'S HEART?
YOU'RE DYING?
YES, SHE'S DYING...
OF A COUGH, APPARENTLY.
YES...
AND IT IS MY DYING WIS H TO HAVE THAT RING.
SEE, IF I'M NOT BURIED WITH THAT RING
THEN MY SPIRIT IS GOING TO WANDER THE NETHERWORLD
FOR ALL ETERNITY.
OKAY, THAT'S ENOUGH, HONEY.
UH... I DON'T KNOW.
LET ME SEE THE RING.
GREAT. OKAY, HERE.
ALL RIGHT. I'LL DO IT.
THANK YOU, THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
AND YOU ARE ABOUT TO MARRY A WONDERFUL MAN.
HEY, I'M MARRYING A DEAD WOMAN.
Rebound, Ronaldson again.
Jamal Faulkner was...
GUYS...
The ball is blocked by Hendren.
I GOT SOMETHING IMPORTANT TO TELL YOU.
GUYS?
...get up in the air.
He's going to make a nice sweep...
I'M GOING TO ASK MONICA TO MARRY ME.
I THINK WE GOT TO END THE FREEZE OUT.
WAIT A MINUTE.
IS THIS... IS THIS FOR REAL?
YEAH.
CHECK OUT THE RING.
OH, MY GOD!
SO YOU TWO ARE REALLY SERIOUS?
YEP, PRETTY MUCH.
Y YOU'RE GOING TO GET MARRIED?
I MEAN... WE'RE GOING TO BE BROTHERS IN LAW.
COME HERE.
A A A A A AND AND WE'RE GOING TO BE FRIENDS AGAIN.
HEY...
WHAT?
WATER UNDER THE BRIDGE.
OKAY. FORGET ABOUT IT.
I WAS GOING TO WAIT TILL, UH, IT WAS OFFICIAL, YOU KNOW
BUT I GOT SO EXCITED
I JUST HAD TO TELL YOU GUYS BECAUSE YOU'RE MY BEST FRIENDS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS!
ME, TOO. AND I WAS PLANNING
YOU ON HAVING A CONVERSATION WITH
ABOUT YOUR INTENTIONS.
I THINK I'M GOING TO CRY.
OH, NO MORE CRYING... PLEASE.
I JUST DUMPED ONE CRYBABY.
I'LL DUMP YOU, TOO.
GO, GO, GO, GO.
I'M GOING TO ASK MONICA TO MARRY ME.
OH, MY GOD.
OH, CHANDLER!
YOU GUYS ARE GOING TO BE SO HAPPY.
I KNOW.
WHERE'S ALL THE TISSUE?
OH!
CHECK OUT THE RING.
NICE. 100 CARAT, EASY.
HEY. CHANDLER'S GOING
TO ASK MONICA TO MARRY HIM.
OH, I KNOW. I HELPED PICK OUT THE RING. OH...
YOU TOLD HER BEFORE YOU TOLDUS?
WELL, SHE WALKED IN
WHILE I WAS LOOKING AT THE RING BROCHURES.
YOU CAN UNDERSTAND THAT, RIGHT?
GUYS?
GOD, THAT RING CHANDLER PICKED OUT WAS SO BEAUTIFUL.
HEY, AND YOU SHOULD KNOW.
YOU'VE BOUGHT, LIKE, A BILLION OF THEM.
AH...
HUMOR BASED ON MY PAIN.
HA.
YOU KNOW WHAT'S FUNNY?
OF ALL OF YOUR WIVES
I'M THE ONLY ONE WHO NEVER GOT A RING.
THIS A BIG ISSUE FOR YOU, OR...?
NO, BUT IT, YOU KNOW, WOULD'VE BEEN NICE
TO HAVE A LITTLE MEMENTO OF OUR MARRIED TIME TOGETHER.
SOMETHING OTHER THAN THE DIVORCE PAPERS
AND THE HANGOVER.
ROSS IS OBVIOUSLY NOT GOING TO GET YOU A RING.
BUT ASK FOR A MUSKET. ASK FOR A MUSKET.
HEY, WHEN WE WERE MARRIED, DO YOU KNOW WHAT I NEVER GOT?
UM... SEX.
WELL, YEAH.
NO RING, NO SEX. BIG SURPRISE.
GET ME A MUSKET AND WE'LL TALK.