WE'VE GOT THREE MINUTES TILL THE REACTOR BLOWS.
WE'RE NEVER GOING TO MAKE IT.
YOU'VE GOT TO GET OUT OF HERE!
SAVE YOURSELF.
NO, I WON'T LEAVE YOU.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
I'M A ROBOT.
I'M JUST A MACHINE!
NO, YOU'RE NOT.
NOT TO ME.
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT?
I AM EXTREMELY TALENTED.
YEAH, YEAH, YOU'RE GREAT.
OKAY, LET'S TAKE IT FROM...
NO, I MEAN I WAS REALLY ACTING MY ASS OFF.
WELL, I THOUGHT I WAS PRETTY GOOD, TOO.
OH, YEAH, YOU'RE SOLID.
ME. YOU'RE JUST NO...
YOU KNOW WHAT? I THINK THAT'S ENOUGH FOR NOW.
I DON'T WANT TO BE OVER REHEARSED.
FINE! I'LL DO IT WITHOUT YOU!
I DON'T NEED YOU OR ANYBODY ELSE!
I'M GOING TO MAKE IT ON MY OWN!
YOU'LL SEE!
YOU'LL ALL SEE!
SO, WHAT'S THIS THING YOU'RE AUDITIONING FOR?
OH, IT'S A NEW TV SHOW.
I'M UP FOR THE PART OF MAC MACHIAVELLI...
OR "MAC."
YEAH.
I'M A DETECTIVE, AND I SOLVE CRIMES
WITH THE HELP OF MY ROBOT PARTNER.
HE'S A COMPUTERIZED HUMANOID
ELECTRONICALLY ENHANCED SECRET ENFORCER.
OR "CHEESE."
SO, MAC AND CHEESE.
THAT'S THE TITLE.
YEAH.
YOU KNOW, THEY REALLY LUCKED OUT
THAT THE INITIALS SPELL "CHEESE."
THAT IS LUCKY.
HUH.
SO, JOEY, IF YOU GET THIS
YOU'RE GOING TO BE, LIKE, THE STAR OF YOUR OWN TV SHOW.
I MEAN, YOU'LL BE LIKE THE BIG CHEESE.
OR THE BIG MAC.
HEY, YOU LOVE THOSE.
WELL, DON'T GET YOUR HOPES UP
BECAUSE IT'S PROBABLY NOT GOING TO HAPPEN.
NOW, NOW, WHY WOULD YOU SAY THAT, JOSEPH?
COME ON, YOU GUYS.
MY OWN TV SHOW?
I JUST... I DON'T KNOW IF I'M GOOD ENOUGH.
I AM.
JOEY
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
YOU'RE A TERRIFIC ACTOR.
YOU REALLY THINK SO?
HOW CAN YOU EVEN ASK THAT QUESTION?
WHOA, SHE'S PRETTY.
YEAH.
OH, AND SHE'S REALLY NICE, TOO.
SHE TAUGHT ME ALL ABOUT, YOU KNOW
HOW TO WORK WITH THE CAMERAS
AND "SMELL THE FART" ACTING.
HUH.
I'M SORRY...
WHAT? EXCUSE ME?
IT'S LIKE, YOU GOT SO MANY LINES
TO LEARN SO FAST
THAT SOMETIMES YOU NEED A MINUTE
TO REMEMBER YOUR NEXT ONE.
SO, WHILE YOU'RE THINKING OF IT
YOU TAKE THIS BIG PAUSE, WHERE YOU LOOK ALL INTENSE
YOU KNOW, LIKE THIS.
OK AY. MMM. OH.
OH, HERE'S MY SCENE! HERE'S MY SCENE!
Mrs. Wallace?
I'm Dr. Drake Ramoray
your sister's neurosurgeon.
Your sister is suffering from a...
: YEAH, EVA...
WE'VE DONE SOME EXCELLENT WORK HERE
AND I WOULD HAVE TO SAY
YOUR PROBLEM IS QUITE CLEAR.
?? ALL YOU WANT IS A DINKLE ??
?? WHAT YOU ENVY'S A SCHWANG ??
?? A THING THROUGH WHICH YOU CAN TINKLE ??
?? OR PLAY WITH OR SIMPLY LET HANG. ??
I PLAY AL PACINO'S BUTT.
ALL RIGHT?
HE GOES INTO THE SHOWER, AND THEN I'M HIS BUTT.
OH, MY GOD.
COME ON, YOU GUYS.
THIS IS A REAL MOVIE, AND AL PACINO'S IN IT
AND THAT'S BIG.
OH, NO, IT'S TERRIFIC.
YOU DESERVE THIS.
AFTER ALL YOUR YEARS
OF STRUGGLING, YOU'VE FINALLY BEEN ABLE TO CRACK
YOUR WAY INTO SHOW BUSINESS.
OKAY, FINE. MAKE JOKES.
I DON'T CARE.
THIS IS A BIG BREAK FOR ME.
NO, YOU'RE RIGHT, YOU'RE RIGHT. IT IS.
SO, YOU GOING TO INVITE US ALL TO THE BIG OPENING?
ALL RIGHT, WELL, I'M OUT OF HERE.
WISH ME LUCK.
?? GOOD LUCK, GOOD LUCK ??
?? WE ALL WISH YOU GOOD LUCK.??
YEAH, WHATEVER.
WOW.
IF I COULD DANCE, I'D BE A TRIPLE THREAT.
IT'S YOUR TURN.
OH, ARE WE PLAYING THIS?
HEY.
HEY. HOW DID THE AUDITION GO?
TERRIBLE.
I MESSED UP EVERY LINE.
I SHOULDN'T EVEN BE AN ACTOR.
WAIT A MINUTE.
ARE YOU DOING THAT THING
WHERE YOU PRETEND IT DIDN'T GO WELL
BUT IT REALLY DID GO WELL?
YEAH. DID I FOOL YOU?
TOTALLY.
SO IT DID GO WELL.
IT WENT AMAZINGLY WELL.
THAT'S GREAT. GREAT.
YEAH. IT'S DOWN TO  ME AND TWO OTHER GUYS
I KNOW BOTH OF THEM, AND THEY'RE REALLY GOOD.
ONE OF THEM IS THE GUY FROM THOSE ALLERGY COMMERCIALS
WHO'S ALWAYS GETTING CHASED BY THOSE BIG FLOWERS.
OH, I LOVE THAT GUY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT AM I DOING?
I'M SO NERVOUS, YOU KNOW.
THE CALLBACK ISN'T UNTIL TOMORROW AT 5:00.
I FEEL LIKE MY HEAD'S GOING TO EXPLODE.
WELL, IT IS OVERDUE.
LOOK, DON'T WORRY, OKAY?
YOU'RE GOING TO BE FINE.
YEAH, BUT IT'S JUST SO MUCH PRESSURE, YOU KNOW.
I MEAN, NO OFFENSE, BUT WHAT YOU GUYS ALL DO IS VERY DIFFERENT.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU'D UNDERSTAND.
YEAH, NONE OF THE REST OF US
HAVE TO DEAL WITH PRESSURE AT OUR JOBS.
YES, FRAN, I KNOW WHAT TIME IT IS
BUT I'M LOOKING AT THE WEENUS AND I'M NOT HAPPY.
WELL, I'M TEAR ING THE LETTUCE.
UH HUH. IS IT DIRTY?
NO, DON'T WORRY, I'M GOING TO WASH IT.
DON'T. I LIKE IT DIRTY.
THAT'S YOUR CALL.
SO, UH... WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO NEXT?
WELL, I THOUGHT THAT I WOULD CUT UP THE TOMATOES.
ARE THEY, UH, FIRM?
THEY'RE ALL RIGHT.
YOU SURE THEY HAVEN'T GONE BAD?
YOU SURE THEY'RE NOT VERY, VERY BAD?
NO, REALLY, THEY'RE OKAY.
YOU GOING TO SLICE THEM UP REAL NICE?
ACTUALLY, I WAS GOING TO DO THEM JULIENNE.
I'M OUT OF HERE.
MONICA, I'M QUITTING.
I JUST HELPED AN 81 YEAR OLD WOMAN PUT ON A THONG
AND SHE DIDN'T EVEN BUY IT.
I'M TELLING YOU, I'M QUITTING.
THAT'S IT. I'M TALKING TO MY BOSS RIGHT NOW.
YES, I AM.
YES, I AM. YES, I AM.
YES, I AM. YES, I AM. YES, I AM.
OKAY, BYE. CALL ME WHEN YOU GET THIS MESSAGE.
WELL, WHAT HAPPENED?
WELL, HE CAME IN FOR A MASSAGE...
AND EVERYTHING WAS FINE UNTIL...
OH... OH... OH, MY GOD.
AND, ALL OF A SUDDEN, HIS HANDS WEREN'T THE PROBLEM ANYMORE.
WAS IT...
OH, BOY SCOUTS COULD HAVE CAMPED UNDER THERE.
YOU ATE MY SANDWICH?
IT WAS A SIMPLE MISTAKE.
IT COULD HAPPEN TO ANYONE.
OH, REAL REALLY?
NOW, NOW, CALM DOWN.
COME LOOK IN MY OFFICE.
SOME OF IT MAY STILL BE IN THE TRASH.
WHAT?
WELL, IT WAS QUITE LARGE.
I HAD TO THROW MOST OF IT AWAY.
YOU... YOU... YOU...
YOU THREW MY SANDWICH AWAY?
MY SANDWICH?!
: MY SANDWICH?!
I JUST... I WANT THIS PART SO MUCH, YOU KNOW.
IF I DON'T GET THIS PART
I'M NEVER GOING TO EAT MACARONI AND CHEESE AGAIN.
NO, I DIDN'T SAY THAT. THAT DOESN'T COUNT.
OH, COME ON, GUYS, IT'S NOT LIKE I MOVED TO EUROPE.
I JUST MOVED ACROSS THE HALL.
AND WE WOULD HAVE YOU OVER ALL THE TIME
IF IT WEREN'T FOR MONICA'S ALLERGIES.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I COULD NEVER LIE TO YOU.
SHE HATES YOU.
SHOULD I GET THAT?
HELLO.
UH, NO, JOEY'S NOT HERE RIGHT NOW.
CAN I TAKE A MESSAGE?
YEAH, OKAY, SO THE AUDITION'S BEEN MOVED FROM 5:00 TO 2:30.
OKAY, GREAT. BYE.
AREN'T YOU DRESSED YET?
AM I NAKED AGAIN?
WE'RE SUPPOSED  TO MEET MY PARENTS IN 15 MINUTES.
YEAH, OKAY, I WAS JUST TALKING TO THE GUYS.
LOOK AT THEM.
I MEAN, IS IT OKAY IF THEY COME VISIT?
WHAT ABOUT MY ALLERGIES?
OH, RIGHT.
YOUR ALLERGIES.
ALL HER. SHE HATES YOU.
OH, OH, OH , OH, OH, OH.
YES! HA HA HA!
HEY, HOW COOL WOULD IT BE
IF YOU COULD WATCH, LIKE, A REAL
LIFE SIZED VERSION OF THIS, HUH?
I MEAN, HOW CRAZY WOULD THAT BE?
AS CRAZY AS SOCCER?
HELLO.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
THE AUDITION'S NOT TILL 5:00.
WELL, NOBODY TOLD ME.
WHO'D YOU TALK TO?
NEVER MIND.
YOU MEAN YOU DIDN'T GET IT FROM THIS?
THE ALLERGY GUY GOT THE PART. THANKS.
WELL, MAYBE WE CAN FIX IT, YOU KNOW
MAYBE WE CAN SEND HIM SOME, SOME BIG, BIG FLOWERS AND SCARE HIM.
HOW COULD YOU DO THIS TO ME, CHANDLER?
THIS PART COULD HAVE TURNED MY WHOLE CAREER AROUND.
I MESSED UP, OKAY?
I'M SORRY. I REALLY MESSED UP.
YOU DON'T EVEN LIVE HERE ANYMORE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING ANSWERING MY PHONE? I HAVE A MACHINE.
WHICH I BOUGHT FOR YOU.
TAUGHT YOU HOW TO USE IT.
YOU THOUGHT IT WAS A COPIER.
LOOK, IF THERE WAS ANYTHING I COULD DO
I WOULD DO IT, OKAY?
BUT EVERYBODY'S ALLOWED ONE MISTAKE, RIGHT?
YOU KNOW, HE COULD'VE GOTTEN ME A VCR
HE COULD'VE GOTTEN  ME A SET OF GOLF CLUBS.
BUT, NO, HE HAS TO GET ME THE WOMAN REPELLER.
THE EYESORE FROM THE LIBERACE HOUSE OF CRAP!
IT'S NOT THAT BAD
OH, YEAH, EASY FOR YOU TO SAY.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO WALK AROUND
SPORTING SOME REJECT FROM THE MR. T COLLECTION.
CHANDLER, CHANDLER...
I PITY THE FOOL WHO PUTS ON MY JEWELRY.
I DO! I DO! I PITY THE FOOL
IF I...
WHEN YOU WERE LATE LAST NIGHT, KATHY AND I GOT TO TALKING
AND... ONE THING LED TO ANOTHER, AND...
AND WHAT?
DID YOU SLEEP WITH HER?
NO, NO, NO. I JUST KISSED HER.
WHAT?! THAT'S EVEN WORSE!
HOW IS THAT WORSE?
I DON'T KNOW, BUT IT'S THE SAME.
YOU'RE RIGHT. I HAVE NO EXCUSES.
I WAS TOTALLY OVER THE LINE.
OVER THE LINE?
YOU'RE SO FAR PAST THE LINE
THAT YOU CAN'T EVEN SEE THE LINE.
THE LINE IS A DOT TO YOU.
LOOK, I'M NOT SAYING
YOU SHOULD MAGICALLY FORGIVE ME
BUT YOU'RE NOT PERFECT.
YOU'VE MADE SOME ERRORS IN JUDGMENT, TOO.
NAME ONE.
WHAT HAPPENED?
OH, MAN! HE PROMISED HE WOULDN'T TAKE THE CHAIRS.
WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED?
HOW WERE YOU LOCKED IN
AND WHERE THE HELL'S ALL OF OUR STUFF?
WELL, THIS GUY CAME BY TO LOOK AT THE UNIT
AND HE SAID HE DIDN'T THINK
IT WAS BIG ENOUGH TO FIT A GROWN MAN.
SO... YOU GOT IN VOLUNTARILY?
I WAS TRYING TO MAKE A SALE.
OH, MAN. IF I EVER RUN INTO THAT GUY AGAIN
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M GOING TO DO?
BEND OVER?
THERE'S LORRAINE.
OKAY, NOW, REMEMBER--
NO TRADING.
YOU GET THE PRETTY ONE, I GET THE MESS.
HI, JOEY.
HEY.
WELL, WELL, LOOK WHAT YOU BROUGHT.
AND WHAT DID YOU BRING?
SHE'S CHECKING HER COAT.
JOEY, I'M GOING TO GO WASH THE CAB SMELL OFF MY HANDS.
WILL YOU GET ME A WHITE ZINFANDEL
AND A GLASS OF RED FOR JANICE.
JANICE?
OH... MY... GOD.
JOEY'S TAILOR...
TOOK ADVANTAGE OF ME.
WHAT?
NO WAY.
I'VE BEEN GOING TO THE GUY FOR 12 YEARS.
OH, COME ON. HE SAID HE WAS GOING TO DO MY INSEAM.
THEN HE RAN HIS HAND UP MY LEG
AND THEN, THERE WAS DEFINITE...
WHAT?
CUPPING.
THAT'S HOW THEY DO PANTS.
ROSS, WILL YOU TELL HIM?
ISN'T THAT HOW A TAILOR MEASURES PANTS?
YES, YES, IT IS-- IN PRISON!
I SAID, "NAMEONE."
I CAN'T BELIEVE I DID THIS.
WHAT AN IDIOT.
OH, STOP BEATING YOURSELF UP.
PEOPLE MAKE MISTAKES.
THESE THINGS HAPPEN.
THERE AREN'T ANY MESSAGES
YOU'VE FORGOTTEN TO GIVE ME, ARE THERE?
APPARENTLY, YOU'RE NOT VERY GOOD AT IT.
DO YOU THINK HE'LL EVER FORGIVE ME?
OF COURSE HE WILL. BUT, CHANDLER
THE MOST IMPORTANT THING IS THAT YOU FORGIVE YOURSELF.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I KIND OF HAVE.
ALREADY?
THAT WAS PRETTY BAD, WHAT YOU DID.
OH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
HE WILL FORGIVE YOU
AND I LIKE TO BRING A PAD WITH ME
WHEN I GO ANSWER THE PHONE, JUST IN CASE... OKAY.
YOU DIDN'T SEE HOW MAD HE WAS, YOU KNOW?
I'M SURE HE WILL FORGIVE YOU.
LOOK, WE'VE ALL BEEN THERE.
YOU KNOW, YOU FIGHT; YOU MAKE UP--
THAT'S JUST THE WAY IT WORKS.
IT TOOK TWO PEOPLE
TO BREAK UP THIS RELATIONSHIP.
YEAH, YOU AND THAT GIRL FROM THE COPY PLACE
WHICH, YESTERDAY, YOU TOOK FULL RESPONSIBILITY FOR.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT I WAS
TAKING RESPONSIBILITY FOR, OKAY?
I DIDN'T FINISH THE WHOLE LETTER.
WHAT?
I FELL ASLEEP.
YOU FELL ASLEEP?
IT WAS 5:30  IN THE MORNING
AND YOU HAD RAMBLED ON FOR 18 PAGES.
FRONT AND BACK!
OH OH OH, AND, BY THE WAY--
Y O U APOSTROPHE R E
MEANS "YOU ARE."
Y O U R MEANS "YOUR."
HA! YOU KNOW, I CAN'T BELIEVE
I EVEN THOUGHT OF GETTING BACK TOGETHER WITH YOU.
WE ARE SO OVER.
: OH... OH... OH...
FINE BY ME!
AND HEY, JUST SO YOU KNOW...
IT'S NOT THAT COMMON
IT DOESN'T HAPPEN TO EVERY GUY
AND IT IS A BIG DEAL!
I KNEW IT!
YOU HAD NO RIGHT TO GO OUT WITH HIM.
THAT IS THE MOST RIDICULOUS...
YOU SOLD ME OUT!
I DID NOT SELL YOU OUT!
YES, YOU DID!
YOU ABSOLUTELY SOLD ME... WOULD YOU LET ME TALK?!
DID YOU JUST FLICK ME?
OKAY, WELL, YOU WOULDN'T LET ME FINISH
AND I WAS JUST...
OW! THAT HURT! OW!
OH! ALL RIGHT. OKAY.
LET'S NOT DO THIS! LET'S NOT DO THIS!
HAPPY THOUGHTS!
NO! NO!
STOP IT!
OH! OH!
OKAY, NOW I'M GOING TO KICK SOME ASS!
OW!
OW! OW! OW! OW! OW! OW!
ALL RIGHT.
NOW, I WILL LET GO IF YOU BOTH STOP.
FINE.
THERE WE GO.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
IF WE WERE IN PRISON
YOU GUYS WOULD BE, LIKE, MY BITCHES.
OKAY, BUDDY BOY, HERE IT IS.
YOU HIDE MY CLOTHES, I'M WEARING EVERYTHING YOU OWN.
OH, MY GOD!
LOOK AT ME!
I'M CHANDLER!
COULD I BE WEARING
ANY MORE CLOTHES?
MAYBE IF I WASN'T GOING COMMANDO...
WHOO! I TELL YOU, IT'S HOT WITH ALL THIS STUFF ON.
I... I BETTER NOT DO ANY, I DON'T KNOW, LUNGES.
?? LIVIN' ALONE ??
?? I THINK OF ALL THE FRIENDS I'VE KNOWN ??
?? BUT WHEN I DIAL THE TELEPHONE ??
?? NOBODY'S HOME ??
?? ALL BY MYSELF ??
?? DON'T WANNA LIVE ??
?? ANYMORE ??
?? ALL BY MYSELF... ??
JOEY...
GOT YOU THE JOEY SPECIAL--
TWO PIZZAS.
JOE?
HELLO.
DAMN IT!
NO, JOEY'S NOT HERE RIGHT NOW
BUT I CAN TAKE A MESSAGE... I THINK.
HE'S STILL GOT A CHANCE FOR THE PART?
OH, THAT'S GREAT NEWS!
WELL, NO, OBVIOUSLY NOT FOR THE ACTOR
WHO WAS MAULED BY HIS DOG.
OH, WELL, THAT'S GREAT.
I WILL GIVE JOEY THE MESSAGE.
THANK YOU.
YES!
OKAY... MAC AUDITION
AT 2:00...
ALLERGY ACTOR ATTACKED...
BY DOG
NOT FLOWERS.
OKAY.
HEY.
PLEASE TELL ME YOU GOT THE MESSAGE.
WHAT MESSAGE?
THE ACTOR PLAYING MAC COULDN'T DO IT.
THEY NEEDED TO SEE YOU AT 2:00.
WHAT?
IT'S 6:00.
: I WROTE IT ON THE BOARD!
I WROTE IT ON THE BOARD
AND THEN I WENT ALL OVER NEW YORK CITY
LOOKING FOR YOU.
I WENT TO ROSS'.
I WENT TO THE COFFEEHOUSE.
I WENT TO ANY PLACE THAT THEY MAKE SANDWICHES.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS, CHANDLER.
I'M SORRY.
I I I I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
WELL, Y YOU MIGHT SAY...
"CONGRATULATIONS."
I SAW THE BOARD.
I WENT TO THE AUDITION.
I GOT THE PART!
IS THAT SUPPOSED TO BE FUNNY?
I WAS REALLY WORRIED OVER HERE.
OH. WELL, I'M SORRY.
SOMETIMES THAT FAKE OUT THING IS MEAN.
OH, WOW, OKAY, MAN, I'M SORRY.
I DID NOT MEAN TO MAKE YOU FEEL BAD.
WELL, THAT'S GOOD...
BECAUSE YOU DIDN'T...
AND I'M INCREDIBLY HAPPY FOR YOU.
THAT'S MEAN!
YOU REALLY
HAD ME GOING THERE.
OH, WE COULD DO THIS ALL DAY.
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
OKAY, LOOK, LET'S TALK
ABOUT WHAT A HUGE STAR I'M GOING TO BE.
YOU ARE GOING TO BE A HUGE STAR.
I'M GOING TO HUG YOU.
YOU HUG ME.
ALL RIGHT.
?? YOU REALLY GOT A HOLD ON ME ??
??YOU REALLY GOT A HOLD ON ME ??
?? BABY, I LOVE YOU ??
?? YOU REALLY GOT A HOLD... ??
?? DO IT, DO IT, JUST HOLD ME ??
??HOLD ME ?? ?? SQUEEZE ??
?? HOLD ME, HOLD ME. ??
HEY, DO WE DO THIS TOO MUCH?
I THINK SO.
YEAH. YEAH, GET OFF ME.
"COME ON, C.H.E.E.S.E.
"I'M NOT LEAVING WITHOUT YOU.
"TRY ROUTING YOUR BACKUP POWER SOURCE
THROUGH YOUR PRIMARY C.P.U. "
"I CAN'T.
"MY CIRCUITS ARE FRIED.
THEY'RE FRIED, I TELL YOU!"
WOW.
"WELL, THEN, I'LL JUST HAVE TO CARRY YOU."
"THAT'LL BE A NEAT TRICK, WHEN YOU'RE...
WHEN YOU'RE DEAD!"
ROSS, YOU DON'T HAVE TO YELL.
THERE WAS JUST AN EXPLOSION, OKAY?
MY HEARING WOULD BE IMPAIRED.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE EXCELLENT.
IN FACT, FOR A MINUTE THERE
I WAS, LIKE, "OOH, WHERE'D ROSS GO?"
THANK YOU
AND I HAVE TO SAY, THAT FIRST SCENE
WHERE YOU MEET MAC...
OH, MY GOD.
I MEAN...
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK THAT'S ENOUGH FOR TODAY.
THANKS FOR YOUR HELP.
HOLDING US BACK.
TOTALLY.