WELL, THAT THING'S CLEARLY IN THE WAY.
ALL RIGHT. AHA!
DAMN FRIDGE!
HEY, JOEY, HOW YOU DOING?
GREAT...
ROOMIE.
HUH. YEAH, I GUESS WE ARE ROOMMATES NOW.
NOW THAT YOU BRING IT UP
UH, OUR FRIDGE IS BROKEN.
WE HAVE TO GET A NEW ONE.
I CHECKED AROUND, AND YOUR HALF IS $400 DOLLARS.
THANKS A LOT, RACH.
I'M NOT PAYING FOR HALF OF THAT.
I'M ONLY STAYING HERE UNTIL MY APARTMENT GETS FIXED.
LOOK, RACH, MY PARENTS BOUGHT THIS FRIDGE
JUST AFTER I WAS BORN, OKAY?
NOW, I HAVE NEVER HAD A PROBLEM WITH IT.
THEN YOU SHOW UP AND IT BREAKS.
WHAT DOES THAT TELL YOU?
THAT REFRIGERATORS DON'T LIVE AS LONG AS PEOPLE.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, YOU KNOW THAT THE A.T.M.
WILL ONLY LET YOU TAKE OUT $300 AT A TIME
SO I'LL TAKE A CHECK FOR THE OTHER $100 DOLLARS.
YOU'RE JOKING, RIGHT?
OF COURSE I'M JOKING.
I DON'T TAKE CHECKS.
THANK GOD YOU'RE PRETTY.
HEY.
HI. HEY.
DO YOU GUYS KNOW ANY CUTE GUYS?
WELL, OF COURSE I DO.
MY GOOD FRIEND JOEY OVER HERE.
OH, I'M SORRY.
THANK YOU, CHANDLER.
ANYWAY...
THERE'S THIS BIG CHARITY BALL THIS WEEKEND
AND RALPH LAUREN BOUGHT A TABLE, SO I KIND OF HAVE TO GO.
WHAT'S THE CHARITY?
I DON'T KNOW.
SOMETHING, EITHER TREES, OR... DISEASE...
RALPH MUMBLES A LOT.
DOES RALPH MUMBLE WHEN YOU'RE NOT PAYING ATTENTION?
YEAH, IT'S WEIRD.
BUT THE THING IS, I NEED TO FIND A DATE.
WHAT KIND OF GUY ARE YOU LOOKING FOR?
WELL, SOMEONE THAT HAS HIS OWN TUX
OR THE ABILITY TO RENT A TUX.
SO HE HAS TO BE A MALE WHO HAS AT LEAST $50 DOLLARS.
OOH, SO CLOSE.
HEY, EVERYBODY.
HI. HI, THERE.
THIS IS ELIZABETH.
HI.
I'M THE STUDENT.
OH, ISN'T SHE CUTE?
NO.
YOU KNOW, THIS IS PROBABLY NONE OF MY BUSINESS
BUT WEREN'T YOU GUYS SUPPOSED TO NOT BE SEEN IN PUBLIC TOGETHER?
OH, WE'RE NOT TOGETHER.
NO, WE'RE JUST TWO PEOPLE
WHO HAPPENED TO HAVE RUN INTO EACH OTHER
HERE AT THE COFFEE HOUSE.
OH, SLY.
I REALLY WANTED TO MEET YOU GUYS, BUT I HAVE TO RUN.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER?
OKAY.
BYE, ROSS. BYE.
OOPS. DIDN'T MEAN TO RUN INTO YOU LIKE THAT, SIR.
OH, THAT IS QUITE ALL RIGHT, MA'AM.
BYE.
SO, WHY IS SHE LEAVING?
IS IT A SCHOOL NIGHT
AND SHE HAS A LOT OF HOMEWORK TO DO?
YES, HER MOLECULAR EPIDEMIOLOGY PAPER IS DUE TOMORROW.
OH, TELL HER GOOD LUCK WITH THAT.
ANYONE ELSE? HUH?
BRING THEM ON.
OH! WHEN'S HER BIRTHDAY?
I DON'T KNOW, RACHEL. WHY?
WELL, YOU KNOW, IT'S JUST BEEN SO LONG
SINCE I'VE BEEN TO CHUCK E. CHEESE.
OH, I LIKE ELIZABETH.
WELL, THANKS.
YEAH, IN FACT, I LIKE HER SO MUCH
THAT YOU TELL HER I WANT MY COOKIES
EARLY THIS YEAR.
YOU KNOW...
A BOX OF THIN MINTS AND SOME TAGALONGS.
HEY, COME ON, GIVE HIM A BREAK.
ROSS, SERIOUSLY, HOW'S IT GOING WITH HER?
WELL, IT'S ACTUALLY BEEN GREAT.
SHE'S 20, SO SHE'S NOT LOOKING FOR ANYTHING TOO SERIOUS
WHICH IS PERFECT FOR ME RIGHT NOW.
WELL, THAT IS GREAT.
AND SERIOUSLY, SHE SEEMS VERY NICE.
THANKS. I KNOW YOU GUYS LIKE TO GIVE ME A HARD TIME AND ALL
BUT IT REALLY MEANS A LOT TO ME THAT YOU LIKE HER.
JUST KNOWING THAT YOU GUYS ARE LIKE...
OKAY, I GOT A GOOD ONE.
OKAY, UM...
WHAT IS SHE, LIKE, 12?
CHANDLER, DO YOU THINK
WE TALK ABOUT OUR RELATIONSHIP ENOUGH?
YEAH. DO WE HAVE ANY FRUIT ROLL UPS?
HEY.
HEY. HEY.
OKAY, I JUST THOUGHT OF THE PERFECT GUY FOR RACHEL
TO TAKE TO HER THING.
OH, THAT'S SO FUNNY, BECAUSE WE FOUND SOMEONE, TOO.
OH, THAT'S GOOD.
I GUESS SHE'LL HAVE A CHOICE
BETWEEN MY GUY AND YOUR WEIRDO.
WHY WOULD OUR GUY BE A WEIRDO?
BECAUSE THAT'S JUST YOUR TASTE.
SEE, RACHEL'S NOT GOING TO PICK YOUR STUPID GUY.
OH, YEAH?
YEAH.
MY GUY IS A LAWYER WHO DOES VOLUNTEER WORK
AND HE HAS ONE OF THESE.
A FACE ASS?
A CHIN DIMPLE.
WELL, UH, YOU KNOW, OUR GUY WORKS WITH CHANDLER
AND HE'S REALLY NICE AND SMART
AND HE'S A GREAT DRESSER.
HAVE YOU SEEN YOUR GUY'S BODY?
NO. OUR GUY'S JUST A FLOATING HEAD.
WELL, MY GUY IS SPECTACULAR, OKAY?
HE'S A MASSAGE CLIENT.
AND ONE TIME, WHEN HE WAS ON THE TABLE
I LOOKED AT IT, AND I MEAN ALL OF IT.
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO LOOK.
OH, YEAH, LIKE THERE ARE POLICE FOR THAT.
YOU LOOK? YOU YOU MASSAGE ME.
I KNOW.
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
YOUR GUY MAY HAVE A GREAT BODY
BUT OUR GUY IS REALLY FUNNY.
CHANDLER FUNNY?
OUR GUY'S A GREAT DANCER.
MY GUY'S WELL READ.
OUR GUY HAS GREAT HAIR.
MY GUY HAS GREAT TEETH.
OUR GUY SMELLS INCREDIBLE.
DO YOU WANT OUR GUY TO BE YOUR GUY?
HEY.
UH...
WELL, YOU...
YOU DON'T LOOK GOOD, JOE.
WELL, THE FRIDGE BROKE
SO I HAD TO EAT EVERYTHING.
COLD CUTS, ICE CREAM, LIMES...
HEY, WHAT WAS IN THAT BROWN JAR?
THAT'S STILL IN THERE?
NOT ANYMORE.
SO, ANYWAY, HOW DO YOU WANT TO PAY ME?
IS THIS A SERVICE YOU'RE PROVIDING ME?
NO, NO, NO... FOR MY NEW FRIDGE--
OUR NEW FRIDGE.
OUR NEW FRIDGE?
I DON'T LIVE HERE ANYMORE.
SO WHAT?
LOOK, OKAY, SUPPOSE WE WERE A DIVORCED COUPLE.
UH HUH.
AND I GOT CUSTODY OF THE KID, RIGHT?
NOW, SUPPOSE THE KID DIES AND I GOT TO BUY A NEW KID.
OKAY.
GIVE ME $400 DOLLARS.
THANK GOD YOU'RE PRETTY.
PROFESSOR GELLER?
MM? OH, A STUDENT I DON'T KNOW.
I WAS WONDERING IF I COULD TALK TO YOU FOR A MOMENT?
YES, OF COURSE.
WHAT WOULD THIS BE REGARDING?
MAKING OUT IN YOUR OFFICE.
WH... SHH!
OF OF COURSE.
WHY DON'T WE GO INSIDE?
MM MM...
OH, OH...
WHAT? DOORKNOB.
DOORKNOB.
SORRY.
UM, I ACTUALLY DO NEED TO TALK TO YOU.
OH, OKAY. WHAT ABOUT?
SPRING VACATION.
YEAH. WE HAVE TIME OFF
AND A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE GOING ON TRIPS, AND...
PROFESSOR GELLER?
YES, PROFESSOR FRIE SEN... STIN LINDER.
I'LL BE WITH YOU IN ONE MOMENT.
SO, I WILL TAKE ONE BOX OF THE THIN MINTS.
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
ELIZABETH WAS ABOUT TO ASK ME TO GO ON A TRIP WITH HER.
IS THAT TAKING IT SLOW?
I'M NOT READY FOR THIS, OKAY?
WHAT DO I TELL HER?
JUST TELL HER THE TRUTH.
TELL HER YOU'RE NOT READY.
I COULD DO THAT.
WHAT IF SHE GETS UPSET?
THEN YOU DISTRACT HER WITH A BARBIE DOLL.
OR...
YOU COULD JUST, YOU KNOW...
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?
WHA...
WHAT THE HELL AM I DOING?
YOU JUST BROKE MY FRIDGE!
WHAT? HOW DO YOU KNOW IF...
HOW DO YOU KNOW IT'S EVEN BROKEN?
OH, YOU THINK I DON'T KNOW WHAT BREAKS MY FRIDGE?
EXCUSE ME.
WELL, WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
BROKEN.
THAT'LL BE $400 DOLLARS.
JOEY, I SAW YOU PUSH HIM.
YOU PUSHED HIM.
JOEY, I DID NOT BREAK THIS, OKAY?
THAT HAS BEEN BROKEN FOR A WHILE.
CHANDLER, REMEMBER I TOLD YOU ABOUT OUR FRIDGE?
UH HUH.
I STILL HAVEN'T GOTTEN
A CHECK FOR YOUR HALF YET.
DO NOT GIVE HIM ANY MONEY.
I'M NOT TALKING TO YOU!
YOU BROKE MY FRIDGE!
YOU WANTED TO SEE ME, PROFESSOR GELLER?
YES. YES, PLEASE COME IN.
OOH OOH...
DOORKNOB?
YEAH. IT KIND OF GROWS ON YOU.
ACTUALLY, I WANTED TO FINISH TALKING TO YOU
ABOUT SPRING VACATION.
OH, GOOD.
LOOK, I...
LOOK, I'M HAVING A GREAT TIME WITH YOU
AND I JUST DON'T WANT US TO MOVE TOO FAST
OR PUT TOO MUCH PRESSURE ON US.
SO, I'M SORRY.
I JUST DON'T THINK WE SHOULD GO AWAY TOGETHER YET.
IT'S TOO SOON.
UM, ROSS, I THINK YOU MISUNDERSTOOD
WHAT I WAS SAYING.
I JUST WANTED TO TELL YOU
THAT I'M GOING TO FLORIDA FOR A COUPLE OF WEEKS.
NO. I THINK YOU MISUNDERSTOOD WHAT I WAS SAYING.
WHAT I MEANT WAS...
YOU ARE SO ADORABLE.
THAT... LET'S TALK ABOUT THAT.
HI. HEY.
HOW DID IT GO WITH ELIZABETH?
OH, OH, IT WAS FINE.
UH, IT WAS JUST A MISUNDERSTANDING.
SHE DIDN'T WANT ME TO GO WITH HER.
SHE JUST WANTED TO LET ME KNOW
THAT SHE'S GOING TO FLORIDA FOR SPRING VACATION.
WAIT A MINUTE.
IS SHE GOING FOR SPRING VACATION
OR IS SHE GOING FOR SPRING BREAK? WHOO HOO!
WHAT'S WHAT'S THE DIFFERENCE?
WELL, A SPRING VACATION
YOU'RE DOING NICE THINGS WITH YOUR GRANDPARENTS.
SPRING BREAK, YOU'RE DOING FRAT GUYS.
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
NOT ALL SPRING BREAKS ARE LIKE THAT.
WHAT'D YOU DO ON YOURS?
I WENT TO EGYPT WITH MY DAD.
I CAN SEE IT NOW.
LOOK, DAD, IT'S THE SPHINX.
WHOO WHOO!
I THINK ELIZABETH IS A LITTLE MORE SERIOUS
THAN SPRING BREAK... WHOO HOO!
ALL RIGHT, I MEAN, COME ON.
SHE'S TAKING MY CLASS.
AND SLEPT WITH THE PROFESSOR.
I'M GOING TO CALL HER.
YEAH.
HEY.
YOU GUYS, UM, I WANT YOU TO MEET SEBASTIAN.
HI.
WE JUST MET AT THE NEWS STAND.
WE BOTH GRABBED FOR THE LAST FIELD AND STREAM.
WHAT? I READ THAT.
CAN I GET YOU A CUP OF COFFEE?
OH, YES, THANK YOU.
RACHEL, WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
WHAT?
YOU ASKED US TO FIND YOU A GUY
AND THEN YOU COME TRAIPSING IN HERE WITH A GUY OF YOUR OWN?
YOU FOUND ME A GUY?
YES, WE FOUND YOU A REALLY CUTE
AND FUNNY GUY FROM CHANDLER'S WORK.
YEAH, AND I FOUND YOU ONE, TOO
WHO IS NOT A WEIRDO.
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT, THOUGH, YOU GUYS?
I REALLY APPRECIATE THAT
BUT I'M JUST GOING TO TAKE SEBASTIAN TO THE CHARITY.
ARE YOU SURE?
BECAUSE OUR GUY SMELLS INCREDIBLE.
WOULD YOU STOP IT WITH THAT ALREADY?
HERE YOU GO.
OH, THANK YOU.
SURE.
SO, SEBASTIAN
DO YOU DO ANY VOLUNTEER WORK?
UH, NO. NOT REALLY. WHY?
NO REASON; IT'S JUST I KNOW A SINGLE GUY
WHO DOES CARE ABOUT OTHER PEOPLE.
ARE YOU FUNNY?
EXCUSE ME?
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
ARE YOU FUNNY?
TELL US A JOKE.
LOOK, I JUST WANTED TO HAVE COFFEE WITH RACHEL.
WELL, SO DO A LOT OF PEOPLE.
ACTUALLY, UH, I GOT TO GET GOING.
OH...
GIVE ME A CALL SOMETIME.
YOU DIDN'T GIVE ME YOUR PHONE NUMBER.
OKAY, SEE YOU LATER.
TURNS OUT HE IS KIND OF FUNNY.
I CANNOT BELIEVE YOU GUYS.
HE WAS REALLY NICE
AND HE JUST LEFT BECAUSE OF YOU.
YEAH, BUT SEBASTIAN?
WHAT IS THAT, A CAT'S NAME?
YEAH, YOU KNOW WHAT
I NOTICED, RACHEL?
HE SCARES EASY, YOU KNOW.
IS THAT THE KIND OF GUY YOU WANT TO TAKE TO A BALL?
"HEY, SEBASTIAN, WOULD YOU LIKE TO DANCE?"
"UH... OKAY, I GOT TO GO."
ALL RIGHT, GUYS, STOP IT.
RACHEL, WE'RE VERY SORRY.
THAT WAS A VERY INSENSITIVE THING FOR US TO DO.
AND, YOU KNOW WHAT, LET US MAKE IT UP TO YOU.
WE HAVE TWO REALLY GREAT GUYS FOR YOU.
YEAH, WHAT HAVE YOU GOT TO LOSE?
YOU MIGHT EVEN END UP WITH SOMEONE REALLY SPECIAL
IF YOU PICK MY GUY.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, SO YOU WILL MEET OUR GUYS?
YES, I'LL MEET THEM.
IT DOESN'T MATTER WHICH ONE YOU CHOOSE.
IT'S COMPLETELY UP TO YOU.
OUR GUY IS PERFECT...
OR YOU COULD GO OUT WITH THE GUY
PHOEBE DEEMED NOT GOOD ENOUGH TO GO OUT WITH HERSELF.
PHOEBE, THERE YOU ARE.
OKAY, YOU BROKE MY FRIDGE.
YOU OWE ME 400 BUCKS.
OKAY, SURE.
REALLY?
OOH! TECHNICALLY, YOU OWE ME $600 DOLLARS
FOR SENDING OUT HAPPY THOUGHTS ON YOUR LAST TEN AUDITIONS.
CALL IT EVEN?
OKAY.
WELL, THERE YOU ARE.
SO WHAT DID ELIZABETH SAY?
WELL, IT TURNS OUT SHE IS GOING TO DAYTONA FOR SPRING BREAK...
WHOO HOO.
THAT MEANS WET T SHIRT CONTESTS
GUYS DOING SHOTS OFF OF GIRLS' BODIES
WAKING UP NEXT TO PEOPLE YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW.
MAN, SHE IS GOING TO HAVE A GREAT TIME!
IS SHE STAYING AT THE HOTEL CORONA?
YOU KNOW THE HOTELS?
SURE. I WAS THERE.
SPRING BREAK '81. WHOO!
IN 1981, YOU WERE 13.
SO WHAT?
I DROVE DOWN, SOLD T SHIRTS.
HAD A BLAST.
AND YOU KNOW WHO KNOWS HOW TO PARTY?
DRUNK COLLEGE CHICKS.
OKAY, SHE CAN'T GO.
ROSS, YOU CAN'T TELL HER NOT TO GO.
YOU JUST STARTED DATING.
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO?
NOTHING. YOU JUST HAVE TO BE COOL WITH IT.
WELL, WHAT IF SHE GOES DOWN THERE
AND SLEEPS WITH A BUNCH OF GUYS?
WELL, MAYBE YOU DON'T MARRY THIS ONE.
NO, I'M SORRY. THIS IS VERY SERIOUS. IT IS.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT, ROSS? HERE:
YOU LIKE HER, SHE LIKES YOU-- EVERYTHING'S GOING TO BE FINE.
YOU'RE RIGHT. I'M PROBABLY JUST OVERREACTING.
IT'S JUST SHE'S STAYING AT THIS PARTY HOTEL ON THE BEACH
WITH A HUGE POOL AND FREE DRINKS WITH EVERY MEAL.
IF SHE'S GOT ENOUGH MONEY FOR THAT
SHE CAN CERTAINLY PAY FOR THE FRIDGE SHE BROKE.
I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE GOING ON THIS TRIP.
YEAH. I'VE BEEN WORKING SO HARD THIS SEMESTER.
I REALLY NEED TO GO CRAZY, YOU KNOW?
BLOW OFF SOME STEAM.
SURE, SURE.
LOOK, I DON'T KNOW
IF YOUR PLANS ARE FINALIZED YET, BUT...
HEY, I KNOW ANOTHER GREAT WAY TO BLOW OFF STEAM.
WHAT?
ARE YOU INTO CRAFTS AT ALL?
ROSS, ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH, OF COURSE... I'M OKAY.
I'M JUST BEING... SUPPORTIVE.
SUPPORTIVE OF YOU AND THIS WHOLE TRIP, AND...
WHAT WHAT IS... WHAT'S THIS?
IT'S A BATHING SUIT.
TO WEAR IN FRONT OF PEOPLE?
IS THAT SUPPORTIVE?
IS THIS?
HEY.
WE'RE REALLY GLAD YOU DECIDED TO MEET OUR GUY.
YOU'RE GOING TO LIKE HIM SO MUCH.
WHEN DO YOU WANT TO MEET HIM?
I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T WORK LATE TOMORROW NIGHT.
TOMORROW NIGHT IS GOOD. TOMORROW NIGHT IS GOOD.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
WHY PUT OFF SOMETHING TILL TOMORROW
YOU COULD DO RIGHT NOW?
ELDAD, COME HERE.
ELDAD, THIS IS RACHEL.
HOW ARE YOU?
WELL, A LITTLE BLINDSIDED
BUT, YOU KNOW, GOOD.
ELDAD, SIT DOWN.
MOVE OVER. MOVE OVER NOW.
THERE YOU GO. THERE YOU ARE.
OKAY, OKAY, WE CAN TAKE A HINT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
THIS IS PATRICK. HI.
OKAY, YOU'RE TOO LATE, OKAY
BECAUSE SHE'S ALREADY WITH OUR GUY.
OH, MY GOD, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I AM TOO LATE.
THEY'RE SITTING ON THE COUCH AND TALKING.
COME ON.
RACHEL.
YEAH?
THIS IS PATRICK.
OH, HI.
THIS IS THE GUY I WAS TELLING YOU ABOUT.
AND BELIEVE ME, THIS SUIT DOES NOT DO JUSTICE
TO WHAT'S UNDERNEATH IT.
OKAY...
BUT, PHEEBS...
I'M JUST SORT OF IN THE MIDDLE OF SOMETHING.
OH, OKAY, YEAH, THAT'S OKAY.
HAVE A SEAT.
YOU CAN'T DO THAT.
MAYBE I SHOULD GO.
SIT DOWN. WE'RE WINNING.
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT, MAYBE I SHOULD GO.
NO! NO! NO! NO!
YOU HAVE A SEAT.
RACHEL, RACHEL, YOU HAVEN'T TOUCHED
ELDAD'S HAIR.
IT IS THE SOFTEST HAIR.
I'M GOOD.
RACHEL, PATRICK IS REALLY RICH.
GIVE HER SOME MONEY.
WHAT?
UH... YOU KNOW WHAT, PHOEBE.
THIS ISN'T REALLY WORTH THE FREE MASSAGE.
THAT'S RIGHT, PATRICK. BYE BYE.
ELDAD IS MUCH MORE COOPERATIVE
AND HE CAN DANCE.
YOU DANCE FOR RACHEL.
OH, MY GOD...
NO, NO, NO, DON'T DANCE FOR ME!
PLEASE, DON'T DANCE.
WHAT IS THE MATTER WITH YOU GUYS?
YEAH, OKAY, LET'S TALK IT OUT.
AM I THE ONLY ONE THAT THIS IS EMBARRASSING FOR?
I'M EMBARRASSED.
SHH, SHH, SHH.
I'LL TELL YOU
WHO SHOULD BE EMBARRASSED-- IT'S YOU GUYS.
COME ON, THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
THANK YOU, BUT I DO NOT NEED YOU TO GET ME A DATE.
THEN WHY DID SHE ASK US...?
I AM STILL TALKING!
AND THEN YOU CHASE AWAY THE ONE GUY
THAT I ACTUALLY LIKED.
I MEAN, NO OFFENSE TO YOU GUYS, REALLY.
I MEAN, CONGRATULATIONS ON... ALL THE CASH.
AND... AND... YOU KNOW, YOU REALLY
WOW, YOU DO HAVE VERY SOFT HAIR.
BUT I WOULD MUCH RATHER  GO TO THE BALL ALL BY MYSELF
THAN GO THROUGH ANY MORE OF THIS.
GOOD BYE.
NOW, DO YOU USE SOME SORT
OF SPECIAL CONDITIONER ON THAT HAIR?
YES. PAPAYA EXTRACT.
THANK YOU.
SO, UH, HAVE A GREAT TIME DOWN THERE.
I WILL.
DID YOU PACK THAT BATHING SUIT?
YEAH.
IT WAS PRETTY FUNNY WHEN I HID IT FOR A WHILE, HUH?
ANYWAY, UM...
I AM WORRIED ABOUT THAT BATHING SUIT.
NOT BECAUSE IT'S REVEALING
WHICH I'M FINE WITH.
NO, I'M CONCERNED ABOUT YOUR HEALTH...
UM, SUN EXPOSURE.
OH, DON'T WORRY.
I HAVE PLENTY OF SUNBLOCK.
IT'S SPF 30.
WELL, IF WHAT'S IN THE BOTTLE
IS ACTUALLY 30.
I MEAN, SOMETIMES YOU GET 30
SOMETIMES IT'S FOUR.
AND I SWEAR TO GOD
MORE OFTEN THAN NOT, IT'S JUST MILK.
ROSS, IT'S GOING TO BE OKAY.
I'M NOT GOING DOWN THERE
TO HOOK UP WITH A BUNCH OF GUYS.
I REALLY LIKE YOU.
I LIKE HOW THINGS ARE GOING BETWEEN US.
REALLY?
YEAH. I'M JUST GOING DOWN THERE TO RELAX
AND HANG OUT WITH MY FRIENDS.
OKAY. COOL.
OH, HEY, HERE THEY ARE.
HEY, ELIZABETH!
CALL ME.
RACHEL, WE'RE SORRY FOR PUSHING
THOSE GUYS ON YOU.
OH, THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
I ENDED UP HAVING A REALLY GOOD TIME.
THE CHARITY WAS A BIG SUCCESS
AND THEY RAISED A LOT OF MONEY AND AWARENESS.
SO WHAT WAS IT FOR, ANYWAY?
I WANT TO SAY A DISEASE.
HEY.
I GOT THIS REALLY WEIRD MESSAGE FROM ROSS.
HE SAID TURN ON MTV.
ALL RIGHT.
OH, MY GOD! LOOK!
THAT'S ELIZABETH!
OH, OH, PROFESSOR GELLER.
AH, TO BE 13 AGAIN.