HEY, YOU GUYS EVER WONDER WHY THEY CALL IT "THANKSGIVING"?
OKAY. HEY, MONICA,
YOU'RE DOING THANKSGIVING NEXT WEEK, RIGHT?
BECAUSE, UH, CAROL'S TAKING BEN
TO HER PARENTS' PLACE IN FLORIDA.
OKAY, OKAY...  I'LL MAKE THANKSGIVING DINNER.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BEG.
I I DIDN'T BEG.
I I JUST ASKED ONCE.
YOU COULD BEG, YOU KNOW?
MONICA SAID I COULD MAKE DESSERT THIS YEAR.
UH, YOU'RE GOING TO COOK SOMETHING?
HEY, I COOK.
OFFERING PEOPLE GUM IS NOT COOKING.
ARE YOU SURE MONICA SAID
YOU COULD MAKE SOMETHING THIS YEAR?
BECAUSE I REMEMBER HER SAYING, "IN TWO YEARS."
YOU SAID, "IN TWO YEARS," RIGHT?
NO, I... I PROMISED HER
BUT, UH, RACH, ARE YOU SURE YOU DO WANT TO START OUT
WITH SOMETHING AS BIG AS THANKSGIVING DINNER?
I MEAN, MAYBE YOU WANT TO TRY A LITTLE THANKSGIVING BREAKFAST...
MAYBE THANKSGIVING SNACK.
WHAT? HEY, COME ON.
YOU GUYS, I CAN DO THIS.
REMEMBER, I MADE THOSE PEANUT BUTTER COOKIES.
AAH...
I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU GUYS ARE SO WORRIED ABOUT.
COOKING IS EASY.
YOU JUST FOLLOW THE RECIPE.
IF IT SAYS, "BOIL TWO CUPS OF SALT"
YOU JUST BOIL TWO CUPS OF SALT.
OKAY, GREAT. BYE.
HEY. SO, GUESS WHO'S COMING TO THANKSGIVING DINNER.
SIDNEY POITIER.
I MISS RACHEL.
OH, THAT'S GREAT. NO, MY PARENTS.
THEY HAVEN'T SEEN THE PLACE SINCE I MOVED IN.
YEAH, AND YOU KNOW IF YOU COULD NOT MENTION TO THEM
THAT WE LIVE TOGETHER, THAT WOULD BE GREAT.
I WAS THINKING WE'D EAT AROUND 4:00.
WHY CAN'T I TELL THEM THAT WE LIVE TOGETHER?
BECAUSE THEY DON'T KNOW WE'RE DATING.
DO YOU THINK WE SHOULD EAT IN THE KITCHEN?
WHY HAVEN'T YOU TOLD THEM?
UM, WELL, I WAS GOING TO, I WAS REALLY WAS
BUT, UM, THEN, SOMEWHERE, JUST OUT OF NOWHERE, I DIDN'T.
WHY HAVEN'T YOU TOLD THEM?
WOULDN'T THEY BE HAPPY?
SO DINNER IN THE KITCHEN AROUND 4:00.
I'LL SEE YOU THEN.
WHY WOULDN'T THEY BE HAPPY?
WELL, UH, BECAUSE...
MAINLY, UH...
THEY DON'T LIKE YOU.
I'M SORRY.
WHAT? WHAT? WHY?
MAYBE BECAUSE YOU USED TO BE ALOOF, OR THAT YOU'RE
REALLY SARCASTIC, OR THAT, YOU KNOW
YOU JOKE AROUND ALL THE TIME
OR THAT YOU TAKE OFF YOUR CLOTHES
AND YOU THROW THEM ON THE COUCH.
IS THIS WHY THEY DON'T LIKE ME OR WHY YOU DON'T LIKE ME?
LOOK, I KNOW THAT I SHOULD HAVE TOLD THEM.
I KNOW I SHOULDN'T CARE WHAT THEY THINK. I'M SORRY.
YOU KNOW WHAT? IT'LL BE OKAY, IT'LL BE OKAY
BECAUSE WHEN THEY COME OVER, I WILL BE ALL CHARMING.
I WILL MAKE THEM FALL IN LOVE WITH ME
AND THEN WE'LL TELL THEM.
YOU REALLY THINK THAT'LL WORK?
HEY, I CAN BE PRETTY CHARMING, BABE.
WON YOU OVER, DIDN'T I?
I DON'T THINK YOU'LL EVER GET MY PARENTS THAT DRUNK.
HEY. OH, GOOD.
ROSS, YOUR PARENTS LIKE ME, RIGHT?
YES, OF COURSE THEY LIKE YOU.
WELL, MONICA JUST TOLD ME THAT THEY DON'T.
YEAH, THEY DON'T LIKE YOU.
DO YOU KNOW WHY?
I DON'T KNOW. MAYBE IT'S BECAUSE YOU'RE REALLY SARCASTIC
OR, I DON'T KNOW, MAYBE IT'S BECAUSE...
WELL, IF PEOPLE DON'T KNOW
THEY SHOULDN'T JUST GUESS.
THIS IS GREAT. ANOTHER THANKSGIVING
WITH NOTHING TO GIVE THANKS FOR.
MAYBE I GIVE THANKS FOR YOU SHUTTING UP, HUH?
MAYBE I GIVE THANKS
BY TAKING MY PLAYSTATION OVER TO MY NEW APARTMENT.
WELL, MAYBE I LOVE YOU.
HI. HI.
HEY, GUYS.
NO, I DON'T WANT TO PLAY VIDEO GAMES, JOE.
ARE YOU GUYS GOING TO CHANDLER'S FOR THANKSGIVING?
YEAH, YEAH, WHY? WHAT'S UP?
WELL, ME AND MY DANCER FRIENDS
ARE THINKING OF DOING THANKSGIVING UPTOWN.
I THOUGHT YOU GUYS MIGHT LIKE TO COME.
FOR REAL?
YOU SHOULD GO TO CHANDLER'S
BECAUSE NONE OF US KNOWS HOW TO COOK.
WE'LL PROBABLY JUST END UP DRINKING ALL DAY.
YEAH. WE GO TO YOURS, YEAH.
YEAH. SEE, WE HAVE TO STOP ACROSS THE HALL
BECAUSE IT'S MY SISTER, BUT YOU KNOW, ACTUALLY
GROWING UP WITH A SISTER WAS NICE
BECAUSE IT REALLY HELPED ME UNDERSTAND WOMEN.
YOU SHOULD TELL YOUR FRIENDS THAT.
OKAY.
HOW YOU GOT THREE WOMEN TO MARRY YOU, I'LL NEVER KNOW.
HEY, MON, LOOK--
I'M MELTING BUTTER.
THAT'S GREAT, RACH.
YOU NOW HAVE THE COOKING SKILLS OF A HOT DAY.
HEY.
HEY, PHEEBS, CHECK IT OUT.
YEAH. FOR MY DESSERT
I HAVE CHOSEN TO MAKE A TRADITIONAL ENGLISH TRIFLE.
WOW, THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
AND WHAT ARE YOU MAKING, MONICA, YOU KNOW
IN CASE RACHEL'S DESSERT IS SO GOOD THAT I EAT ALL OF IT.
THERE'S NONE LEFT FOR ANYBODY ELSE.
NOTHING.
NOTHING?
YEAH, SWEETIE, I TRUST YOU.
SO IF I MESS THIS UP, THERE'S NOTHING ELSE FOR DESSERT?
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO MESS IT UP.
WOW, MONICA, I LOVE THAT.
YOU REALLY HAVE FAITH IN ME. THANK YOU.
TECHNICAL QUESTION.
HOW DO YOU KNOW WHEN THE BUTTER IS DONE?
WELL, IT'S DONE ABOUT TWO MINUTES BEFORE IT LOOKS THAT.
HEY. HEY. HEY.
OH, THE FOOD SMELLS GREAT, MON.
YEAH, AND THE PLACE LOOKS SO NICE.
HEY, HAPPY THANKSGIVING, EVERYBODY.
HAPPY THANKSGIVING.
WELL, THIS HAS BEEN GREAT.
SEE YA.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
OH, WE DID SAY
WE'D STOP BY THIS LITTLE THING JOEY'S ROOMMATE IS HAVING.
OH, JANINE, THE REALLY HOT DANCER GIRL?
SOME WOULD SAY SHE'S ATTRACTIVE, YES.
AND WHO ELSE IS GOING TO BE THERE?
SOME OF HER FRIENDS.
HER DANCER FRIENDS?
YES, ALL RIGHT?
ALL OF HER HOT DANCER FRIENDS ARE GOING TO BE THERE
AND THEY'LL BE DRINKING AND DANCING
AND WE REALLY WANT TO GO.
DUDE, WE WERE GOOD.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO GO ANYWHERE.
YOU SAID YOU WERE GOING TO EAT HERE
AND YOU'RE GOING TO EAT HERE.
AND LEAVING US TO GO SEE HOT DANCER GIRLS
IS NOT VERY THANKSGIVING Y.
OH, BUT IT IS.
IT'S JUST LIKE THE FIRST THANKSGIVING
WHEN THE INDIANS AND THE PILGRIMS SAT DOWN TO DINNER.
YEAH, YEAH, AND THEN THE INDIANS TAUGHT THE PILGRIMS
WHAT IT MEANT TO BE HOT IN THE NEW WORLD.
ALL RIGHT, FELLAS
I REALLY THINK YOU SHOULD STAY HERE.
YOU'RE JUST JEALOUS BECAUSE YOU CAN'T GO.
THAT IS SO NOT TRUE.
HI. HELLO, EVERYBODY.
HI.
HI, DAD. MOM.
LOOK... LOOK WHO IT IS.
IT'S CHANDLER.
OH, YES, OF COURSE.
HELLO, CHANDLER.
MR. AND MRS. GELLER, YOU LOOK WONDERFUL.
IT IS GREAT TO HAVE YOU HERE.
LET US TAKE OFF YOUR COATS.
WHOA, SNOWING OUT THERE?
NO.
MONICA, ALL THIS FOOD LOOKS WONDERFUL.
YOU SHOULD THINK ABOUT DOING THIS FOR A LIVING.
OKAY. I HAVE DANDRUFF.
THERE'S NO NEED TO LAUGH AND POINT.
DAD, CHANDLER WAS JUST LAUGHING AT YOUR JOKE.
MY JOKE WASN'T FUNNY.
WELL, CHANDLER LAUGHS AT EVERYTHING.
THAT THAT'S ONE OF THE GREAT THINGS ABOUT HIM.
WHOA.
RACH...
YEAH.
I JUST REMEMBERED. I HAD A DREAM ABOUT MR. GELLER LAST NIGHT.
REALLY?
YEAH.
I DREAMT THAT HE SAVED ME FROM A BURNING BUILDING
AND HE WAS SO BRAVE AND SO STRONG
AND IT'S MAKING ME LOOK AT HIM TOTALLY DIFFERENTLY.
YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, HE USED TO BE JUST, YOU KNOW
JACK GELLER, MONICA AND ROSS'S DAD
AND NOW HE'S JACK GELLER, DREAM HUNK.
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU KNOW, TO ME, HE'LL ALWAYS BE JACK GELLER--
WALKS IN WHILE YOU'RE CHANGING.
YOU KNOW, DAD, CHANDLER IS ONE
OF ROSS'S VERY BEST FRIENDS.
YES, I KNOW.
YOU KNOW, ROSS SURE IS A GREAT GUY.
YOU KNOW, I'VE ALWAYS FELT
THAT HOW A YOUNG MAN TURNS OUT IS A REFLECTION ON HIS FATHER.
I ALWAYS THOUGHT THAT, TOO.
TELL ME, WHAT DOES YOUR FATHER DO?
HE'S A HEADLINER OF A...
GAY BURLESQUE SHOW.
RACH, YOU'RE KILLING US HERE.
WILL YOU SERVE THE DESSERT ALREADY?
THERE'S DRUNKEN DANCERS AWAITING.
WELL, LOOK AT IT. ISN'T IT BEAUTIFUL?
YEAH, YEAH, WHAT IS IT?
IT'S A TRIFLE
AND IT'S GOT ALL OF THESE LAYERS.
FIRST, THERE'S A LAYER OF LADYFINGERS
THEN A LAYER OF JAM
THEN CUSTARD, WHICH I MADE FROM SCRATCH.
THEN RASPBERRIES
MORE LADYFINGERS
THEN BEEF SAUTEED WITH PEAS AND ONIONS
AND THEN A LITTLE BIT MORE CUSTARD, AND THEN BANANAS
AND THEN I JUST PUT SOME WHIPPED CREAM ON TOP.
WHAT WAS THE ONE RIGHT BEFORE BANANAS?
THE BEEF? YEAH, THAT WAS WEIRD TO ME, TOO, BUT, THEN, YOU KNOW
I THOUGHT, WELL, THERE'S MINCEMEAT PIE.
I MEAN, THAT'S AN ENGLISH DESSERT.
THESE PEOPLE JUST PUT
VERY STRANGE THINGS IN THEIR FOOD, YOU KNOW?
OH, BY THE WAY, CAN I BORROW SOME RUM FROM YOUR PLACE?
YEAH, SURE, YEAH.
AND WHILE I'M GONE, DON'T YOU BOYS SNEAK A TASTE.
RIGHT. OKAY.
BEEF IN A DESSERT?
THERE... NO, NO, NO. THERE IS NO WAY.
I KNOW, AND ONLY ONE LAYER OF JAM?
WHAT IS UP WITH THAT?
OH, MY GOD.
THE PAGES ARE STUCK TOGETHER.
CHANDLER!
OH, MY GOD.
SHE... SHE MADE HALF AN ENGLISH TRIFLE AND...
HALF A SHEPHERD'S PIE.
OH, MAN.
NOW SHE'S GOING TO START ALL OVER.
WE'RE NEVER GOING TO GET TO INTRODUCE
THE HOT GIRLS TO THE NEW WORLD.
NO, NO, WE WILL.
WE JUST WON'T TELL HER SHE MESSED UP.
JUST LET HER SERVE THE BEEF CUSTARD THING?
YEAH.
IT WILL BE LIKE A FUNNY THANKSGIVING STORY.
VOMITING STORIES ARE FUNNY, I GUESS.
JOEY, GOD, YOUR APARTMENT IS, LIKE, A HUNDRED DEGREES.
DID IT MAKE YOU WANT TO WALK AROUND IN YOUR UNDERWEAR?
NO.
STILL NOT HOT ENOUGH.
YEAH. RACHEL.
OKAY. LOOK AT HIM.
LOOK AT THOSE STRONG HANDS.
OH, WHAT I WOULDN'T GIVE TO BE THAT CAN OF CONDENSED MILK.
MOM, CHANDLER WAS JUST SAYING
HOW BEAUTIFUL YOUR SWEATER IS.
OH, THANK YOU, CHANDLER. I JUST BOUGHT IT.
OH, YES. WELL, IT'S VERY BEAUTIFUL.
IT'S CREAM COLORED AND TIGHT, AND...
I DON'T MEAN TIGHT.
IT'S NOT TOO TIGHT.
NOT THAT I WAS LOOKING AT...
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH HIM?
I THINK HE'S STONED AGAIN.
WHAT?
DUDE, I NEED TO TALK TO YOU A SEC.
OKAY.
I THINK I MIGHT KNOW WHY MY PARENTS DON'T LIKE YOU.
YOU DO? WHY?
OKAY, REMEMBER-- WE WERE YOUNG...
SPRING BREAK, SOPHOMORE YEAR.
I GOT HIGH IN MY BEDROOM
AND MY PARENTS WALKED IN AND SMELLED IT
AND SO I TOLD THEM
THAT YOU HAD GOTTEN STONED AND JUMPED OUT THE WINDOW.
WHAT?
WHY DID YOU DO THAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
YOURS WAS THE FIRST NAME THAT POPPED INTO MY HEAD.
I'M SORRY. I DIDN'T THINK IT WOULD MATTER.
HOW COULD IT NOT MATTER?
WELL, HOW WAS I SUPPOSED TO KNOW
WE'D END UP BEING FRIENDS AFTER COLLEGE
LET ALONE YOU'D BE LIVING WITH MY SISTER?
WHAT ABOUT ALL THAT "FRIENDS FOREVER" STUFF?
I DON'T KNOW.
I WAS ALL HIGH.
MOM AND DAD JUST SENT ME IN HERE TO FIND OUT
IF YOU WERE TRYING TO GET ROSS STONED.
YOUR PARENTS CAUGHT ROSS SMOKING POT IN COLLEGE
AND HE BLAMED IT ON ME.
ROSS, I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'D DO THAT.
THE REASON WE HAVEN'T TOLD THEM WE'RE TOGETHER
IS BECAUSE THEY HATE ME.
OKAY? SO, WILL YOU FIX THIS?
OKAY. OKAY.
I'LL TELL THEM IT WASN'T CHANDLER WHO GOT HIGH.
NOW, WHO SHOULD I SAY IT WAS?
YOU!
IT'S NOT LIKE IT WAS A BIG DEAL.
YOU DON'T STILL DO IT OR ANYTHING.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
NOW, WHO SHOULD I SAY "TRICKED" ME INTO DOING IT?
NOBODY.
YOU'RE GOING TO GO OUT THERE
AND TELL THEM EXACTLY WHAT HAPPENED.
REALLY?
YES.
OKAY.
OKAY, GOOD.
OH, WAIT, IS THERE ANYTHING ELSE I SHOULD KNOW?
NO.
OH... YEAH, UM...
YOU MICROWAVED A BUNCH OF MY DAD'S RECORDS.
WHY?
EVIDENTLY, YOU YOU WEREN'T VERY GOOD AT HANDLING YOUR HIGH.
DAD.
DAD, PLEASE DON'T PICK YOUR TEETH OUT HERE.
ALL RIGHT, AND IF YOU'RE GOING TO PUT YOUR FEET UP...
MONICA, LEAVE HIM ALONE!
WILL YOU HURRY UP?!
DID YOU NOT HEAR ME BEFORE
WHEN I TOLD YOU THAT ALL OF JANINE'S FRIENDS ARE DANCERS, HUH?
AND THAT THEY'RE GOING TO BE DRINKING A LOT?
NO, I DID, BUT TELL ME AGAIN BECAUSE IT'S SO ROMANTIC.
YOU'RE WHIPPING SO SLOW. CAN'T YOU DO IT ANY FASTER?
JOEY, COME ON. I DON'T WANT TO MAKE ANY MISTAKES, ALL RIGHT?
THIS IS THE ONLY DESSERT AND IF I SCREW IT UP
EVERYBODY'S GOING TO BE, LIKE
"OH, REMEMBER THAT THANKSGIVING
WHEN RACHEL SCREWED UP THE TRIFLE?"
OKAY?
SO WHY DON'T YOU JUST LET ME WORRY ABOUT MAKING THE TRIFLE
AND YOU JUST WORRY ABOUT EATING IT, ALL RIGHT?
OH, I AM.
ROSS, IF YOU DON'T TELL THEM, THEN I WILL.
OKAY, FINE.
ROSS, CAN I TALK TO YOU FOR A SECOND?
OH, UH, CAN'T IT WAIT A SECOND, JOEY?
I HAVE TO TELL MY PARENTS SOMETHING.
NO, IT CAN'T? OKAY.
OKAY, LOOK, I THINK WE HAVE TO TELL RACHEL
SHE MESSED UP HER DESSERT.
WHAT? WHAT IS WITH EVERYBODY?
IT'S THANKSGIVING, NOT TRUTH DAY.
LOOK, WHEN EVERYONE EATS THAT BANANA MEAT THING
THEY'RE ALL GOING TO MAKE FUN OF HER.
DO YOU WANT THAT?
OKAY, OKAY, WE'LL JUST GET EVERYONE
TO ACT LIKE THEY LIKE IT.
THAT WAY, NO ONE MAKES FUN OF HER
AND WE STILL GET TO  GO TO SWEET POTATO PIE.
DUDE, THEY'RE NOT OBJECTS.
JUST KIDDING. I'LL TALK TO THEM.
YOU DISTRACT HER.
HEY, RACH, CAN I TALK TO YOU OUTSIDE FOR A SEC?
OKAY.
WHAT'S UP, ROSS?
SO, UM...
THANKSGIVING.
THE HOLIDAY SEASON IS UPON US, HMM?
YEAH.
AND, UM, YOU LOOK NICE TODAY.
OH, NO.
NO, ROSS. DON'T DO THIS.
WHAT?
I JUST... I DON'T THINK
US GETTING BACK TOGETHER IS A GOOD IDEA.
HUH?
I THOUGHT THIS MIGHT HAPPEN TODAY.
ROSS...
I KNOW THE HOLIDAYS CAN BE ROUGH, YOU KNOW?
AND IT'S PROBABLY REALLY HARD FOR YOU TO BE ALONE RIGHT NOW.
YOU'RE ALONE.
NO, I I LIVE WITH PHOEBE.
I MEAN, YOU'RE ALONE ALONE.
YOU KNOW? AND I JUST...
IT'S JUST NOT THE TIME FOR US.
I'M SORRY.
OH, WELL. CAN'T BLAME A GUY FOR TRYING.
SO...
OKAY...
AND, UH, IF ANYONE NEEDS HELP
PRETENDING TO LIKE IT
I LEARNED SOME THINGS IN ACTING CLASS.
TRY RUBBING YOUR STOMACH.
OR, UH...
OR SAYING "MMM."
AND, UH, OOH, OHH-- SMILING.
OKAY.
I'M NOT GOING TO PAY FOR THOSE ACTING CLASSES ANYMORE.
RACHEL, THERE YOU ARE.
COME ON. LET'S SERVE THAT DESSERT ALREADY.
JOEY, YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO STOP RUSHING ME.
YOU KNOW WHAT? YOU DON'T GET ANY DESSERT.
REALLY?
NO, I'M JUST KIDDING.
I WOULD NEVER DO THAT TO YOU.
OKAY, EVERYBODY, IT'S TRIFLE TIME.
SO, NOW, RACH...
THIS IS A TRADITIONAL ENGLISH TRIFLE, ISN'T IT?
IT SURE IS.
WOW. SO, THEN, DID YOU MAKE IT WITH BEEF OR EGGPLANT?
BEEF.
I CAN'T HAVE ANY, YOU KNOW?
I DON'T EAT BEEF.
ALL RIGHT, MONICA
I WANT YOU TO HAVE THE FIRST TASTE.
REALLY?
OH, WAIT WAIT!
YOU ONLY GOT WHIPPED CREAM IN THERE.
YOU'VE GOT TO TAKE A BITE
WITH ALL THE LAYERS.
OKAY.
OOPS, YOU DROPPED A PEA.
WELL?
MMM...
IT'S GOOD.
REALLY? HOW GOOD?
IT'S SO GOOD THAT  I FEEL REALLY SELFISH
BEING THE ONLY ONE WHO'S EATING IT.
AND I THINK WE SHOULD HAVE EVERYONE TASTE HOW GOOD IT IS.
ESPECIALLY ROSS.
MM HMM.
MMM...
YEAH, THIS IS SO GOOD
THAT I'M GOING TO GO ENJOY IT ON THE BALCONY.
SO I CAN ENJOY THE VIEW WHILST I ENJOY MY DESSERT.
AND I'M GOING TO CALL MY FRIEND, MARY
AND TELL HER HOW GOOD THIS IS FROM MONICA'S ROOM.
I'LL HELP YOU DIAL.
AND I'M GOING TO GO INTO THE BATHROOM
SO I CAN LOOK AT IT IN THE MIRROR AS I EAT IT.
OKAY, NOW, WHAT WAS THAT ALL ABOUT?
IS IT... DOES IT NOT TASTE GOOD?
LET ME TRY THAT.
NO! NO!
ALL GONE.
SO GOOD.
MAYBE CHANDLER HAS SOME LEFT.
IT TASTES LIKE FEET.
I LIKE IT.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
WHAT'S NOT TO LIKE?
CUSTARD? GOOD.
JAM? GOOD.
MEAT? GOOD!
SO A BIRD JUST GRABBED IT AND THEN...
AND THEN TRIED TO FLY AWAY WITH IT AND...
AND THEN JUST DROPPED IT ON THE STREET?
YES, BUT IF IT'S ANY CONSOLATION
BEFORE THE BIRD DROPPED IT, HE SEEMED TO ENJOY IT.
RACHEL, COME HERE.
OKAY...
I WAS JUST STARTING TO TAKE MY THANKSGIVING NAP
AND I HAD ANOTHER DREAM ABOUT JACK.
UH, PHOEBE, DO I WANT TO HEAR THIS?
I DON'T KNOW. LET'S SEE.
SO... OKAY, I DREAMT
THAT WE WERE GOING TO GET MARRIED
AND HE LEFT BECAUSE HE HAD TO GO FIGHT A FIRE.
AND, UM, SO, OKAY, I WENT TO A NIGHTCLUB
AND I SAW HIM MAKING OUT WITH A GIRL.
OH, MY GOD.
HE DREAM CHEATED ON YOU.
YEAH.
BUT THEN JACQUES COUSTEAU CAME
AND HE KICKED HIS  ASS FOR BETRAYING ME.
HE WAS SO COOL.
AND THEN, HE TOOK ME DIVING
AND HE INTRODUCED ME TO HIS PET SEA HORSE
WHO, BY THE WAY, WAS TOTALLY COMING ON TO ME
AND PLEASE, THAT IS NOT GOING TO HAPPEN.
BOY, I'M GLAD I WORE THE BIG BELT TODAY.
WOW.
FIVE MINUTES AGO, A LINE LIKE THAT WOULD HAVE FLOORED ME.
NOW NOTHING.
WELL, NOT NOTHING.
I AM STILL A WOMAN.
ROSS...
LET'S GO.
OH, YEAH, ABOUT TELLING MOM AND DAD
I WAS THINKING ABOUT MAYBE WRITING A LETTER.
YOU KNOW WHAT? THAT'S IT.
YOU'VE HAD YOUR CHANCE.
MOM, DAD, ROSS SMOKED POT IN COLLEGE.
WHAT? WHAT?
YOU ARE SUCH A TATTLETALE!
MOM, DAD...
YOU REMEMBER THAT...
THAT TIME YOU WALKED IN MY ROOM AND SMELLED MARIJUANA?
YES. YES.
WELL, I TOLD YOU IT WAS CHANDLER WHO WAS SMOKING THE POT, BUT...
IT WAS ME.
I'M SORRY.
IT WAS YOU?
YEAH, AND DAD
CHANDLER DIDN'T MELT YOUR RECORDS.
ROSS DID.
IS THAT TRUE?
YEP... AND YOU KNOW THAT MAILMAN THAT YOU GOT FIRED?
HE DIDN'T STEAL YOUR PLAYBOYS.
ROSS DID.
OH...
YEAH, WELL, HURRICANE GLOR IA DIDN'T BREAK THE PORCH SWING.
MONICA DID!
ROSS HASN'T WORKED AT THE MUSEUM FOR A YEAR!
MONICA AND CHANDLER ARE LIVING TOGETHER!
ROSS MARRIED RACHEL IN VEGAS AND GOT DIVORCED AGAIN!
I LOVE JACQUES COUSTEAU!
I WASN'T SUPPOSED TO PUT BEEF IN THE TRIFLE!
I WANT TO GO!
THAT'S A LOT OF INFORMATION TO GET IN 30 SECONDS.
ALL RIGHT
JOEY, IF YOU WANT TO LEAVE, JUST LEAVE.
RACHEL, NO, YOU WEREN'T SUPPOSED TO PUT BEEF IN THE TRIFLE.
IT DID NOT TASTE GOOD.
PHOEBE, I'M SORRY, BUT I THINK JACQUES COUSTEAU IS DEAD.
MONICA...
WHY YOU FELT
YOU HAD TO HIDE THE FACT
THAT YOU ARE IN AN IMPORTANT RELATIONSHIP IS BEYOND ME.
AND WE KIND OF FIGURED ABOUT THE PORCH SWING.
ROSS...
DRUGS, DIVORCED... AGAIN.
WHAT HAPPENED, SON?
I... I, UH, I GOT TRICKED INTO ALL THOSE THINGS.
CHANDLER, YOU'VE BEEN ROSS'S BEST FRIEND ALL THESE YEARS
STUCK BY HIM DURING THE DRUG PROBLEMS.
AND NOW YOU'VE TAKEN ON MONICA AS WELL.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
YOU'RE A WONDERFUL HUMAN BEING.
THANK YOU.
NO!
AND MONICA AND ROSS
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M GOING TO DO ABOUT THE TWO OF YOU
I'LL TALK TO THEM.
YOU GUYS, IT WAS BANANAS
CREAM AND BEEF.
I JUST CANNOT BELIEVE THAT YOU ATE THAT
SO THAT I WOULDN'T FEEL BAD.
ACTUALLY, I DIDN'T EAT MINE.
IT'S STILL IN THE BATHROOM.
NO, IT ISN'T. I ATE THAT.
AND WE LEFT OURS IN MONICA'S BEDROOM.
NO. GOT IT AND GOT YOURS, TOO.
SO, CHANDLER
ARE YOU GOING TO STICK WITH THAT BIRD STORY?
IT WAS A BIG BIRD, SWOOPED RIGHT IN THERE.
HI.
OH, JANINE... OH, NO.
OH, IT'S NOT OVER, IS IT?
YEAH. WE ALL GOT DEPRESSED.
YOU KNOW, THE HOLIDAYS AND EVERYTHING AND WE'RE ALONE.
YEAH, WELL, AT LEAST YOU HAVE JOEY
BUT ROSS IS REALLY ALONE.
WELL, YOU'RE ALWAYS WELCOME HERE.
THIS IS MY MOM AND MY DAD.
THIS IS JANINE.
HI. NICE TO MEET YOU.
I THINK WE'VE ALREADY MET.
REALLY?
I LIVE ACROSS THE HALL.
YOU WALKED IN ON ME WHEN I WAS CHANGING.