LET ME ASK YOU, WHY IS EVERYBODY USING
THESE TINY LITTLE LIGHTS NOWADAYS?
I REMEMBER WHEN PEOPLE USED TO USE BIG LIGHTS.
.
THAT'S A GOOD STORY, GRANDPA
HEY.
WOW.
MONICA'S LETTING OTHER PEOPLE HELP DECORATE HER TREE.
DID SOMEONE GET HER DRUNK AGAIN, OR...?
HAVING A PERFECTLY DECORATED TREE
IS NOT WHAT CHRISTMAS IS ABOUT.
IT'S ABOUT BEING WITH THE PEOPLE THAT YOU LOVE.
THAT IS NICE
AND WE'RE DONE, TA DA!
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS.
IT JUST DOESN'T QUITE FEEL LIKE CHRISTMAS TO ME.
OH, YEAH.
SEE, NOW IT FEELS LIKE CHRISTMAS.
AND THAT'S THE STORY OF THE DREIDEL.
NOW, SOME PEOPLE TRACE THE CHRISTMAS TREE
BACK TO THE EGYPTIANS
WHO USED TO BRING GREEN PALM BRANCHES
INTO THEIR HUTS ON THE SHORTEST DAY OF THE YEAR
SYMBOLIZING LIFE'S TRIUMPH OVER DEATH
AND THAT WAS, LIKE, 4,000 YEARS AGO.
SO, PRETTY MUCH AROUND THE SAME TIME
THAT YOU STARTED TELLING THIS STORY.
HEY, YOU GUYS.
HEY, JOE, WHAT'S UP?
I HAD TO GET OUT OF THE APARTMENT.
JANINE IS, LIKE, STRETCHING ALL OVER THE PLACE.
YOU KNOW, EVERYWHERE I LOOK, SHE'S, LIKE...
I CAN SEE WHY THAT'S HARD TO RESIST.
I LIKE HER SO MUCH!
OH, I'M SORRY, SWEETIE
THAT SHE DOESN'T FEEL THE SAME WAY.
I KNOW, AND SHE'S SO SWEET.
I JUST WANT TO FEED HER GRAPES AND BRUSH HER HAIR.
YOU ARE AWARE THAT SHE'S NOT A MONKEY, RIGHT?
I AM SO OVER JANINE.
I MEAN...
YEAH, AT FIRST I THOUGHT SHE WAS HOT
BUT NOW, SHE'S LIKE OLD NEWS.
HI, GUYS.
JANINE!
COFFEE TO GO, PLEASE.
I JUST GOT A CALL TO BE A DANCER
ON A TELEVISION SPECIAL FOR NEW YEAR'S EVE.
IT'S CALLED SOME SORT OF "DICKIN' ROCKIN' DICKIE EVE."
HOLD IT.
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT
DICK CLARK'S NEW YEAR'S ROCKIN' EVE?
YEAH. THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
OH, MY GOD!
WE LOVE THAT SHOW.
ROSS AND I HAVE BEEN WATCHING IT
SINCE I CAN REMEMBER. YEAH!
OH, YOU'RE STILL JUST A LITTLE FAT GIRL INSIDE
AREN'T YOU?
WELL, I'M GOING TO BE ON IT THIS YEAR.
I'M GOING TO BE ONE OF THE PARTY PEOPLE.
YOU'RE GOING TO BE A PARTY PERSON?!
THOSE GUYS ROCK THE MOST!
WELL, THEY SAID I SHOULD BRING SOMEONE.
DO YOU WANT TO BE MY DANCE PARTNER?
TOTALLY!
I WOULD LOVE TO SP END NEW YEAR'S WITH YOU.
NO, WELL, ACTUALLY, THEY'RE TAPING TOMORROW.
I DON'T REALLY UNDERSTAND WHY.
OH, WELL, YOU SEE, HOW IT WORKS IS
THE PART WITH DICK CLARK IN TIMES SQUARE
IS ACTUALLY LIVE
BUT THEY TAPE SOME OF THE PARTY STUFF AHEAD OF TIME.
YEAH, NOT A LOT OF PEOPLE KNOW THAT.
YEAH, WELL, DO YOU GUYS WANT TO COME, TOO?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
WE ARE THERE.
WHAT ARE YOU LAUGHING AT?
WELL, I USED TO DATE HIM
BUT YOU'RE STILL GOING OUT WITH HER.
OH, THANKS.
GREAT. SO WE CAN ALL GO TOGETHER.
I GOT TO RUN. I'LL CATCH YOU LATER.
BYE, JANINE.
DID SHE JUST ASK ME OUT ON A DATE?
I DON'T THINK SO.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT? SHE JUST INVITED HIM
TO THE BIGGEST PARTY OF THE MILLENNIUM.
YEAH, BUT SHE ALSO INVITED YOU AND ROSS.
HONEY, I'M... I'M SORRY
BUT I DON'T THINK THAT THAT WAS A ROMANTIC THING.
OH... MAYBE. BUT HEY, I KNOW HOW I CAN FIND OUT.
WE'RE GOING TO A NEW YEAR'S EVE PARTY, RIGHT?
SO AT MIDNIGHT, I CAN KISS HER.
AND IF SHE KISSES ME BACK, GREAT, YOU KNOW?
BUT IF SHE SAYS, "DUDE, WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?"
I CAN SAY, "IT WASN'T ME; IT WAS NEW YEAR'S."
WELL, THAT'S A LOT BETTER
THAN ROSS TRYING TO KISS ME IN HIGH SCHOOL
AND SAYING THAT HE DID IT BECAUSE HE NEEDED CHAPSTICK.
IT WAS A DRY DAY.
WE ARE GOING TO
DICK CLARK'S NEW YEAR'S ROCKIN' EVE!
OH, MY GOD!
OH, MY GOD.
OKAY, NOW LISTEN UP.
I'VE BEEN ON SETS BEFORE.
LET ME GIVE YOU A LITTLE ADVICE.
IT'S A SHOW, BUT WE'RE JUST DANCING, OKAY?
IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
THE IMPORTANT THING TO REMEMBER:
STAY COOL.
GOT IT.
OH, MY GOD, IT'S JUST LIKE I DREAMED IT!
OKAY, EVERYONE, GATHER UP.
EXCUSE US.
HERE'S WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN.
THE MUSIC'S GOING TO START, YOU'RE GOING TO DANCE.
WE'RE GOING TO TAPE YOU; DON'T LOOK AT THE CAMERA.
ANY QUESTIONS?
YEAH, I HAVE A QUESTION.
WHEN IS THIS GOING TO AIR?
YEAH.
NOW, YOU GUYS, DANCE OVER THERE.
YOU GUYS, OVER THERE.
I WANT YOU TWO RIGHT AROUND HERE
AND EVERYONE ELSE, SPREAD OUT.
YOU KNOW, WE'D RATHER NOT DANCE TOGETHER
BECAUSE, UM, SEE, WE'RE BROTHER AND SISTER.
YEAH. IT WOULD SEEM KIND OF WEIRD.
WOULD IT SEEM AS WEIRD AS COMING ALL THE WAY DOWN HERE
AND THEN HAVING TO GO HOME RIGHT NOW?
ROSS.
SO WHEN IS  IT GOING TO AIR?
OKAY, PHEEBS, YOU LOOK IN THE KITCHEN.
I WILL LOOK IN THE BACK CLOSET.
I CAN SAVE YOU TIME, LADIES.
I'M RIGHT HERE.
YEAH.
CHANDLER, WHY DON'T YOU TAKE A WALK?
THIS DOESN'T CONCERN YOU.
WE ARE LOOKING FOR
OUR CHRISTMAS PRESENTS FROM MONICA.
WHAT? THAT'S TERRIBLE.
NO, NO, WE DO IT EVERY YEAR.
OH, WELL, THAT MAKES IT NOT TERRIBLE.
NO, YEAH. WE NEVER FIND THEM.
SHE'S ALWAYS BESTED US, THAT WILY... MINX.
DON'T WORRY.
WE'RE JUST GOING TO SEARCH HERE FOR AN HOUR
AND THEN WE'RE GOING TO GO OVER TO JOEY'S AND SEARCH, OKAY?
NO, NOT OKAY.
YOU CAN'T LOOK FOR MONICA'S PRESENTS.
OH, NO, WE HAVE TO.
NO, YOU DON'T HAVE TO, AND YOU CAN'T
BECAUSE I LIVE HERE, TOO.
WELL, THEN, YOU SHOULD LOOK WITH US.
WHY?
CHANDLER, AREN'T YOU WORRIED
ABOUT WHAT TO GET MONICA FOR CHRISTMAS?
NO. I HAVE A GREAT IDEA FOR A PRESENT FOR HER.
OH, THAT'S IT, "A GREAT IDEA"?
CHANDLER, THAT'S NOT ENOUGH.
WHAT IF SHE GETS YOU A GREAT PRESENT
TWO MEDIUM PRESENTS
AND THEN A BUNCH OF LITTLE PRESENTS
AND YOU'VE JUST GOTTEN HER ONE GREAT PRESENT?
I MEAN, THAT'S JUST GO ING TO MAKE HER FEEL BAD.
WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT TO HER, CHANDLER?
WHY? WHY?
IF I HELPED, WE COULD FIND THEM FASTER.
THAT'S RIGHT.
OOH, WE HAVE A LIVE ONE.
IT'S A MACY'S BAG.
YEAH.
OOH, WHO'S IT FOR?
"DEAR LOSERS, DO YOU REALLY THINK
I'D HIDE PRESENTS UNDER THE COUCH?"
"P.S.: CHANDLER, I KNEW THEY'D BREAK YOU."
UH OH. SHE MAY BE ON TO US.
WE ARE SO GOING TO FIND THEM THIS YEAR.
YOU KNOW, YOU GUYS SAID YOU WERE
GOING TO GO ACROSS THE HALL AND LOOK.
YOU DON'T... YOU DON'T  DO THAT EVERY YEAR, DO YOU?
YEAH.
YOU DON'T, LIKE
GO INTO THE BACK OF MY CLOSET
AND LOOK UNDER MY GYM BAG OR ANYTHING.
NO. WE NEVER DO THAT.
BECAUSE THAT'S WHERE JOEY GAVE ME SOME STUFF TO STORE
THAT I'VE NEVER
SEEN BEFORE IN MY LIFE.
OKAY, THAT DID NOT JUST HAPPEN.
OKAY, HERE COMES ANOTHER CAMERA.
RIGHT. NO BIGGIE; STAY LOOSE.
WHY DO THEY KEEP DOING THAT?
YOU KNOW, IF WE WANT TO GET ON CAMERA
WE HAVE TO GET UP ON ONE OF THOSE PLATFORMS.
THEY'VE BEEN TAPING THOSE PEOPLE UP THERE ALL DAY.
RIGHT.
HEY, WHAT DID YOU GUYS DO TO GET UP ON THERE?
WE LEARNED HOW TO DANCE.
OH, YEAH?
WELL, WHEN YOU LEARNED HOW TO DANCE
DID YOU FORGET HOW  TO PUT ON UNDERPANTS?
YEAH.
HEY, YOU'RE A GOOD DANCER.
REALLY?
YEAH, WELL, YOU'D BE BETTER
IF YOU JUST LOOSENED YOUR HIPS A LITTLE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WELL, LIKE THIS.
THAT'S IT.
JUST FEEL THE RHYTHM.
THAT'S BETTER.
UH HUH.
OKAY, YOU'RE DANCING WITH THAT GIRL OVER THERE.
NO, NO, NO. WE'RE TOGETHER.
YEAH, WE CAME TOGETHER.
I DON'T SEE IT.
YOU ARE DANCING WITH THE TALL GUY OVER THERE.
TALL GUY, RAISE YOUR HAND.
NO, NO, HEY, BUDDY.
PLEASE LET ME DANCE WITH THAT GIRL.
I REALLY LIKE HER AND I THINK I HAVE A SHOT.
REALLY? YOU THINK SO?
YEAH. I DON'T.
I COULDN'T FIND ANYTHING AT JOEY...
HEY, WHOA, WHOA.
YEAH, WE FOUND THEM.
THEY WERE IN THE GUEST ROOM CLOSET BEHIND SOME COATS.
YEAH, AND YOU HAVE NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT
BECAUSE THEY'RE ALL CRAP.
THOSE ARE MY GIFTS.
I GOT THOSE FOR YOU.
OH, THANKS, CHANDLER.
THEY'RE GREAT.
WELL, CHANDLER
THEN WHAT IS THIS VERY WEIRD METAL "A," "Z" THING?
THOSE ARE BOOKENDS.
THAT'S A GREAT GIFT.
OH, OKAY, I'M SORRY.
THANK YOU FOR MY "AZ."
MAKE SURE YOU PUT ALL THAT STUFF BACK IN THE CLOSET, OKAY?
YES, OKAY.
OH, BY THE WAY, I JUST GOT TO SAY
I THINK IT'S REALLY NICE OF YOU THAT EVEN AFTER YOU'VE MOVED
YOU STILL KEEP STORING THAT STUFF FOR JOEY.
HEY, DANCING GIRL.
CAN I... CAN I  GO TO THE BATHROOM?
OKAY, HERE WE GO.
YEAH. THERE YOU GO.
LOOKING GOOD, GELLERS.
WE KNOW.
HEY, LOOK.
YOU KNOW THAT SNIPPY GUY OVER THERE?
HE'S THE ONE WHO DECIDES WHO GETS ON THE PLATFORM.
WE SHOULD GO DANCE BY HIM.
OKAY.
OKAY, EVERYBODY HOLD.
NEXT ON THE PLATFORMS ARE...
YOU TWO.
AND...
EXCUSE ME, SIR.
WOULD IT HELP IF I WEREN'T WEARING UNDERPANTS?
MONICA!
WOULD IT?
HOW ABOUT ME?
HEY, TALL GUY.
LISTEN, I WANT TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT THAT GIRL
THAT YOU'RE DANCING WITH.
SHE'S NICE, HUH?
TO THINK I ALMOST BROUGHT MY WIFE TO THIS.
YEAH, YEAH. OKAY.
UH, LOOK, BUDDY, I CAME WITH THAT GIRL.
AND I HAD THIS PLAN TO KISS HER
AT THE NEW YEAR'S COUNTDOWN.
I'M TRYING TO WIN HER OVER, YOU KNOW?
SO I WAS WONDERING...
I DON'T THINK SO.
OH, COME ON, MAN.
YOU CAN DANCE WITH MY PARTNER.
SHE'S REAL MELLOW.
LOOK, YOU, UH... YOU DATING THIS GIRL YOU CAME WITH?
WELL, I WAS HOPING AFTER TONIGHT
THAT MAYBE I COULD, YOU KNOW...
NO, NO, SHE'S FAIR GAME IF YOU ASK ME.
SORRY, BUDDY.
ALL RIGHT.
HEY, YOU KNOW, FAIR IS FAIR.
I MEAN, WHEN YOU'RE RIGHT YOU'RE RIGHT.
WHAT CAN I SAY, BUT...
HEY!
GOD!
WHAT, ARE YOU  IN THE SECOND GRADE?
HEY, MAN, YOU'RE THE ONE WHO WET HIS PANTS.
HEY! HEY!
HEY!
YOU GUYS, I'M TELLING YOU
MONICA WOULD NOT HIDE THE PRESENTS DOWN HERE.
NO, BUT SHE DID-- LOOK.
THERE'S THAT OLD HIPPIE I'VE ALWAYS WANTED.
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT, IF THEY ARE HERE
GUNTHER KNOWS ABOUT IT.
OH, AND I COULD GET IT OUT OF HIM.
HE'S HAD A HUGE CRUSH ON ME.
OH...
NO, NO, THAT'S NOT FAIR TO PLAY WITH HIS HEAD, THOUGH.
NO, YOU DO IT, RACHEL.
OKAY.
HEY, GUNTHER.
HI.
GETTING TO BE THAT HOLIDAY TIME AGAIN, HUH?
YES, IT'S LIKE A MIRACLE.
AND YOU KNOW, I WAS THINKING, YOU KNOW
SINCE IT'S THE TIME OF GIVING GIFTS...
I WAS WONDERING, ARE THERE ANY PRESENTS AROUND HERE FOR ME
IF YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
HEY, I THINK I FOUND THEM.
THAT'S THE TOYS FOR TOTS COLLECTION BIN.
WELL, THAT'S AWFULLY CONVENIENT, DON'T YOU THINK?
FOR THE TOTS IT IS.
HEY, YOU GUYS, GUESS WHAT?
WHAT? DID YOU FIND THEM?
NO. GUNTHER FAINTED.
MAN, THIS SUCKS.
IF MOM AND DAD DON'T SEE US ON TV
AFTER WE MADE THEM SO JEALOUS
WHO'S GOING TO BE THE LOSERS THEN?
HEY, I KNOW WHAT WILL  GET US UP ON A PLATFORM.
WHAT?
THE ROUTINE.
ROSS, WE HAVEN'T DONE THE ROUTINE SINCE MIDDLE SCHOOL.
HEY, WHEN THE SNIPPY GUY SEES THE ROUTINE
HE'LL WANT TO BUILD  US OUR OWN PLATFORM.
WAS IT REALLY THAT GOOD?
WE GOT HONORABLE MENTION
IN THE BROTHER/SIS TER DANCE CATEGORY.
LOOK, IT'S ALMOST FAKE MIDNIGHT.
DO WE REALLY HAVE ANY OTHER CHOICE?
OKAY, LET'S DO IT.
MOM AND DAD ARE GOING TO BE SO FACED.
FIVE, SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT.
SO, DO WE REALLY NEED TO ASK
WHO'S GOING UP ON THE PLATFORM NEXT?
OH, NO.
GET UP THERE AND DO THAT AGAIN EXACTLY LIKE THAT.
YEAH!
MAKE SURE AND GET THIS.
DICK WILL WANT IT FOR THE BLOOPERS SHOW.
ALL RIGHT, CUT.
LISTEN UP, EVERYONE.
WHEN WE START AGAIN
IT'S GOING TO BE THE COUNTDOWN TO NEW YEAR'S
SO I WANT TO SEE EVERYBODY'S EXCITEMENT.
HEY, GUY, YOU'VE GOT ABOUT THREE SECONDS
TO GET AWAY FROM MY PARTNER.
WHAT'S GOING ON OVER HERE?
TAKE A LOOK AT THE GUY'S PANTS, HUH?
I MEAN, I KNOW YOU TOLD US TO SHOW EXCITEMENT
BUT DON'T YOU THINK HE WENT A LITTLE OVERBOARD.
WHAT'S THE MAT TER WITH YOU?
GET OUT OF HERE.
YEAH, TAKE A HIKE, WET PANTS.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THIS?
WE'RE GOING TO  BE ON THE PLATFORM
FOR THE MILLENNIAL MOMENT.
I KNOW.
HEY, YOU HAVEN'T BEEN PRACTICING
THE ROUTINE, HAVE YOU?
NO.
ME, TOO.
HEY, WHEN THE MUSIC STARTS UP AGAIN
I WAS THINKING ABOUT MAYBE GOING INTO THE ROBOT, YOU KNOW.
ROSS, I THINK WE SHOULD STICK TO THE ROUTINE.
WE DON'T WANT TO LOOK STUPID.
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE BACK.
TEN SECONDS LEFT. HERE WE GO.
TEN...
NINE...
EIGHT...
SEVEN...
OKAY...
IT ALL COMES DOWN TO THIS.
WHATEVER HAPPENS, HAPPENS.
DESTINY.
THREE...
TWO...
ONE...
CUT!
NO!
YEAR!
HAPPY NO YEAR.
OKAY, HERE'S WHERE WE GO TO THE LIVE SHOT OF TIMES SQUARE.
NICE WORK, EVERYONE.
THAT'S A WRAP.
HEY, WHAT DID THAT SNIPPY GUY SAY?
I THINK HE'S KICKING OUT ANYONE WHO'S NOT DANCING
SO JUST KEEP DANCING!
HEY, LOOK WHO I FOUND.
OH, HI, GUYS.
YOU KNOW, BIRDS HAVE A VERY GOOD SENSE OF DIRECTION.
I THOUGHT MAYBE THEY COULD HELP US FIND
WHERE THE PRESENTS ARE HIDDEN.
YES, IF THE PRESENTS ARE HIDDEN SOUTH FOR THE WINTER.
OR WE COULD JUST FOLLOW YOUR CLEVER JOKES.
ANY IDEAS? NO? DIDN'T THINK SO. OKAY!
COME ON, GUYS.
SHOW US WHERE THE PRESENTS ARE.
THE DUCK SEEMS TO THINK THAT MONICA GOT ME GARBAGE.
HMM, I WONDER WHAT I CAN GET MONICA
THAT'S AS GOOD AS GARBAGE?
HMM, HOW ABOUT MY "AZ"?
HEY, THIS IS HOLLOW.
WHAT?
THIS BENCH, IT'S HOLLOW.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I NEVER KNEW THAT.
OH! THE PRESENTS!
NO, DON'T LOOK DIRECTLY AT THEM.
WHAT?
ALL RIGHT, NO, WE COULD LOOK AT THEM.
OH, THIS ONE'S FOR ME.
THIS ONE'S FOR CHANDLER.
ALL RIGHT.
AND THE BIG ONE'S FOR ME.
LET'S OPEN THEM.
OKAY, OKAY.
WAIT A MINUTE, WAIT A MINUTE.
WE CAN'T DO THIS.
WHY? WHY?
I DON'T WANT TO KNOW WHAT MONICA GOT ME, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, LOOK, I'M SURE SHE WORKED REALLY HARD
AT GETTING ME A PRESENT AND WANTING TO SURPRISE ME
AND YOU GUYS ARE GOING TO RUIN THAT.
LOOK, WE HAVE TO PUT THESE BACK.
THIS IS NOT WHAT CHRISTMAS IS ABOUT.
WHATEVER, LINUS.
I'M OPENING MINE.
NOBODY IS OPENING ANYTHING, OKAY?
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU GUYS
BUT I WANT TO SEE THE LOOK ON MONICA'S FACE
WHEN I GIVE HER MY PRESENT.
AND I'M SURE SHE WANTS TO SEE THE LOOK ON MY FACE
WHEN I GET MINE.
SO, PLEASE, PLEASE, CAN WE JUST...
CAN WE PUT THEM BACK?
WILL YOU GET US BETTER GIFTS?
FINE.
HEY, GUYS.
YOU FOUND THE PRESENTS?
CHANDLER, YOU LET THEM FIND THE PRESENTS?
GREAT.
DO YOU KNOW HOW LONG IT TOOK ME TO FIND YOU THAT WATER PURIFIER?
THAT'S WHAT YOU GOT ME?
OH, YES, I SEE WHAT YOU MEAN. THAT LOOK IS PRICELESS.
HOME SWEET HOME, HUH?
NICE TO GET BACK TO REALITY.
PLUS, WE KNOW  HOW THE NEW YEAR'S
GOING TO GO OFF.
I GUESS THERE'S NO REASON
FOR ALL THAT Y2K PANIC, YOU KNOW.
ANYWAY, GOOD NIGHT.
JOEY.
YEAH?
THREE...
TWO... ONE.
HAPPY NEW YEAR.
WHAT WAS THAT FOR?
OH, I DON'T KNOW.
TONIGHT WHEN THEY YELLED CUT
AND WE DIDN'T GET TO KISS
I WAS REALLY, REALLY DISAPPOINTED.
AND I JUST...
I JUST REALLY WANTED TO KISS YOU.
REALLY?
IN THE MOMENT
I REALLY WANTED TO KISS YOU, TOO.
IN THE MOMENT.
IN THE MOMENT, HUH?
BUT ONLY IN THE MOMENT.
SO, DO YOU...
WANT TO KISS AGAIN?
SURE. NEW YEAR'S EVE IS ONLY TWO WEEKS AWAY.
CAN YOU WAIT?
NO.
ME NEITHER.
THREE... TWO...
JOEY, YOU DON'T HAVE TO COUNTDOWN
EVERY TIME WE KISS.
OKAY.
EXCEPT THAT I SORT OF FELT LIKE I NEEDED
A COUPLE SECONDS TO GET READY.
?? FOR AULD LANG SYNE ??
?? WE'LL TAKE A CUP OF KINDNESS YET ??
?? FOR AULD LANG SYNE. ??
WE WERE ON THE PLATFORM
READY TO DANCE THE WORLD INTO THE NEW MILLENNIUM
AND THE GUY YELLS "CUT."
OH, SO, JOEY DIDN'T GET TO KISS JANINE?
NOPE, HE SURE DIDN'T.
WOW. SO, THEN I GUESS THAT MEANS THAT YOU GUYS ARE STILL TIED.
OH, I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT.
I THINK SHE SAW US DO OUR ROUTINE.
YEAH.
I MAY HAVE BOOGIED RIGHT INTO FIRST PLACE.
WAIT A MINUTE, SO YOU GUYS ARE TELLING ME
THAT YOU ACTUALLY DID THE ROUTINE FROM EIGHTH GRADE?
YEAH.
BUT OF COURSE WE HAD TO UPDATE IT A LITTLE BIT.
HEY, BY THE WAY, QUICK THINKING ABOUT CATCHING ME.
YEAH, BECAUSE I WAS GOING TO SAY
THERE'S NO WAY YOU COULD HAVE DONE THE END
THE WAY YOU GUYS DID IT BACK THEN.
WHAT?
WE COULD DO IT.
I DON'T KNOW. I MEAN, YOU WERE A LOT BIGGER...
I MEAN, STRONGER BACK THEN.
I CAN DO IT, OKAY.
COME ON, LET'S GO. COME ON.
ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR, FIVE...
SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT.
I CAN'T DO IT!
NOW, YOU DO THAT, YOU'RE ON TV.