HEY, CHECK THIS OUT.
YOU ARE NOT GOING TO BELIEVE THIS.
YES, ROSS, WE KNOW THEY HAVE MAGAZINES
WITH PICTURES OF NAKED WOMEN IN THEM.
OH, DON'T TELL HIM ABOUT THE VIDEOS
I MADE UP A JOKE AND SENT IT IN TO PLAYBOY.
THEY PRINTED IT.
I DIDN'T KNOW PLAYBOY PRINTS JOKES.
YEAH, THEY PRINT JOKES, UH, INTERVIEWS
HARD HITTING JOURNALISM.
IT'S NOT JUST ABOUT THE PICTURES.
IT DIDN'T WORK ON MOM.
IT'S NOT GOING TO WORK ON US.
HERE, CHECK IT OUT.
IT'S THE FIRST ONE, TOO.
RIGHT THERE.
THAT IS FUNNY.
IT WAS ALSO FUNNY WHEN I MADE IT UP.
WHAT?
I MADE THAT JOKE UP.
UH, OH, NO, YOU DIDN'T. I DID.
UH UH OH, YES, I DID.
I TOLD IT TO DAN AT WORK AND HE SAID IT WAS
THE FUNNIEST JOKE HE'D EVER HEARD.
HEY, TELL DAN "THANKS."
WHAT?
I'M SORRY. I WAS JUST READING THE JOKE BELOW IT.
MAN, THAT ONE IS FUNNY.
MONICA, YOU REMEMBER ME TELLING YOU THAT JOKE, RIGHT?
NO.
SERIOUSLY?
WELL, YOU TELL A LOT OF JOKES.
LOOK, CHANDLER, IT'S MY JOKE.
HEY, IF IT MAKES YOU FEEL ANY BETTER
THEY DON'T PRINT THE NAME
SO IT DOESN'T REALLY MATTER WHO GETS CREDIT, RIGHT?
YEAH, I GUESS NOT.
HEY, GUYS.
HEY, JOEY! PLAYBOY PRINTED MY JOKE!
NO! NO! IT'S MINE!
CALL THEM. THEY'LL TELL YOU.
IT'S MY JOKE. IT'S MY JOKE!
WHOA! WHOA! WHOA!
JOKES?
YOU GUYS KNOW THEY HAVE NAKED CHICKS IN THERE, RIGHT?
DUDE, DUDE, YOU HAVE GOT TO TURN ON BEHIND THE MUSIC.
THE BAND HEART IS HAVING A REALLY TOUGH TIME
AND I THINK THEY MAY BREAK UP.
HEY, LET'S GO WATCH THAT AT YOUR PLACE.
NO, NO, NO. MONICA'S WATCHING SOME COOKING SHOW.
COME ON, I DON'T WANT TO MISS WHEN THEY WERE SKINNY.
UH, HEY HEY, CHANDLER, CHANDLER
YOU KNOW WHAT WE SHOULD DO?
YOU AND I SHOULD GO OUT AND GET SOME NEW SUNGLASSES.
WHAT? NO. I WANT TO WATCH THIS.
DID YOUR CABLE GO OUT?
NO, NO. THAT'S VH1.
I GOT TO TELL YOU, THE MUSIC THESE KIDS LISTEN TO TODAY
IT'S LIKE A LOT OF NOISE TO ME. I DON'T KNOW.
JOEY, WHY IS YOUR CABLE OUT?
UH... OH, BECAUSE I HAVEN'T REALLY PAID THE BILL.
LOOK, IF YOU NEED MONEY, WOULD YOU PLEASE, PLEASE
JUST LET ME LOAN YOU SOME MONEY? NO, CHANDLER.
LOOK, FORGET ABOUT IT, OKAY?
LOOK, I KNOW THINGS HAVE BEEN A LITTLE TIGHT
SINCE JANINE MOVED OUT-- GOD, WAS SHE HOT.
WHOA HO. I KNOW.
BUT LOOK, I CAN HANDLE IT, ALL RIGHT?
I CAN... LISTEN TO THE RADIO, HUH?
AND, UH, HEY, ROSS GAVE ME THIS GREAT BOOK.
OKAY, FINE. YOU WANT TO SEE IF THE JOKE STEALER
WILL LET US WATCH THE SHOW AT HIS PLACE?
SURE. YEAH.
PAID YOUR PHONE BILL? NOT SO MUCH.
HEY.
OH. IT'S ONLY YOU.
WH WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WE ARE LOOKING AT A PLAYBOY.
OH, I WANT TO LOOK, TOO.
YIKES!
SO DO YOU THINK THAT THESE PICTURES...
ARE THEY TRYING TO TELL A STORY?
OH, WELL, YEAH, SURE.
I MEAN, LIKE IN THE CASE OF THIS YOUNG WOMAN
SHE HAS LOST HER CLOTHES, SO...
SO SHE RIDES NAKED ON  THE HORSE, SHE'S CRYING OUT.
"WHERE ARE THEY? WHERE ARE THEY?"
WELL, SHE'S NOT GOING TO FIND THEM
LYING IN THE GRASS LIKE THAT.
OH... YEAH.
OH, REMEMBER THE DAYS
WHEN YOU USED TO GO OUT TO THE BARN
LIFT UP YOUR SHIRT AND BEND OVER?
YEAH.
YOU SEE, NOW...
.
SEE, NOW, I WO ULD DATE THIS GIRL
SHE'S CUTE; SHE'S OUTDOORSY.
YOU KNOW, AND SHE KNOWS HOW TO BUILD A FIRE.
I MEAN, THAT'S GOT TO COME IN HANDY.
HEY, I GOT A QUESTION. MM HMM?
IF YOU HAD TO PICK ONE OF US TO DATE, WHO WOULD IT BE?
I DON'T KNOW.
ME, NEITHER. RACHEL.
WHAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
ME, NEITHER.
YOU KNOW, YOU FORGET HOW MANY GREAT SONGS HEART HAD.
YEAH. YEAH.
YOU KNOW, "BARRACUDA" WAS THE FIRST SONG
I LEARNED TO PLAY ON THE KEYBOARD.
SO YOU HEARD IT, YOU REPEATED IT...
SO THAT MUST MEAN... YOU WROTE IT.
OH, YOU GUYS WITH THIS JOKE.
LOOK, I GOT TO SAY, I KNOW I CRACKED UP
BUT I'M NOT EVEN SURE I GOT IT.
WHAT?
YOU DIDN'T GET IT?
THE DOCTOR IS A MONKEY.
AND MONKEYS CAN'T WRITE OUT PRESCRIPTIONS.
YOU ARE NOT ALLOWED TO LAUGH AT MY JOKE.
YOUR JOKE?
WELL, I THINK THE HEF WOULD DISAGREE
WHICH IS WHY HE SENT ME A CHECK FOR $100 DOLLARS.
SO YOU STOLE MY JOKE, AND YOU STOLE MY MONEY?
YOU KNOW...
I WAS GOING TO STICK IT IN THE ATM
BUT NOW I THINK I'LL SHOW THE SEXY TELLER
THAT I AM A PUBLISHED WRITER.
WELL, SHE IS GOING TO KNOW THAT YOU STOLE THE JOKE.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO, FOLLOW ME DOWN THERE? YEAH.
WELL, I'M NOT GOING TO GO NOW ANYWAY. OKAY.
HERE YOU GO. OH.
UH...
UH, GUNTHER...
I CAN'T PAY FOR THIS RIGHT NOW
BECAUSE, UH, I'M NOT WORKING
SO I'VE HAD TO CUT DOWN  ON SOME LUXURIES LIKE, UH...
PAYING FOR STUFF, SO...
WELL... IF YOU WANT, YOU CAN WORK HERE.
UH, I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S, UH, IT'S JUST...
SEE, I WAS A REGULAR ON A SOAP OPERA, YOU KNOW...
AND TO GO FROM THAT TO THIS, IT'S JUST...
AND PLUS, YOU KNOW, I'D HAVE TO WAIT ON ALL MY FRIENDS.
OKAY, BUT THE MONEY'S GOOD.
PLUS YOU GET TO STARE AT RACHEL AS MUCH AS YOU WANT.
WHAT?
FLEXIBLE HOURS.
OH.
MAYBE... MAYBE I COULD BE A WAITER.
COULD I USE THE PHONE?
SHE PICKED RACHEL.
I MEAN, SHE TRIED TO BACK OUT OF IT
BUT IT WAS OBVIOUS-- SHE PICKED RACHEL.
HE TOOK MY JOKE; HE J JUST TOOK IT.
THAT'S WRONG.
YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE IS WRONG?
PHOEBE PICKING RACHEL.
YOU KNOW WHO ELSE PICKED RACHEL?
ROSS. YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE ROSS DID?
HE STOLE MY JOKE.
YOU KNOW WHAT? I'M GOING TO GET A JOKE JOURNAL, YOU KNOW?
AND DOCUMENT THE DATE AND TIME
OF EVERY SINGLE ONE OF MY JOKES.
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA. YEAH.
YOU KNOW WHAT'S A BAD IDEA? PICKING RACHEL.
THAT'S RIGHT.
DID YOU HEAR SOMETHING?
WELL, MAYBE IT'S THE SOUND OF ROSS
CLIMBING INTO MY BRAIN AND STEALING MY THOUGHTHS.
I THINK IT'S COMING FROM THE LIVING ROOM.
I FINISHED MY BOOK.
HEY, YOU GUYS.
HEY. HEY.
OH, DON'T YOU GUYS LOOK CUTE.
YOU GUYS MAKE SUCH A CUTE COUPLE.
MONICA, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
NOTHING. I'M JUST TRYING TO RECREATE SOME OF THE FUN
THAT WE HAD AT MY PLACE THE OTHER DAY.
REMEMBER? WHEN YOU PICKED RACHEL OVER ME?
THAT WAS FUNNY.
YES, IT WAS KIND OF FUNNY.
IT WASN'T FUNNY AT ALL.
WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT?
WHY DIDN'T YOU PICK ME?
FINE.
THE REASON THAT I WAS LEANING
A LITTLE BIT MORE TOWARD RACHEL THAN YOU
IS JUST, YOU KNOW, YOU'RE... KIND OF HIGH MAINTENANCE.
OKAY, LET'S GO TO LUNCH.
THAT... THAT IS COMPLETELY UNTRUE.
YOU THINK I'M HIGH MAINTENANCE?
OKAY, PROVE IT-- I WANT YOU TO WRITE OUT A LIST
AND WE'RE GOING TO GO THROUGH IT POINT BY POINT.
NO, YOU'RE RIGHT -- YOU'RE EASYGOING.
YOU'RE JUST NOT
AS EASYGOING AS RACHEL.
YOU KNOW, SHE'S JUST MORE... FLEXIBLE
AND AND MELLOW, THAT'S ALL.
WELL, PEOPLE ARE DIFFERENT.
YEAH, YOU KNOW, RACHEL--
SHE'LL DO WHATEVER YOU WANT, YOU KNOW?
YOU CAN JUST WALK ALL OVER HER.
WHAT? WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT, ARE YOU SAYING I'M A PUSHOVER?
I'M NOT A PUSHOVER.
OH, OKAY. YOU'RE NOT A PUSHOVER.
OH, MY... YOU THINK I'M A PUSHOVER.
WELL, WATCH THIS. YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU'RE NOT INVITED TO LUNCH.
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THAT?
I THINK THAT'S PRETTY STRONG, IS WHAT I THINK.
COME ON, MONICA, LET'S GO TO LUNCH.
YOU START WORKING ON THAT LIST!
I CANNOT BELIEVE HER. I KNOW.
WHERE DO YOU WANT TO GO EAT?
OH... OH! I LOVE THAT JAPANESE PLACE.
I'M SICK OF JAPANESE. WE'RE NOT GOING THERE.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, WHERE VER YOU WANT TO GO IS COOL.
ALL RIGHT.
OH, HEY, GUNTHER
CHECK THIS OUT.
YEAH, THAT CHANDLER CRACKS ME UP.
HEY, ROSS, LISTEN, YOU WANT ANYTHING TO DRINK?
BECAUSE I'M HEADING UP THERE.
UH, YEAH, I'LL TAKE A COFFEE.
THANKS, MAN. SURE.
COFFEE? NO.
COFFEE? BECAUSE I'M GOING UP THERE.
OH, NO, THANK YOU. OKAY.
YOU GUYS NEED ANYTHING?
BECAUSE I'M HEADING UP THERE.
I'D LOVE A... ICE WATER.
YOU GOT IT.
JOEY... WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
JUST BEING FRIENDLY.
JOEY, I I DON'T THINK YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO GO BACK THERE.
NO, NO, IT'S OKAY. RIGHT GUNTHER?
DON'T WINK AT ME.
AND PUT ON YOUR APRON.
OKAY.
I DON'T SEE YOU ASKING ANY OTHER PAYING CUSTOMERS
TO PUT ON APRONS.
JOEY... DO YOU WORK HERE?
NO.
WAITER? YEAH?
JOEY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL US YOU WORK HERE?
WELL...
WELL... IT'S KIND OF EMBARRASSING, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, I WAS AN ACTOR; NOW I'M A WAITER.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO GO IN THE OTHER DIRECTION.
SO IS YOUR APRON-- YOU'RE WEARING IT LIKE A CAPE.
I MEAN, THE JOB'S EASY, AND THE MONEY'S GOOD, YOU KNOW
AND I GUESS IF I'M GOING TO BE HANGING OUT HERE ANYWAY
I MIGHT AS WELL GET PAID FOR IT, RIGHT?
I JUST FEEL KIND OF WEIRD SERVING YOU GUYS, YOU KNOW?
IT'LL BE GREAT. OH...
JOEY, COME ON, I DID IT
AND IT WAS FINE.
YEAH. WHY WOULD IT BE WEIRD?
HEY, JOEY, UH, COULD I GET SOME COFFEE?
OKAY, I GUESS IT DOESN'T SEEM THAT WEIRD.
SERIOUSLY, I ASKED YOU BEFORE-- YOU STILL HAVEN'T GOTTEN IT.
SEE, NOW IT'S WEIRD AGAIN.
I THINK IT'S GREAT THAT YOU WORK HERE.
YOU'LL MAKE A LOT OF MONEY, AND HERE'S YOUR FIRST TIP:
DON'T EAT YELLOW SNOW.
2:15. COFFEE HOUSE.
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT? THIS IS GREAT.
FINALLY, I HAVE SOMEONE I CAN PASS ON MY WISDOM TO.
LET ME TELL YOU ABOUT A COUPLE THINGS I LEARNED
WHILE WORKING AT THE COFFEE HOUSE.
UM, FIRST OF ALL, THE CUSTOMER IS ALWAYS RIGHT;
A SMILE GOES A LONG WAY;
AND IF ANYONE IS EVER RUDE TO YOU...
SNEEZE MUFFIN.
THANKS, RACHE.
HEY, LOOK...
YOU GUYS ARE JUST TERRIFIC, YOU KNOW?
NOW, HOW ABOUT CLEARING OUT OF HERE
SO I CAN GET SOME NEW CUSTOMERS, HUH?
IT'S ALL ABOUT TURNOVER.
JOEY...
SERIOUSLY
CAN I GET MY COFFEE?
OH, I'M SORRY, ROSS.
I'LL GET IT FOR YOU RIGHT NOW.
AND SINCE I MADE YOU WAIT, I'LL TOSS IN A FREE MUFFIN.
PHOEBE, WE WOULD LIKE TO TALK TO YOU FOR A SECOND.
OKAY.
SO...
MAYBE I AM A LITTLE HIGH MAINTENANCE
AND MAYBE RACHEL IS A LITTLE BIT OF A PUSHOVER
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT WE DECIDED THAT YOU ARE?
YES, WE ARE VERY SORRY TO TELL YOU THIS
BUT YOU, PHOEBE, ARE FLAKY.
HA!
THAT'S TRUE.
I AM FLAKY.
SO, WHAT?
YOU'RE JUST, UH, YOU'RE JUST OKAY WITH BEING FLAKY?
YEAH, TOTALLY.
WELL, THEN I'M OKAY WITH BEING HIGH MAINTENANCE.
YEAH, AND I AM OKAY WITH BEING A PUSHOVER.
THAT'S GREAT.
GOOD FOR YOU GUYS!
I AM NOT HIGH MAINTENANCE!
I AM NOT A PUSHOVER!
WHO SAID YOU WERE?!
YOU DID! YOU DID!
I'M FLAKY.
I'LL SAY ANYTHING.
HEY, GUNTHER, CAN YOU COVER FOR ME?
I JUST GOT AN AUDITION.
NO. I'M LEAVING TO GET MY HAIR DYED.
REALLY? I LIKE YOUR NATURAL COLOR.
COME ON, MAN, IT'S A GREAT PART.
CHECK IT OUT.
I'M THE LEAD GUY'S BEST FRIEND
AND I WAIT FOR HIM IN THIS BAR AND SAVE HIS SEAT.
LISTEN. LISTEN.
I'M SORRY. THAT SEAT'S SAVED.
THAT'S THE WHOLE PART?
OKAY, MAYBE HE'S NOT HIS BEST FRIEND, BUT...
OKAY, I'LL SEE YOU IN AN HOUR.
I COULD TOTALLY GET THAT PART.
I'M SORRY. THIS SEAT IS TAKEN.
OH, EXCUSE ME.
NO, NO, NO, I... I DIDN'T MEAN YOU
BUT, UH, YOU BELIEVED ME, HUH?
I BELIEVED YOU WERE SAVING THIS SEAT FOR SOMEONE.
SO YOU'D HIRE ME, RIGHT?
FOR WHAT?
EXACTLY!
ALL RIGHT, UH, EVERYBODY, LISTEN UP.
THE COFFEEHOUSE IS GOING TO BE CLOSED FOR ABOUT AN HOUR.
WHAT?!
WE JUST GOT HERE.
YEAH, IT'S, UH, IT'S FOR THE KIDS.
YEAH, TO, UH, KEEP THE KIDS OFF DRUGS.
YUP, IT'S
A VERY IMPORTANT ISSUE IN THIS MONTH'S PLAYBOY.
I'M SURE YOU ALL READ ABOUT IT.
HEY, HEY, DON'T YOU WANT
TO KEEP GUNS AWAY FROM KIDS?
YOU SAID DRUGS.
IT'S A VICIOUS CYCLE. GET OUT!
GO!
IT'S MY JOKE.
IT'S MY JO IT'S MY JOKE.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T THINK WE'RE GO ING TO SETTLE THIS.
NO. LET'S HAVE MONICA DECIDE.
YEAH.
YEAH. HEY, MON!
MON, GET OUT HERE!
MONICA!
OKAY, OKAY.
YOU HAVE TO HELP US DECIDE WHOSE JOKE THIS IS.
WHY DO I HAVE TO DECIDE?
BECAUSE YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE THAT CAN BE FAIR.
I CAN'T BE FAIR.
YOU'RE MY BOYFRIEND.
YEAH, BUT I'M YOUR BROTHER.
WE'RE FAMILY.
THAT'S THE MOST IMPORTANT THING IN THE WORLD.
DON'T TRY TO SWAY HER.
I'M YOUR ONLY CHANCE TO HAVE A BABY.
OKAY, LET'S GO.
ALL RIGHT, UM, OKAY, WE'LL EACH TELL YOU
HOW WE CAME  UP WITH THE JOKE
AND THEN YOU DECIDE
WHICH ONE OF US IS TELLING THE TRUTH-- ME.
CHANDLER, YOU GO FIRST.
OKAY, I THOUGHT OF THE JOKE
TWO MONTHS AGO AT LUNCH WITH STEVE.
OH, WAIT, IS HE THE GUY I MET AT CHRISTMAS?
CAN I FINISH MY STORY?
DO YOU WANT ME TO PICK YOU?
SEE, I WOULD NEVER SNAP AT YOU LIKE THAT.
CONTINUE.
OKAY, SO STEVE SAID HE HAD TO GO TO THE DOCTOR
AND STEVE'S DOCTOR'S NAME IS DR. MOMPEY.
SO I SAID, "DR. MONKEY?"
AND THAT IS HOW THE WHOLE DR. MONKEY THING CAME UP.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
OKAY, LOOK, I STUDY EVOLUTION.
REMEMBER? EVOLUTION?
MONKEY INTO MAN.
PLUS, I'M A DOCTOR
AND IHADA MONKEY.
I'M DR. MONKEY!
I'M NOT ARGUING WITH THAT.
ALL RIGHT, I'VE HEARD ENOUGH.
I HAVE MADE MY DECISION.
YOU ARE BOTH IDIOTS.
THE JOKE IS NOT FUNNY, AND IT'S OFFENSIVE TO WOMEN...
AND DOCTORS... AND MONKEYS.
YOU SHOULDN'T BE ARGUING OVER WHO GETS CREDIT.
YOU SHOULD BE ARGUING OVER WHO GETS BLAMED
FOR INFLICTING THIS HORRIBLE JOKE UPON THE WORLD.
NOW, LET IT GO.
THE JOKE SUCKS!
IT'S YOUR JOKE.
IT IS NOT.
MY GOD, CHANDLER, THERE YOU ARE.
HI I!
HEY, IT'S PHOEBE AND RACHEL.
WHY DON'T YOU TELL THEM
WHAT YOU WERE TELLING ME EARLIER
ABOUT ME NOT BEING HIGH MAINTENANCE.
MONICA IS A SELF SUFFICIENT, TOGETHER LADY.
BEING WITH HER HAS BEEN LIKE BEING ON A VACATION.
AND WHAT MAY BE PERCEIVED AS HIGH MAINTENANCE
IS MERELY ATTENTION TO DETAIL AND...
GENEROSITY OF SPIRIT.
WOW.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THAT IS THE BEST FAKE SPEECH I THINK I'VE EVER HEARD.
REALLY? NO, I'VE HEARD BETTER.
WAIT. WAIT. HE CAME UP WITH THAT HIMSELF.
TELL THEM, CHANDLER.
I'M OUT OF WORDS.
SHOULD I JUST SAY THE WHOLE THING AGAIN?
I AM NOT HIGH MAINTENANCE.
I AM NOT.
CHANDLER!
YOU'RE A LITTLE HIGH MAINTENANCE.
YOU ARE ON MY LIST.
LOOK, I'M SORRY, BUT YOU'RE NOT EASYGOING
BUT YOU'RE PASSIONATE
AND THAT'S GOOD.
AND WHEN YOU GET UPSET ABOUT THE LITTLE THINGS
I THINK THAT I'M PRETTY GOOD
AT MAKING YOU FEEL BETTER ABOUT THAT.
AND THAT'S GOOD, TOO.
SO THEY CAN SAY THAT YOU'RE HIGH MAINTENANCE
BUT IT'S OKAY BECAUSE I LIKE...
MAINTAINING YOU.
I DIDN'T EVEN TELL HIM TO SAY THAT.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, YOU'RE OFF MY LIST.
I'M OFF THE LIST.
PHOEBE...
IT'S OKAY THAT YOU DON'T WANT ME TO BE YOUR GIRLFRIEND
BECAUSE I HAVE THE BEST BOYFRIEND.
YOU KNOW, SUDDENLY I FIND YOU VERY ATTRACTIVE.
HEY, BUDDY BOY, HOW DID THE AUDITION GO?
OH, NOT GOOD.
I DIDN'T GET THE PART AND, UH, LOST MY JOB HERE
SO...
WOW, THAT IS A BAD AUDITION.
HOW DID YOU LOSE YOUR JOB HERE?
WELL, I HAD THE AUDITION
BUT GUNTHER SAID I HAD TO STAY HERE AND BE IN CHARGE
SO HE COULD GO GET HIS HAIR DYED.
SO, I WENT ANYWAY AND THEN HE FIRED ME.
HE LEFT WORK IN THE MIDDLE OF THE DAY
TO DO A PERSONAL ERRAND AND LEFT YOU IN CHARGE
WHEN YOU'VE BEEN WORKING HERE FOR TWO DAYS.
THAT'S NOT RIGHT.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
WELL, JOEY
YOU CAN'T LET HIM GET AWAY WITH THAT.
YOU KNOW WHAT? I'M NOT GOING TO LET HIM GET AWAY WITH THAT.
I'M GOING TO SAY SOMETHING TO...
NO, I REALLY SHOULDN'T SAY ANYTHING TO HIM.
NO, I SHOULD SAY
SOMETHING TO HIM!
GUNTHER, I WANT YOU TO GIVE JOEY HIS JOB BACK.
THAT IS REALLY NOT FAIR THAT YOU HAVE TO FIRE...
OKAY.
WHAT?
HE CAN HAVE HIS JOB BACK.
THAT'S RIGHT, HE CAN HAVE HIS... JOB BACK.
GLAD WE GOT THAT ALL STRAIGHTENED OUT.
THERE YOU GO, JOEY.
YOU GOT YOUR JOB BACK.
THAT'S GREAT.
THANKS, RACHE.
YEAH, PRETTY NICE, HUH?
NOW WHO'S A PUSHOVER?
RACHE, YOU'RE IN MY SEAT.
I'M SORRY.
HEY, I NEVER GOT TO HEAR WHO YOU GUYS WOULD PICK TO BE
YOUR GIRLFRIEND.
OH, I'D PICK YOU, PHOEBE.
OH, YEAH. DEFINITELY YOU, PHEEBS.
YEAH, WELL, I KIND OF THOUGHT.
HEY.
OH, HEY.
WAIT. I HAVE A QUESTION.
IF ONE OF  YOU HAD TO PICK
ONE OF THE OTHER TWO GUYS TO GO OUT WITH
WHO WOULD YOU PICK?
NO WAY.
I'M NOT ANSWERING THAT JOEY.
I'M NOT ANSWERING THAT.