OKAY, CHANDLER...
OKAY.
AND YOUR HOROSCOPE SAYS
"ON THE FIFTH, A SPECIAL SOMEONE
IS GOING TO GIVE YOU A GIFT."
OH. WELL, THANK YOU IN ADVANCE.
OH, BUT THE 12th BRINGS A LOVERS' SPAT.
YOU'RE GOING TO MAKE A JOKE ABOUT MY SPECIAL PRESENT.
WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT?
OH, WAIT. AND ON THE 19th
"A SECRET CRUSH ANNOUNCES ITSELF."
HEY, GUYS. HEY!
OH, MY GOD, IT'S JOEY TRIBBIANI
OF MAC AND C.H.E.E.S.E.!
OH, THAT'S RIGHT. IT'S YOUR FIRST DAY.
SO, YOU PSYCHED TO FIGHT FAKE CRIME
WITH YOUR ROBOT SIDEKICK?
AM I PSYCHED?
THE LEAD IN MY OWN TV SERIES?
I'VE DREAMED ABOUT THIS FOR YEARS!
WHY HAVE I NOT BEEN PREPARING?
NO, JOEY, YOU'RE GOING TO BE GREAT.
BUT I GOT TO ACT WITH A ROBOT, PHEEBS
AND I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT TECHNOLOGY.
I CAN'T EVEN USE CHANDLER'S COMPUTER, EXCEPT TO FIND PORN.
AND THAT'S ONLY
BECAUSE IT'S RIGHT THERE WHEN YOU TURN IT ON.
I THINK OUR LOVERS' SPAT
WILL START A LITTLE EARLY THIS MONTH.
I'LL BE WAITING.
ARE YOU JUDGING THEM BY THEIR COVERS?
BECAUSE YOU'RE REALLY NOT SUPPOSED TO DO THAT.
NO, I'M JUST DECIDING WHICH ONE TO USE.
I'M GOING TO START WRITING ANOTHER BOOK.
B BECAUSE THE LAST ONE WAS SUCH A BIG SELLER?
WELL, IF YOU MUST KNOW, I HAVE WRITTEN 14 BOOKS
AND, AS I'M THE ONLY ONE WHO HAS READ THEM
I CAN TELL YOU THAT THEY HAVE ALL BEEN VERY WELL RECEIVED.
BUT, YOU KNOW, I LOST ALL OF THEM IN THE FIRE.
SO THIS ONE... THIS ONE I'M GOING TO KEEP
IN AN ASBESTOS LINED BOX FAR AWAY FROM RACHEL.
WHO I FORGIVE.
HEY. HEY.
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING LATER?
OH, RACHEL AND I HAVE APPOINTMENTS
TO GET OUR HAIR CUT.
WE DO?
I WANT TO SEE WHAT HE WANTS FIRST.
OH.
I JUST FOUND OUT
ELIZABETH'S DAD WANTS TO MEET ME.
WAIT A MINUTE; HOLD THE PHONE--
YOU'RE NOT ELIZABETH'S DAD?
THAT'S THE ONLY ONE YOU GET.
AND HE HATES ME, OKAY?
APPARENTLY, HE ASKED ELIZABETH
WHY SHE WOULD WANT TO GO OUT WITH A GUY
WHO COULDN'T GET A GIRL HIS OWN AGE.
HUH. AND WHAT DID SHE SAY TO THAT?
AND THAT'S YOURS.
LOOK, COME ON, GUYS.
I REALLY WANT THIS GUY TO LIKE ME.
IT WOULD REALLY HELP ME OUT
IF YOU GUYS COULD BE HERE
TO KIND OF MAKE ME LOOK GOOD.
WE CAN BE HERE. OH, OF COURSE!
THANKS.
WE KNOW HOW TOUGH
THOSE PARENT TEACHER CONFERENCES CAN BE.
SO, HERE'S YOUR OFFICE SET.
WOW, HUH?
MAC MACHIAVELLI, PRIVATE INVESTIGATOR.
HUH?
OOH... HUH?
LOOK AT ALL THE BOOKS I'VE READ.
LET'S, UH, GET YOU TO WARDROBE FOR A FITTING.
OKAY. HEY, UH, WHEN DO I GET TO MEET THE ROBOT?
WHY DON'T WE DO THAT RIGHT NOW?
HE'S RIGHT HERE.
OKAY.
JOEY TRIBBIANI, THIS IS...
OH, MY... WOW!
HE'S SO LIFELIKE.
THIS IS WAYNE. UNBELIEVABLE.
THE MAN WHO CREATED AND OPERATES C.H.E.E.S.E.
HOW DO YOU DO, THERE, WAYNE?
I'LL LET YOU TWO GUYS GET ACQUAINTED, HUH?
OKAY.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
UH, SO, WHERE'S C.H.E.E.S.E.?
C.H.E.E.S.E. IS RIGHT HERE.
NICE TO MEET YOU, MAC.
THIS IS, LIKE, THE TEMPORARY ROBOT, RIGHT?
NO. WHY?
WELL, I JUST THOUGHT IT WAS GOING TO BE
LIKE, A REALLY COOL ROBOT, YOU KNOW?
LIKE THE TERMINATOR
OR, UH, WHEN I FIRST SAW YOU.
I SPENT TWO YEARS DEVELOPING THIS MACHINE.
IT'S ABSOLUTELY STATE OF THE ART.
I'M SORRY, IT JUST...
IT DOESN'T REALLY LOOK LIKE IT CAN DO ANYTHING.
IT CAN DO THIS.
WHOO!
THIS IS MY FATHER, PAUL STEVENS.
DAD, THIS IS ROSS GELLER.
IT IT IT'S GREAT TO MEET YOU, PAUL.
I USUALLY PREFER LIZ'S BOYFRIENDS
TO ADDRESS ME AS MR. STEVENS.
WELL, OF COURSE, OF COURSE, MR. STEVENS.
SO, ROSS...
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
EXCUSE ME?
WHY CAN'T YOU GET A GIRLFRIEND YOU OWN AGE?
OH, IT'S FUNNY.
UM...
IT'S NOT FUNNY.
I DON'T LIKE YOU GOING OUT WITH MY DAUGHTER, ROSS.
OKAY, UM... I CAN, I CAN SEE THAT.
UM, BUT I THINK IF YOU GIVE ME, UM, ONE CHANCE
I I CAN CHANGE YOUR MIND.
OKAY.
WHAT?
I'LL GIVE YOU ONE CHANCE TO CHANGE MY MIND.
YOU GOT ONE MINUTE.
DADDY...
FINE. TWO MINUTES.
GO.
A MINUTE, 50 SECONDS.
OKAY, UM...
I WANT YOU TO KNOW
I HAVE NEVER DONE ANYTHING LIKE THIS BEFORE.
I MEAN, I'VE BEEN IN,  UM, RELATIONSHIPS IN GENERAL
BUT I'VE NEVER DONE IT WITH A STUDENT.
I MEAN, I... NOT...
NOT "IT"... I MEAN ... I DON'T MEAN...
WE HAVEN'T DONE "IT".
UH, WE... I MEAN, WE'VE DONE STUFF, BUT I...
OKAY, OKAY.
A JOKE, A JOKE.
LIGHTEN THE MOOD.
UM, TWO GUYS GO INTO A BAR.
ONE OF THEM'S IRISH...
I'M IRISH.
AND THE IRISH  GUY WINS THE JOKE.
ROSS! ROSS!
HOW CRAZY THAT WE WOULD RUN INTO YOU.
OH, MY GOD, THANK YOU.
UM, UH, MR. STEVENS, I'D LIKE YOU TO MEET MY FRIENDS.
THIS IS PHOEBE, MONICA AND CHANDLER.
HI. HELLO.
HI, MONICA.
CHANDER.
CHANDLER.
NEVER GOING TO REMEMBER THAT.
WOW. SO YOU'RE ELIZABETH'S FATHER, HUH?
I CAN SEE NOW WHERE SHE GETS HER...
RUGGED HANDSOMENESS.
IS THERE A MRS. STEVENS?
THERE'S A MR. BING.
NO.
UNFORTUNATELY, LIZZY'S MOM PASSED AWAY
SHORTLY AFTER SHE WAS BORN.
I RAISED HER BY MYSELF.
OH! OH!
I GET THAT A LOT.
OKAY.
UM, WHY DON'T WE ALL TAKE A SEAT, YOU KNOW?
AND, UH, AND I'LL  GET US ALL SOME COFFEES.
YEAH, WHY DON'T YOU...?
UH, AND YOU GUYS CAN TALK ABOUT WHATEVER...
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
YOU KNOW, WHATEVER POPS INTO YOUR HEAD.
IT IS SO STRANGE SEEING ROSS HERE THIS TIME OF DAY
BECAUSE USUALLY, WELL, HE'S AT THE CHILDREN'S HOSPITAL.
YEAH.
NOT LOOKING FOR DATES.
SO, UH, MONICA IS ROSS'S SISTER.
YEAH. HE'S A GREAT BROTHER.
I HAD A SISTER.
OH.
SHE PASSED AWAY.
OH! OH!
OH, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO DO THAT EVERY TIME.
BUT, UH, ROSS, ROSS IS A GREAT GUY.
I, UH, WAS ROOMMATES WITH HIM IN COLLEGE.
FUNNY STORY--
YOUR ROOMMATE IN COLLEGE DIED, DIDN'T HE?
A PART OF HIM DID, YES.
OKAY, HERE WE ARE-- PAUL, ELIZABETH.
SO, I HOPE YOU GUYS
WERE FINDING SOMETHING TO TALK ABOUT.
YES. WE WERE JUST...
HI, SORRY I'M LATE, BUT I AM READY.
READY TO TALK YOU UP.
WHEN DOES LIZ'S FATHER GET HERE?
I'M ALREADY HERE.
OH!
ROSS IS SO GREAT.
HEY, PHEEBS. HEY.
HOW'S THE BOOK WRITING GOING?
REALLY WELL.
I'M UP TO PAGE 47.
WOW. WHAT ARE YOU WRITING?
PAGE NUMBERS.
HONEY, YOU GOT THE KIND WITH THE LITTLE GIRL.
YOU SAID WE WERE GOING TO GET THE KIND WITH THE BABY.
NO. YOU SAID THE BABY CREEPS YOU OUT.
NO. THE LITTLE GIRL CREEPS ME OUT.
YOU SAID THE BABY.
WHY WOULD THE BABY CREEP ME OUT?
WHY WOULD THE LITTLE GIRL
CREEP YOU OUT?
YOU GUYS, I'M SORRY, CAN YOU PLEASE TALK A LITTLE SLOWER?
THIS IS GOING IN YOUR BOOK?
YEAH. IT'S ABOUT RELATIONSHIPS.
YOU KNOW, THE TRAPS, THE PITFALLS, WHAT NOT TO DO.
KEEP GOING. THIS STUFF'S GREAT.
WHAT?!
EXCUSE ME...
AND HOW NONE OF IT MATTERS
WHEN THE PEOPLE REALLY LOVE EACH OTHER.
AND HOW PEOPLE WILL BELIEVE ANYTHING YOU TELL THEM
AS LONG AS IT'S A COMPLIMENT.
OH, HI.
HI. HI. HI.
I THINK I LEFT MY KEYS HERE SOMEWHERE.
OH, WELL, LET'S LOOK FOR THEM.
USUALLY UNDER HERE, THEY'RE...
OH, OH, HEY, HEY, ARE THESE THEM?
NO.
ALL RIGHT.
OH!
HERE THEY ARE RIGHT HERE.
OH, GOOD.
THANKS FOR YOUR HELP.
YEAH... WAIT!
OH, SORRY, MR. PAUL, MR. PAUL.
JUST CALL ME PAUL. PAUL.
UM, I JUST WANTED YOU TO KNOW
THAT, YOU KNOW, ROSS REALLY IS A GREAT GUY.
WELL, MAYBE YOU COULD DATE HIM, THEN.
THAT WOULD SAVE ME THE TROUBLE OF KILLING HIM.
ARE YOU OKAY?
YOU JUST DON'T LOOK OLD ENOUGH TO HAVE A 20 YEAR OLD DAUGHTER.
WELL, WE WERE VERY YOUNG WHEN WE HAD HER.
OH, WE?
WELL, YEAH.
IT USUALLY TAKES TWO PEOPLE TO...
OH, NO! YES!
OF COURSE... I KNOW THAT.
I MEANT, ARE YOU STILL WE, OR ARE YOU JUST YOU?
I'M JUST ME, YEAH.
MY WIFE DIED SHORTLY AFTER LIZZY WAS BORN.
OH!
SO YOU RAISED HER ALL ON YOUR OWN?
YES, I DID.
OH! OH...
WHAT ARE YOU WRITING THERE?
I'M DRAWING A PICTURE OF YOU.
MMM. WELL, THAT'S VERY FLATTERING.
YEAH, BUT IT WOULD BE GREAT
IF YOU COULD DRAW ME WITH SOME CLOTHES
AND, YOU KNOW, A HEAD.
HEY.
HOW WAS YOUR FIRST DAY? PRETTY GREAT.
EXCEPT I DID GET A LITTLE ATTITUDE FROM THE ROBOT.
DAMN THOSE ROBOTS.
THEY'RE SUPPOSED TO BE OUR FAITHFUL SERVANTS!
ANYWAY, IT WASN'T THE ROBOT,
IT WAS THE GUY WHO CONTROLS HIM.
YEAH, HE DOESN'T LIKE ME.
HE HAD C.H.E.E.S.E. KNOCK OVER THE SANDWICH TABLE
RIGHT WHEN I WAS REACHING FOR ONE-- OH!
SO WHY DON'T YOU JUST GET HIM FIRED?
I MAY HAVE TO.
I HATE TO DO IT, BUT I'M THE STAR, YOU KNOW?
THERE'S A LIMIT TO HOW MANY SANDWICHES
I CAN EAT OFF THE FLOOR.
EXCUSE ME.
JOEY TRIBBIANI.
JOE! I'M GLAD I FOUND YOU!
I GOT AN AUDITION FOR YOU!
Wow!
The thing is, it's kind of on the Q.T.
THE ACTOR WHO HAS THE PART
DOESN'T KNOW HE MIGHT BE FIRED.
It's the lead in a series--
MAC AND C.H.E.E.S.E.
I'M THE LEAD IN MAC AND C.H.E.E.S.E.!
UH OH!
JOEY?
HI, ROSS.
I WAS JUST GETTING HIM TO LIKE YOU.
JOEY!
JOEY?!
HEY, ROSS.
ROSS, JOEY IS NOT HERE.
OKAY, I'LL JUST WAIT FOR HIM IN HERE.
ROSS, IT'S OKAY.
YOU CAN COME OUT.
YEAH, ROSS, IT'S OKAY.
IT'S ME-- MR. STEVENS.
PAUL, I DIDN'T...
OH, MY GOSH, I DIDN'T EVEN SEE YOU.
SURE, YOU DID.
YOU CAME IN, YOU GOT ALL AWKWARD.
YOU RAN TO THE BEDROOM.
YOU WERE SHOUTING, "JOEY! JOEY!"
BYE, RACHEL. BYE.
I'LL CALL YOU LATER.
OKAY. SEE YOU.
BYE, ROSS.
WHAT...
WHAT... HOW... WHAT THE... HOW... WHAT?
WELL, YOU KNOW, HE LOST HIS KEYS
SO HE WAS LOOKING FOR THEM.
IN YOUR MOUTH?
NO...
DOWNSTAIRS.
AND WE GOT TO TALKING, YOU KNOW, FOR, LIKE, TWO HOURS
AND I REALLY LIKED HIM.
SO I INVITED HIM UP HERE FOR A CUP OF COFFEE.
YOU WERE AT THE COFFEEHOUSE.
ROSS, WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
SO I KISSED THE GUY.
HE'S MY GIRLFRIEND'S FATHER, OKAY?
IT'S... IT'S WEIRD.
YOU DATED MY SISTER.
THAT WAS DIFFERENT.
WHAT? WHY?
THIS IS WEIRD FORME.
ROSS, LOOK, LOOK...
THIS IS GOOD FOR YOU, OKAY?
LET'S FACE IT.
SO FAR, THE GUY'S NOT LOVING YOU
BUT I CAN TURN THAT AROUND.
I GOT THE INSIDE TRACK.
WE CAN ALL GO OUT TO DINNER.
YOU KNOW, AND I CAN TALK YOU UP.
PLUS, THE GUY IS A VERY, VERY SUCCESSFUL LAWYER.
HOW IS THAT IMPORTANT?
OH, IT'S IMPORTANT.
SO, APPARENTLY, THERE'S, LIKE, A MILLION GUYS OUT THERE
THAT CAN PLAY MAC.
AND THERE'S ONLY THIS ONE ROBOT
AND THIS ONE GUY WHO CONTROLS IT.
I DIDN'T KNOW HE COULD GET ME FIRED.
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?
WELL, YOU KNOW, JOEY
YOU'RE A PRETTY CHARMING GUY.
THANKS, BUT I KIND OF HAVE A PROBLEM TO DEAL WITH HERE.
NO, SWEETIE, YOU'VE GOT TO WIN OVER THE GUY
WHO CONTROLS C.H.E.E.S.E.
YOU GOT TO GO BACK THERE
AND KISS SOME SERIOUS ROBOT ASS.
THAT'S NOT A BAD IDEA.
OKAY, BUT IF I GOT TO TURN ON THE CHARM TOMORROW
I'M NOT WASTING ANY MORE OF IT OVER HERE WITH YOU GUYS.
WELL, ACTUALLY, I GOT A LITTLE BIT SAVED FOR YOU, PHEEBS.
SO YOU DO YOU THINK, UH, JOEY'S MORE CHARMING THAN ME?
YEAH. THAT'S WHY I'M SLEEPING WITH HIM ON THE SIDE.
YEAH, YOU WISH.
"YOU WISH."
PHOEBE, STOP WRITING ABOUT US.
I'M NOT WRITING ABOUT YOU.
I'M WRITING ABOUT OTHER PEOPLE.
WHO?
MARSHA AND CHESTER.
OKAY, FINE, FINE.
THEN YOU KNOW WHAT?
I WILL JUST WRITE ABOUT PHYLLIS.
"PHYLLIS IS SITTING IN A CHAIR."
OOH.
I SEE WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
"PHYLLIS SEES WHAT I'M DOING."
OOH HOO.
OOH, I HAVE TASTED MY OWN MEDICINE, AND IT IS BITTER.
MORNING. HEY...
HOW'S MY FAVORITE GENIUS
AND HIS LITTLE ROBOT BUDDY?
DON'T TOUCH HIM.
OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
UH, ALL RIGHT, WAYNE... LOOK
LEVEL WITH ME, OKAY?
I KEEP HEARING ALL THESE RUMORS
THAT I MIGHT GET FIRED.
OKAY, THEY EVEN HAVE ACTORS COMING IN
TO READ FOR MY PART.
COME ON, MAN.
YOU GOT TO GIVE  ME A SECOND CHANCE.
I MEAN, I LOVE THIS LITTLE GUY...
OKAY.
THAT'S WHY YOU DIDN'T WANT ME  TO TOUCH HIM, RIGHT?
HERE YOU GO.
STUPID...
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
GOD...
HEY, HOW YOU DOING?
SO, IT SEEMED THAT MY PROM DATE
HAD STOOD ME UP, SO ROSS SELFLESSLY
OFFERED TO TAKE ME.
WHAT A NICE STORY.
SO ROSS WAS IN COLLEGE
AND DECIDED TO JUMP AT THE CHANCE
TO TAKE A YOUNG GIRL TO HER HIGH SCHOOL PROM.
WOW...
I DEFINITELY DID NOT SEE THAT ONE BACKFIRING.
I'M GOING TO GO TO THE BATHROOM.
YEAH, TAKE YOUR TIME.
YOU KNOW, JUST SO YOU KNOW
I WAS A FRESHMAN AND SHE WAS A SENIOR.
SO IT WASN'T AS BAD AS...
ROSS, LOOK, I KNOW I HAVE BEEN GIVING YOU A LOT OF JABS
AND IT'S PARTLY BECAUSE I'M VERY PROTECTIVE OF LIZZY
AND PARTLY BECAUSE, WELL, THEY JUST KEEP COMING TO ME.
BUT I HAVE TO ADMIT THAT AFTER
ALL THE WONDERFUL THINGS LIZZY HAS TOLD ME
AND THE MANY, MANY, MANY STORIES
THAT RACHEL HAS TOLD ME
THAT, WELL...
YOU'RE NOT... ALL BAD.
"NOT ALL BAD."
AND YOU KNOW, I'M SORRY I WAS SO HARSH BEFORE
BUT YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND
I STILL LOOK AT LIZZY
LIKE SHE'S A 12 YEAR OLD GIRL.
YEAH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN.
I DO THAT, TOO.
I BEG YOUR PARDON.
NO, NO, I'M NOT...
I DON'T MEAN I SEE HER AS A 12 YEAR OLD GIRL.
I MEAN, I HAVE A SON WHO'S SIX
AND I STILL THINK OF HIM AS A BABY.
YOU HAVE A SON?
WELL, MY EX WIFE AND I
SHARE CUSTODY OF BEN
AND, UH, JUST SO YOU KNOW
CAROL AND I ARE ON EXCELLENT TERMS
AS I'M SURE YOU ARE WITH YOUR WIFE.
OH, I'M SORRY.
IT'S UNBELIEVABLE!
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
I JUST DIDN'T REALIZE YOU WERE MARRIED.
OH, WE WERE, BUT THAT WAS JUST A...
I MEAN, THAT WAS JUST A BIG DRUNKEN MISTAKE.
YOU'RE BACK.
YOU TWO WERE MARRIED?
OH, WHOOPS, I'M SORRY.
YOU WERE TALKING ABOUT EMILY.
CHANDLER, WE SAID WE WOULD MEET
AT THE COFFEEHOUSE AT 6:00.
WE SAID 7:00.
WE SAID 6:00.
THE ONLY WAY THAT I SAID 6:00
WOULD BE IF I SAID THE SENTENCE:
"LET'S MEET AT 7:00, NOT AT 6:00."
YEAH, AND IF I HAD SAID 7:00
MAYBE I WOULD HAVE SAID SOMETHING LIKE THIS:
"WOW, MY BOYFRIEND IS SUCH A WISE ASS, 7:00."
HI.
OH, MY GOOD GOD.
I KNOW WHAT TIME YOU SAID.
WHAT?
WELL, ACTUALLY, I KNOW WHAT TIME
CHESTER AND MARSHA SAID.
WHAT TIME?
QUITE AN INTERESTING TURN OF EVENTS.
SUDDENLY, IT'S MY BOOK TO THE RESCUE, HUH?
LET'S SEE.
OOH, VERY INTERESTING.
YEAH, WELL, THIS CERTAINLY CLEARS THINGS UP.
WHAT DOES IT SAY?
I WILL TELL YOU
AS SOON AS YOU THANK ME FOR WRITING MY BOOK.
THANK YOU FOR WRITING YOUR BOOK.
IT'S A GREAT BOOK
AND YOU ARE THE QUEEN OF EVERYTHING.
THANKS. SO ARE YOU.
TOLD YOU I SHOULD NOT WEAR THIS COLOR.
"MONICA... MARSHA AND CHESTER
"ARE PLANNING ON SEEING A MOVIE SUNDAY NIGHT.
"MARSHA THINKS THEY'RE SUPPOSED TO MEET AT 6:00.
CHESTER THINKS IT'S AT 7:00."
SO YOU KNEW WE WERE GOING TO MISS THE MOVIE?
THAT'S RIGHT.
INSTEAD OF TELLING US
YOU DECIDED TO WRITE IT IN YOUR STUPID BOOK?
"MARSHA AND CHESTER ARE MAD AT PHYLLIS."
I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M GOING TO LOSE THIS JOB.
OH, I'M SO SORRY, MAN.
IS THERE ANYTHING I CAN DO?
YEAH. HELP ME GET THIS MINI FRIDGE
PAST THE SECURITY GUARD.
HEY, JOEY, I WANT TO TALK TO YOU.
YEAH, WELL, I DON'T WANT TO TALK TO YOU, WAYNE.
I HATE YOU.
YOU RUINED MY LIFE.
OH. CHANDLER, WAYNE. WAYNE, CHANDLER.
HI, HOW ARE YOU?
JOEY, JOEY, I'LL GET YOU YOUR JOB BACK IF YOU HELP ME OUT.
WHY SHOULD I HELP YOU OUT?
THE REASON HE JUST SAID.
WHAT DO YOU NEED?
I SAW YOU ON STAGE
TALKING TO THAT BEAUTIFUL WOMAN.
YOU KNOW, SARAH.
I WISH I COULD TALK TO HER.
WHAT? ARE YOU IN LOVE WITH HER OR SOMETHING?
YEAH... HER... ALL OF THEM... ANYONE.
YEAH, I BEEN THERE, MY FRIEND.
LISTEN, I GUARANTEE YOU KEEP YOUR JOB
IF YOU CAN TEACH ME HOW TO TALK TO WOMEN LIKE YOU DO.
OH, WELL, WAYNE...
IT'S NOT REALLY SOMETHING YOU CAN TEACH, YOU KNOW?
IT'S PRETTY MUCH SOMETHING YOU'RE BORN WITH...
YOU CAN TEACH IT.
I CAN SHOW YOU HOW TO DO IT.
REA... REA... REALLY?
SURE. YEAH. TAUGHT HIM.
YEAH. YOU SHOULD SEE THE WOMAN I'M WITH--
WAY OUT OF MY LEAGUE.
IN FACT, IF YOU WANT, I CAN GET YOU HER.
I MEAN, IF YOU THINK ABOUT IT
I MEAN, ROSS DID LEARN SOMETHING
FROM EACH MARRIAGE.
HOW TO MAKE THE NEXT ONE EVEN SHORTER?
NOW, WAIT A MINUTE.
THAT'S NOT FAIR.
I MEAN, HE WAS MARRIED TO ME
A HELL OF A LOT LONGER THAN HE WAS MARRIED TO EMILY.
HE JUST DIDN'T TELL ME.
MAYBE I HAVE TO PEE AGAIN.
WELL, THIS IS FUN.
SO, ROSS, DID YOU KILL ANY OF THESE WIVES?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I HAVE HAD ENOUGH OF THIS.
YOU KNOW, I CARE A GREAT DEAL ABOUT YOUR DAUGHTER
AND I HAVE TREATED HER WITH NOTHING BUT RESPECT.
SO, IF YOU GOT A PROBLEM WITH ME, FRANKLY, I...
ARE YOU YELLING AT ME?
GOD, NO.
YOU KNOW WHAT, DADDY?
IF YOU DON'T LIKE ROSS, THAT'S FINE.
IT DOESN'T MATTER TO ME.
I'M GOING TO GO OUT WITH HIM ANYWAY.
REALLY?
WELL, IF IT DOESN'T MATTER TO HER
IT DOESN'T MATTER TO ME.
STILL NOT YELLING.
WELL...
WHAT CAN I SAY?
THIS DOESN'T MAKE ME LIKE YOU ANY BETTER.
THAT'S OKAY.
I'M NOT SO CRAZY ABOUT MYSELF RIGHT NOW EITHER.
THEN WE AGREE?
YEAH, YEAH, I GUESS SO.
NEITHER OF US LIKE ROSS.
I LIKE ROSS.
OH... KIDS.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
I JUST THOUGHT OF ANOTHER STORY
ABOUT HOW NICE ROSS IS.
UH, IT'S OKAY, RACHE.
WE'RE NOT LIKING ROSS RIGHT NOW.
OH, I GOT A LOT OF THOSE, TOO.
WELL, TURNS OUT YOU WERE RIGHT, C.H.E.E.S.E.
THE SHIPMENT NEVER MADE IT THROUGH OMAHA?
YOU GOT IT.
AND THE RABBI'S BEARD--
100% HORSE HAIR.
NICE CATCH, C.H.E.E.S.E.
IT'S YOUR LINE, C.H.E.E.S.E.
WAYNE!