MONICA, WHICH OF ALL OF THIS KITCHEN STUFF
IS MINE?
THIS BOTTLE OPENER.
AND...?
AND IT'S A MAGNET.
GO ON.
LOOK AT THAT.
HOW WEIRD IS THAT?
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE MOVING IN WITH ME
AND YOU HAVE THE ONE THING I DON'T HAVE.
HUH? IT'S LIKE, UH...
IN A WAY YOU, YOU COMPLETE ME.
YOU KNOW?
KITCHEN.
WHAT?
YOU COMPLETE ME KITCHEN, MATEY.
ROSS, I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE THINKING.
WHAT?
THAT SHE'S GOING TO MOVE IN WITH YOU
AND THEN MAYBE SHE'LL FALL IN LOVE WITH YOU
AND THEN, WHEN SHE FINDS OUT YOU'RE ALREADY MARRIED
OH, SHE'LL JUST BE HAPPY, YOU KNOW?
YOU'RE JUST... YOU'RE VERY SAD.
OH... MY... GOD.
I... I SEE WHAT THIS IS.
YOU ARE IN LOVE  WITH RACHEL.
WHAT?!
OF COURSE.
IT ALL ADDS UP.
I MEAN, YOU'RE OBSESSED WITH HER.
IT'S ALWAYS, "ROSS, WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO ABOUT RACHEL?"
"ROSS, WHY ARE YOU MOVING IN WITH RACHEL?"
"WHEN ARE YOU GOING TO CONFESS
YOUR SECRET MARRIAGE TO RACHEL?"
YOU WANT HER.
NO!
UH. OH, SAVED BY THE BELL.
HELLO?
HEY, RACH
AREN'T THESE CANDLE STICKS MINE?
NO, NO, I BOUGHT THOSE.
OH, RIGHT. I FORGOT...
YEAH.
THAT YOU'RE A LIAR.
NO, NO.
THAT'S GREAT.
I'LL BE THERE MONDAY.
AND THANK  YOU AGAIN. OKAY.
UM, THAT WAS THE HEAD OF THE PALEONTOLOGY DEPARTMENT
AT "N"... UH, "Y"... UH, "U."
WOW. UH, WHAT... DID HE... UH, SAY?
WELL, REMEMBER THAT PAPER I HAD PUBLISHED
LAST YEAR ON SEDIMENT FLOW RATE? HUH?
THEY LOVED IT.
WELL, WHO WOULDN'T?
I KNOW.
ANYWAY, THEY ASKED ME TO BE A GUEST LECTURER.
I MEAN, IT'S TEMPORARY, BUT, IF THEY LIKE ME
IT COULD LEAD TO A FULL TIME JOB.
HOW GREAT WOULD THAT LOOK ON THE MAILBOX, HUH?
PROFESSOR GELLER.
YEAH, PROFESSOR AND MRS.
AND MRS.?
UH...
OH, YEAH. YOU KNOW, YOU AND ROSS ARE STILL MARRIED.
WHAT?!
JUST KIDDING.
OH, GOD!
COULD YOU IMAGINE?!
NO!
SAVED YOUR ASS.
HI.
OH, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
WELL... YOU KNOW THAT PSYCHIC I SEE?
YEAH.
WELL, SHE TOLD ME THAT I'M GOING TO DIE THIS WEEK, SO I'M KIND OF
BUMMED ABOUT THAT.
WHAT?
YEAH, AND I KNOW
YOU GUYS DON'T KNOW A LOT ABOUT PSYCHIC READINGS
BUT THAT ONE IS PRETTY MUCH
THE WORST ONE YOU CAN GET.
PHOEBE, THAT'S CRAZY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE SHE WOULD SAY THAT TO YOU.
YEAH, HONEY, YOU DON'T BELIEVE HER, DO YOU?
I DON'T KNOW.
SHE, YOU KNOW, SAID THAT I'D HAVE TRIPLETS.
BUT SHE ALSO SAID ONE OF THEM WOULD BE BLACK.
JUST OUT OF CURIOSITY, DID SHE TELL YOU HOW YOU'RE GOING TO GO?
NO, BECAUSE SHE DIDN'T TELL ME I WAS GOING TO DIE
TILL THE VERY END OF THE SESSION
AND I WAS NOT GOING TO WASTE A WHOLE OTHER HOUR THERE.
I MEAN, I'VE ONLY GOT A WEEK LEFT, YOU KNOW?
I'VE REALLY GOT TO START LIVING NOW.
HEY, EVERYONE.
OH, HI.
HEY, UH, WELL, TODAY'S MY FIRST LECTURE
AND I KIND OF WANTED TO TRY IT OUT ON YOU GUYS.
DO YOU MIND?
NO, THAT'D BE GREAT. OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
SURE.
OKAY.
"THERE ARE THREE PRIMARY THEORIES
"CONCERNING SEDIMENT FLOW RATE.
"EACH OF THESE THEORIES CAN BE FURTHER SUBCATEGORIZED
INTO..."
OH, THIS IS IT.
THIS IS WHAT'S GOING TO KILL ME.
"SUBCATEGORIES:
"THE FIRST OF THESE SUBCATEGORIES...
UH, ROSS.
ARE THERE, UH, ARE THERE NAKED CHICKS ON THAT PIECE OF PAPER?
NO. WHY?
WELL, I JUST NEVER SEEN A GUY STARE SO HARD
AT A PIECE OF PAPER THAT DIDN'T HAVE NAKED CHICKS ON IT.
OH.
OKAY.
"THERE ARE THREE...
"PRIMARY THEORIES...
"CONCERNING SEDIMENT FLOW RATE.
"EACH OF THESE
"THEORIES CAN BE FURTHER SUBCATEGORIZED...
"INTO...
WHY DON'T YOU OPEN WITH A JOKE?
OPEN WITH A JOKE?
IT'S A UNIVERSITY, NOT A COMEDY CLUB.
WELL, WAIT A MINUTE.
HOLD THE PHONE.
YOU'RE NOT TALKING ABOUT CHUCKLES UNIVERSITY?
OKAY.
WE'RE KIDDING. COME ON.
ROSS, HEY, YOU KNOW
WHAT MIGHT MAKE IT LESS BORING?
THANK YOU.
SOME, UM, SOME VISUAL AIDS.
OOH OOH! YOU KNOW WHAT'S A GOOD VISUAL AID?
PLEASE DON'T SAY "NAKED CHICKS."
WHY NOT?
YOU KNOW, I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHY I BOTHER TO EVEN TALK TO YOU GUYS ABOUT IT, YOU KNOW?
I'M JUST GOING TO DO IT ON MY OWN WITH NO NAKED CHICKS.
THAT'S THE WAY I DID IT UNTIL I WAS 19.
ALL RIGHT, 20.
TWENTY THREE.
HI. HEY.
ANY GOOD MAIL?
YES. YOU GOT SOMETHING
FROM THE SCREEN ACTORS GUILD.
OOH. IT'S PROBABLY A RESIDUAL CHECK.
HEY, CAN YOU OPEN IT FOR ME? I GOT A...
"BENEFITS LAPSED."
HMM. THAT'S WEIRD.
I DON'T REMEMBER BEING IN A MOVIE CALLED
"BENEFITS LAPSED."
IT'S NOT A CHECK.
THEY'RE SAYING YOUR HEALTH INSURANCE EXPIRED
BECAUSE... YOU DIDN'T WORK ENOUGH LAST YEAR.
LET ME SEE THAT.
ALL RIGHT.
OH, I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
THIS SUCKS.
WHEN I HAD INSURANCE, I COULD GET HIT BY A BUS OR...
OR CATCH ON FIRE, YOU KNOW?
AND IT WOULDN'T MATTER.
NOW I GOT TO BE CAREFUL?
I'M SORRY, MAN.
THERE'S NEVER A GOOD TIME TO HAVE TO...
STOP CATCHING ON FIRE.
ALL RIGHT, WELL... I GUESS I GOT TO GO GET A JOB.
I'M GOING TO GO SEE MY AGENT.
OKAY, AND MAKE SURE TO LOOK BOTH WAYS
BEFORE YOU CROSS THE STREET.
MAKE SURE TO LOOK BOTH WAYS
HEY.
HEY, PHEEBS, YOU'RE STILL ALIVE.
HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
OH, IT'S SO EXHAUSTING WAITING FOR DEATH.
OH, BY THE WAY, DO YOU THINK...
PHEEBS, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I WAS PREPARING YOU FOR MY DE...
DIDN'T YOU THINK I WAS DEAD?
DID THAT NOT COME OFF?
NO. YEAH, SCARED THE HELL OUT OF ME.
I THOUGHT WE'D LOST YOU FOREVER.
PHEEBS, YOU WANT TO LIE DOWN?
YEAH. THANKS.
AND, LISTEN, CAN YOU DO ME A FAVOR?
CAN YOU JUST, UH, WAKE ME UP IN A COUPLE HOURS--
YOU KNOW, IF YOU CAN?
MONICA...
DID DID YOU TAKE THESE BACK?
NO, NO. I JUST... I LIKED THEM SO MUCH
THAT I WENT OUT AND BOUGHT SOME FOR MYSELF.
OH. YEAH, THEY'RE REALLY GREAT, AREN'T THEY?
I LOVE THEM.
YEAH.
NICE TRY.
HELLO.
HEY. HOW'D THE LECTURE GO?
IT WENT GREAT.
AND I DIDN'T NEED ANY JOKES OR NAKED CHICKS EITHER.
WOW. THAT'S GREAT, ROSS.
I'M SORRY WE WEREN'T MORE SUPPORTIVE BEFORE.
I KNEW ALL I HAD TO DO WAS LET
THE MATERIAL SPEAK FOR ITSELF, HUH?
EVERYONE'S ALL, UH
"ROSS, YOU HAVE TO BE FUNNY AND SEXY."
WELL, I PROVED THEM WRONG.
AND NOW
I'M GOING TO PASS THE NEWS ON TO JOEY AND CHANDLER.
THAT YOU'RE NOT FUNNY OR SEXY?
THAT'S RIGHT.
HEY, ESTEL LE, LISTEN...
WELL, WELL, WELL.
JOEY TRIBBIANI.
SO YOU CAME BACK, HUH?
THEY THINK THEY CAN DO BETTER
BUT THEY ALL COME CRAWLING BACK TO ESTELLE.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I NEVER LEFT YOU.
YOU'VE ALWAYS BEEN MY AGENT.
REALLY?
YEAH.
OH, WELL.
NO HARM, NO FOUL.
LOOK, ESTELLE...
YOU GOT TO GET ME SOME WORK.
I LOST MY HEALTH INSURANCE.
ALL RIGHT.
FIRST THING WE GOT TO DO-- DAMAGE CONTROL.
WHY?
WELL, I THINK, UH...
SOMEONE OUT THERE...
MAY HAVE BEEN BAD MOUTHING YOU ALL OVER TOWN.
THAT BASTARD!
WE'RE A LITTLE EARLY.
THE LECTURE DOESN'T END FOR 15 MINUTES.
YEAH, BUT, YOU KNOW, WE COULD SNEAK IN AND WATCH.
YEAH, COULD.
OH, HEY, LOOK!
THERE'S SOME KAPPA KAPPA DELTAS!
I WAS A KAPPA.
HEY, SISTERS!
WOW, WE REALLY ARE BITCHES.
RIGHT. SO WHEN RIGBY GOT HIS SAMPLES
BACK FROM THE LABORATORY
HE MADE A STARTLING DISCOVERY.
WHAT HE BELIEVED TO BE IGNEOUS WAS, IN FACT, SEDIMENTARY.
IMAGINE HIS CONSTERNATION WHEN...
OH, BLOODY 'ELL.
HI.
HEY.
SO ESTELLE
LINED UP A BUNCH OF AUDITIONS FOR ME TOMORROW
AND I'LL HAVE MY HEALTH INSURANCE BACK IN NO TIME.
THAT'S GREAT, BUT...
SHOULDN'T YOU BE ON THE TOILET RIGHT NOW?
WHAT?
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
NOTHING.
WELL, I GOT THIS BLINDING PAIN IN MY STOMACH
WHEN I WAS LIFTING WEIGHTS BEFORE
AND THEN I, UH, PASSED OUT
AND, UH, I HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO STAND UP SINCE.
BUT, UH, I DON'T THINK IT'S ANYTHING SERIOUS, YOU KNOW?
THIS SOUNDS LIKE A HERNIA.
YOU HAVE TO... YOU GO TO THE DOCTOR.
NO WAY. OKAY, LOOK, IF I'M GOING TO GO TO THE DOCTOR FOR ANYTHING
IT'S GOING TO BE FOR THIS THING STICKING OUT OF MY STOMACH.
THAT'S A HERNIA.
WHY'D I HAVE TO START WORKING OUT AGAIN?
DAMN YOU 15s!
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?
LOOK, I WAS NERVOUS.
YOU GUYS HAD ME ALL WORRIED I WAS GOING TO BE BORING.
I GOT UP THERE AND THEY WERE ALL, LIKE, STARING AT ME.
I OPENED MY MOUTH
AND THIS BRITISH ACCENT JUST CAME OUT.
YEAH, AND NOT A VERY GOOD ONE.
WILL YOU PLEASE...?
DR. GELLER, KURT RATHMAN.
I'M A PROFESSOR  IN THE PALEONTOLOGY DEPARTMENT HERE.
DO YOU HAVE A MOMENT TO TALK ABOUT YOUR LECTURE?
I'M SORRY, I'VE GOT PLANS WITH MY SISTER.
MONICA GELLER R R R....
RIGHT. WILL YOU EXCUSE US FOR ONE MOMENT?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
OH, YOU CAN HAVE AN ACCENT, BUT I CAN'T?
TOP O' THE MORNIN' TO YE, LADDIES!
WILL YOU JUST PLEASE STOP?
YES, YES, BOMBAY IS
VERY, VERY NICE THIS TIME OF YEAR.
HEY, WILL YOU GRAB ME A CRULLER?
SIT DOWN!
WILL YOU GO TO THE HOSPITAL?
DUDE, HERNIA OPERATIONS COST, LIKE... A LOT, PROBABLY, OKAY?
BESIDES, IT'S GETTING DARKER AND MORE PAINFUL.
THAT MEANS IT'S HEALING.
LOOK, I WILL LOAN YOU THE MONEY.
JUST GO TO THE HOSPITAL, AND LET'S JUST GET THAT THING...
PUSHED BACK IN.
THANK YOU, BUT IT WOULD TAKE ME FOREVER
TO PAY YOU THAT MONEY BACK, AND...
I DON'T WANT THAT HANGING OVER MY HEAD, OKAY?
AND BESIDES, AS SOON AS MY INSURANCE KICKS IN
I CAN GET ALL THE FREE OPERATIONS I WANT, OKAY?
I THINK I'LL PROBABLY START WITH THAT LASER EYE SURGERY THING.
HEY... HEY. HEY...
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WELL, JOEY'S GOT A REALLY BAD HERNIA
BUT IT'S NOTHING THAT A LITTLE LASER EYE SURGERY WON'T FIX.
LOOK, I'M TELLING YOU--
IF I PUT MY HAND ON MY STOMACH RIGHT HERE
IT DOESN'T HURT THAT BAD.
HEY! MAYBE YOU'LL DIE.
CHANDLER, I'M SCARED.
NO, WE CAN  GO TOGETHER!
JUST DON'T WAIT TOO LONG, THOUGH, OKAY?
BECAUSE I'M OUT OF HERE SOMETIME BEFORE FRIDAY.
YEAH, BUT I DON'T WANT TO DIE.
NO, NO, IT'LL BE FUN.
WE CAN COME BACK AND WE CAN HAUNT THESE GUYS.
OOH, WAIT.
COULD I COME BACK AND HAUNT MONICA AND RACHEL
WHEN THEY'RE IN THE SHOWER?
THAT'S MY GIRLFRIEND.
HEY, I'M DEAD!
GIVE ME THEM!
NO! THEY ARE MINE!
YOU STOLE THEM FROM ME! YOU STOLE THEM FROM ME!
GIVE ME THEM! GIVE ME THEM!
YOU JUST WANT TO EACH TAKE ONE?
YEAH, THAT SEEMS FAIR-- WE NEVER USE THEM.
LOOK, I REALLY NEED SOME HELP, OKAY?
WHY, WHY DID I HAVE TO SPEAK IN A BRITISH ACCENT?
WHAT DO I DO?
WELL, WHY DON'T YOU
CALL MUMMY AND DADDY?
I'M SERIOUS! SOMEONE'S GOING TO FIND OUT I'M A FAKE
AND THEN THEY'RE NEVER GOING TO OFFER ME A JOB!
WHY DON'T  YOU PHASE IT OUT?
YEAH, PHASE THE ACCENT OUT--
PEOPLE WILL THINK THAT, YOU'RE, YOU KNOW
JUST ADJUSTING TO LIFE IN AMERICA.
YEAH, I MEAN, COME ON, ROSS--
NO ONE'LL EVEN NOTICE.
I MEAN, THEY'RE PROBABLY NOT EVEN LISTENING TO YOU.
THEY'RE NOT LISTENING TO ME?
OF COURSE THEY'RE LISTENING TO YOU.
EVERYBODY LISTENS TO YOU.
MONICA, UH, YOU REALLY THINK I SHOULD TRY
THIS "PHASING OUT" THING?
I THINK YOU LOOK FINE.
WHENEVER YOU'RE READY.
OKAY.
HEY, TIMMY...
I'VE GOT A...
SURPRISE... FOR YOU.
HOLD IT, I'M SORRY.
THE SURPRISE IS A NEW SWING SET.
IF YOU COULD PLAY IT A LITTLE LESS INTENSE?
YEAH, SURE. NO PROBLEM.
UH, JUST HOLD ON ONE SECOND.
HEY, TIMMY...
I'VE GOT A SURPRISE FOR YOU.
OH, MY GOD!
...SO THAT'S WHY I FEED MY DOG PURINA ONE.
PICK UP A BAG TODAY.
THAT'S WHERE YOU PICK UP THE BAG.
EXACTLY.
NO, THE LINE IS "PICK UP A BAG," SO YOU NEED TO PICK UP THE BAG.
OR...
I COULD JUST POINT TO IT, HUH?
"BLAH BLAH BLAH, PURINA ONE.
POINT TO A BAG TODAY."
I DIDN'T GET IT, DID I?
NO.
YEAH, OKAY.
HI. I'M, UH, JOEY TRIBBIANI.
I'M HERE TO AUDITION FOR "MAN."
YOU MEAN "DYING MAN"?
YES!
OKAY, COME ON-- DO IT ONE MORE TIME.
REALLY? REALLY?
YES! OKAY.
HELLO, ROSS?
THIS IS DR. McNEELY FROM THE FAKE ACCENT UNIVERSITY.
WE'D LIKE YOU TO COME ONBOARD WITH US FULL TIME.
HEY!
LISTEN TO THIS--
MY READING WAS WRONG; I'M NOT GOING TO DIE.
REALLY? HOW DO YOU KNOW?
BECAUSE MY PSYCHIC IS DEAD.
SHE MUST HAVE READ THE CARDS WRONG.
OH... WELL, I'M SORRY.
EH, BETTER HER THAN ME.
HEY, LET'S BAKE COOKIES!
LISTEN, I'M REALLY GLAD YOU GOT THE PART.
BUT ARE YOU SURE YOU CAN DO THIS?
YEAH! AND, HEY, MAN, THANKS FOR COMING WITH ME.
AND THANKS AGAIN FOR HELPING ME TAKE A SHOWER.
NOW, IS THAT "NEVER TALKING ABOUT IT AGAIN"?
HIYA.
HEY, JOEY, WE'RE READY FOR YOU.
UH, JOEY, THIS IS ALEX.
HE'S GOING TO BE PLAYING YOUR SON.
HI, ALEX.
AND, UH, AS YOU CAN SEE, MY HANDS-- NOT IN MY PANTS.
OKAY...
ALL RIGHT, UH, ALEX, NOW, WHEN JOEY SAYS HIS LINE
"TAKE GOOD CARE OF YOUR MAMA, SON"--
THAT'S YOUR CUE TO CRY.
GOT IT?
ALL RIGHT, LET'S DO THIS.
SCENE FIVE, TAKE ONE.
AND... ACTION!
TAKE GOOD CARE OF YOUR MAMA, SON.
COME ON, SON...
YOUR MAMA'S GOOD PEOPLE.
CUT!
ALEX, REMEMBER...
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO CRY.
CAN YOU CRY FOR  US THIS TIME?
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, FROM THE TOP.
SCENE FIVE, TAKE TWO.
TAKE 36 IS UP.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S TRY THIS AGAIN.
ARE YOU READY, JOE?
UH, ONE THING--
IS IT ALL RIGHT WITH YOU IF I... IF I SCREAM
RIGHT UP UNTIL YOU SAY "ACTION"?
UH, SURE.
ACTION!
TAKE GOOD CARE OF YOUR MAMA, SON.
CUT!
I'M SORRY.
HEY, HEY, JOE, WHY DON'T YOU LIFT UP YOUR SHIRT?
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS, KIDDO.
WE HAVE HIM CRYING, JOHN!
ROLL THE DAMN CAMERAS!
HELLO?
HELLO, IS ROSS THERE?
UH, NO, HE'S NOT.
CAN I TAKE A MESSAGE?
Yes. This is Russell, Ross's divorce lawyer.
JUST TELL HIM THAT SINCE I HAVEN'T HEARD FROM HIM
I ASSUME HE'S DECIDED TO GIVE THE MARRIAGE A TRY.
ROSS GOT MARRIED AGAIN?
NO!
ALL RIGHT, KEEP GOING.
WE ARE PHASING THE ACCENT OUT-- PHASING IT OUT.
SO WITHOUT RETESTING THE RESULTS IN THE LABORATORY
THE TEAM WOULD NEVER HAVE I DENTIFIED...
THE INITIAL ERRORS IN THEIR...
CARBON DATING ANAL YSIS.
WERE THERE ANY QUESTIONS AT THIS POINT?
YES?
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO YOUR ACCENT?
COME AGAIN.
WHAT'S WHAT'S THIS NONSENSE?
ALL RIGHT, I'M I'M NOT ENGLISH.
I'M FROM LONG ISLAND.
I WAS REALLY NERVOUS, AND THE ACCENT JUST, UH...
JUST CAME OUT.
I'M SORRY.
SO, IF WE COULD JUST GET BACK TO THE LECTURE.
UM... WERE THERE ANY QUESTIONS?
ABOUT PALEONTOLOGY?
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, I WAS JUST TRYING
TO MAKE A GOOD FIRST IMPRESSION.
OBVIOUSLY, I SCREWED UP.
BUT WHAT YOU GUYS THINK OF ME IS REALLY IMPORTANT
BECAUSE I'M I'M HOPING TO GET A PERMANENT JOB HERE.
SO IF YOU JUST GIVE ME ANOTHER CHANCE
TO MAKE A GOOD IMPRESSION...
ROSS! ARE YOU CRAZY?!
I AM STILL YOUR WIFE?!
WHAT, WERE YOU JUST NEVER GOING TO TELL ME?!
WHAT THE HELL IS WRONG WITH YOU?!!
OH! I COULD JUST KILL YOU!
WELL, 'ELLO, RACHEL!
YOU'VE REALLY DONE THIS BEFORE?
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
YOU JUST TAKE A BIG, BIG SWING, OKAY?
NOW, DON'T HOLD BACK.
OKAY.
HEY!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WE'RE JUST CELEBRATING
THAT JOEY GOT HIS HEALTH INSURANCE BACK.
OH, ALL RIGHT.
SEE? NOW LET'S TRY ONE WITHOUT THE HELMET.