OKAY, THIS IS IT.
YOU SURE YOU WANT TO DO THIS?
HELLO, MRS. ROSS!
WHY, HELLO, MR. RACHEL!
WHOA!
OH, MY GOD.
COME ON, PHEEBS! HURRY! HURRY! HURRY UP!
YEAH, YEAH, OKAY.
HURRY! HURRY!
OH, MY GOD!
IS EVERYBODY GETTING MARRIED?!
NO RUNNING IN THE CHAPEL.
HEY, DON'T YOU GIVE ME ANY OF YOUR...
HEY!
HEY.
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING HERE?
ROSS AND RACHEL LEFT US A MESSAGE
SAYING THEY WERE GETTING MARRIED.
ISN'T THAT WHY YOU GUYS ARE HERE?
YES. WELL, YES...
WHY ELSE WOULD WE BE HERE?
WELL, WHAT HAPPENED?
DID WE MISS IT?
WE ACTUALLY MISSED IT.
WELL, MAYBE YOU WOULDN'T HAVE
IF YOU COULD RUN IN THE CHAPEL!
I CAN'T BELIEVE ROSS AND RACHEL GOT MARRIED.
I KNOW. I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW THEY WERE DATING AGAIN.
I DON'T THINK THEY'RE AS MUCH DATING
AS THEY ARE TWO BOTTLES OF VODKA
WALKING AROUND IN HUMAN FORM.
THIS IS INSANE.
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL, YOU KNOW?
IT'S NOT LIKE IT'S A REAL MARRIAGE.
WHAT?
IF YOU GET MARRIED IN VEGAS, YOU'RE ONLY MARRIED IN VEGAS.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
IF YOU GET MARRIED IN VEGAS, YOU'RE MARRIED EVERYWHERE.
REALLY?
YEAH.
OH, MY GOD.
EH, WELL.
??  ? ?
??  ??
MMM...
OH.
WHY ARE WE IN BED TOGETHER?
I DON'T KNOW.
DID WE...?
DO YOU... DO YOU HAVE
ANY CLOTHES ON?
YES.
REALLY?
NO.
BUT WE DIDN'T HAVE...
SEX, DID WE?
I DON'T...
I DON'T REMEMBER MUCH ABOUT LAST NIGHT.
IT WAS SUCH A BLUR.
OH!
I REMEMBER LAUGHING.
I LAUGHED A LOT.
THEN WE DIDN'T HAVE SEX.
SO WHAT... WHAT DID WE DO LAST NIGHT?
I DON'T KNOW
BUT I THINK IT WAS A LOT OF FUN.
YEAH.
LUCKILY, NOT TOO MUCH FUN, RIGHT?
OH, I DON'T THINK SO.
OH, THANK GOD.
OH, I MEAN, WE WERE REALLY DRUNK.
I'M GLAD WE DIDN'T DO ANYTHING STUPID.
TELL ME ABOUT IT.
MORNING, PHEEBS.
HEY.
WELL, MY MOVIE HAS BEEN OFFICIALLY CANCELED.
JOEY, I'M SO SORRY.
YOU WANT SOME OF MY BREAKFAST?
NAH. I'M TOO DEPRESSED TO EAT.
I'LL PROBABLY BE EATING IN, LIKE, FIVE MINUTES.
SO I GUESS I'LL JUST FLY HOME WITH YOU GUYS.
WHAT TIME'S YOUR FLIGHT?
WHAT ABOUT MY CAB?
I DON'T NEED THAT ANYMORE.
NO, JOEY, YOU BORROWED MY CAB.
YOU HAVE TO DRIVE IT BACK.
I DON'T WANT TO DRIVE ALL THE WAY BACK BY MYSELF.
I GET SO LONELY.
OH, OH, HOW ABOUT IF YOU COME WITH ME?
I DON'T KNOW. IT'S SUCH A LONG TRIP.
IT'LL BE GREAT.
WE CAN TALK AND PLAY GAMES, HUH?
THIS COULD BE OUR CHANCE TO, LIKE, RENEW OUR FRIENDSHIP.
ARE YOU ASKING ME TO HAVE A FRIEND AISSANCE?
SURE?
ALL RIGHT.
ALTHOUGH I DON'T THINK WE REALLY NEED ONE, BABY.
I NEVER STOPPED LOVING YOU.
HEY.
SO HAS ANYBODY TALKED TO DR. AND MRS. GELLER YET?
MM HMM. YEAH.
THEY LEFT ME A MESSAGE.
THEY SHOULD BE HERE ANY MINUTE.
WHERE IS THE WAITRESS?
I'M STARVING.
IT'S A BUFFET, MAN.
OH, HERE'S WHERE I WIN ALL MY MONEY BACK.
LISTEN, I GOT TO TALK TO YOU.
SURE. WHAT'S UP?
MONICA AND I ALMOST GOT MARRIED LAST NIGHT.
OH, MY GOD!
THAT'S HUGE!
HEY!
WAIT A MINUTE.
WHY WASN'T I INVITED?
AND WHO WAS GOING TO BE
YOUR BEST MAN?
DON'T SAY ROSS.
DO NOT SAY ROSS.
I JUST DON'T THINK THAT MONICA AND I
ARE READY TO GET MARRIED YET, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, I LOVE HER AND EVERYTHING, BUT...
SEEING ROSS AND RACHEL COME OUT OF THAT CHAPEL
WAS LIKE A... LIKE A WAKE UP CALL
THAT MONICA AND I ARE MOVING SO FAST, YOU KNOW.
HOW DO I TELL HER WITHOUT CRUSHING HER?
OH.
TELL HER SHE'S NOT MARRIAGE MATERIAL.
WHAT?
GIRLS SAY IT TO ME ALL THE TIME.
AND BELIEVE ME
IF SHE'S ANYTHING LIKE ME
SHE'S JUST GOING TO BE RELIEVED.
HOW DO I TELL CHANDLER THAT IT'S TOO SOON?
IT'S GOING TO BREAK HIS HEART.
HE'S GOING TO THINK I DON'T LOVE HIM ANYMORE.
WELL, YOU DON'T.
YES, I DO.
GOOD, GOOD. I WAS JUST TESTING YOU.
HI.
OH, HI, HI.
YOU KNOW, WE WERE JUST TALKING ABOUT BACON.
NO, WE WERE TALKING ABOUT TENNIS.
TENNIS IS MORE BELIEVABLE.
HEY.
HEY. HEY.
HI.
THANK YOU.
COFFEE.
MMM!
WHAT?
ARE WE GOING TO TALK ABOUT
WHAT YOU GUYS DID LAST NIGHT, OR...?
WHAT... WHAT DO YOU MEAN LAST NIGHT?
NOTHING NOTHING...
NOTHING HAPPENED LAST NIGHT.
YEAH.
UH HUH.
ROSS INVITED US ALL TO WATCH.
WHAT IS THE MATTER WITH YOU?
RACH, WE WEREN'T GOING TO MISS
OUR FRIENDS GETTING MARRIED.
WHO GOT MARRIED?!
YOU DID?
WHAT? WHAT?
WE... WE... HELLO?
NO, WE DIDN'T. WE DIDN'T GET MARRIED.
THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
I REMEMBER BEING IN A CHAPEL.
THEY WOULD NOT LET US GET MARRIED
WHEN WE WERE THAT DRUNK.
THEY LET YOU GET MARRIED WHEN YOU'RE DRUNK.
MOST PEOPLE GETTING MARRIED IN VEGAS ARE DRUNK.
I'M DRUNK RIGHT NOW.
I CAN'T HAVE A MIMOSA WITH BREAKFAST?
I'M ON VACATION.
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS GOING TO DO?
I GUESS WE JUST FIND A DIVORCE LAWYER?
WELL, I THINK...
I THINK ROSS ALREADY HAS ONE.
YEAH, YEAH. THAT GUY'S FINALLY GOING
TO BE ABLE TO PUT IN THAT POOL.
OKAY...
THIS ONE'S FREE, RIGHT?
BECAUSE YOU PAID FOR THE FIRST TWO
SO YOU GET THE THIRD ONE FOR FREE.
LAUGH IT UP
BUT THE JOKE'S ON YOU.
BECAUSE WE DON'T NEED TO GET DIVORCED, OKAY?
WE'RE JUST GOING TO GET AN ANNULMENT.
AN ANNULMENT?
ROSS, I DON'T THINK SURGERY'S THE ANSWER HERE.
OH, THAT'S YOUR THING.
WHAT?
YOUR THING, YOUR THING, YOU KNOW.
YOU'RE THE GUY WHO GETS DIVORCED.
OH, YEAH.
IT MIGHT BE TRUE.
IT'S NOT MY "THING."
I DO NOT LOVE GETTING DIVORCED.
YES, YOU DO.
THIS IS YOUR THIRD DIVORCE.
GOD, YOU LOVE DIVORCE SO MUCH
YOU'RE PROBABLY GOING TO MARRY IT
AND THEN...
THEN IT WON'T WORK OUT
SO YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO DIVORCE IT, DIVORCING GUY.
I'M SO DRUNK.
YOU WANT TO PLAY SOME PAI GOW?
MAYBE.
BUT I KIND OF THINK
WE SHOULD TALK ABOUT LAST NIGHT.
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA
BECAUSE I WANT TO TALK ABOUT LAST NIGHT, TOO
AND I DON'T KNOW WHAT PAI GOW IS.
I SEE.
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK WE SHOULD DO?
I DON'T KNOW.
I I I KNOW I LOVE YOU.
I KNOW I LOVE YOU.
SO WHERE ARE WE ON THE WHOLE
GOING BACK TO THE PLACE- WHERE THEY HAVE ALL- THE MARRIAGES THING?
I LOVE YOU.
THAT'S A GOOD QUESTION.
WELL, LAST NIGHT WE LET THE DICE DECIDE.
MAYBE WE SHOULD LEAVE IT UP TO FATE AGAIN.
I LOVE YOU.
YES, WE DON'T GET MARRIED UNLESS THERE'S A SIGN, OKAY?
SO, SAY... SAY YOU ROLL ANOTHER EIGHT
THEN THERE IS A DEFINITE SIGN
THAT WE SHOULD GET MARRIED.
ALL RIGHT, EIGHT, WE GET MARRIED
BUT TWO, THREE, FOUR, FIVE, SIX, SEVEN, NINE, 10, 11, 12
WE DON'T GET MARRIED.
SOUNDS GREAT. OKAY.
OKAY, WE GOT A SHOOTER.
MONEY PLAYS.
YOU READY?
READY.
COME ON, EIGHT.
YES, YES, EIGHT.
EIGHT.
EASY EIGHT.
WOW, I CAN'T BELIEVE I ACTUALLY ROLLED AN EIGHT.
THAT WAS SO UNLIKELY.
WELL, LET'S GET MARRIED...
I GUESS.
THAT WASN'T A HARD EIGHT.
LAST NIGHT, I ROLLED A HARD EIGHT.
THAT'S RIGHT, IT WAS THE WRONG KIND OF EIGHT.
NO WEDDING! DAMN IT!
I WANTED IT SO BAD.
WANT TO GO PACK?
YEAH.
WE'RE DOING THE RIGHT THING, RIGHT?
OF COURSE WE ARE.
WE LEFT IT UP TO FATE.
IF WE WERE SUPPOSED TO GET MARRIED
THERE WOULD BE A CLEAR CUT SIGN.
OKAY, YOU HAVE 19 QUESTIONS LEFT.
USE THEM WISELY.
COME ON, JOEY, YOU CAN'T WIN
IF YOU DON'T ASK ANY...
QUESTIONS!
I'M UP! WHAT?!
WHAT?
WELL, YOU PROMISED ME A FUN ROAD TRIP
AND WE'VE BEEN ON THE ROAD FOR SIX HOURS
AND YOU'VE BEEN ASLEEP FOR FIVE AND A HALF.
WE ARE SWITCHING AT THE NEXT REST STOP
AND YOU ARE GOING TO DRIVE THE WHOLE WAY BACK.
THAT WILL BE YOUR PUNISHMENT
YOU GREEDY SLEEPER.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
AND, UNTIL THEN, YOU ARE GOING TO SING TO ME.
BECAUSE THE RADIO'S BROKEN
AND YOU ARE SELFISH
BUT YOU HAVE A NICE VOICE.
REALLY? I DON'T...
SING!
?? I WANNA ROCK 'N' ROLL ALL NIGHT... ??
MAN, THIS IS A LONG DRIVE.
ARE MY EYES OPEN?
NO!
MORNING.
HEY.
HEY, HUBBY.
ACTUALLY, UM, I WANTED TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT
THAT WHOLE ANNULMENT THING.
UH HUH?
YEAH, I'M NOT GOING TO DO THAT.
OKAY!
SO... WE'LL JUST STAY MARRIED.
YES, EXACTLY.
AND I WILL MAKE EVERYONE CALL ME MRS. GELLER.
WOW, THIS IS SO AMAZING.
I, UH...
I REALLY THOUGHT I'D HAVE TO TALK YOU INTO THIS MORE.
OKAY, SEE, NOW I'M SCARED
BECAUSE I DON'T ACTUALLY THINK YOU'RE KIDDING.
I'M I'M NOT KIDDING.
LOOK, I I...
I CAN'T HAVE THREE FAILED MARRIAGES.
I CAN'T, OKAY?
I I I AM NOT GOING TO BE THAT GUY, OKAY?
NO, NO. THAT IS NOT GOING TO BE MY THING.
WHAT? WELL, WH WHAT...
SO... SO, WHAT, WE JUST STAY MARRIED FOREVER?
I DON'T KNOW.
WHA...?
I HAVEN'T WORKED IT ALL OUT YET, BUT...
LOOK, OKAY, I KNOW IT'S A BIT CRAZY...
YEAH. HON...
HOW HOW IS THIS GOING TO AFFECT YOU, REALLY?
I MEAN, YOU FILL SOME FORM OUT ONCE IN A WHILE.
INSTEAD OF CHECKING THE BOX THAT SAYS "MISS"
YOU CHECK THE BOX THAT SAYS "MRS."
IT'S RIGHT NEXT TO IT.
OH, OKAY, I'M SORRY, YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU KNOW WHAT? WE ABSOLUTELY CAN STAY MARRIED
BECAUSE I WAS UNDER THE IMPRESSION
NO. THEY'RE RIGHT...
ROSS! OH!
OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
JUST...
PLEASE, TAKE A MOMENT HERE
AND THINK ABOUT WHAT YOU'RE ASKING OF ME, OKAY?
I AM ASKING YOU TO DO ME A FAVOR.
YOU ARE ASKING ME TO BE YOUR WIFE.
AND AS MY WIFE, I THINK YOU SHOULD GRANT ME THIS FAVOR.
WE DID MAKE VOWS.
THAT KID KICKED ME REALLY HARD ON THE PLANE.
WELL, YOU DID PULL HIS HAIR.
HE TOOK MY SNACK.
I'M NOT GETTING INTO THIS AGAIN! OKAY!
OH, GOD, YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT HURTS REALLY BAD.
WELL, I TOLD YOU NOT TO WALK...
HERE. HERE.
OKAY.
THIS DOESN'T MEAN ANYTHING, DOES IT?
NO.
OKAY.
HOW COULD YOU PICK UP A HITCHHIKER?
HE COULD BE A RAP...
HE COULD BE A RAPIST OR A KILLER OR SOMETHING.
DON'T YOU THINK I ASKED HIM THAT BEFORE HE GOT IN?
YOU KNOW WHAT? I'M NOT TALKING TO YOU.
YOU GO BACK TO SLEEP. AND YOU--
ARE YOU A RAPIST?
NO.
DO YOU LIKE CAR GAMES?
YEAH. YOU KNOW, THE, UH, LICENSE PLATE GAME?
I LOVE THE LICENSE PLATE GAME.
OH, I'LL PLAY. I'LL PLAY.
NO, NO. YOU NEED YOUR SLEEP. NIGHT, NIGHT.
SHH!
HEY.
HEY. LISTEN.
I KNOW YOU WANTED TO TALK TO ME
BUT I HAVE AN IDEA THAT MAY MAKE YOU WANT TO STAY MARRIED.
WE REGISTER, AND YOU GET TO KEEP ALL THE PRESENTS.
NO.
ROSS, COME ON.
NO. LISTEN. LOOK, I'VE THOUGHT A LOT
ABOUT HOW TO TELL YOU THIS AND, UM...
ACTUALLY, I CAME UP WITH AN ANALOGY
ABOUT A LITTLE GOLDFISH IN A POND
THAT FREEZES OVER IN THE WINTER.
THEN I REALIZED THAT WAS MORE OF A STORY
ABOUT WHAT TO DO WHEN PEOPLE PICK ON YOU
SO I'M ACTUALLY GOING TO SAVE THAT ONE
FOR MY CHILDREN'S BOOK.
RACH, WHAT'S UP?
OH, SORRY. OKAY.
THE BOTTOM LINE, ROSS,  IS WE CANNOT STAY MARRIED.
I DON'T KNOW IF THAT'S TRUE.
BUT IT IT IT IS.
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT THIS IS?
THIS IS A DIFFERENCE OF OPINION.
AND WHEN THAT HAPPENS IN A MARRIAGE...
OH, ROSS, COME ON! THIS IS NOT A...
THIS IS NOT A MARRIAGE.
THIS IS THE WORLD'S WORST HANGOVER!
ROSS, LISTEN.
IF YOU DO NOT GET THIS ANNULMENT, I WILL.
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL DO IT.
THANK YOU.
HEY HEY, UM...
UH, IS THERE ANY SUCH THING
AS AN ANNULMENT SHOWER?
OH, WAIT, WAIT.
THERE'S THE TRAIN STATION.
THIS IS WHERE I GET OFF.
I HAVE YOUR ADDRESS AND PHONE NUMBER.
AND I HAVE YOUR NAME
AND THE FACT THAT YOU'RE A DRIFTER, SO...
BALL'S PRETTY MUCH IN YOUR COURT.
ALL RIGHT.
SEE YOU, PHEEBS.
COME ON, PHEEBS.
I CAN'T TAKE THIS ANYMORE.
PLEASE TALK TO ME.
LET LET ME MAKE IT UP TO YOU, HUH?
?
?? GROUND CONTROL TO MAJOR TOM ?
?? COMMENCING COUNTDOWN, ENGINES ON ??
?? TAKE YOUR PROTEIN PILLS AND PUT YOUR HELMET ON ??
STOP IT! ?? THIS IS GROUND... ??
STOP IT! NO!
THAT'S NOT FAIR.
YOU KNOW I CAN'T RESIST THAT BEAUTIFUL VOICE.
PHEEBS, LOOK, I'M SO SORRY.
I KNOW I PROMISED YOU A FUN ROAD TRIP WITH YOUR FRIEND
AND I DIDN'T DELIVER, OKAY, BUT BUT BUT NOW I KNOW
THAT YOU THINK BEING AWAKE
IS AN IMPORTANT PART OF FRIENDSHIP, SO...
SO...
SO I WILL STRIVE TO TO STAY AWAKE
FOR AS LONG AS I KNOW YOU.
YOU CAN STILL, LIKE, SLEEP AT NIGHT AND STUFF.
WELL, THANK YOU.
SO, CAN WE PLAY 20 QUESTIONS NOW?
I GOT A REALLY GOOD ONE.
I'VE BEEN THINKING ABOUT IT SINCE KANSAS.
OKAY.
IS IT... A KIND OF HOT SANDWICH?
YES.
IS IT A MEATBALL SUB?
THAT IS INCREDIBLE.
YOU ARE THE MASTER.
BUG!
ENOUGH ALREADY.
WELL, YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO CATCH THEM.
THAT'S FUNNY.
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU'RE GOING TO BE THE NEXT ONE...
DON'T SAY IT.
DON'T EVEN THINK IT.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, CHANDLER, ENJOY YOUR HANDFUL.
ALL RIGHT, SHOULD WE JUST...
SHOULD WE JUST GET MARRIED, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, SHOULD WE JUST DO IT?
ALL THE SIGNS ARE TELLING US TO DO IT.
I'M SICK OF THE SIGNS. IT'S TOO FAST.
ME, TOO. I'M HAPPY THE WAY THINGS ARE.
I DON'T WANT THINGS TO CHANGE; DO YOU?
NO.
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
THEN NOTHING CHANGES!
EVERYTHING IS GREAT!
EVERYTHING STAYS THE SAME!
NOW, YOU GO AND UNPACK BECAUSE IT'S BEEN THREE DAYS
AND IT'S DRIVING ME INSANE.
AH, GEEZ, RELAX.
IT'S NOT LIKE WE'RE MA...
AH! AH!
YOU KNOW, I WAS THINKING, WHAT IF I, UH, UNPACK HERE?
THEN ALL YOUR STUFF WOULD BE HERE.
WELL...
WHAT IF ALL MY STUFF WAS HERE?
THEN YOU'D BE GOING BACK AND FORTH ALL THE TIME.
I MEAN...
DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
OKAY.
WHAT IF WE LIVE TOGETHER
AND YOU UNDERSTAND WHAT I'M SAYING?
LIVE TOGETHER?
THERE HAVE BEEN NO SIGNS FOR THAT.
ME ASKING IS KIND OF A SIGN.
YES!
YES! OKAY!
YES. OKAY. OKAY, WAIT.
WAIT. WAIT. WAIT.
OKAY.
OKAY. HERE'S YOUR KEY.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, YOU HAVE TO GO OUT AND CHRISTEN IT.
NOW, GO OUT AND THEN COME BACK IN.
THE DOOR HASN'T BEEN LOCKED IN FIVE YEARS, BUT OKAY.
READY?
READY!
OKAY, A LITTLE PROBLEM.
THE KEY BROKE IN THE LOCK, AND I CAN'T GET IN.
OH, MY GOD. I CAN'T GET OUT.
THIS ISN'T A SIGN.
NO, NO, NO. IT'S NOT A SIGN.
IT'S A VERY OLD KEY.
IT'S JUST AN OLD KEY!
OH, MY GOD, IT'S OLD.
I LOVE YOU.
ARE YOU HUGGING THE DOOR RIGHT NOW?
NO.
YEAH, YEAH. ME NEITHER.
HEY.
HEY. SO, DID EVERYTHING GO ALL RIGHT
WITH THE, UH, ANNULMENT?
OH, YEAH.
NO PROBLEMS. IT'S ALL TAKEN CARE OF.
ROSS, THANK YOU. AAH...
HEY, DO YOU GUYS WANT TO GO SEE A MOVIE?
OH, YEAH. WHY NOT?
YEAH. PHEEBS?
NO, THANKS.
I'VE ALREADY SEEN ONE.
OKAY. UM...
I'M GOING TO GET MY SWEATER.
OKAY.
YOU WANT YOU WANT TO HEAR SOMETHING WEIRD?
ALWAYS.
I DIDN'T GET THE ANNULMENT.
WHAT?
WE'RE STILL MARRIED.
DON'T TELL RACHEL.
SEE YOU LATER.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
KEY'S STUCK IN THE LOCK.
I CAN FIX IT. HOLD ON.
WATCH OUT. WATCH OUT.
STILL DOESN'T WORK.
I'M NOT FINISHED.
OH.
NICE JOB, JOE.
YOU'RE QUITE THE CRAFTSMAN.