OKAY...
NOW, LISTEN, I'M GOING TO BE MOVING OUT
SO YOU ARE GOING TO BE IN CHARGE OF PAYING THE RENT.
RIGHT, AND WHEN IS
THAT DUE?
FIRST OF THE MONTH.
AND THAT'S EVERY MONTH?
NO, JUST THE MONTHS YOU ACTUALLY WANT TO LIVE HERE.
AH...
OKAY, HERE'S THE PHONE BILL.
OH, MY GOD.
THAT'S OUR PHONE NUMBER.
NOW, LOOK, I KNOW
I KIND OF SPRUNG THIS WHOLE
"ME MOVING OUT ON YOU" THING, SO WHY DON'T I JUST...
WHY DON'T I JUST COVER YOU FOR A WHILE?
NO, NO, NO WAY.
JOEY TRIBBIANI DOES NOT TAKE CHARITY...
ANYMORE.
IT'S NOT CHARITY, JOE.
NO. FORGET IT, OKAY?
I MEAN, THANKS, BUT I'M DONE
TAKING MONEY FROM YOU, ALL RIGHT?
I CAN TAKE CARE OF MYSELF.
NOW, WHAT'S NEXT? COME ON.
OKAY, UH, HERE'S THE ELECTRIC BILL.
THIS IS HOW MUCH WE PAY FOR ELECTRIC?!
WELL, YEAH.
SO WE'LL DO THE REST OF THE BILLS LATER, THEN?
SO, IS JOEY GOING TO HAVE TO GIVE UP THE APARTMENT?
WELL, I HOPE NOT. I TRIED TO OFFER HIM
SOME MONEY, BUT HE WOULDN'T TAKE IT.
WELL, HOW MUCH DO YOU THINK HE NEEDS?
I FIGURED $1,500 DOLLARS WOULD COVER HIM
FOR A FEW MONTHS, YOU KNOW?
BUT I HAVE TO TRICK HIM INTO TAKING IT
SO I DON'T HURT HIS PRIDE.
YEAH, WELL, WHY DON'T YOU HIRE HIM AS AN ACTOR?
YOU COULD HAVE HIM DRESS UP
AND PUT ON LITTLE SKITS-- JUST WHATEVER YOU WANT.
WELL, THAT WOULD HELP THE PRIDE THING.
HEY.
HEY, WOW, YOU LOOK GREAT.
DO YOU WANT TO MOVE IN WITH ME TOMORROW?
OKAY.
OKAY. SO, WHAT DO YOU GIRLS
HAVE PLANNED FOR TONIGHT?
WELL, INSTEAD OF BEING SAD
THAT TONIGHT'S MY LAST THAT NIGHT WITH RACHEL
WE THOUGHT WE'D GO OUT TO DINNER
AND CELEBRATE THE FACT THAT RACHEL'S MOVING IN WITH PHOEBE.
AND ALSO, MY BIRTHDAY.
IT'S NOT YOUR BIRTHDAY.
WHAT A MEAN THING TO SAY.
I WOULD NEVER TELL YOU IT WAS NOT YOUR BIRTHDAY.
HEY. HEY.
HEY.
SO, YOU GUYS HAVE ANYTHING PLANNED
FOR THE BIG LAST NIGHT?
WELL, INSTEAD OF JUST HANGING OUT
WE FIGURED WE'D DO NOTHING.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA--
KNICKS SEASON OPENER TONIGHT.
I THOUGHT MAYBE YOU GUYS WOULD COME OVER AND WATCH IT.
I DON'T KNOW, ROSS.
NOT IF YOU'RE GOING TO TALK ABOUT
HOW YOU GAVE UP A CAREER IN BASKETBALL
TO BECOME A PALEONTOLOGIST.
I DID GIVE UP A CAREER IN BASKETBALL
PHEEBS, I WAS WONDERING...
YOU'RE NOT DRESSED YET?
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO START HAVING FUN IN 15 MINUTES!
WELL, AND CLEARLY, NOT A MINUTE SOONER.
RACHEL, YOU ARE PACKED, THOUGH, RIGHT?
I MEAN, PLEASE TELL ME THAT YOU'RE PACKED.
OF COURSE I'M PACKED.
MONICA, RELAX.
I JUST WANTED TO ASK PHOEBE HER OPINION
ON WHAT I SHOULD WEAR TONIGHT.
MY GOD, I CANNOT GET A MINUTE OF PEACE AROUND HERE.
OH, MY GOD!
MONICA'S JUST GOING TO KILL YOU.
YEAH, I I KNOW.
WELL, WHAT YOU'RE WEARING IS FINE FOR THAT.
RACHEL, I NEED TO TALK...
YOU'RE NOT PACKED!
YOU'RE NOT PACKED EVEN A LITTLE BIT.
SURPRISE!
WHAT?
DON'T GET MAD, BECAUSE, LOOK
THIS IS WHAT HAPPENED-- SO I I STARTED PACKING
AND THEN I REALIZED, "WHAT AM I DOING?
I AM LOUSY AT PACKING," RIGHT?
BUT YOU LOVE PACKING
SO AS A GIFT TO YOU ON OUR LAST NIGHT...
TA DA.
I'LL BE COORDINATOR.
OH, MY GOD, I'M SO SORRY-- I DIDN'T GET YOU ANYTHING.
OKAY, LOOK, EVERYBODY HAS TO HELP, OKAY?
PHOEBE, YOU CAN HELP, CAN'T YOU?
I HAVE PLANS.
YOU HAVE PLANS WITH US.
THAT'S... RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, CHANDLER CAN MAKE BOXES
ROSS CAN WRAP AND JOEY CAN LIFT THINGS.
NOW, PHOEBE, GO TELL THE GUYS THEY HAVE TO HELP OUT.
OKAY. OKAY.
MY GOD, THANK YOU!
HURRY. MONICA'S GOING
TO MAKE YOU PACK -- SHE'S GOT JOBS FOR EVERYONE.
NOW, IT'S TOO LATE FOR ME, BUT SAVE YOURSELVES.
OKAY, THE MOVERS WILL BE HERE
IN 11 HOURS.
RACHEL HAS NOT PACKED.
NOW, EVERYBODY HAS TO HELP.
CHANDLER, WE'RE GOING TO START...
NO, I I I HAVE PLANS WITH JOEY.
I THOUGHT YOU SAID
YOU WERE GOING TO DO NOTHING.
YES, BUT FOR THE LAST TIME.
OKAY, FINE.
NOW, ROSS...
OH, BUT I I CAN'T DO IT.
WHY NOT?
DON'T YOU HAVE BEN?
BECAUSE... I HAVE BEN.
IT'S ALMOST 8:00. IT'S ALMOST PAST HIS BEDTIME.
WHERE IS HE?
HE'S AT A DINNER PARTY.
IS HE REALLY COMING? BECAUSE I CAN SEE INTO YOUR APARTMENT.
OF COURSE HE IS.
UH, WHAT, YOU THINK I'D JUST USE MY SON AS AS AN EXCUSE?
WHAT KIND OF FATHER DO YOU THINK I AM?
ALL RIGHT, SORRY.
I GOT TO GO MAKE A FAKE BEN.
HERE IT IS--
OUR LAST PIZZAS TOGETHER AS ROOMMATES.
I WISH I'D KNOWN YOU WERE GOING TO DO THAT. I ORDERED CHINESE.
OH, WELL, THAT'S OKAY.
HEY, ACTUALLY, IN A WAY, IT'S KIND OF NICE.
YOU KNOW, OUR LAST DINNER TOGETHER--
ME, BRINGING THE FOOD OF MY ANCESTORS
YOU, THE FOOD OF YOURS.
HUH?
SAY, JOE, I HAD A STRANGE IDEA
FOR WHAT WE COULD DO FOR OUR LAST NIGHT.
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE PLAY A LITTLE FOOSBALL FOR MONEY?
ARE YOU CRAZY?
YOU HAVEN'T BEATEN ME ONCE SINCE MY INJURY PLAGUED '97 SEASON.
IT'D BE EASIER IF YOU JUST GIVE ME YOUR MONEY.
YES, IT WOULD.
WHAT DO YOU SAY TO $50 DOLLARS?
I'D SAY TO IT, "$50 DOLLARS, YOU ARE MORE THAN I HAVE."
IF YOU KNOW THAT YOU'RE GOING TO WIN, THOUGH
WHAT DIFFERENCE DOES IT MAKE?
OKAY, YOU'RE ON.
OKAY, LET'S PLAY.
THE BIG GAME-- ITALY VERSUS...
CHINA, APPARENTLY.
OH, LOOK...
IT'S THE ROLLERBLADES.
OH, GOD...
DO YOU REMEMBER WHEN WE GOT THESE?
NO.
AW, I GUESS YOU WEREN'T THERE.
YOU GUYS, WE SAID WE WERE GOING TO HAVE FUN.
COME ON, HEY.
REMEMBER THE TIME...?
YOU DON'T REMEMBER?
I'M SORRY, PHEEBS.
I GUESS I'M JUST REALLY SAD THAT I'M LEAVING.
I'M GOING TO MISS YOU SO MUCH.
WELL, THIS DOESN'T HAVE TO BE SO SAD, THOUGH, YOU KNOW?
MAYBE INSTEAD OF JUST THINKING ABOUT
HOW MUCH YOU'RE GOING TO MISS EACH OTHER
YOU SHOULD, LIKE, THINK ABOUT SOME OF THE THINGS
THAT YOU'RE NOT GOING TO MISS.
I DON'T THINK THERE'S ANYTHING.
COME ON, THERE'S GOT TO BE SOMETHING.
NOPE.
SHE'S PERFECT.
HMM.
I HAVE ONE.
GREAT. OKAY, YOU CAN GO FIRST.
UH, WELL, I GUESS I'M NOT GOING TO MISS THE FACT...
THAT YOU'RE NEVER ALLOWED TO MOVE THE PHONE PEN.
GOOD. THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
OKAY, MONICA, ANYTHING?
YOU KNOW, DOES RACHEL MOVE THE PHONE PEN?
AW, SOMETIMES...
ALWAYS, ACTUALLY.
OKAY, GOOD. THERE YOU GO.
DOESN'T EVERYONE FEEL BETTER?
IT'S NOT JUST THE PHONE PEN.
I NEVER GET MY MESSAGES.
YOU GET YOUR MESSAGES.
YEAH, WELL, I DON'T THINK IT REALLY COUNTS
IF YOU HAVE TO READ THEM OFF THE BACK OF YOUR HAND
AFTER YOU'VE FALLEN ASLEEP ON THE COUCH.
SO SO, YOU MISSED A MESSAGE FROM WHO?
CHANDLER OR YOUR MOM?
OR CHANDLER?
OR YOUR MOM?
GREAT, IT WORKED.
NO ONE'S SAD.
YES.
I WIN AGAIN.
HA HA, THAT'S, LIKE, 500 BUCKS YOU OWE ME.
WHOO HOO HOO.
YEAH. $500 DOLLARS...
THAT IS A LOT OF ELECTRICITY, HUH?
WHOO HOO HOO.
OOH, I GOT TO BUY SOME FOOD.
OKAY, OKAY, GIVE ME A CHANCE TO WIN MY MONEY BACK, OKAY?
SUDDEN DEATH, ONE GOAL...
$1,000.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
OH, YES.
OKAY...
GET READY TO OWE ME.
OKAY.
OKAY, HERE WE GO. READY?
NO, NO, NO.
NO.... ONE CAN BEAT ME.
SEE? NOW, THAT'S WHY
ONLY THE LITTLE FAKE MEN ARE SUPPOSED TO DO THE KICKING.
HELLO?
OH, HI, ROSS.
SEE? OTHER PEOPLE CALL ME.
OOH, YOUR BROTHER-- SCORE.
WHAT'S UP?
Oh, I'm just over here with Ben.
THOUGHT WE'D SAY HI.
OH, PUT HIM ON.
BEN, SAY HI TO AUNT MONICA.
OH, I GUESS HE DOESN'T FEEL LIKE TALKING RIGHT NOW.
UH, HE'S SMILING, THOUGH.
OKAY, TALK TO YOU LATER.
YOU KNOW, DADDY WAS GOING TO BE A BASKETBALL PLAYER.
I THINK IT WAS BETTER WHEN YOU GUYS WERE SAD.
HEY, OH...
REMEMBER THE ROLLERBLADES?
OH...
YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE
I'M NOT GOING TO MISS?
"I'M MONICA. I WASH THE TOILET 17 TIMES A DAY
EVEN IF PEOPLE ARE ON IT."
"HI, I'M RACHEL. IS MY SWEATER TOO TIGHT?
NO? OH, I BETTER WASH IT AND SHRINK IT."
"I'M MONICA.
I DON'T GET PHONE MESSAGES FROM INTERESTING PEOPLE. EVER."
HEY, I CALL HER.
"OH, MY GOD, I LOVE ROSS, I HATE ROSS.
I LOVE ROSS, I HATE ROSS."
"OH, MY GOD, I CAN'T FIND A BOYFRIEND
"SO I GUESS I'LL JUST STUMBLE ACROSS THE HALL
AND SLEEP WITH THE FIRST GUY I FIND IN THERE."
YOU GUYS, COME ON. THIS IS THE LAST NIGHT.
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT, YOU'RE RIGHT
AND SO, FOR THE LAST TIME, I WOULD LIKE TO ASK YOU...
BOO HOO. GET OUT OF MY ROOM!
YEAH, WE SHOULD GET A MOVE ON
IF WE WANT TO MAKE THOSE DINNER RESERVATIONS.
STILL BROKEN?
IT SUCKS, MAN.
IT'S YOUR LAST NIGHT HERE
AND I LOSE THE TWO MOST IMPORTANT THINGS
IN MY LIFE-- THE FOOSBALL TABLE AND...
$500 DOLLARS.
BUT, YOU KNOW, THERE ARE OTHER WAYS
YOU CAN WIN BACK YOUR MONEY.
HOW ABOUT A LITTLE, UH, A LITTLE BLACKJACK?
NAH, NOT MY GAME.
OKAY, UH, HOW ABOUT-- HOW ABOUT...
YOU KNOW, WE COULD PLAY A NEW GAME.
A NEW GAME-- IT'S FUN.
WELL, WHAT'S IT CALLED?
CUPS.
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO PLAY CUPS.
I'LL TEACH YOU. COME ON.
IT'S REAL EASY... REALLY, REALLY FUN.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, HERE YOU GO.
I HAVE TWO QUEENS.
WHAT DO YOU HAVE?
A TWO AND A FIVE.
HO HO, YOU WIN, $50 DOLLARS.
REALLY?
OH, YEAH. OKAY, LET'S PLAY AGAIN.
READY?
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT?
FOUR AND A NINE.
YOU'RE KIDDING, RIGHT?
NO. WHY?
WELL, THAT'S A FULL CUP.
DAMN, I AM GOOD AT CUPS.
I'M NOT TALKING TO HER.
ONE OF YOU HAS TO TAKE THE FIRST STEP
AND IT SHOULD BE YOU
BECAUSE SHE'S THE ONE WHO'S LEAVING.
IT'S HARDER FOR HER.
WELL, MAYBE YOU'RE RIGHT...
BUT SHE MADE FUN OF MY PHONE PEN!
I KNOW.
I TOOK IT HARD, TOO.
SHE'S IN THERE RIGHT NOW CRYING. I CAN HEAR HER.
SHE'S NOT CRYING.
SHE'S HOLDING IT IN.
SHE'S SO BRAVE. GO.
LISTEN, RACHEL, I FEEL REALLY BAD ABOUT WHAT HA...
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'M UNPACKING.
WHAT?!
I'M NOT MOVING.
IS THAT PICTURE STRAIGHT?
IT NEEDS TO GO ABOUT 20 BLOCKS TO THE LEFT.
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT-- YOU'RE THE ONE WHO WANTS
TO MAKE THIS BIG CHANGE AND MOVE IN WITH CHANDLER.
YOU SHOULD BE THE ONE TO GO;  WHY DO I HAVE TO LEAVE?
BECAUSE IT'S MY APARTMENT.
WELL, IT'S MINE, TOO.
WHAT ELSE YOU GOT?
HOW ABOUT... YOU'RE MOVING?!
WH...
NO. NO. NO NO-
YES, YES, YES YES YES. NO NO NO NO.
YES. NO NO NO.
OKAY, MONICA, WAIT!
COME ON.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
WE SHOULD BE PACKING YOU!
WH...
HEY, HOW YOU GUYS DOING?
GREAT.
MONICA'S MOVING.
I AM NOT.
OH, REALLY?
WELL, HOW COME ALL YOUR STUFF IS IN THIS BOX?
OKAY, YOU GUYS, YOU GUYS
I THINK I KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON, HERE, OKAY?
YOU GUYS... STOP!
I KNOW THAT... I KNOW THAT YOU'RE ACTING MAD
BECAUSE YOU THINK THAT'LL MAKE IT EASIER TO LEAVE
BUT DEEP DOWN, YOU'RE STILL REALLY SAD--
DEEP, DEEP DOWN.
NO, PHOEBE, I AM MAD.
WELL, DEEP, DEEP,DEEP DOWN. YEAH, I'M JUST MAD.
THEN, KEEP RUNNING.
YOU WIN.
WELL, WHAT DID YOU HAVE?
WELL, IT DOESN'T MATTER.
NOTHING BEATS A. .. THREE AND A SIX.
THAT, MY FRIEND, IS "D" CUP.
OKAY, NOW, HOW MUCH HAVE YOU WON SO FAR?
UH... WOW...
$700 DOLLARS.
NOT $700 DOLLARS EXACTLY!
YEAH.
DOUBLE IT.
WHAT?
YEAH, SEE, IN CUPS
ONCE YOU GET $700 DOLLARS, YOU HAVE TO DOUBLE IT.
REALLY?
HEY, I DIDN'T MAKE UP THE RULES.
NOW OKAY, SO,
AFTER YOU RECEIVE THE DOUBLING BONUS
YOU GET, UH, ONE CARD.
NOW, THAT ONE CARD COULD BE WORTH $100 DOLLARS
WHICH BRINGS YOUR TOTAL TO $1,500 DOLLARS
OH HO... NO, WAIT.
DON'T GET TOO EXCITED
BECAUSE THAT'S NOT GOING TO HAPPEN
UNLESS YOU GET THE... NO WAY!
WELL, THIS IS THE LAST BOX OF YOUR CLOTHES.
I'M JUST GOING TO LABEL IT
"WHAT WERE YOU THINKING?"
HUH, THAT'S SO FUNNY
BECAUSE I WAS JUST GOING TO GO ACROSS THE HALL
AND WRITE THAT ON CHANDLER.
OKAY, YOU GUYS, I DON'T MEAN TO MAKE THINGS WORSE
BUT, UM, I DON'T WANT TO LIVE WITH RACHEL ANYMORE.
WHAT? WHAT?
YOU'RE JUST SO MEAN TO EACH OTHER
AND I DON'T WANT TO END UP LIKE THAT WITH RACHEL.
I STILL LIKE YOU.
WELL, PHOEBE, THAT'S FINE BECAUSE I'M NOT MOVING.
WHOA WHOA WHOA WHOA WHOA.
PHOEBE, YOU GOT TO TAKE HER.
I KNOW I SAID SOME BAD STUFF ABOUT HER
BUT RACHEL DOES HAVE SOME GOOD QUALITIES
THAT MAKE HER A GOOD ROOMMATE.
OH, REALLY?
LIKE WHAT, MONICA?
OKAY...
YOU KNOW HOW SHE HAS 147,000 PAIR OF BOOTS?
OH, YEAH, GOOD START, MON.
SHE LETS YOU BORROW THEM.
YEAH, AND YOU STRETCH THEM OUT WITH YOUR BIG OLD CLOWN FEET.
DO YOU WANT TO LIVE OUTSIDE?
BECAUSE IT'S GETTING COLD.
SHE GETS TONS OF CATALOGS
AND, UM, SHE'LL FOLD DOWN THE PAGES
OF THE THINGS THAT SHE THINKS THAT I'D LIKE.
WHAT ELSE?
WELL...
WHEN I TAKE A SHOWER...
SHE LEAVES ME LITTLE NOTES ON THE MIRROR.
YEAH, I DO.
I I DO DO THAT.
THAT'S NICE.
I LIKE HAVING THINGS TO READ IN THE BATHROOM.
WHEN I FALL ASLEEP
ON THE COUCH AFTER READING...
SHE COVERS ME OVER WITH A BLANKET.
WELL, YOU KNOW...
I DON'T WANT YOU TO BE COLD.
AND... WHEN I TOLD HER
THAT I WAS GOING TO BE MOVING IN WITH CHANDLER...
SHE WAS REALLY SUPPORTIVE.
YOU WERE SO GREAT.
YOU MADE IT
SO EASY...
AND NOW YOU HAVE TO LEAVE...
AND I HAVE TO LIVE WITH A BOY!
OH...
OH, HONEY...
OH, IT'S GOING TO BE FINE.
OKAY, RACHEL, NOW I CAN'T WAIT TO LIVE WITH YOU.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT WE SHOULD DO?
BRING MONICA, AND THEN WE COULD ALL LIVE THERE TOGETHER.
WE'LL HAVE SO MUCH FUN!
BUT, HONEY, I THINK SHE'S MOVING IN WITH CHANDLER.
OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU'RE STILL SET ON THAT?
KIND OF.
OH, MY GOD!
HELLO?
HEY, MON.
HOW'S THE PACKING GOING?
BEN? HE'S FINE.
YEAH, HE'S RIGHT...
OH, MY GOD!
WELL...
GET YOUR HEAD OUT OF YOUR SHIRT THERE, SON.
WHAT?
YEAH, IT'S A PUMPKIN.
I'LL COME PACK.
HEY.
WHAT'S WRONG?
ROSS AND I
WERE HELPING THE GIRLS PACK
TOOK A LITTLE BREAK...
I LOST $1,500 DOLLARS TO HIM AT CUPS.
WHA...
HOW DID YOU LOSE AT CUPS?
THE SAME WAY YOU LOST.
I STARTED OUT WITH A KING AND A QUEEN.
BAM! ROSS GETS A TWO AND A THREE.
THEN I GET A JACK AND A KING.
BOOM! ROSS GETS A FOUR AND FIVE.
ROSS WAS GETTING THE CUP CARD
TH THE "D" CUP, THE THE SITTING DOWN BONUS...
MEANWHILE, I DIDN'T EVEN GET A HALF A CUP, NOTHING!
OH, MAN!
HE NEVER PLAYED BEFORE EITHER.
YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK?
I THINK BEGINNER'S LUCK-- VERY IMPORTANT IN CUPS.
OKAY, I... LET'S JUST PLAY ONE MORE HAND--
JUST ONE MORE HAND.
NO, NO, NO MORE-- I CANNOT LOSE ANOTHER DIME.
I'M SERIOUS THIS TIME.
I IN FACT, LOOK, THERE'S, UH...
I WANT TO GIVE YOU SOMETHING, OKAY?
AND LET ME GIVE IT TO YOU NOW, BEFORE I PAWN IT FOR CUPS MONEY.
NOW... I WANT YOU TO HAVE
THE BIG WHITE DOG AS A... KIND OF A, YOU KNOW
LIKE A THANK YOU FOR... BEING SUCH A GREAT ROOMMATE.
I CAN'T TAKE THE BIG WHITE DOG.
YOU LOVE IT.
IT'S "HIM", NOT "IT."
NO, BUT WHAT WHAT IF I BOUGHT IT
FROM YOU, YOU KNOW?
AND, THEN, YOUR YOUR NICE GESTURE WOULD BE
GIVING IT TO ME AT A REASONABLE PRICE--
SAY, $1,500 DOLLARS?
WAIT A SECOND.
I SEE WHAT YOU'RE TRYING TO DO HERE.
YOU'RE YOU'RE YOU'RE TRYING TO GIVE ME MONEY AGAIN.
WHEN DID I TRY TO GIVE YOU MONEY?
BEFORE, OVER THERE, WITH THE BILLS.
YOU TRIED TO GIVE ME CHARITY.
I SAID, "NO."
YOU DROPPED IT.
OKAY, THEN, WE HAD A NICE LAST NIGHT TOGETHER.
WE HAD SOME FUN; WE GAMBLED.
NOBODY TRIED
TO GIVE ANYBODY ANY MONEY.
NOW, OUT OF THE BLUE, YOU START WITH THE CHARITY THING AGAIN.
I'M JUST TRYING TO HELP YOU OUT, OKAY?
I WANT TO MAKE SURE THAT YOU'RE OKAY.
I WILL BE OKAY.
LOOK, CHANDLER, YOU GOT TO GET IT OUT OF YOUR HEAD
THAT I CAN'T TAKE CARE OF MYSELF, OKAY?
LOOK, I'M NOT GOING
TO MISS YOU HELPING ME OUT WITH MONEY.
THE ONLY THING THAT I'M GOING TO MISS...
IS YOU.
AND NOW THE DOG.
HEY...
CALL ME WHEN YOU GET THERE, OKAY?
OKAY.
I'M REALLY GOING TO MISS YOU.
MMM.
OH, I HAVE YOUR KEY.
HERE YOU GO.
THANKS.
YEAH.
OH, GOD, THIS IS SILLY.
I'M GOING TO SEE YOU IN A COUPLE OF HOURS.
MM HMM.
BYE, HOUSE.
BYE, BABE. BYE.
HI.
SHE REALLY LEFT.
I KNOW.
THANK YOU.
NO PROBLEM, ROOMIE.
CAN I ASK YOU A QUESTION?
SURE.
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT DOG DOING HERE?
I INVENTED CUPS AS A WAY TO GIVE JOEY MONEY.
AND NOW YOU WANT THAT MONEY BACK.
EXACTLY.
CHANDLER, WHAT KIND OF IDIOT DO YOU TAKE ME FOR?
IT'S NOT A REAL GAME.
I MADE IT UP.
I'M SORRY YOU LOST YOUR MONEY, BUT I WON IT FAIR AND SQUARE.
AT A FAKE GAME!
NOW, IF YOU WANT TO TRY TO MAKE SOME OF IT BACK...
I'D BE GLAD TO PLAY YOU FOR IT, BUT I SHOULD WARN YOU--
I AM VERY GOOD AT CUPS.
OKAY...
NOW, I ASSUME THE SAUCER CARD CAME UP
WHEN YOU PLAYED LAST.
NO.
HMM...
LET'S SEE IF IT COMES UP THIS TIME.