READY? YEAH.
OKAY.
HI. IT'S...
RACHEL... AND...
PHOEBE'S... PLEASE...
LEAVE...
WAIT, I I JUST SAID, "LEAVE."
YEAH, I KNOW, BECAUSE YOU HAVE
ALL THE GOOD WORDS.
WHAT DO I GET?
I GET "IT'S, AND"-- OH, I'M SORRY, I HAVE "A."
FORGET IT.
PHOEBE, COME ON.
THAT'S SILLY.
ALL RIGHT, SO, LET'S SWITCH.
NO, I HAVE ALL THE GOOD WORDS.
OKAY, FINE, FINE.
WE CAN SWITCH.
OKAY.
HI...
EVERYBODY...
IT'S... RACHEL...
AND... PHOEBE'S...
PLEA... WAIT.
HOW DID YOU DO THAT?
WHAT?
OH... YOU'RE NO ORDINARY ROOMMATE, ARE YOU?
THIS IS GOING TO BE INTERESTING.
PH PHOEBE, COME ON.
CAN WE FINISH THIS LATER
BECAUSE I WANT TO GO RUNNING BEFORE IT GETS DARK.
OH! WHY DON'T YOU COME WITH ME?
REALLY? YEAH.
OH, IT'LL BE FUN.
WE'LL RUN IN THE PARK.
IT'LL BE, LIKE, OUR FIRST
YOU KNOW, ROOMMATE BONDING THING.
YEAH... OKAY, LET'S GO RUNNING.
AND THERE'S REALLY CUTE GUYS THERE.
LET'S RUN TOWARDS THEM!
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, WAIT JUST ONE MORE SECOND.
HI. IT'S PHOEBE AND RACHEL'S.
PLEASE LEAVE A MESSAGE. THANKS.
WELL, NOW, WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU JUST TOOK ALL THE WORDS.
UH HUH, YOU'VE MET YOUR MATCH, RACHEL GREEN.
SO, I JUST FINISHED THIS FASCINATING BOOK.
BY THE YEAR 2030, THERE'LL BE COMPUTERS
THAT CAN CARRY OUT THE SAME AMOUNT OF FUNCTIONS
AS AN ACTUAL HUMAN BRAIN.
SO, THEORETICALLY, YOU COULD DOWNLOAD
YOUR THOUGHTS AND MEMORIES INTO THIS COMPUTER
AND AND AND LIVE FOREVER, AS A MACHINE.
AND I JUST REALIZED I CAN SLEEP WITH MY EYES OPEN.
HEY.
HEY. HEY.
HONEY, THAT'S A GREAT IDEA-- NAILING THE BOXES
TO THE FLOOR.
I DIDN'T NAIL THE BOXES TO THE FLOOR.
OH, SO YOU CAN MOVE THEM?
YES.
YES, AND WHILE I'M DOING THAT
ROSS HAS A GREAT COMPUTER STORY FOR YOU.
HEY, EVERYBODY.
UH, I'D LIKE YOU TO MEET JANINE.
SHE'S SHE'S GOING TO BE MY NEW ROOMMATE.
HI.
YEAH, SHE'S GOING TO LIVE WITH ME!
IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU.
UH, JANINE...
LECROIX, JANINE LECROIX.
I DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
WH WHAT A PRETTY LAST NAME.
SO, UH, WH WHERE ARE YOU FROM?
AUSTRALIA. I JUST MOVED HERE A COUPLE OF WEEKS AGO.
FROM THE LAND DOWN UNDER?
YEAH.
I DIDN'T KNOW THAT, EITHER.
SO, UH, WHAT, UH, WHAT DO YOU DO?
I'M A DANCER.
YOU'RE A DANCER?
SHE SHE'S A DANCER.
WELL, I THINK
I'LL GO AND... UNPACK.
OH, HEY, LET ME.
THANKS. OKAY.
JOEY...
YEAH?
DID YOU EVEN INTERVIEW THIS WOMAN
BEFORE YOU ASKED HER TO MOVE IN?
OF COURSE I DID.
UH HUH. WHAT EXACTLY DID YOU ASK HER?
"WHEN CAN YOU MOVE IN?"
THANK YOU FOR BRINGING HER INTO OUR LIVES.
UNBELIEVABLE.
DOWN, BOY.
NO, NO, NO, NO. SHE'S NOT MY TYPE.
NOT FOR ME. SHE'S  NOT MY TYPE. SHE'S TOO...
BEAUTIFUL, TALL, SEXY, SHOWING HER STOMACH?
HEY, LOOK AT ALL THE BOXES.
OH, I CANNOT WAIT TO ASK HER OUT.
WAIT A MINUTE, JOEY.
JOEY, YOU CAN'T ASK HER OUT.
SHE'S YOUR ROOMMATE.
YOU KNOW, IT'S... IT'LL BE WAY TOO COMPLICATED.
YEAH, YEAH, MAN, DON'T DO IT.
I MEAN, IF YOU DATE HER
THEN THEN THEN I CAN'T DATE HER.
LOOK, YOU KNOW, WHAT IF YOU STARTED GOING OUT WITH HER
AND IT DIDN'T WORK OUT?
THAT'S WHEN I MAKE MY MOVE.
NOW, REMEMBER WHEN YOU WERE GOING OUT
WITH THAT GIRL DONNA AND YOU GUYS BROKE UP?
REMEMBER HOW HORRIBLE IT WAS
WHEN YOU GUYS BUMPED INTO EACH OTHER AT THE SUPERMARKET?
OH, GOD, YEAH.
NOW, IMAGINE YOU LIVE... AT THE SUPERMARKET.
OKAY.
NO, NO.
OH. OH.
OH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I DON'T WANT THAT.
I CAN'T DATE HER.
YEAH, AND YOU BETTER WATCH THE FLIRTING, TOO
BECAUSE IN SUCH CLOSE QUARTERS...
IT COULD BE TROUBLE.
WELL, THAT'S GOING TO BE TOUGH, MON.
I MEAN, IT'S HARD FOR ME TO BE AROUND AN ATTRACTIVE WOMAN
AND NOT FLIRT.
WELL, YOU'RE AROUND MEALL THE TIME
AND YOU DON'T FLIRT.
YOU A LITTLE SAD ABOUT THAT, SWEETHEART?
I HAVE TO TIE MY SHOE.
SO YOU GO AHEAD. I'LL CATCH UP.
OKAY.
COME ON!
THAT'S NOT RUNNING!
LET'S GO!
YOU GUYS,  I'M TELLING YOU
WHEN SHE RUNS, SHE LOOKS LIKE
A CROSS BETWEEN KERMIT THE FROG AND THE SIX MILLION DOLLAR MAN.
MONICA HAD SUCH A CRUSH ON HIM.
YEAH, SHE USED TO KISS HIS POSTER
EVERY NIGHT BEFORE SHE WENT TO BED.
OH, I USED TO DO THAT, TOO.
DID YOU ALSO HAVE HIS ALBUM
IT'S NOT EASY BEING GREEN?
AW, MON...
SO, PHOEBE RUNS WEIRD, HUH?
YEAH, YEAH, AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
AND I KNOW SHE'S GOING TO WANT TO RUN AGAIN.
I JUST DON'T KNOW HOW TO GET OUT OF IT.
I MEAN, I LIVE WITH HER.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST  BE STRAIGHT WITH HER?
TELL HER THE TRUTH.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU'RE RIGHT, I SHOULD JUST TELL HER THE TRUTH.
HEY. HEY.
HEY, PHEEBS, MONICA TRIPPED ME.
I DON'T THING I CAN EVER RUN AGAIN, EVER.
BUT WE WERE HAVING SO MUCH FUN.
ALL THOSE CUTE GUYS WERE CHECKING US OUT.
I KNOW. THEY WERE DEFINITELY STARING.
WHY?
WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
RACHEL, I'M I'M SORRY THAT I HURT YOUR ANKLES.
ANKLE.
WE'LL SEE.
OKAY, I AM OFFICIALLY UNPACKED.
THANKS FOR HELPING ME, MAN.
JOE?
WELL, I GUESS JOEY WENT HOME.
OH, AND LOOK, THERE'S STILL ONE BOX
THAT I HAVE TO UNPACK.
I GOTCHA!
OH, MY GOD!
YOU ALMOST GAVE ME A HEART ATTACK.
BOY, IT WAS SO HARD NOT TO LAUGH
I'LL TELL YOU.
OH, HEY HEY...
THE PLACE LOOKS GREAT.
YEAH, NOT BAD, RIGHT?
YOU KNOW WHAT? MONICA'S GOING TO BE WORKING LATE.
SO, I'M GOING TO MAKE THIS PLACE SPOTLESS.
YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE I'M GOING TO DO?
I'M GOING TO GO DOWNSTAIRS.
I'M GOING TO GET HER SOME FLOWERS.
NOW, WHO WOULD NOT WANT TO LIVE WITH ME?
I DON'T.
NO, I WANT TO LIVE
WITH THE SUPER HOT AUSTRALIAN DANCER.
OKAY, NOW, HOW'S THAT GOING NOW?
ARE YOU OKAY WITH THE NOT FLIRTING THING?
UH, YEAH, BUT... SO FAR, YEAH
BUT IT'S TOUGH , YOU KNOW?
I GOT ALL THIS THIS BUILT UP FLIRTING ENERGY
AND AND I DON'T KNOW HOW TO GET RID OF IT.
HOW YOU DOING?
GET OUT!
OH, MAN.
SORRY, THERE'S JUST MORE ROOM OUT HERE.
OH, NO, NO, NO, IT'S IT'S, UH... YOU JUST, UH, UH, REMINDED ME
THAT, UH, I HAVE TO DO MY STRETCHES, TOO, YEAH.
WHY DON'T YOU TRY TO...
WHAT'S WRONG?
UH, UH, NOTHING.
I JUST, UH... I I DIDN'T WANT YOU TO TOUCH ME
BECAUSE I'M I'M ALL SWEATY
FROM THE WORKOUT.
I'M GOING TO HIT THE SHOWER.
OH, MY GOD!
OH, SORRY ABOUT THAT STUFF HANGING IN THERE.
IT'S JUST MY THONGS ARE TOO DELICATE FOR THE DRYER.
OH...
HI!
OH, YEAH, UH HUH, IT'S ME.
I SAW YOU GRAB
YOUR RUNNING SHOES THIS MORNING
AND SNEAK OUT.
YOU LIED SO YOU COULD RUN
BY YOURSELF.
NO, PHOEBE, NO, I WAS... NO.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I WAS... I WAS ACTUALLY JUST CHECKING...
TO SEE... IF I COULD RUN AND I CAN.
PLEASE, RACHEL, I AM NOT AN IDIOT.
NO, WAIT, PHOEBE.
WOW...
COUPLES WHO LIVE TOGETHER DO START TO LOOK ALIKE.
LOOK, I AM WORKING RIGHT NOW, OKAY?
SO JUST SAY WHAT YOU HAVE TO SAY AND LEAVE ME ALONE.
HUH. SOUND ALIKE, TOO.
SO... MONDLER...
UH...
WHAT, UH... WH...
WHAT YOU DOING?
WHAT DOES IT LOOK LIKE?
I AM CLEANING.
DID YOU GET MONICA'S AUTHORIZATION
TO MOVE ALL OF HER STUFF.
"AUTHORIZATION"-- I DON'T NEED THAT.
I'M GOING TO PUT EVERYTHING BACK.
PUT IT BACK EXACTLY WHERE YOU FOUND IT?
YES, I'M GOING TO PUT IT BACK "EXACTLY" WHERE I FOUND IT.
OKAY, FIRST OF ALL, THAT ATTITUDE IS NOT HELPING.
OKAY, SHE IS NOT GOING TO CARE
IF I PUT HER STUFF BACK IN THE SAME STUPID PLACE.
OH, HELLO?
DID YOU JUST MEET MONICA?
SHE'S GOING TO RECOGNIZE THAT I DID A NICE THING
AND AND APPRECIATE IT.
HUH.
YOU KNOW, ACTUALLY
THIS WILL WORK OUT WELL
BECAUSE WHEN YOU HAVE TO MOVE BACK IN WITH JOEY
JOEY'S HOT NEW ROOMMATE CAN COME LIVE WITH ME.
I SEE. I SEE.
Y Y YOU'RE TRYING TO FREAK ME OUT.
LOOK, CHANDLER, MONICA IS REALLY WEIRD
ABOUT THIS KIND  OF STUFF, ALL RIGHT?
BELIEVE ME, I LIVED WITH HER FOR 16 YEARS.
SHE IS GOING TO FREAK OUT.
OH, MY GOD, SHE'S GOING TO SIT ON YOU.
THAT PROBABLY WON'T HURT AS MUCH ANYMORE, BUT...
NO, SHE'S NOT, OKAY?
YOU KNOW, I'LL PROVE IT TO YOU.
I'M GOING TO CALL HER RIGHT NOW.
PHONE'S DONE.
Hi. HEY, MON, HOW'S IT GOING?
Terrible.
I TELL YOU, IF IF IF I WANT SOMETHING DONE RIGHT
I HAVE TO DO IT MYSELF.
Other people just wreck stuff.
I REALLY THINK I MIGHT KILL SOMEONE TONIGHT.
OH, COME ON, COME ON, IT CAN'T BE THAT BAD.
IT'S WORSE. THE ONLY THING THAT'S GETTING ME THROUGH
IS KNOWING THAT I'M GOING TO BE SEEING YOU SOON.
I think I may even try to get out of here early.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
NO, IT SOUNDS LIKE THEY REALLY NEED YOU DOWN THERE.
YOU'RE JUST HANGING OUT WITH ROSS?
IT'S ALL GOOD. OKAY, BYE BYE, MON.
SH SHE'S GOING TO KILL ME.
YOU KNOW, THE PHONE WAS FACING THE OTHER WAY...
AND THAT GOES BACK UP THERE.
OKAY, THIS IS GOOD.
THIS IS UNDER CONTROL.
YOU KNOW WHAT WE SHOULD DO?
WE SHOULD START WITH THE BIG STUFF, YOU KNOW?
THAT'LL BE THE EASIEST.
SO, UH, LET'S START WITH THE COUCH.
I GOT IT.
YEAH, THAT THAT
DOESN'T LOOK RIGHT.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
THE COUCH IS PERFECTLY IN LINE WITH THE CARPET
AND THEN I COULD JUST WALK OVER HERE
AND CAUSALLY JUST PUT MY FEET RIGHT UP ON...
OKAY, HERE'S WHAT WE DO--
WE JUST, UH, MOVE THE COUCH CLOSER TO THE COFFEE TABLE.
WHOA, YEAH, BUT THEN THE BACK OF THE COUCH
WON'T LINE UP WITH THE BACK OF THE CARPET.
OKAY, WELL, HERE--
WE'LL JUST, UH...
WE'LL MOVE THE COFFEE TABLE CLOSER TO THE COUCH.
NO, WHOA! WHOA!
BUT THEN THE COFFEE TABLE
WON'T BE CENTERED IN THE SEATING AREA.
YES, BUT THE COFFEE TABLE DOESN'T HAVE TO...
ROSS!
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?
I'M NOT FLIRTING, BUT STILL, I'M I'M DRAWING HER TO ME
LIKE LIKE LIKE A MOTH TO A FLAME!
WHAT THE HELL'S GOING ON OVER HERE?!
MONICA'S GOING TO KILL YOU.
LOOK, I NEED YOUR HELP, OKAY?
I HAVE TO DO SOMETHING TO TO REPEL THIS WOMAN.
WAIT A MINUTE, WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU GUYS REPEL WOMEN ALL THE TIME!
HEY, I'VE BEEN MARRIED THREE TIMES.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO!
I'VE SEEN IT HAPPEN.
YOU GET A RAPPORT GOING WITH A WOMAN
BUT SOMEHOW YOU MANAGE TO KILL IT.
TIME AFTER TIME AFTER TIME AFTER TIME.
WHAT'S YOUR SECRET?
LOOK, WE DO NOT REPEL WOMEN, OKAY?
THAT IS COMPLETELY UNTRUE.
UH, YES, WE DO, MY MAN.
REMEMBER WHEN WE WERE BACK IN COLLEGE
AND WE WENT TO THAT SPRING DANCE
AND YOU WALKED RIGHT UP TO THAT GIRL YOU LIKED
AND YOU COULD NOT STOP TALKING ABOUT
THE IRISH POTATO FAMINE?
WELL, WHAT ABOUT YOU?
YOU WEREN'T SO, YOU KNOW, HOT IN COLLEGE, EITHER.
AFTER EVERYTHING HE SAID, HE'D GO "BA DUM BUMP. CHSSH."
YEAH, MONICA DOESN'T LIKE THAT, EITHER.
MAYBE I SHOULD STOP DOING THAT.
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT? GIRLS DON'T LIKE IT
WHEN I START TALKING ABOUT SCIENCE.
THAT'S NOT SPECIFIC TO GIRLS.
THIS IS GREAT, THIS IS GREAT!
WHAT WHAT ELSE, WHAT ELSE?
UH... OH, THEY DON'T LIKE IT WHEN YOU CORRECT THEIR GRAMMAR.
AND THEY DON'T LIKE IT
WHEN YOU EXPLAIN WHY YOUR JOKES ARE FUNNY.
YOU KNOW, THEY DON'T LIKE IT WHEN YOU KEEP ASKING THEM
IF THEY LIKE YOU.
MAN, I AM SO LUCKY I HAVE MONICA.
I'M NEVER GOING TO FIND LOVE AGAIN.
HEY.
PHOEBE, CAN I TALK TO YOU FOR A SECOND?
SURE.
OKAY, UM, I...
ALL RIGHT, PHOEBE, LOOK--
I JUST WANTED TO SAY THAT I'M SORRY, OKAY?
I HANDLED THE SITUATION HORRIBLY
AND AND I SHOULD NOT HAVE LIED TO YOU.
SO, WHAT SHOULD YOU HAVE DONE?
WELL, I I SHOULD HAVE TOLD YOU THE TRUTH.
UH HUH...
WHICH IS?
WELL, YOU KNOW...
THE REASON THAT I DIDN'T WANT TO GO RUNNING WITH YOU IS
BECAUSE, UH, WELL, YOU KNOW, THE WAY THAT YOU RUN
IS JUST A LITTLE...
SO?
WELL, IT'S EMBARRASSING.
PEOPLE WERE LOOKING AT US LIKE WE WERE CRAZY.
WHY DO YOU CARE?
BECAUSE THEY'RE PEOPLE.
BUT PEOPLE THAT YOU DON'T KNOW AND WILL NEVER SEE AGAIN.
YES, BUT STILL, THEY ARE PEOPLE...
WITH EYES.
WELL, I DIDN'T GET EMBARRASSED RUNNING NEXT TO MISS...
BUT, OH, OKAY.
NO, NO, I CAN SEE WHY RUNNING WITH ME
WOULD BE EMBARRASSING TO YOU.
YEAH, OKAY.
YOU'RE UPTIGHT.
WH...!
I... LIS...
I AM NOT UPTIGHT...
NO...
LISTEN, I AM NOT...
UPTIGHT, MAN.
THAT'S OKAY, RACHEL.
I'M NOT JUDGING YOU.
THAT'S JUST WHO YOU ARE.
ME, I'M MORE FREE, YOU KNOW?
I RUN LIKE I DID WHEN I WAS A KID
BECAUSE IT'S THE ONLY  WAY IT'S FUN, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, DIDN'T YOU EVER RUN SO FAST
YOU THOUGHT YOUR LEGS WERE GOING TO FALL OFF?
YOU KNOW, LIKE WHEN YOU WERE RUNNING TOWARD THE SWINGS
OR OR RUNNING AWAY FROM SATAN?
THE NEIGHBORS' DOG.
OH.
OKAY, IS THIS LAMP IN THE RIGHT PLACE?
WHO CARES? I REPEL WOMEN.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO!
YOU CAN'T COME IN HERE.
R R ROSS IS NAKED!
WHAT?!
I COULDN'T SAY THAT I WAS NAKED
BECAUSE SHE'S ALLOWED TO SEE ME NAKED.
WHY DOES ANYONE HAVE TO BE NAKED?
WHY IS ROSS NAKED?
I... I HAD TO... SHOW CHANDLER SOMETHING.
NAKED?
YEAH, I I, UH...
I GUESS I HAVE A, UH...
A GUY PROBLEM.
IS IT THE SAME THING THAT CHANDLER HAD?
LOOK, UH, JUST JUST COME BACK LATER.
WE'LL GET EVERYTHING SQUARED AWAY
AND YOU CAN COME BACK LATER.
OKAY.
HEY, LISTEN, THERE'S STILL SOME OF CHANDLER'S MEDICINE LEFT
UNDER THE SINK IN THE BATHROOM. BYE.
BYE BYE.
THANK GOD.
DUDE, WHAT'D YOU HAVE?
LOOK, WE HAVE NO TIME, OKAY?
WE MUST FOCUS.
WE GOT TO GET EVERYTHING BACK
INTO ITS ORIGINAL PLACE.
THE PHOTO ALBUM.
THERE WERE MILLIONS OF PICTURES OF THE APARTMENT
IN THE PHOTO ALBUM.
WE JUST GO THROUGH IT AND MATCH EVERYTHING TO THE PICTURES.
THAT'S PERFECT.
THAT'S BRILLIANT.
SO, REALLY, WHAT'D YOU HAVE?
HEY, JOEY, I GOT SOME BEER FOR YOU.
UH, DON'T DON'T YOU MEAN, "FOR WHOM"?
SURE.
LISTEN, I WAS GOING TO ORDER SOME PIZZA.
YOU WANT TO SHARE ONE?
PIZZA? HA! IT'S NOT LIKE I'VE NEVER HAD THAT BEFORE.
BA DUM BUMP. CHSSH.
IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG?
YEAH, I'M DEPRESSED ABOUT THAT IRISH POTATO FAMINE.
NO, I MEAN WITH ME
BECAUSE YOU SEEM TO BE ACTING REALLY WEIRD AROUND ME.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
LET'S JUST GET THIS OUT IN THE OPEN, OKAY?
YOU'RE HOT.
I'M LOVABLE.
CLEARLY, THERE'S A VIBE GOING ON BETWEEN US
BUT WE'RE ROOMMATES
AND IT'S A HUGE MISTAKE FOR US TO CONTINUE DOWN THIS ROAD.
JOEY...
NO, NO, NO, I'M TELLING YOU.
IMAGINE YOURSELF LIVING IN A SUPERMARKET
AND YOU WILL UNDERSTAND.
OKAY, SO THE QUESTION IS, WHAT DO WE DO?
WELL, I DON'T THINK THERE IS ANYTHING TO DO.
I MEAN, I THINK YOU'RE REALLY SWEET
BUT I'M JUST NOT INTERESTED IN YOU LIKE THAT.
OH!
NO, I MEAN...
YOU'RE A REALLY NICE GUY
AND I'M HAPPY TO BE YOUR ROOMMATE
AND YOUR FRIEND.
I'M JUST...
YOU KNOW, I JUST DON'T FEEL THAT WAY ABOUT YOU.
OH... I SEE WHAT HAPPENED.
IT'S BECAUSE I WAS TRYING TO REPEL YOU, RIGHT?
BELIEVE ME, YOU'D FEEL A LOT DIFFERENT IF I TURNED IT ON.
I DON'T THINK SO.
OH, I DO.
HOW YOU DOING?
I'M OKAY.
WHAT?
OH, DEAR GOD!
HEY! HEY!
PHEEBS!
OH, HONEY, I'M SO SORRY.
YOU WERE RIGHT-- THIS FEELS GREAT!
SEE? AND YOU DON'T CARE IF PEOPLE ARE STARING.
IT'S JUST FOR A SECOND, BECAUSE THEN YOU'RE GONE!
GONE!
I MEAN, IT'S AMAZING, PHEEBS!
I FEEL SO FREE, AND SO GRACEFUL...
AAH!
HEY! LOOK OUT FOR THE HORSE.
SORRY.
IS IT OKAY FOR ME TO COME IN NOW?
UH HUH.
WHY IS EVERYTHING DIFFERENT?
BYE.
NO, I DON'T SEE ANYTHING DIFFERENT
OTHER THAN THE FACT THAT THE ROOM GOT SO MUCH BRIGHTER
WHEN YOU CAME INTO IT.
WELL, THE END TABLE IS WRONG AND THE COUCH LOOKS BIZARRE
AND DON'T EVEN GET ME STARTED ON THE REFRIGERATOR MAGNETS.
OKAY, LOOK, DON'T... DON'T BE MAD, OKAY?
BUT AFTER I UNPACKED THE BOXES
I WANTED TO DO SOMETHING NICE FOR YOU
SO I I I CLEANED THE APARTMENT.
SO I MOVED EVERYTHING AROUND
AND THEN I I FORGOT WHERE IT... WHERE IT WENT BACK.
AND I'M SORRY.
I'M VERY SORRY, I'M SORRY, I'M SORRY.
THAT'S OKAY.
CHANDLER, ARE YOU AFRAID OF ME OR SOMETHING?
DO YOU WANT ME TO BE AFRAID OF YOU?
OF COURSE NOT.
OH, MY GOSH, CHANDLER, WHAT YOU DID--
IT'S IT'S SUCH A WONDERFUL THING AND I REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
I KNOW I HAVE THIS WEIRD THING
WHERE I WANT EVERYTHING TO BE IN THE PERFECT PLACE
BUT I WOULD NEVER EXPECT YOU TO WORRY ABOUT THAT.
REALLY?
OF COURSE.
OH, WELL, YOU'RE THE BEST.
YOU COME HERE TO ME.
ALL RIGHT, HOLD ON, OKAY?
FIRST THINGS FIRST.
OKAY, NOW...
DID ROSS SIT ANYWHERE WHILE HE WAS NAKED?
SO IT'S SAID THAT BY THE YEAR 2030
THERE'LL BE COMPUTERS THAT CAN CARRY OUT
THE SAME NUMBER OF FUNCTIONS AS AN ACTUAL HUMAN BRAIN.
SO THEORETICALLY, YOU CAN DOWNLOAD
YOUR THOUGHTS AND YOUR MEMORIES
INTO THIS COMPUTER...
AND LIVE FOREVER AS A MACHINE!
UH, SO, JANINE, YOU YOU YOU KNOW WHAT...
YOU KNOW WHAT WE'RE DOING RIGHT NOW?
YOU AND I, WE'RE WE'RE INTERFACING.
YEAH. I GOT TO GO.
BA DUM BUMP. CHSSH.