HEY, I JUST GOT MY, UH... TEACHER EVALUATIONS.
CHECK OUT WHAT THIS ONE STUDENT WROTE.
"I LOVED DR. GELLER'S CLASS.
"MIND BLOWING LECTURES.
"DR. GELLER, YOU ARE DEFINITELY
THE 'HOTTIE' OF THE PALEONTOLOGY DEPARTMENT."
AH...
"HOTTIES OF THE PALEONTOLOGY DEPARTMENT."
THERE'S A BIG SELLING CALENDAR, HUH?
WHO WROTE IT?
OH, I WISH I KNEW
BUT THE EVALUATIONS ARE ALL ANONYMOUS.
DO YOU STILL HAVE THEIR FINAL EXAMS?
YEAH.
OH. BECAUSE YOU COULD JUST MATCH
THE EVALUATION TO THE EXAM
WITH THE SAME HANDWRITING AND, BOOM
THERE'S YOUR ADMIRER.
A HOT GIRL'S AT STAKE
AND, ALL OF A SUDDEN, HE'S RAIN MAN.
HEY, WAIT A MINUTE, WAIT A MINUTE.
WHY ARE WE SO SURE THAT THIS IS A GIRL?
IT'S A GIRL.
ANYWAY, IT WOULDN'T MATTER, OKAY?
BECAUSE I'M A TEACHER, SHE'S A STUDENT.
OH, IS THAT AGAINST THE RULES?
NO, BUT IT IS FROWNED UPON.
I SEE.
BESIDES, THERE'S A BIG AGE DIFFERENCE.
WELL, THINK OF IT LIKE THIS:
WHEN YOU'RE 90...
I KNOW. WHEN I'M 90, SHE'LL BE, LIKE, 80
AND IT WON'T SEEM LIKE SUCH A BIG DIFFERENCE.
NO, THAT'S NOT WHAT I WAS GOING TO SAY AT ALL.
NO. WHAT I WAS GOING
TO SAY IS WHEN YOU'RE 90, YOU'LL STILL HAVE THE MEMORY
OF WHAT IT WAS LIKE TO BE
WITH A 20 YEAR OLD.
MONICA?
I DON'T KNOW.
OKAY.
HEY, CHANDLER, YOU KNOW THAT GIRL
YOU WENT TO COLLEGE WITH WHO BECAME A MOVIE DIRECTOR?
OH, YEAH, DANA KEYSTONE.
SHE WAS IN MY MOVEMENT CLASS.
WHAT'S A MOVEMENT CLASS?
IT'S CHANDLER'S WAY OF PRETENDING
HE DIDN'T TAKE MIME.
WELL, LISTEN, ANYWAY, SHE'S DIRECTING
THE NEW AL PACINO MOVIE.
YOU GOT TO GET ME AN AUDITION.
I DON'T KNOW, MAN.
I HAVEN'T TALKED TO HER IN, LIKE, TEN YEARS.
OH, NO, NO, NO. PLEASE, PLEASE, CHANDLER?
I WOULD OWE YOU SO MUCH.
YOU DO OWE ME SO MUCH.
YOU OWE ME $3,400...
DUDE, WHY ARE YOU CHANGING THE SUBJECT?
WILL YOU MAKE THE CALL OR WHAT?
OKAY, I'LL TRY. ALL RIGHT.
THANKS. YOU'RE THE BEST.
NOW, LISTEN
THE LAST DAY OF AUDITIONS IS THURSDAY, OKAY?
SO I GOT TO GET IN THERE BY THURSDAY, OKAY?
JUST REMEMBER THURSDAY. THURSDAY.
CAN YOU REMEMBER THURSDAY?
YEAH, SO, TUESDAY?
THURSDAY.
LOOK, IF YOU NEED HELP REMEMBERING
JUST THINK OF IT LIKE THIS:
THE THIRD DAY, ALL RIGHT?
MONDAY, ONE DAY.
TUESDAY, TWO DAY.
WEDNESDAY, WHEN? HUH? WHAT DAY?
THURSDAY!
THE THIRD DAY, OKAY?
THANK YOU.
OKAY.
HEY, MONICA...
SHE DOESN'T KNOW.
HEY, MON, I'M GOING TO CHECK MY MESSAGES.
YOU JUST THOUGHT OF THAT IN THERE?
SURE. YOU KNOW, NATURE CALLED.
SHE WANTED TO SEE WHO ELSE DID.
HELLO.
UH, RACHEL.
YOU GUYS, SOMEONE IS IN OUR APARTMENT.
CALL THE COPS!
YOU'RE ON THE PHONE!
OH, MY GOD!
WHAT?
OH, MY GOD. THANK YOU.
THAT WAS THE FIRE DEPARTMENT.
THERE WAS A FIRE AT OUR PLACE!
OH, MY GOD!
HOW BAD WAS IT?
WELL, HE DIDN'T SAY, BUT IT WAS A FIRE.
I'M GUESSING NOT VERY GOOD.
COME ON. WE GOT TO GO.
YEAH, COME ON.
WHAT ARE YOU SMILING ABOUT?
WHAT IS SO FUNNY?
THE PART I WANT TO AUDITION FOR IS A FIREMAN.
THIS IS SO MEANT TO BE!
WOW!
LOOKS LIKE YOU WERE VERY GENEROUS
WITH YOUR GRADES THIS SEMESTER.
PROFESSOR GELLER?
YEAH?
I WANTED TO SAY
HOW MUCH I ENJOYED YOUR CLASS.
OH, THANK YOU.
THANKS VERY MUCH.
OW.
UM, I'M A LITTLE EMBARRASSED
ABOUT CALLING YOU A HOTTIE ON MY EVALUATION.
THAT WAS YOU?
YEAH.
I FELT A LITTLE WEIRD ABOUT IT.
YOU'RE A TEACHER.
I'M A STUDENT
BUT WOULD YOU
MAYBE WANT TO GO OUT WITH ME SOMETIME?
OH, I DON'T THINK THAT WOULD BE THE BEST IDEA.
OH, BECAUSE I WAS THINKING... THE SEMESTER IS OVER.
YOU'RE NOT MY TEACHER ANYMORE.
WHAT TIME?
OH, YOU KNOW WHAT? FORGET IT.
I SEE YOU ALREADY GAVE ME AN "A."
GOTCHA.
I'M KIDDING! GOD!
OH.
SO, SERIOUSLY, WHAT TIME?
COMING THROUGH.
OH! COMING THROUGH.
OH, HELLO.
HI.
NO. RIGHT.
COMING THROUGH.
OKAY, WELL, IT'S NOT SO BAD.
YEAH, MOST OF THE DAMAGE
IS PRETTY MUCH CONTAINED TO THE BEDROOMS.
HEY, BUDDY. OH!
THINK I COULD BORROW YOUR UNIFORM THIS THURSDAY?
EXCUSE ME?
JOEY, HE'S WORKING.
YOU WOULD LOOK GOOD IN THAT.
HOW BAD IS IT?
OH, IT'S BAD. IT'S REALLY BAD.
THE ONLY THING THERE THAT ISN'T BURNED IS AN AX...
WHICH I DO NOT REMEMBER BUYING.
HOW'S YOUR ROOM, RACH?
EVERYTHING'S RUINED: MY BED, MY CLOTHES.
LOOK AT MY FAVORITE BLUE SWEATER.
ISN'T THAT MINE?
FINE. I'M SORRY FOR YOUR LOSS.
SO, UH, YOU'RE NOT
GOING TO BE ABLE TO LIVE HERE FOR A WHILE.
YOU LADIES HAVE A PLACE TO STAY?
OH, WOW. OKAY.
LOOK, PAL, I AM NOT IN THE MOOD
TO BE HIT ON RIGHT NOW.
BUT IF YOU GIVE ME YOUR NUMBER
I WILL CALL YOU SOME OTHER TIME.
YES. THEY CAN STAY WITH US.
HAVE YOU FIGURED OUT
WHAT STARTED THE FIRE, MR. FIREMAN?
WELL, UH, DO EITHER OF YOU SMOKE?
NO, NOT USUALLY
BUT, YEAH, I COULD USE ONE RIGHT NOW. THANKS.
NO, NO, NO. DO YOU LIGHT CANDLES, BURN INCENSE?
YES, I DO ALL THE TIME.
I LOVE THEM!
OH, MY GOD. I DID IT.
IT'S ME, IT'S ME.
I BURNED DOWN THE HOUSE! I BURNED DOWN THE HOUSE!
OKAY, PHOEBE, CALM DOWN. THERE'S NO NEED
TO PLACE BLAME, OKAY?
I WARNED HER ABOUT THOSE CANDLES.
GOD, IT'S GREAT TO CATCH UP.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HOW LONG IT'S BEEN.
HEY, CHANDLER, IS THAT...?
OH, THAT'S GREAT.
GOOD FOR YOU.
HEY, HEY, HEY, IS IT...?
OKAY, SO, YEAH, MAYBE WE CAN GET TOGETHER, UM...
CAN YOU HOLD ON FOR ONE SECOND, PLEASE?
WHAT?
WHEN YOU'RE OFF THE PHONE, YOU WANT TO GET A PIZZA?
HI. I'M BACK.
YEAH, THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
OKAY, WELL, WE'LL DO IT THEN.
OKAY, BYE.
HEY, LISTEN, SO WHEN'S MY AUDITION?
I MEAN, I KNOW IT'S THURSDAY
BUT WHAT TIME?
HEY. HI.
WE DIDN'T GET TO THE AUDITION.
I'LL TAKE HER TO COFFEE AND THEN WE'LL DO IT THEN.
WOW. SO, NOW YOU'RE GOING
ON A DATE WITH THIS GIRL?
HONEY, IT IS NOT A DATE.
I HAVEN'T TALKED TO HER IN TEN YEARS.
YOU CAN'T CALL UP SOMEBODY
YOU HAVEN'T TALKED TO IN TEN YEARS
AND ASK THEM FOR A FAVOR.
THERE ARE RULES.
YOU GOT TO PUT IN SOME TIME.
YOU'RE RIGHT. I'M SORRY.
IT'S NOT LIKE YOU'RE, YOU KNOW
GOING OUT WITH AN EX GIRLFRIEND.
NO. WE ONLY WENT OUT ONCE.
YOU DATED HER?!
NOT ONCE.
GREAT. WELL, WHY DON'T I JUST GO OUT WITH AN EX BOYFRIEND
YOU KNOW, AND DO JOEY A FAVOR?
HEY, YOU WANT TO DO JOEY A FAVOR?
MAYBE YOU GO OUT WITH JOEY.
OH, THAT'S GREAT.
MY FRIEND JOEY'S IN THE MOVIE BUSINESS.
MM, YOU KNOW WHO I RAN INTO FROM SCHOOL?
HOWIE.
MY FRIEND'S NAME IS JOEY.
APPARENTLY, HOWIE'S EDITING NOW.
YEAH. HE CALLS ME UP AND ASKS ME
IF HE CAN EDIT MY NEW MOVIE.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT?
YOU KNOW, I HAVEN'T SPOKEN TO HIM
IN WHAT, TEN YEARS, AND HE ASKS ME FOR A FAVOR?
YEAH, I'VE ALWAYS HATED THAT HOWIE.
NO, NO "HOW YOU DOING?"
MAN, I MEAN, NOT EVEN A CUP OF COFFEE FIRST.
THE NERVE, HUH?
YEAH.
REFILL?
NOW, THIS IS LAST MINUTE
SO I WANT TO APOLOGIZE FOR THE MESS, OKAY?
WHO CARES?
OH, MY GOD.
SURE DIDN'T LOOK THIS WAY
WHEN I LIVED HERE.
I KNOW!
NOW, LOOK
THERE'S ONLY ONE PROBLEM.
THERE'S ONLY ROOM FOR ONE
SO I GUESS ONE OF YOU WILL HAVE TO STAY AT JOEY'S.
WELL, SINCE THE FIRE WAS KIND OF MY FAULT
I GUESS YOU SHOULD GET TO STAY HERE.
HEY, HEY, HEY, NOW, THIS WAS
NO ONE'S FAULT, PHEEBS, OKAY?
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
IT WAS MY FAULT, SO YOU SHOULD GET THE NICE ROOM.
OKAY!
WHOO WHOO!
RACH, YOU'RE THE FIRST GUEST
AT HOTEL MONICA.
HOTEL MONICA!
JUST TELL ME HOW
YOU LIKE YOUR EGGS IN THE MORNING.
I THOUGHT I WOULD BRING THEM TO YOU, YOU KNOW, IN BED.
WELL, YOU'VE BEEN THROUGH SO MUCH.
I HAVE.
THIS RIGHT HERE IS WHERE I KEEP THE PIZZA
AND, UH, THAT'S WHERE THE NAPKIN IS.
WHAT'S THAT SMELL?
I KNOW.
OH, PLEASE.
IT WAS SUCH A BIG CLASS.
YOU NEVER EVEN NOTICED ME.
WHAT? OF COURSE, I DID.
YOU, UH, YOU SAT NEXT TO SLEEPY SLEEPERSON.
WHO?
OH, UH, I HAD TROUBLE
REMEMBERING EVERYONE'S NAME
SO I KIND OF CAME UP WITH NICKNAMES.
LIKE THE GUY ON THE OTHER SIDE OF YOU WAS
UH, SMELLY VON BROWN SHIRT.
OH, YEAH.
SO, UH, DID YOU HAVE A NICKNAME FOR ME?
OH, NO, NO.
YES, YOU DID.
WHAT WAS IT?
UM, IT'S CUTIE McPRETTY.
OH, THAT'S SO SWEET.
LISTEN, I GOT TO TELL YOU
I'M HAVING A GREAT TIME.
YOU KNOW HOW BEFORE YOU SAID
IT MIGHT BE WEIRD
THE WHOLE STUDENT TEACHER THING?
AND TO BE FRANK
I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE, TOO, BUT IT'S NOT.
I MEAN, IT'S NOT AT ALL.
DR. GELLER!
BURT!
SO, DID YOU SLEEP WELL LAST NIGHT?
I DID. YEAH?
MONICA WAS SO SWEET.
SHE LEFT A LITTLE MINT ON MY PILLOW.
YOU KNOW WHAT JOEY LEFT ON MY PILLOW?
WHAT?
GUM.
WELL, WE DETERMINED THE CAUSE OF THE FIRE.
YEAH, I KNOW, I KNOW.
IT WAS MY CANDLE, MY CANDLE.
NO. THERE WAS AN APPLIANCE LEFT ON IN THE BATHROOM.
IT LOOKS LIKE A CURLING IRON.
I DON'T USE A CURLING IRON.
WELL, SOMEONE DOES.
DON'T LOOK AT ME.
MY HAIR'S STRAIGHT. STRAIGHT, STRAIGHT, STRAIGHT.
COULD HAVE BEEN A HAIR STRAIGHTENER.
OH.
THIS IS WHERE I KEEP THE PIZZA
AND... HEY, WHERE'D THE NAPKIN GO?
WHAT IS THAT?
IS THAT OLD SHRIMP?
I THINK IT IS!
NOW, THERE YOU GO.
I WOULDN'T WANT MY BEST GUEST TO STRAIN HER EYES.
THANKS, MONICA.
DOES THAT SMELL BOTHER YOU?
THE SMELL FROM JOEY'S?
NO. I CAN HARDLY SMELL IT OVER HERE.
WELL, YOU LET ME KNOW IF YOU CAN.
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, I CAN BAKE A PIE TO COVER IT.
I CAN SMELL IT A LITTLE.
BAKE THE PIE.
OKAY.
HELLO.
OH, YES. ONE MINUTE, PLEASE.
IT'S FOR YOU. IT'S THE FIRE INSPECTOR.
OH.
HELLO.
YEAH, THIS IS PHOEBE.
REALLY?
YEAH.
SO, IT TURNS OUT
THAT IT WASN'T THE HAIR STRAIGHTENER
THAT STARTED THE FIRE.
NO, NO. IT WAS THE CANDLES.
YEAH.
IT'S VERY NOT GOOD
LEAVING CANDLES UNATTENDED.
IN FACT, ONE OF THE FIRST THINGS
THEY TEACH YOU IN FIRE SCHOOL
IS, UH...
UH, OKAY.
WELL, I HAVE TO GO NOW.
WE HAD SUCH A GREAT TIME.
SHE'S INCREDIBLE.
I THOUGHT THE AGE DIFFERENCE MIGHT BE A PROBLEM
BUT IT WASN'T.
IT WASN'T AT ALL.
ELIZABETH IS VERY MATURE FOR HER AGE.
A CONCEPT LOST ON SOME PEOPLE.
SO, IT'S OKAY TO DATE A STUDENT?
WELL, NOT REALLY.
I MEAN, TECHNICALLY
IT'S NOT AGAINST THE RULES OR ANYTHING
BUT IT IS FROWNED UPON.
ESPECIALLY BY THAT PROFESSOR
WE RAN INTO LAST NIGHT--
JUDGEY VON HOLIER THAN THOU.
WELL, ROSS, YOU JUST BE CAREFUL, OKAY?
YOU DON'T WANT TO GET A REPUTATION
AS, YOU KNOW, PROFESSOR McNAILS HIS STUDENTS.
YEAH.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
WELL, ROSS, IT SEEMS PRETTY CLEAR.
I MEAN, WHAT'S MORE IMPORTANT--
WHAT PEOPLE THINK OR HOW YOU FEEL?
ROSS, YOU GOT TO FOLLOW YOUR HEART.
JOEY, THAT IS SO SWEET.
HEY.
HEY, HEY, SO, HOW'D IT GO WITH DANA?
ANY REASON I SHOULD LEAVE A BLOCK OF TIME OPEN--
SAY, THURSDAY?
I COULDN'T DO IT.
YOU COULDN'T DO IT?
RELAX. I JUST NEED MORE TIME.
WE'RE GOING TO DINNER TONIGHT.
WHAT? YOU'RE GOING OUT WITH HER AGAIN?
GOING OUT WITH WHO?
DANA KEYSTONE FROM COLLEGE.
OH, YEAH.
WASN'T SHE...?
NO, THAT WAS DANA KAPLAN.
OH, YEAH.
JOEY, YOU DIDN'T EVEN KNOW HER.
AW, WHATEVER.
GREAT STORY AGAIN.
THE YARNS THAT YOU WEAVE...
WHOO HOO.
YOU KNOW, I SHOULD GET GOING.
OH, NO, NO.
STAY, STAY, BECAUSE YOU SHOULD...
YOU SHOULD STAY.
WOW.
OH, I AM
REALLY FLATTERED
BUT I JUST... I DON'T FEEL THAT WAY ABOUT YOU.
OH, NO, NO, NO. THAT'S NOT... NO, NO, NO.
I'M SORRY, CHANDLER.
YOU KNOW, YOU ARE SUCH A SWEET GUY
AND I DON'T WANT TO HURT YOU.
OH, I WISH THERE WAS SOMETHING
I COULD DO TO MAKE YOU FEEL BETTER.
NO, NO...
REALLY?
OF COURSE.
WELL, IT JUST HURTS SO BAD.
I, UH...
OH, I'M SORRY.
WELL, MAYBE THERE IS ONE THING YOU CAN DO.
WHAT? ANYTHING. ANYTHING.
WELL, I MEAN, THIS IS
JUST OFF THE TOP OF MY HEAD NOW.
UM, BUT I HAVE THIS FRIEND--
UH, THIS ACTOR FRIEND--
AND HE WOULD KILL ME IF HE KNEW THAT I WAS DOING THIS.
UM, BUT, UM...
WOULD IT BE POSSIBLE FOR HIM TO GET AN AUDITION
FOR YOUR MOVIE
SAY, ON THURSDAY?
ABSOLUTELY.
BUT YOU'D REALLY FEEL BETTER
ABOUT ME REJECTING YOU IF YOUR ACTOR FRIEND
CAN AUDITION FOR MY MOVIE?
THE HEART WANTS WHAT IT WANTS.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
HEY, HOW'S IT GOING?
WELL, NOT MUCH HAS CHANGED IN THE LAST FIVE MINUTES.
YES, IT HAS.
I MADE COOKIES.
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'M STILL FULL FROM YOUR HOMEMADE POTATO CHIPS.
BUT YOU SHOULD EAT THEM NOW
BECAUSE THEY'RE HOT FROM THE OVEN.
OKAY.
OH, BUT NOT IN HERE.
YOU CAN'T EAT THEM IN BED, REMEMBER?
NO CRUMBIES.
OKAY.
I'LL BE OUT IN A SECOND.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
THIS DOESN'T LOCK, DOES IT?
OH, JOEY, I'M SORRY.
OH, THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
NO, BUT LOOK.
OH, THAT'S GOING TO LEAVE A STAIN.
RACH, HEY, IT'S FINE.
YOU'RE AT JOEY'S.
REALLY?
YEAH.
LOOK.
I'VE NEVER LIVED LIKE THIS BEFORE.
I KNOW.
WELL, DON'T WASTE IT. IT'S STILL FOOD.
GEEZ.
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO NOW, HUH?
YOU WANT TO GO GET A DRINK?
UH, I CAN'T.
YOU HAVE
SOME STUDYING TO DO?
NO, I HAVE SOME TURNING 21 TO DO.
YOU KNOW, I REMEMBER WHEN I WAS IN COLLEGE
WE USED TO...
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
NOTHING.
I'M JUST... I'M SO COMFORTABLE WITH YOU.
DO YOU NOT WANT TO BE SEEN WITH ME?
OF COURSE, I DO.
ARE THEY GONE?
UH, NO, THEY'RE STILL HERE
BUT I THINK I'M ABOUT TO LEAVE.
WHAT?
NO, NO, WAIT.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
THIS IS STUPID.
WHO CARES WHAT PEOPLE THINK?
I MEAN, WE LIKE EACH OTHER, RIGHT?
THERE'S NOTHING WRONG WITH THAT.
COME ON.
BURT.
LYDIA.
MEL.
THIS IS ELIZABETH.
HI.
AREN'T YOU IN MY POPULAR CULTURE CLASS?
THAT'S RIGHT, LYDIA.
ELIZABETH HERE IS A STUDENT
AND, UH, WE'RE DATING.
AND YOU MAY FROWN UPON THAT
BUT WE'RE NOT GOING TO HIDE IT ANYMORE.
YOU ARE SO FIRED.
WHAT?
THEY'RE GOING TO FIRE YOU.
YOU CAN'T DATE A STUDENT.
IT'S AGAINST THE RULES.
REALLY?
IT'S NOT JUST FROWNED UPON?
I LOVE IT AT JOEY'S!
HERE YOU GO.
NICE.
THANKS.
SO, YOU BUSY THURSDAY?
OH, VERY FUNNY.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU REMEMBER
BUT MY AUDITION WAS SUPPOSED TO BE THURSDAY.
YOU GOT ME THE AUDITION?
LET'S HUG IT UP!
OKAY. OKAY.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO TO ME
IF YOU GET THE PART?
HEY.
LISTEN, UM...
YEAH, OKAY, I NEED TO TALK TO YOU.
NOW, I KNOW THAT THEY SAID
THAT THE, UM, THE HAIR STRAIGHTENER
STARTED THE FIRE
BUT I THINK I'M PARTLY AT FAULT.
YOU SEE, I DIDN'T TELL YOU
BUT, UM, BUT, UH...
I HAD RECENTLY REFILLED THE TISSUES.
AND, SO, LET'S FACE IT, THAT'S JUST KINDLING.
SO, YOU KNOW, I THINK IT'S BETTER
THAT I STAY AT JOEY'S.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
PHOEBE, THIS WAS MY FAULT.
AND BESIDES, YOU KNOW WHAT, I'M FINE HERE.
OKAY.
CHANDLER, MONICA IS LOOKING FOR YOU.
REALLY?
YEAH. SHE SAID SOMETHING ABOUT CRUMBIES.
NO, NO, NO. I WAS SO CAREFUL.
OKAY, YOU HAVE TO SWITCH WITH ME.
MONICA IS DRIVING ME CRAZY.
THAT'S RIGHT.
ALL THE LADIES
WANT TO STAY AT JOEY'S.
NO, NO.
PHOEBE, I DON'T WANT TO SWITCH.
PLEASE, COME ON.
I CAN THROW WET PAPER TOWELS HERE.
NO, BUT AT MONICA'S, YOU CAN EAT COOKIES
OVER THE SINK.
I KNOW.
I'M SORRY.
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
THIS LOOKS LIKE SO MUCH FUN.
YEAH.
GOD, WHAT A MESS.
WOW. IT ACTUALLY IS IN THE HANDBOOK.
I CAN'T DATE YOU OR HAVE A HOT PLATE IN MY OFFICE.
OH, I CAN'T BELIEVE
WE HAVE TO STOP SEEING EACH OTHER.
FOR WHAT IT'S WORTH
I DID APPRECIATE YOU STANDING UP FOR ME.
IT FELT REALLY NICE.
KIND OF MADE ME LIKE YOU EVEN MORE.
I KNOW, I KNOW.
I REALLY LIKE YOU, TOO.
BUT WE CAN'T DATE.
IT'S AGAINST THE RULES.
IT'S FORBIDDEN.
WOW.
WHAT?
JUST HEARING YOU
DESCRIBE IT AS FORBIDDEN--
IT'S REALLY HOT.
REALLY?
YEAH.
WELL... I I DON'T CARE HOW HOT IT IS--
IT'S.... IT'S WRONG.
STOP IT.
NO, NO.
IT'S WRONG.
IT'S IT'S, IT'S NAUGHTY.
IT'S...
TABOO.
SHUT THE BOOK.
LET'S ALSO GET A HOT PLATE.
HEY. HEY.
SO?
SO...?
IT'S THURSDAY.
HOW WAS THE AUDITION?
MONDAY, ONE DAY...
TUESDAY, TWO DAY...
WEDNESDAY...
THURSDAY...
OH!