I CANNOT BELIEVE THAT YOU DIDN'T TELL ME
WE ARE STILL MARRIED.
LOOK, I WAS GOING TO TELL YOU.
WHEN? AFTER THE BIRTH OF OUR FIRST SECRET CHILD?
ROSS DIDN't
GET THE ANNULMENT.
WE ARE STILL MARRIED.
WHAT?
OH, MY GOD!
ROSS?
OKAY, MAYBE IT WASN'T MY BEST DECISION
BUT I JUST COULDN'T FACE ANOTHER FAILED MARRIAGE.
LET ME JUST JUMP IN AND ASK.
AT WHAT POINT DID YOU THINK
THIS WAS A SUCCESSFUL MARRIAGE?
RACH, COME ON.
IF YOU THINK ABOUT IT, IT'S ACTUALLY KIND OF FUNNY.
MAYBE IT'S BEST NOT TO THINK ABOUT IT.
THIS IS INEXCUSABLE.
I AM SHOCKED TO MY VERY CORE.
PHOEBE, I TOLD HER YOU ALREADY KNEW.
ANOTHER LIE.
YOU HAVE A SICKNESS.
ROSS, JUST FOR MY OWN PEACE OF MIND
YOU'RE NOT MARRIED
TO ANY MORE OF US, ARE YOU?
LOOK, RACH, I I WAS GOING TO TELL YOU.
I JUST WANTED TO DO IT, UM, YOU KNOW, MY OWN WAY.
AH, YES. SILENTLY, WITH NO WORDS.
HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY...
HEY!
HEY.
LOOK, IN ROSS' DEFENSE, OKAY...
YO, HEY, SOMEONE LEFT THEIR KEYS.
OOH! TO A PORSCHE, HUH?
HEY, GUNTHER, THESE YOURS?
YEAH, THAT'S WHAT I DRIVE.
I MAKE FOUR BUCKS AN HOUR.
I SAVED UP FOR 350 YEARS.
NUH UH...
HEY, DID ANYBODY LOSE THEIR KEYS?
JOEY, WHY DON'T YOU PUT THEM
IN THE LOST AND FOUND?
THERE'S A LOST AND FOUND?
MY SHOE!
YOU LEFT A SHOE HERE?
WELL, I DIDN'T REALIZE TILL I GOT HOME.
I WASN'T GOING TO WALK ALL THE WAY
BACK DOWN HERE WITH ONE SHOE.
I'M GOING TO GO FIND THAT GUY'S CAR
AND LEAVE A NOTE ON THE WINDSHIELD.
WHEN HE COMES BACK FOR HIS KEYS
I'LL BE SURE TO GIVE HIM YOUR SHOE.
GREAT. THANKS.
OH, GOOD, GOOD.
YOU GUYS ARE HERE.
LISTEN.
HOW WOULD YOU LIKE TO SPEND TOMORROW
TAKING CARE OF THREE INCREDIBLY CUTE LITTLE PUPPIES?
MY GOD! WHAT A FUN DAY.
THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
OKAY. WELL, I'LL BRING THEM BY TOMORROW MORNING.
OKAY, AND, UM... BY THE WAY, THEY'RE NOT ACTUALLY PUPPIES.
THEY'RE FRANK AND ALICE'S TRIPLETS.
OKAY, SEE YA.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA! WHAT?
PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE, OH, PLEASE.
FRANK AND ALICE ASKED ME
TO BABY SIT THE TRIPLETS, AND I'M NERVOUS
CAUSE I'VE NEVER DONE THAT BEFORE BY MYSELF.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT. WE'LL ABSOLUTELY DO IT.
YEAH, I'M GOING TO PASS
BECAUSE I WAS KIND OF IFFY WHEN IT WAS PUPPIES.
COME ON, CHANDLER, COME ON.
IT WILL GIVE US GREAT PRACTICE FOR WHEN...
PEOPLE WITH BABIES COME TO VISIT.
IT'S THE WRONG CAR!
SO, I STILL HAVE BOXES HERE
I STILL HAVE BOXES AT ROSS'
AND I HAVE NOWHERE TO LIVE.
WOW, I CAN SO EASILY FREAK OUT RIGHT NOW.
OKAY, WHAT ABOUT ME?
I JUST FOUND OUT DENISE IS LEAVING TOWN FOR A WHILE.
I DON'T HAVE A ROOMMATE.
WELL, MAYBE...
MAYBE I CAN BE YOUR ROOMMATE, PHEEBS.
MAYBE YOU COULD BE MY ROOMMATE.
WELL, THERE'S AN IDEA.
YEAH!
THAT WOULD BE GREAT!
WAIT. HOW LONG IS DENISE GONE FOR?
UM... SHE SAID SHE'D BE BACK DECEMBER 26.
OH, DECEMBER 26.
HA! MAYBE SHE'S SANTA CLAUS.
OH, LOOK WHO IT IS.
MY HUSBAND.
THE APPLE OF MY EYE.
OKAY, I GOT US A COURT DATE
FOR TOMORROW AT 2:00
AND I PICKED UP ALL THE FORMS.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF EVERYTHING.
WELL, SURE.
IF YOU SAY YOU'RE GOING TO TAKE CARE OF EVERYTHING
I HAVE NO REASON TO DOUBT YOU.
GIVE ME THOSE FORMS.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, I'M GOING TO DO THIS MY WAY
AND I DON'T WANT TO HEAR A PEEP OUT OF YOU.
OKAY, RACH, BUT...
AH! YOU'RE PEEPING.
ROSS, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I JUST GOT...
WHY? WHY DID YOU DO THIS?
LOOK, I TOLD YOU I...
I DON'T WANT TO HEAR THREE FAILED MARRIAGES.
LOOK, IF YOU'D HAD TWO FAILED MARRIAGES
YOU'D UNDERSTAND.
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT?
THANKS TO YOU
I'M HALFWAY THERE.
OH! OH, I  AM SO MAD, ROSS.
I DON'T THINK I'VE EVER BEEN THIS ANGRY.
WHAT ABOUT THE TIME I SAID WE WERE ON A BREAK?
OH!
HO, HO, HO!
NICE CAR.
YEAH, IT'S, UH, IT'S NOT MINE.
I LOVE YOUR CAR.
YEAH, IT'S... MINE.
I BET IT'S FAST.
ME, TOO. YEAH.
AND COMFORTABLE.
DO YOU, UH, DO YOU LIKE LEATHER SEATS?
YEAH.
IT'S GOT THEM
PHEEB, HOW'S IT GOING?
I'M DOING OKAY.
I THINK IT'S GOING WELL.
DO YOU THINK THEY'RE HAVING FUN? AM I TALKING TOO FAST?
NO. SOUND LIKE ME.
PHEEBS, IT'S GOING GREAT.
LOOK AT CHANDLER WITH LITTLE BABY GIRL CHANDLER.
LITTLE BABY GIRL CHANDLER?
WHERE HAVE I HEARD THAT BEFORE?
OH, RIGHT-- COACH RUBIN.
OOH!
YOU KNOW WHAT, PHEEBS?
WHEN YOU'RE DONE OVER THERE
WE'VE GOT A KIND OF SITUATION OVER HERE, TOO.
UH UH. NO.
WE ARE ALL RESPONSIBLE FOR OUR OWN BABIES.
SEE, THAT'S WHERE I THINK THAT YOU'RE WRONG.
WE'VE BEEN PLAYING THESE BABIES MAN TO MAN.
WE SHOULD REALLY BE PLAYING A ZONE DEFENSE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I JUST THINK
THINGS WILL GO A LOT SMOOTHER
IF WE EACH HAVE OUR OWN ZONE.
PHOEBE, YOU CAN BE IN CHARGE OF WIPING.
AND, YOU KNOW, MON
YOU CAN BE IN CHARGE OF DIAPERING.
AND I CAN BE IN CHARGE OF LOOKING HOW CUTE THEY ARE
WHEN THEY PUT THEIR HANDS AROUND...
THAT SOUNDS REALLY GREAT.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD BE IN CHARGE OF WIPING.
OKAY, I'M A ROOKIE.
I SHOULD NOT BE IN THE END ZONE.
THIS IS SO GREAT.
THIS IS EXACTLY HOW WE SET THE PLATES AT THE RESTAURANT.
OH, YEAH?
WELL, THIS IS NOT WHAT I ORDERED.
HEY, GUYS. HI. HEY.
HEY, BABIES.
OH, I'M HAVING
THE BEST MORNING.
THAT PORSCHE I'VE GOT THE KEYS TO--
IT'S STILL THERE.
SHOCKING, SINCE YOU STILL HAVE THE KEYS.
YOU SHOULD SEE THE TREATMENT I GET WHEN I'M WITH THAT CAR.
PEOPLE ARE FRIENDLY, THEY WANT TO TALK
AND NOT JUST ABOUT THE CAR.
ONE GUY GAVE ME ADVICE ABOUT MY EQUITY INVESTMENTS.
WHAT EQUITY INVESTMENTS?
THE ONES THAT GOT ME THE PORSCHE.
WILL YOU KEEP UP?
BUT I FIGURED IF PEOPLE KEEP SEEING ME JUST STANDING THERE
THEY'RE GOING TO START TO THINK I DON'T OWN IT
SO, I FIGURED I'LL WASH IT, RIGHT?
MONICA, YOU GOT A BUCKET AND SOME SOAP I CAN BORROW?
OH, YEAH.
I GOT SOAP AND SPONGES AND RAGS
AND CARNUBA WAX AND POLISHING COMPOUND.
YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE A CAR.
I KNOW, BUT ONE TIME THERE WAS THIS REALLY DIRTY CAR
PARKED IN FRONT OF THE BUILDING, SO I WASHED IT.
AND?
AND SIX OTHERS.
THERE YOU ARE.
YEAH, SHE TOPS OUT AT 130.
WOW.
AND THAT'S JUST
IN THE CITY.
I GET HER UP TO 160 WHEN I TAKE HER UPSTATE.
REALLY?
YOU GOT A PLACE UPSTATE?
SURE.
ER. WELL, I'LL SEE YOU LAT
OKAY. TAKE IT EASY.
HEY, THAT'S MY CAR.
REALLY? OH. UH...
JUST GIVE ME FIVE MORE MINUTES, WILL YOU?
WHAT... WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
OH, I... I FOUND THE KEYS
AND NOW I'M JUST POLISHING HER UP.
BUT IT'S MY CAR.
YEAH, BUT IT'S MY WAX.
LISTEN, I DON'T COME TO THE CITY MUCH
AND I DON'T KNOW IF YOU'RE CRAZY
OR IF THIS IS SOME KIND OF STREET THEATER...
BUT COULD
I HAVE MY KEYS?
SURE. HERE.
I'LL SAVE YOU A PARKING SPOT.
I'M NOT COMING BACK.
WHY NOT?
I LIVE UPSTATE.
YEAH, SO DID I.
I DON'T KNOW WHY I WAS SO NERVOUS ABOUT THIS.
AND I DON'T KNOW WHY FRANK AND ALICE ARE ALWAYS COMPLAINING.
THIS IS SO EASY.
YEAH, TWO HOURS, A LIFETIME-- THAT'S THE SAME.
CHECK IT OUT. CHECK IT OUT.
WHEN THE BABIES WAKE UP, THEY CAN MEET KROG.
CHANDLER, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
THAT THING COULD PUT SOMEONE'S EYE OUT.
HE CAN DO MORE THAN THAT.
HE CAN DESTROY THE UNIVERSE.
NO. CHANDLER, THEY COULD SWALLOW ONE OF THOSE LITTLE PARTS.
AND ALSO, LOOK AT HIS SMOOTH AREA--
THAT'S JUST GOING TO MESS THEM UP.
IT'S JUST NOT AN APPROPRIATE TOY FOR ONE YEAR OLDS.
OR 30 YEAR OLDS.
THEY'RE NOT GOING TO SWALLOW ANYTHING.
YOU GUYS ARE BEING WAY TOO OVER PROTECTIVE.
WHEN I WAS A KID, MY MOM USED TO JUST THROW ME
INTO A PILE OF BROKEN GLASS.
WHAT?
GLASS, SAND, WHATEVER.
OH, LOOK AT LITTLE LESLIE STRETCHING IN HER SLEEP.
OH, IT'S SO CUTE.
I WONDER WHAT AGE IT IS THAT YOU STOP BEING ABLE
TO PUT BOTH LEGS BEHIND YOUR HEAD?
OH, I CAN STILL DO THAT.
HOW ARE YOU  STILL SINGLE?
ALL RIGHT.
I'VE THOUGHT ABOUT IT AND MAYBE YOU'RE RIGHT.
MAYBE KROG IS NOT A SAFE TOY.
GOOD. WHAT MADE YOU CHANGE YOUR MIND?
I SWALLOWED HIS SONIC BLASTER GUN.
WHAT?
HOW DID THAT HAPPEN?
WELL, I WAS TRYING TO PROVE THAT I WAS RIGHT.
YOU KNOW, AND
IT TURNS OUT I WAS WRONG
AND... NOW IT'S LODGED IN MY THROAT.
DAMN IT. YOU KNOW, THIS WHOLE TIME
WE WERE CONCENTRATING ON THE BABIES
AND NO ONE WAS WATCHING CHANDLER.
OKAY, YOU TWO ARE ASKING THE COURT FOR AN ANNULMENT?
YES, YOUR HONOR
AND HERE ARE OUR FORMS, ALL FILLED OUT.
SO, BASED  ON YOUR PETITION
YOU ARE SEEKING AN ANNULMENT ON THE GROUNDS
THAT MR. GELLER IS MENTALLY UNSTABLE?
FINE. I'M MENTALLY UNSTABLE.
AND BASED ON THE FACT THAT MR. GELLER
IS AN INTRAVENOUS DRUG USER?
WHAT?
UH, YES, HEROIN AND CRACK.
CRACK ISN'T EVEN AN INTRAVENOUS DRUG.
WELL, YOU WOULD KNOW.
NOW, IT ALSO SAYS HERE THAT YOU, UM
LIED ABOUT YOUR SEXUAL PREFERENCE BEFORE MARRIAGE.
OH, COME ON.
ROSS, PLEASE. I FOUND THE MAGAZINES.
AND FINALLY, THAT YOU WERE UNABLE
TO CONSUMMATE THE MARRIAGE.
WELL, THAT MAKES SENSE
SINCE YOU'RE GAY AND ADDICTED TO HEROIN.
OKAY, YOU KNOW, I'M SORRY...
THIS IS INSANE.
I'M NOT ADDICTED TO HEROIN.
I'M NOT GAY AND THERE IS NO PROBLEM
WITH MY ABILITY TO CONSUMMATE ANYTHING.
LOOK, I'LL CONSUMMATE THIS MARRIAGE RIGHT HERE, RIGHT NOW.
THAT WON'T BE NECESSARY.
AND WHEN WE WERE DATING, WE CONSUMMATED LIKE BUNNIES.
AH!
NOW, IF YOU TWO WERE INVOLVED IN A SERIOUS RELATIONSHIP
THAT REALLY CREATES A PROBLEM.
YOUR HONOR, REST ASSURED
THAT RELATIONSHIP ENDED TWO YEARS AGO
AND CAN YOU PLEASE STRIKE "CONSUMMATED LIKE BUNNIES"
FROM THE RECORD?
IS THERE ANYTHING IN THIS RECORD
THAT IS ACTUALLY TRUE?
WELL, YES, WE GOT MARRIED IN VEGAS
AND, UH... THE NAMES, I THINK.
THAT'S NOT THE WAY THE LEGAL SYSTEM WORKS.
THIS PROCESS IS BASED ON AN OBJECTIVE REVIEW
OF THE FACTS, NOT OF THE LIES.
OBJECTION!
IT DOESN'T WORK LIKE THAT EITHER.
OVERRULED.
OH, STOP IT.
WELL, BASED ON WHAT I'VE HEARD
YOU TWO CERTAINLY DON'T QUALIFY FOR AN ANNULMENT.
IF YOU DON'T WANT TO BE TOGETHER
YOU'LL HAVE TO FILE FOR DIVORCE.
THAT'S GREAT. YOU HAPPY NOW?
LOOK WHAT YOU DID WITH YOUR FUNNY, FUNNY FORM.
WHAT? ME?
WHAT ABOUT YOU
AND YOUR "CONSUMMATED LIKE BUNNIES" NONSENSE?
IT WAS...
WHAT ARE YOU TYPING THAT FOR?
SHE ALREADY SAID WE DON'T GET THE ANNULMENT.
DON'T TYPE THAT.
STOP TYPING.
HEY. STOP TYPING.
STOP TYPING! STOP TYPING!
OKAY. OKAY. DO YOU SEE?
DO YOU SEE WHAT YOU'RE KEEPING ME MARRIED TO?
YOU NEED TO GET OUT OF MY CHAMBERS.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, LADY, HERE IS THE DEAL:
I CAME HERE FOR AN ANNULMENT
AND I AM NOT LEAVING H ERE UNTIL I GET ONE.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO SPEND THE NIGHT IN JAIL?
OKAY, THANK YOU FOR YOUR TIME.
SO THAT PORSCHE GUY TOOK HIS CAR BACK.
BUT YOU FOUND THE KEYS TO HIS CLOTHES?
NO. I JUST, UH...
I JUST LOVE THE WAY IT FEELS
WHEN EVERYBODY THINKS I OWN A PORSCHE.
AND PEOPLE WILL THINK YOU OWN A PORSCHE
BECAUSE YOU'RE WEARING THE CLOTHES?
OF COURSE.
ONLY AN IDIOT WOULD WEAR THIS STUFF
IF HE DIDN'T HAVE THE CAR.
THAT IS TRUE.
YEAH, BUT ONLY A GENIUS WOULD SWALLOW A SONIC BLASTER GUN.
OH, I'VE BEEN THERE.
WELL, I AM GOING TO GO DRIVE MY PORSCHE.
JOEY, YOU KNOW YOU DON'T ACTUALLY HAVE ONE.
COME ON. WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'M IN CHARACTER.
WILL YOU TALK TO HER?
AH, I THINK IT JUST MOVED.
IT'S REALLY POKING ME.
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S IT.
WE'RE GOING TO THE EMERGENCY ROOM.
WHAT? NO, YOU CAN'T LEAVE ME HERE WITH THEM.
WE'RE BABY SITTING.
THE BABIES ARE ASLEEP.
I'M SURE YOU'LL BE OKAY ON YOUR OWN FOR A WHILE.
BUT YOU CAN'T LEAVE ME WITH THEM.
WE'RE A TEAM. WE'RE PLAYING A ZONE.
THEY'RE GOING TO TRIPLE TEAM ME.
HE'S GOT SOMETHING PLASTIC LODGED INTO HIS THROAT.
WE'VE GOT TO GO TO THE HOSPITAL.
BUT, NO, BECAUSE A DOCTOR WON'T BE ABLE TO HELP HIM.
IT'S JUST GOING TO, YOU KNOW
NATURALLY PASS THROUGH HIS SYSTEM IN, LIKE, SEVEN YEARS.
I THINK THAT'S GUM.
I'M PRETTY SURE IT'S GUN.
OKAY, LISTEN, THIS REALLY HURTS. LET'S GO.
BUT NO, A REAL MAN WOULDN'T JUST RUN TO THE HOSPITAL.
NO... WHAT WOULD KROG DO?
OH, WHY ISN'T THAT VALET BACK WITH MY PORSCHE?
MAYBE BECAUSE YOU'VE GOT THE KEYS.
PORSCHE.
THAT WAS TOTALLY YOUR FAULT.
MY FAULT?
YOU THREATENED THE JUDGE.
WELL, YOU RIPPED THE PAPER
OUT OF THE COURT REPORTER'S MACHINE.
THAT WAS THE ONLY WAY I COULD GET HIM TO STOP TYPING!
OH.
HI. HOW ARE THE GELLERS?
DON'T CALL US THAT.
THE JUDGE WOULDN'T LET US GET AN ANNULMENT.
NOW WE GOT TO GET A DIVORCE!
DID A PORSCHE THROW UP ON YOU?
HEY, THAT'S PORSCH AH!
LOOK AT ME TAKING CARE OF YOU WITH NO PROBLEM, HUH?
YOU GUYS FEEL SAFE, RIGHT?
OKAY, I'M GOING TO TAKE THAT SPIT BUBBLE AS A "YEAH, I DO."
OKAY, LET'S GET RID OF THIS DIRTY DIAPER, LESLIE.
I'LL SET YOU UP WITH A NICE CLEAN ONE.
OKAY, I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO SCARE YOU.
I JUST HAVE TO CLEAN THAT UP, OKAY?
BECAUSE, LET'S FACE IT, WE'RE AT MONICA'S.
OKAY. I BROKE IT.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, THAT'S JUST THE WAY THINGS GO.
OKAY. GOOD.
WHY ARE THERE ONLY TWO OF YOU?
WHERE'S LESLIE?
WELL, YOU CAN'T ANSWER.
LESLIE, WHERE ARE YOU, LESLIE?
LESLIE, NOW WOULD BE A GOOD TIME FOR YOUR FIRST WORDS.
WELL, LOOK AT YOU.
HEY...
YOU ARE A LITTLE BIT MISCHIEVOUS.
MY GOSH.
OH, YOU'RE A LOT MISCHIEVOUS.
WELL, IT'LL DRY.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO PLAY.
YOU SIT WITH YOUR BROTHER AND SISTER NOW
WHO AREN'T THERE.
HI.
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
WELL, LET'S JUST SAY THAT KROG
WILL BE FULLY EQUIPPED
TO DESTROY THE UNIVERSE AGAIN IN 12 TO 14 HOURS.
OKAY.
SO, I TOTALLY TOOK CARE OF THE BABIES ALL BY MYSELF.
I FED THEM, BATHED THEM AND PUT THEM TO BED.
AND PROTECTED THEM FROM A TORNADO?
OH, MY GOD.
I KNOW. THE BABIES ARE ASLEEP.
PHOEBE, WHAT HAPPENED HERE?
I DID IT.
I TOOK CARE OF THE BABIES ALL BY MYSELF.
B B BUT MY APARTMENT?
WAS THE SETTING
OF PHOEBE'S TRIUMPH.
BUT THE MESS...
IS NOT AS IMPORTANT AS THE FACT
THAT PHOEBE TOOK CARE OF THE BABIES ALL BY HERSELF.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU'RE RIGHT, I SHOULDN'T FREAK OUT
BECAUSE THIS IS WHAT IT'S GOING TO BE LIKE
WHEN YOU AND I HAVE BABIES.
WHEN WILL THAT BE?
PHOEBE, WOULD YOU TAKE A LOOK AT THIS MESS?
OH, HONEY, THANK GOD YOU'RE HOME.
I WAS GETTING WORRIED.
I PICKED UP THE DIVORCE PAPERS.
UH, I'VE ALREADY SIGNED EVERYTHING
AND I PUT LITTLE X's WHERE YOU NEED TO SIGN.
OH, LITTLE X's... GREAT.
THAT MAKES UP FOR EVERYTHING.
YOU KNOW, YOU'VE DONE A LOT OF STUPID STUFF, TOO, OKAY?
OH, NAME ONE STUPID THING THAT IS AS STUPID AS THIS ONE.
OKAY, HOW ABOUT YOU FLEW TO LONDON TO STOP MY WEDDING.
UH, HOW ABOUT YOU TOLD ME YOU LOVED ME
AFTER I WAS ALREADY MARRIED.
HEY, WAIT A MINUTE.
THAT WAS DIFFERENT.
I DID THOSE THINGS BECAUSE I WAS IN LOVE WITH YOU.
YEAH, RIGHT.
YOU'RE RIGHT. THAT'S VERY DIFFERENT.
SO, LET'S... LET'S JUST SIGN THE PAPERS.
WHAT?
NOTHING.
OKAY, CAN WE JUST SIGN, PLEASE?
MM HMM.
CONGRATULATIONS.
OKAY, WAIT, ROSS.
WAIT A MINUTE. UM...
I, UH...
KIND OF HAVE A LITTLE CONFESSION.
WHAT?
UH, WELL, YOU KNOW THIS WHOLE MARRIAGE THING...
KIND OF MY IDEA.
EXCUSE ME?
UH, WELL, REMEMBER HOW WE WERE TOO DRUNK
TO REMEMBER ANYTHING THE NIGHT WE WERE MARRIED?
YEAH.
AND, UH...
YEAH, I DIDN'T WANT TO SAY ANYTHING
BUT IT JUST KEPT COMING BACK TO ME
AND, UM, REMEMBER WE WERE IN THE CASINO
AND FOR SOME REASON YOU THOUGHT
IT WOULD BE FUNNY TO EAT A LOT OF GRAPES?
AND, UH, AND I THOUGHT
IT WOULD BE FUNNIER IF WE GOT MARRIED.
SO, AS A COMPROMISE, WE DECIDED FIRST TO GET MARRIED
AND THEN...
TO EAT A LOT OF GRAPES.
SO, UM, SORRY I GOT US INTO THIS WHOLE THING.
SO, THEN, I MEAN, IF YOU THINK ABOUT IT
THIS IS ALL YOUR FAULT.
YEAH, DON'T PUSH IT THOUGH.
I GOT TO SAY, I KNOW I DIVORCE A LOT OF WOMEN.
NEVER THOUGHT I'D BE DIVORCING YOU.
I KNOW.
I ALWAYS THOUGHT IF YOU AND I GOT MARRIED
THAT WOULD BE THE ONE THAT STUCK.
AND IT WOULDN'T BE A SECRET.
AND WE WOULDN'T HAVE OUR WEDDING DINNER AT PIZZA HUT.
OH... DID I... DID I EVEN TREAT?
NO, IT WAS ON THE HOUSE.
IT WAS A NEWLYWED SPECIAL.
THAT MAY BE THE MOST DEPRESSING THING I'VE HEARD IN MY LIFE.
YEAH.
I SHOULD PROBABLY GET THESE TO MY LAWYER'S OFFICE.
YEAH-- HEY, THANKS, ROSS
FOR TAKING CARE OF ALL THIS.
AH, NO PROBLEM.
I'M GOING TO NEED A COPY OF THOSE.
TOTALLY. YEAH.
HEY! HEY! CAREFUL AROUND MY PORSCHE.
HI, JOEY.
HEY, HOW YOU DOING?
HE HAS THE MOST AMAZING PORSCHE UNDER THERE.
I'D LOVE TO SHOW YOU, BUT I JUST TUCKED HER IN.
SHE'S SLEEPING.
HEY, WOULD YOU TWO GIRLS LIKE TO GO FOR A DRINK?