Not so fast, Wesley.
Ramoray.
That's right, Wesley.
I just stopped by to say that...
you're not a real doctor...
and that woman's brain...
is fine.
OH, THANK GOD!
OH, THANK GOD.
Hope.
Drake.
You're not dying, Hope.
You're going to live a long, healthy life...
with me.
Oh, Drake.
OKAY. HERE WE GO.
OKAY.
MM...
HI, JOEY.
IT'S RACHEL.
UM, I AM FREE TOMORROW NIGHT.
YEAH, SURE. SURE, I COULD BRING SOME SANDWICHES.
SO, HONEY, THIS, UH...
THIS THREESOME THING, UH
I MEAN, HOW ARE WE EVEN GOING TO START TO FIND...
ACTUALLY, I'VE BEEN MAKING A LIST OF ALL THE WOMEN I KNOW
WHO MIGHT BE INTO DOING THIS.
OH. WOW.
HUH?
BOY.
WOW, SOMEONE'S BEEN DOING THEIR HOMEWORK.
YEAH.
OH, AND I KNOW GAIL ROSTEN IS IN THERE TWICE
BUT SHE IS SO...
OH, I KNOW.
YOU KNOW, JUST, JUST TALKING ABOUT IT IS...
GETTING ME KIND OF...
I KNOW, ME, TOO.
YEAH?
WELL, I THINK BEN'S ASLEEP.
OH, UM...
YOU KNOW, I THINK IT'LL BE BETTER
IF WE JUST SAVE IT.
YEAH.
RIGHT. SAVE IT-- I CAN DO THAT.
WHY DO YOU ALWAYS WEAR THAT DUMB HAT?
WHAT, ARE YOU LATE FOR YOUR PAPER ROUTE?
: HI, MR. AND MRS. JONES.
HERE'S YOUR PAPER. I'M SORRY ABOUT YOUR WINDOW.
OH, I'M... EH...
HEY, PHEEBS.
HEY.
HOW'S IT GOING?
WELL, I GOT TO GET OUT OF THIS BED!
I'M GOING CRAZY HERE!
CRAZY!
HERE YOU GO, SWEETIE.
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS, HERBAL TEA?
I HATE HERBAL TEA.
I PUT SOME HONEY IN IT.
NYI, NYI, HONEY IN IT.
SHE DOESN'T KNOW SHE WAS FIRED YET, DOES SHE?
NO. THE DOCTORS SAY IT MAY KILL HER.
WHAT ARE YOU TWO GIRLS WHISPERING ABOUT OVER THERE?
BUT I THINK WE SHOULD TELL HER.
LOOK, PHEEBS, MAYBE THIS WHOLE HEART ATTACK THING IS A SIGN
THAT YOU SHOULD START THINKING ABOUT
GETTING A DIFFERENT JOB.
OKAY, WHAT IS THIS, A STUPID CONTEST?
BECAUSE WE'VE GOT A WINNER HERE!
LOOK, PHOEBE, HE'S RIGHT.
PEOPLE ARE NOT SUPPOSED TO HAVE HEART ATTACKS AT 31.
I KNOW, BUT IF I DIDN'T WORK THERE
WHAT ELSE WOULD I DO?
YOU USED TO LIKE PLAYING THE GUITAR.
YEAH, THAT WAS LUCRATIVE.
SMART, LIKE YOUR BROTHER.
UH, WHAT ABOUT, YOU KNOW, THE MASSAGE THING.
THAT NEVER GAVE YOU A HEART ATTACK.
HMM, PULLING IN A SALARY IN THE HIGH SIX FIGURES
OR RUBBING GROSS, NAKED PEOPLE FOR CHUMP CHANGE.
OOH, WHAT DO I DO?
WHAT WILL I DO?!
I MEAN, IT'S JUST SO REALISTIC.
YEAH, I KNOW.
HIS NAME'S PAT.
PAT THE DOG.
OH! OH! I GET IT!
OH, GOD.
ARE YOU, UH, YOU...
READY FOR A REFILL?
OH, I PROBABLY SHOULDN'T.
SO I WILL!
OH... WOW.
IT'S LIKE IT'S RAINING.
PRETTY COOL, HUH?
BUT IF YOU'RE THINKING YOU COULD PUT A FISH IN THERE
AND IT WOULDN'T GET SUCKED UP INTO THE MECHANISM
WELL, YOU'D BE WRONG.
UM, CAN I USE YOUR BATHROOM?
IT'S, UH, RIGHT THROUGH THERE.
OKAY.
YOU KNOW, I GOT TO TELL YOU
IF SOMEONE TOLD ME A WEEK AGO
THAT I WOULD BE PEEING IN JOEY TRIBBIANI'S APARTMENT...
YEAH, LIFE'S PRETTY GREAT, ISN'T IT?
IT IS; IT REALLY IS.
OH, GEE! OH! WHOO!
I HOPE YOU'RE HUNGRY.
WE'RE STARTING WITH OYSTERS.
YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY ABOUT OYSTERS, DON'T YOU?
THEY HAVE PARASITES?
NO.
UM, WELL, SOME PEOPLE SAY THAT OYSTERS ARE...
AN APHRODISIAC.
WHAT PEOPLE?
PEOPLE.
PEOPLE SAY IT.
COME HERE.
SO, OYSTERS, HUH?
AND THEN WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
A LITTLE MIDDLE EASTERN COUSCOUS.
SOMETHING WE CAN EAT WITH OUR HANDS.
YOU KNOW, IT'S FUNNY
WHEN WE WERE STUDYING COMMUNICABLE DISEASES...
NO, NO, NO, NO.
IT'S SENSUAL.
OH. DIDN'T KNOW. OKAY.
OKAY.
OH, NO!
I'M SORRY, SWEETIE, IT'S THE HOSPITAL.
THAT FOOD LOOKS GREAT. MAYBE SAVE ME SOME?
I CAN'T PROMISE ANYTHING.
WE'RE REALLY GOING TO DO THIS, HUH?
LOOKS LIKE IT.
YOU KNOW, IF... IF THIS IS TOO WEIRD FOR YOU
YOU CAN STILL BACK OUT, ANYTIME...
I GOT IT.
OKAY.
SUSAN, HI.
HEY.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR COMING.
I WOULDN'T HAVE MISSED IT FOR THE WORLD.
I'M I'M ROSS, BY THE WAY.
HELLO, ROSS.
I LOVE WHAT YOU'VE DONE WITH THIS SPACE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
HOW HOT IS THIS?!
I'M SORRY YOU'RE HERE WITH ME
INSTEAD OF ROGER.
YEAH, ME, TOO.
WELL, I COULD MAKE IT SEEM LIKE HE'S HERE.
HERE'S SOME LITTLE KNOWN FACTS ABOUT COUSCOUS:
THEY DIDN'T ADD THE SECOND COUS UNTIL 1979.
STOP IT! THAT'S NOT FUNNY.
OKAY.
I'M SORRY, OKAY.
IT'S JUST, TONIGHT WAS SUPPOSED TO BE, YOU KNOW...
WELL, IT WAS SUPPOSED TO BE A BIG DEAL.
WHAT WAS TONIGHT?
YOU DON'T WANT TO KNOW WHAT TONIGHT WAS.
OKAY.
WHAT WAS TONIGHT?
WELL, TONIGHT WAS...
WAS GOING TO BE MY FIRST TIME.
WITH ROGER?
NOT JUST WITH ROGER?
OH, MY GOD!
ALL RIGHT, RELAX, MR. I'VE HAD SEX FOUR TIMES!
FOUR DIFFERENT WOMEN.
I'VE HAD SEX WAY MORE TIMES.
HOW MANY?
NINE.
I WAS WAITING FOR THE PERFECT GUY, YOU KNOW.
WELL, GOOD. GOOD FOR YOU.
YOU REALLY THINK THAT ROGER IS THE PERFECT GUY?
NO. HE'S NOT A HORRIBLE GUY.
HEY, THAT'S WHAT I TELL GIRLS ABOUT ME.
CHANDLER, I'M GOING TO DIE A VIRGIN!
NO, YOU ARE NOT.
YOU ARE SWEET AND WONDERFUL
AND THIS IS GOING TO HAPPEN FOR YOU.
REALLY? WHEN?
YOU WANT TO DO IT WITH ME?
OKAY.
I WAS KIDDING.
SO WAS I.
JOEY...
YOU'RE SUCH AN AMAZING ACTOR.
HOW DO YOU KNOW WHERE DR. DRAKE RAMORAY LEAVES OFF
AND JOEY TRIBBIANI BEGINS?
WELL, WITH DR. DRAKE
THEY ALWAYS TELL ME WHAT TO SAY.
AND WITH JOEY, I PRETTY MUCH HAVE TO MAKE IT UP ON MY OWN.
WOW.
HMM.
TELL ME SOMETHING, JOEY...
WHOA!
OOP, OOP!
I JUST FELL RIGHT OFF THE COUCH THERE.
YEAH, YOU DID.
I'M OKAY.
OKAY, HERE YOU GO. WHOOPS.
LET ME ASK YOU A QUESTION.
YEAH?
WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME SOMEONE TOLD YOU
JUST HOW BEAUTIFUL YOU ARE?
WOW.
I CAN'T... I CAN'T FEEL MY HANDS.
OH, WELL, COME HERE.
HUH?
OOH?
WE CAN'T DO THIS.
NO.
OYSTER?
YEAH.
OKAY, NOW, IF,IF, IF WE DID DO THIS
THERE'D BE A LOT OF PRESSURE ON ME, YOU KNOW?
BECAUSE YOU'VE BEEN WAITING FOR A VERY LONG TIME
AND I WOULDN'T WANT TO DISAPPOINT YOU.
YEAH, BUT SEE, I HAVE NOTHING TO COMPARE IT TO.
SO EVEN IF YOU WERE HORRIBLE, HOW WOULD I KNOW?
I DO LIKE THAT.
IT'S HARDER FOR ME--
I'VE GOT THOSE FOUR OTHER WOMEN TO COMPETE WITH.
WELL, IF IT HELPS, THERE WERE ONLY THREE.
SO, IT WOULD JUST BE FOR TONIGHT, RIGHT?
ABSOLUTELY. IT WOULD JUST BE ONE FRIEND
HELPING OUT ANOTHER FRIEND.
STOP IT. WE'RE NOT DOING THIS.
LET'S DO IT.
NO. OKAY!
OKAY!
SO, UM...
DO YOU HAVE ANY, UH, MOVES?
I HAVE SOME MOVES.
I HAVE NO MOVES.
OKAY.
OKAY, WHAT YOU DOING THERE?!
OH, YOU KNOW WHAT? I'M SORRY, THIS IS JUST TOO WEIRD.
YEAH, LET'S JUST FORGET IT.
YEAH. WHAT IF I TURN OUT THE LIGHTS?
OKAY.
OH, YEAH.
CHANDLER?
: YEAH?
THAT'S THE COUCH.
I KNOW.