OKAY, RACHE, THAT'S MUFFIN AND ESPRESSO, $4.50 DOLLARS
ROSS, DOUBLE LATTE, $2.75 DOLLARS
CHANDLER, COFFEE AND SCONE, $4.25 DOLLARS
AND PHEEBS, HERBAL TEA, $1.25 DOLLARS.
SO, ALL TOGETHER, THAT'S $12.75 DOLLARS.
THIS COMING FROM THE MAN
WHO COULDN'T SPLIT OUR $80 PHONE BILL IN HALF.
HI. HI.
HOW MUCH DO I OWE FOR THE MUFFIN AND LATTE?
THAT'S ON THE HOUSE
COURTESY OF JOEY TRIBBIANI.
OH, GREAT.
WELL, TELL HIM THANKS.
AND SINCE, UH, JOEY SEEMS LIKE SUCH A NICE GUY
MAYBE WE COULD GO ON A DATE SOMETIME.
WELL, HE'S NOT USED TO WOMEN BEING SO FORWARD
BUT, UH, I COULD CHECK WITH HIM.
HE SAYS IT'S OKAY.
GREAT. THANKS. BYE BYE.
HEY, JOEY, HOW COME OUR STUFF ISN'T FREE?
IT WILL BE WHEN YOU LOOK LIKE THAT
IN A TIGHT SKIRT.
THIS IS GREAT. I'M GETTING MORE DATES THAT EVER.
WAIT A MINUTE.
JOEY, YOU'RE ONLY GIVING AWAY FREE STUFF TO THE PRETTY GIRLS?
JOEY, THAT IS SO GROSS.
HOW ABOUT A SCONE ON THE HOUSE, BABY?
I'M PRETTY.
HEY, DOES ANYONE HAVE ANY GUM?
OH, I DO. I DO.
HERE. SORRY.
OH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
NO.
WAIT A SECOND...
I KNOW IT'S IN HERE SOMEWHERE.
YOU KNOW WHAT? I'M GOOD, I'M GOOD.
ALL RIGHT. SORRY.
I GUESS IT'S IN MY BIG BAG.
SAY, DOES ANYBODY HAVE A GOLDFISH?
OH.
HEY.
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
SHOULDN'T YOU BE AT WORK?
UH, THEY SENT ME HOME.
THEY SAID I CAN'T WORK IF I'M SICK.
OH!
I'M SO SORRY YOU'RE SICK.
I'M NOT SICK!
I DON'T GET SICK.
GETTING SICK IS FOR WEAKLINGS.
IT'S FOR PANSIES.
HONEY, NO ONE THINKS THAT YOU'RE A PANSY.
BUT WE DO THINK THAT YOU NEED A TISSUE.
I HAVE NOT BEEN SICK IN OVER THREE YEARS.
I THINK YOU'RE SICK
BECAUSE THAT USED TO BE IN YOUR NOSE.
I'M GOING TO GRAB YOU SOME TISSUE.
I I DON'T NEED
A TISSUE!
I'M FINE'D!
WHEN YOU PUT A "D" AT THE END OF "FINE"
YOU'RE NOT FINE.
I'M FINE... 'D.
OKAY.
YOU KNOW, IT'S A REALLY HARD WORD TO SAY.
YES?
HI. IS RACHEL HERE?
I'M HER SISTER.
OH, MY GOD! JILL!
OH, MY GOD! RACHEL!
HI!
OH, MY GOD!
INTRODUCE US.
WELL, THIS IS CHANDLER.
AND YOU KNOW MONICA AND ROSS.
AND THAT'S PHOEBE
AND THAT'S JOEY.
HEY, HOW YOU DOING?
DON'T!
HONEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
WHICH WHICH SISTER IS THIS?
IS THIS THE SPOILED ONE OR THE ONE THAT BIT HER?
DADDY CUT ME OFF.
NEVER MIND. I GOT IT.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT I SAID TO HIM?
I SAID, "I'M GOING TO HIRE A LAWYER
"AND I'M GOING TO SUE YOU
"AND TAKE ALL YOUR MONEY
AND THEN I'M GOING TO CUT YOU OFF!"
WOW. WHAT DID HE SAY?
HE SAID HE WOULDN'T PAY FOR MY LAWYER.
AND THEN HE TOLD ME TO COME HERE AND LEARN ABOUT THE VALUE OF MONEY
FROM THE ONE DAUGHTER HE'S ACTUALLY PROUD OF.
DID YOU HEAR THAT?
MY DAD'S PROUD OF ME.
RACHE...
OH, YEAH, SORRY.
OKAY, HONEY, SO WHAT DID YOU DO
THAT MADE DAD CUT YOU OFF?
OKAY, I BOUGHT A BOAT.
YOU BOUGHT A BOAT?
YEAH, BUT IT WASN'T FOR ME. IT WAS FOR A FRIEND.
BOY, DID WE MAKE FRIENDS WITH THE WRONG SISTER.
I KNEW IT WAS STUPID
AND I KNOW I SHOULDN'T HAVE DONE IT
BUT SHE BOUGHT  ME ALL THESE CDs
AND SHE SAID I HAD A REALLY CUTE HAIRCUT.
AND YOUR DADDY DIDN'T UNDERSTAND?
I KNOW. AND, USUALLY, I JUST CRY AND SAY I'M SORRY
AND THEN HE FORGIVES ME.
OH, YES. GOOD CRIERS, THE GREEN GIRLS.
I MEAN... I MEAN THE, UH...
YOU KNOW, THE... THE GREEN SISTERS.
MAN, NO MATTER HOW YOU SAY IT
IT STILL SOUNDS LIKE LIKE YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT GREEN PEOPLE.
I'M AT ROCK BOTTOM.
JILL, HONEY, I THINK THIS IS THE BEST THING
THAT COULD HAVE EVER HAPPENED TO YOU.
YOU'VE NEEDED TO GET OUT ON YOUR OWN, ANYWAY.
AND, YOU KNOW, WHEN I DID IT
I I, AT FIRST I WAS SCARED
BUT, THEN, LOOK AT ME NOW.
I AM THE ONLY DAUGHTER
THAT DAD IS PROUD OF.
I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE HIM.
HOW DOES HE EXPECT ME TO BUY STUFF?
WELL, MAYBE, YOU JUST WON'T BUY STUFF FOR A WHILE.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
OKAY, THIS IS WHAT YOU'RE GOING TO DO.
YOU'RE GOING TO GET A JOB.
YOU'RE GOING TO GET AN APARTMENT.
THEN YOU WILL LIVE OFF THE MONEY THAT YOU EARN.
OKAY. I KNOW THIS IS WHAT YOU DID
BUT THAT DOESN'T SOUND LIKE ME.
OKAY, BUT IT CAN BE.
IT CAN BE YOU.
AND I'LL HELP YOU
AND YOU CAN STAY WITH US.
RIGHT, PHEEBS?
OF COURSE. YEAH.
OH, THAT'S SO GREAT.
OKAY, I'M REALLY GOING TO DO THIS.
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO THANK YOU GUYS.
OH... I LIKE CARS.
UH, YOU ALL FINISHED HERE? YES.
GREAT.
OKAY, HERE ARE THE TIPS FOR THIS MORNING.
MMM.
JAN GETS $50 DOLLARS, $50 DOLLARS FOR ME
AND JOEY OWES EIGHT DOLLARS.
WHAT?
FOR ALL THE FREE FOOD YOU GAVE AWAY.
WELL, IF IT'S FREE FOOD
HOW COME YOU'RE CHARGING ME FOR IT?
WE DON'T GIVE ANYTHING AWAY
UNLESS IT'S SOMEONE'S BIRTHDAY.
OH... WHA WHAT IF THEY CAME IN THIRD IN A MODELING CONTEST?
NO.
HMM...
SORRY.
I JUST HAD THE HARDEST DAY.
SOME OF THESE ARE SO HEAVY.
JILL, HOW DID YOU PAY FOR ALL THIS?
I THOUGHT YOUR DAD TOOK AWAY YOUR CREDIT CARD.
OH, PLEASE. I MEMORIZED THOSE NUMBERS WHEN I WAS 15.
BUT LOOK AT ALL THE COOL MAKE IT ON MY OWN STUFF I GOT.
THIS IS MY "PLEASE HIRE ME" SWEATER.
AND THESE ARE MY...
"DON'T YOU WANT TO RENT ME THIS APARTMENT?" PANTS.
I DON'T THINK CHARGING NEW CLOTHES TO YOUR DAD
QUALIFIES AS MAKING  IT ON YOUR OWN.
OH, MR. SCIENTIST HAS TO GET ALL TECHNICAL.
SERIOUSLY, I DON'T THINK RACHEL'S GOING TO THINK IT'S SUCH A GOOD IDEA.
SO WHO MADE HER QUEEN OF THE WORLD?
I WOULD LOVE THAT JOB.
HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
HEY.
JILL...
DID YOU SHOP?
NO.
THEY DID.
YEAH, WE WENT SHOPPING!
YOU WENT SHOPPING?
WHAT? AND THEN YOU JUST CAME IN HERE
AND PARADED IT RIGHT UNDER JILL'S NOSE
WHEN YOU KNOW SHE'S TRYING TO QUIT?
WOW, YOU GUYS, IT'S TERRIBLE.
SORRY, JILL.
SORRY SORRY, JILL.
WHAT DID
YOU GET?
OH, WELL, ALL RIGHT.
I GOT... THANK YOU.
I GOT THIS "I WANT A JOB" SWEATER.
OH.
AND THEN I GOT, UH...
THESE ARE APARTMENT PANTS.
APARTMENT PANTS?
YEAH. YOU'VE NEVER HEARD OF THEM?
NO, OF COURSE...
OF COURSE I'VE HEARD OF THEM.
ROSS, WHAT DID YOU GET?
HUH?
I GOT THIS... THIS.
A PASHMINA?
YEAH.
I I LOVE THESE BABIES.
REALLY?
MMM.
ROSS, WHAT'S A PASHMINA?
IT'S A RUG.
JILL.
I'M SORRY, RACHEL.
OH, COME ON.
YOU REALLY THINK THAT'S GOING TO WORK ON ME?
I INVENTED THAT.
RIGHT.
BUT I AM SORRY.
ALL RIGHT, IT'S OKAY.
ONE LITTLE SETBACK
IS OKAY.
BUT JUST DON'T LET IT HAPPEN AGAIN, ALL RIGHT?
OKAY.
NOW, SINCE DADDY PAID FOR ALL THIS STUFF
I SHOULD TAKE IT ALL AWAY
BUT I'M JUST GOING TO TAKE...
THE THE PASHMINA.
AND THE AND THE, UH, PANTS.
YOU KNOW WHAT? I'M JUST GOING TO TAKE IT ALL AWAY
BECAUSE THAT WAY, YOU'LL JUST REALLY LEARN THE LESSON, OKAY?
ALL RIGHTY.
WELL, I'M GOING
TO RUN A COUPLE OF ERRANDS
AND I WILL SEE YOU AT DINNER.
SHE TOOK ALL MY STUFF.
YEAH. EVERYTHING BUT...
THE LITTLE BLUE ONE.
OH! THAT'S THE BEST ONE!
OH, MY GOD! THANK YOU SO MUCH!
WELL, HEY...
OH, MY GOSH, THAT WAS SO LAME.
LIKE A PASHMIN A COULD BE A RUG.
OH, YEAH, WELL, HOW ABOUT YOU WITH
"OH, I'M SORRY..."
OH, SHUT UP! IT WASN'T LIKE THAT AT ALL.
WHAT ABOUT- WHAT ABOUT WHAT I SAID
ABOUT THE APARTMENT PANTS?
HOW DUMB WAS I? HA!
WERE YOU THIS CU TE IN HIGH SCHOOL?
OH, STOP.
NO, YOU STOP.
YOU STOP.
OKAY, OKAY, WHY DON'T I SIT HERE
AND THEN YOU'LL BOTH STOP IT.
OKAY, SO WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
LET'S DO SOMETHING CRAZY!
I KNOW. LET'S REST AND DRINK LOTS OF FLUIDS.
OKAY, I'LL REST, BUT, YOU KNOW, IF I'M GOING TO BED
THEN YOU'RE COMING WITH ME.
SEE, THAT WOULD BE IMPOSSIBLE TO RESIST
IF YOU WEREN'T ALL DRIPPY HERE.
ARE YOU SAYING THAT YOU DON'T WANT TO GET WITH THIS?
YEAH, I DON'T THINK YOU SHOULD SAY THAT
EVEN WHEN YOU'RE HEALTHY.
OH, COME ON.
DON'T TAKE THIS PERSONALLY, OKAY?
IT'S JUST THAT I JUST CAN'T HAVE SEX WITH A SICK PERSON.
I'M WITH YOU, CHANDLER.
I MEAN, I CAN'T HAVE SEX WITH A SICK PERSON, EITHER.
IT'S DISGUSTING.
BUT I'M NOT SICK.
LET ME PROVE IT TO YOU.
WE ARE TWO HEALTHY PEOPLE IN THE PRIBE OF LIBE.
SEE, THAT'S THE THING.
I WOULD LIKE TO STAY IN THE PRAHM UB LABH.
OH. OKAY. NOW I'LL DO IT.
HEY.
HEY. WHAT'S UP?
UM... I THINK THERE'S SOMETHING YOU SHOULD MAYBE KNOW.
WELL, IT BETTER NOT BE ABOUT THE APARTMENT PANTS
BECAUSE I JUST PITCHED THE IDEA TO MY BOSS AT RALPH LAUREN
AND SHE LOVED IT.
NO, NO. IT'S JUST...
I WAS, UM, I WAS WITH ROSS AND JILL
AFTER YOU LEFT AND, UM, I'M PRETTY SURE
I SAW A LITTLE SPARK BETWEEN THEM.
WHAT?
YEAH, I MEAN IT'S PROBABLY NOTHING
BUT I JUST WANTED TO WARN YOU
THAT THERE MIGHT BE SOMETHING THERE.
WITH ROSS AND JILL?
YEAH.
WITH ROSS AND MY SISTER?
WITH MY SISTER, JILL, AND MY EX BOYFRIEND, ROSS?
YEAH.
OH, THERE IS NO WAY.
OKAY, THEN.
OH, MY GOD!
I CANNOT BELIEVE THAT!
I DON'T REALLY LIKE IT
WHEN ROSS GOES OUT WITH ANYONE
BUT MY SISTER?!
ISN'T THAT LIKE INCEST OR SOMETHING?
OH, MY GOD
AND THEY'RE GOING TO HAVE SEX.
OH, NO, AND WHAT IF HE MARRIES HER, TOO?
OH, THIS IS JUST TERRIBLE.
THIS IS JUST TERRIBLE.
AND I CAN'T STOP IT.
I DON'T OWN ROSS, YOU KNOW.
AND JILL, SHE SHOULD BE ABLE
TO DO WHATEVER IT IS THAT SHE WANTS TO DO.
AND, OH, MY GOD, I CAN'T BELIEVE
ROSS IS MARRYING MY LITTLE SISTER.
OH, MY GOD. THIS IS JUST THE WORST THING
THAT COULD HAVE EVER HAPPENED TO ME.
BUT GREAT NEWS ABOUT THE APARTMENT PANTS, HUH?
THAT'LL BE $3.85 DOLLARS.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN? YESTERDAY, YOU SAID
I WAS TOO PRETTY TO PAY FOR STUFF.
IT'S JUST I CAN'T BECAUSE MY MANAGER SAID THAT...
?? HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO YOU ??
?? HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO YOU ? ?
?? HAPPY BIRTHDAY, DEAR ANNIE... ??
AMY.
?? AMY ??
?? HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO YOU. ??
HEY, THAT'S WEIRD.
TODAY'S MY BIRTHDAY, TOO.
YEAH? NOT IN HERE IT ISN'T.
SORRY I'M LATE.
WHAT'S UP?
OH, HI.
UH, YOU KNOW, I JUST WANTED TO SEE
IF THERE WERE ANY LEADS ON THE OLD JOB FRONT.
OH, NO, BUT I JUST WALKED PAST THREE SALES AND I DIDN'T GO IN.
HOW STRONG AM I?
OH...
THAT IS GREAT.
HEY, YOU KNOW WHO DOESN'T HAVE TO JOB HUNT?
ROSS.
HE WORKS AT THE UNIVERSITY.
YEAH.
SO YOU KNOW THAT? YOU GUYS TALKED ABOUT THAT?
SO YOU GET ALONG? SO YOU THINK YOU'RE GOING TO GO OUT?
ME GO OUT WITH ROSS?
NO.
GOD, NO!
WHAT WOULD MAKE YOU THINK THAT?
IT'S JUST... PHOEBE... SAID SHE, YOU KNOW
THOUGHT SHE SAW SOMETHING BETWEEN YOU GUYS.
NO.
MEAN, HE'S NICE.
HE'S THE KIND OF GUY YOU'RE FRIENDS WITH
BUT HE'S NOT THE KIND OF GUY YOU DATE.
I MEAN, HE'S THE KIND OF GUY YOU DATE
BECAUSE YOU DID, BUT...
ME...
NOT SO MUCH.
WHY NOT SO MUCH?
UM, WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I MEAN, IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG WITH ROSS?
OH, NO, NO, NO..
HE'S JUST... I DON'T KNOW.
YOU KNOW, HE'S JUST A LITTLE... BOOKISH.
ARE YOU SAYING HE'S A GEEK?
YOU THINK SO, TOO?
NO. NO, ROSS IS NOT A GEEK.
FINE.
THEN LET'S JUST SAY HE'S NOT MY TYPE.
HANDSOME IS NOT YOUR TYPE?
SMART, KIND, GOOD KISSER?
WHAT? THOSE THINGS AREN'T ON YOUR LIST?
ROSS IS A GREAT GUY.
YOU WOULD BE LUCKY TO BE WITH HIM.
WELL, OKAY, IF IT MEANS THAT MUCH TO YOU
THEN I'LL JUST ASK HIM OUT.
OH, NO, NO.
THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT.
I WAS JUST TRYING...
YOU KNOW WHAT, RACHEL. YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU KNOW, HE HAS BEEN REALLY NICE TO ME.
YEAH, BUT HE'S NOT YOUR TYPE.
YEAH, BUT MAYBE THAT'S A GOOD THING.
YOU KNOW, I'M DOING ALL THESE DIFFERENT SORTS OF THINGS.
MAYBE I SHOULD JUST TRY DATING A GEEK, TOO.
YEAH, BUT YOU DON'T WANT TO TRY TOO MUCH TOO FAST.
YOU KNOW, I MEAN
YOU DO REMEMBER WHAT HAPPENED TO THE LITTLE GIRL
WHO TRIED TOO MUCH TOO FAST, DON'T YOU?
WHAT?
SHE SHE DIED, JILL.
CHANDLER!
OH, WHAT IS IT, HONEY?
YOU NEED SOME TEA?
SOME SOUP?
OH, OH, OH!
CALLING DR. BING...
DR. BING, TO THE BED.
OH, GEEZ, HONEY, I THOUGHT...
I THOUGHT YOU WERE ASLEEP.
HOW CAN I BE ASLEEP
KNOWING THAT YOU WERE IN THE NEXT ROOM?
IWAS ASLEEP.
OH, NO, NO, NO, HONEY.
YOU KNOW WHAT'S SEXY?
LAYERS.
LAYERS ARE SEXY... AND BLANKETS ARE SEXY
AND, OH, HOT WATER BOTTLES ARE SEXY.
COME ON, GET INTO BED.
I WANT TO PROVE THAT I'M NOT SICK.
I WANT TO MAKE YOU FEEL... AS GOOD AS I FEEL.
WOULD YOU PLEASE GET SOME REST?
I'M FINE...
YOU'RE COUGHING.
NO, I'M NOT.
NO, I'M NOT. I'M LAUGHING.
AT WHAT?
OH, JUST SOMETHING I HEARD BEFORE.
TELL ME.
OH, NO. I DON'T WANT IT TO SPOIL...
THE MOOD.
?? HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO YOU. ??
YOU'RE PAYING FOR THAT.
WHAT? NO, NO. IT'S HER BIRTHDAY.
YOU'VE SUNG HAPPY BIRTHDAY
TO 20 DIFFERENT WOMEN TODAY.
BUT IT REALLY...
YOU ARE NO LONGER AUTHORIZED
TO DISTRIBUTE BIRTHDAY MUFFINS.
DAMN IT!
RACHE.
HI. HI.
DID YOU TELL YOUR SISTER TO ASK ME OUT?
WELL, YEAH...
OH, WOW!
I MEAN, WOW!
I THINK SHE'S CUTE
BUT I NEVER WOULD HAVE THOUGHT
OF GOING OUT WITH HER-- NEVER!
REALLY?
YEAH, BUT AFTER YOU SAID IT WAS OKAY, I FIGURED, WHY NOT?
OH, SO... SO, NOT REALLY NEVER?
I HAVE TO SAY
YOU ARE A MUCH BIGGER  PERSON THAN I AM.
I MEAN, AFTER ALL WE'VE BEEN THROUGH
I JUST...
I WISH I HAD A BROTHER TO RECIPROCATE.
OH.
IF YOU EVER WANT TO GO OUT WITH MONICA
YOU HAVE MY BLESSING.
AND MINE.
CHANDLER...
I THINK I'M SICK.
REALLY?
STRUCK DOWN IN THE PRIBE OF LIBE.
OKAY, FINE, I ADMIT IT.
I FEEL TERRIBLE.
WILL YOU PLEASE RUB THIS ON MY CHEST?
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO!
YOU ARE NOT GETTING ME THIS WAY.
I REALLY NEED YOUR HELP.
NO, NO, NO, NO!
FINE. I'LL JUST RUB IT ON MYSELF.
OKAY.
SO, YOU'RE JUST...
KIND OF RUBBING IT ON YOURSELF?
YEAH?
IT'S NICE.
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
IS THIS TURNING YOU ON?
YES.
WELL, I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
WHAT IS IT? IS IT THE RUBBING OR THE SMELL?
IT'S ALL VERY, VERY GOOD.
OH...
SO, YOU WANT TO GO, UH...
MIX IT UP?
NOT NOW. I'M SICK.
OH, COME ON, YOU BIG FAKER!
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOUR RULE
ABOUT NEVER SLEEPING WITH SICK PEOPLE?
WELL, THAT WAS BEFORE ALL THE...
VAPORIZING ACTION.
OKAY, IF YOU REALLY WANT TO HAVE SEX.
OKAY!
WORKED LIKE A CHARM.
HI.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
THIS IS WHERE ROSS AND  I ARE MEETING FOR OUR DATE.
SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WELL, I... I DON'T LIKE IT.
REALLY?
IT'S KIND OF SLUTTY.
IT'S YOURS.
YEAH, WELL, I'M... I'M A SLUT.
ME, TOO.
HEY.
HI, JILL.
HI...
RACHEL!
RACHEL.
WELL...
YOU'RE NOT AT HOME. YOU'RE, YOU'RE RIGHT HERE.
YEAH, I KNOW.
I BET YOU THOUGHT IT WOULD BE WEIRD...
BUT IT'S NOT.
OKAY.
SO, WELL, I'LL, UM...
I'LL HAVE HER HOME BY MIDNIGHT.
WHY AREN'T YOU HOME YET?
IS SOMEONE THERE?
OH, YEAH, IT'S ME.
SORRY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
UH, I'M JUST...
I'M JUST LOOKING OUT YOUR WINDOW...
AT THE VIEW.
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
WE GOT SOME VAPO RUB IN SOME PLACES.
OH!
OH, HE BROUGHT HER BACK TO HIS APARTMENT.
WHO?
IS THAT YOUR SISTER?
OH, SHE IS A SLUT!
OH, MY GOD.
ROSS IS ON A DATE WITH YOUR SISTER?
HOW WEIRD IS THAT?
OH, MY GOD, LOOK, LOOK.
HE'S TAKING OFF HER CLOTHES.
HE'S TAKING OFF HER COAT.
OH, THIS IS JUST TERRIBLE.
OH, NO, IT'S NOT. IT'S A FIRST DATE.
I'M SURE THAT NOTHING IS GOING TO...
OH!
OOH HOO...
HE'S GOING TO GET SOME.
OF THE GLARE...
FROM THE STREETLIGHT... OUT OF HIS APARTMENT.
YOU KNOW, SO, UM... HE'S CLOSED THE DRAPES THERE
SO HE CAN HAVE A NICE, PLEASANT CONVERSATION
WITH YOUR LITTLE SISTER.
WELL, I'M OFF TO BED.
I DON'T FEEL GOOD.
YOU BETTER NOT GET ME SICK.
I NEED SOME FRUIT OR SOME...
JUICE OR SOME...
OR SOME NOTHING.
THERE'S NOTHING IN HERE. WHO TOOK OUR FOOD?
CAN I INTEREST YOU IN A SLICE OF LASAGNA?
OR A DRUMSTICK?
NO, THANKS.
ARE YOU SURE?
IT'S ON THE HOUSE.
NO, THANKS.
HOW ABOUT GOING OUT WITH ME FRIDAY NIGHT?
AW, WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?