YOU KNOW, STARRING IN A MOVIE AND ALL.
NOW JUST HOW BIG OF A STAR IS MARCEL?
IN HUMAN TERMS?
I'D SAY... CYBILL SHEPHERD.
WHOA! WHOA! REALLY?
SO, YOU GUYS IN THE MOVIE
OR ARE YOU JUST REALLY PARANOID?
HEY, SAL, JERRY WANTS TO KNOW
IF THE MONKEY'S READY FOR THE SUBWAY STUNT.
UH, EXCUSE ME.
JERRY IS THE DIRECTOR?
WHICH ONE IS HE?
THE ONE IN THE DIRECTOR'S CHAIR.
GOTCHA.
PHEEBS, WALK WITH ME.
OKAY.
UM, HOW COME I'M WALKING WITH YOU?
WELL, WE'RE JUST GOING OVER HERE
SO THAT WE CAN GET AWAY FROM
THE HORRIBLE FLESH EATING VIRUS!
FOR THE LOVE OF GOD, WOMAN, LISTEN TO ME!
IS HE LOOKING? IS HE LOOKING?
WE'VE GOT A PROBLEM.
HI. TELL ME.
I CAN'T DO CHRISSIE'S MAKEUP.
SHE REFUSES TO ACKNOWLEDGE THAT SHE HAS A MOUSTACHE.
IS IT BAD?
IT LOOKS LIKE ONE OF HER EYEBROWS FELL DOWN.
GOT IT. NOW UNLESS SOMEONE
CONVINCES HER TO LET ME BLEACH IT
JEAN CLAUDE VAN DAMME'S GOING TO BE MAKING OUT WITH GABE KAPLAN.
I'LL TALK TO HER.
I HATE ACTORS.
NICE CAMOUFLAGE, MAN.
FOR A MINUTE THERE, I ALMOST DIDN'T SEE YOU.
EXCUSE ME.
WHOO!
UH... IS YOUR NAME CHANDLER?
UH... YES. YES, IT IS.
CHANDLER BING?
DO YOU KNOW ME
OR ARE YOU JUST REALLY GOOD AT THIS GAME?
I'M SUSIE MOSS.
FOURTH GRADE. GLASSES.
I USED TO CARRY AROUND A BOX OF ANIMAL CRACKERS LIKE A PURSE.
SUSIE MOSS.
RIGHT. YEAH. WOW!
YOU LOOK...
GREAT JOB GROWING UP.
THANK YOU.
IT'S NICE TO SEE YOU'RE NOT STILL WEARING THAT DENIM CAP
WITH ALL THE LITTLE MIRRORS ON IT.
OH, RIGHT. WELL, I GRADUATED FOURTH GRADE
AND REALIZED I WASN'T A PIMP.
REMEMBER THE CLASS PLAY?
YOU PULLED UP MY SKIRT
AND THE ENTIRE AUDITORIUM SAW MY UNDERPANTS?
YES. BACK THEN, I, UH...
USED HUMOR AS A DEFENSE MECHANISM.
THANK GOD, I DON'T DO THAT ANYMORE.
SO...
WHAT HAVE YOU BEEN DOING SINCE CHILDHOOD?
WELL, UM... I GOT A NEW BELT.
I WONDERED.
OH, MY GOD. OH, MY GOD.
WHAT? WHAT, WHAT, WHAT, WHAT?
IT'S JEAN CLAUDE VAN DAMME.
I DIDN'T KNOW HE WAS IN THIS MOVIE.
HE IS SO HOT!
YOU THINK?
"THE MUSCLES FROM BRUSSELS"?
"WHAM BAM VAN DAMME"?
DID YOU SEE TIME COP?
NO. WAS HE ANY GOOD IN IT?
RACHEL, HE, LIKE, TOTALLY CHANGED TIME.
WOW! SO WHY DON'T YOU GO TALK TO HIM?
OH, YEAH!
WHAT? SO YOU GO OVER THERE, YOU TELL HIM YOU THINK HE'S CUTE.
WHAT'S THE WORST THAT COULD HAPPEN?
HE COULD HEAR ME.
OH, COME ON, MONICA.
OKAY, I'M DOING IT FOR YOU.
OH, RACHEL, DON'T. DON'T YOU DARE.
DON'T! DON'T!
TELL HIM I COOK!
EXCUSE ME. HI.
HI.
UM, THIS IS GOING TO SOUND KIND OF GOOFY
BUT MY FRIEND
OVER THERE--
WHO COOKS, BY THE WAY--
UM... SHE THINKS YOU'RE CUTE.
YOU DON'T THINK I'M CUTE?
I DON'T KNOW. UM...
DO YOU THINK YOU'RE CUTE?
OKAY, WE'RE KIND OF GETTING OFF THE TRACK HERE.
I WAS SUPPOSED TO COME HERE AND TELL YOU
MY FRIEND THINKS YOU'RE CUTE.
SO WHAT SHOULD I TELL HER?
YOU CAN TELL HER
I THINK HER FRIEND IS CUTE.
WHOA!
STEVEN HERZ WAS THE KID WHO WOULD EAT ANYTHING FOR MONEY.
DAVID STEIN WAS THE GUY WHO HAD NO ELBOWS.
OKAY, WELL, THEN WHO WAS THE KID THAT GOT CAUGHT MASTURBATING?
OKAY, THAT'S NOT WHAT HE WAS DOING.
ALL RIGHT? HE WAS LOOKING FOR HIS BUS MONEY.
MAKEUP!
OH, THAT'S ME.
I GOT TO GO.
OH. UH... OKAY.
UM, SO LISTEN, HOW MANY TIMES
AM I GOING TO HAVE TO TOUCH YOU ON THE ARM
BEFORE YOU ASK ME ON A DATE?
WELL, LET'S TRY ONE MORE.
THERE YOU GO. SAY ERNIE'S, 8:00?
I'LL BE THERE. AND WHO KNOWS?
IF THINGS GO WELL, MAYBE THIS TIME
I'LL GET TO SEE YOUR UNDERWEAR.
AND NO ONE WAS AROUND TO HEAR THAT?
SO WHAT DID HE SAY?
UCCH! WHAT A JERK!
I KEPT TALKING ABOUT YOU
AND HE KEPT ASKING ME OUT.
OH.
I MEAN, NATURALLY
YOU KNOW, I SAID NO.
WELL, THANKS, ANYWAY.
HE JUST KEPT ASKING...
ASKING, ASKING, ASKING, ASKING, ASKING...
RACHEL, IF YOU WANT TO GO OUT WITH HIM, YOU CAN.
HE SOUNDS LIKE A BIG JERK TO ME
BUT IF THAT'S YOU WANT TO DO...
JEAN CLAUDE, SHE SAID YES!
I'LL SEE YOU TONIGHT!
THANK YOU.
AND THEN JEAN CLAUDE TOOK ME TO THAT PLACE CROSSROADS
AND THAT'S WHERE
WE HUNG OUT WITH DREW BARRYMORE.
OH, MAN, SHE'S SO SMOKING!
SHE'S GOT THE GREATEST SET OF...
NO GUYS AROUND, HUH?
DOES ANYBODY NEED ANYTHING?
OH, I'LL HAVE AN ESPRESSO.
OH, ACTUALLY, I'LL GET IT.
IF I ASK YOU TO, YOU'LL PROBABLY END UP
DRINKING IT YOURSELF.
THAT IS SO UNFAIR.
I KNOW. LIKE YOU WOULD DRINK HER COFFEE
AFTER WHAT YOU DID TO HER WITH VAN DAMME.
JOEY, I HAVE TO CANCEL RACQUETBALL FOR TONIGHT.
THAT WAS MARCEL'S TRAINER.
HE'S GOING TO LET ME HAVE HIM FOR A COUPLE OF HOURS.
YOU'RE BLOWING ME OFF FOR A MONKEY?
WE CAN RESCHEDULE FOR SATURDAY.
YEAH. UNLESS YOU HOOK UP WITH A BUNCH OF PIGEONS.
HEY, STICK A FORK IN ME.
I AM DONE.
STICK A FORK WHAT?
LIKE WHEN YOU'RE COOKING A STEAK.
OH. OKAY. I DON'T EAT MEAT.
WELL, THEN, HOW DO YOU KNOW WHEN VEGETABLES ARE DONE?
WELL, YOU DON'T. YOU JUST EAT THEM AND YOU CAN TELL.
OKAY, THEN EAT ME. I'M DONE.
I'VE MET THE PERFECT WOMAN.
OKAY, WE'RE SITTING ON HER COUCH
WE'RE FOOLING AROUND
AND THEN, SUDDENLY, SHE TURNS TO ME AND SAYS
"YOU EVER WANT TO DO IT IN AN ELEVATOR?"
WOW! HEY!
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
I BELIEVE MY EXACT WORDS WERE
I MEAN, I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
HOW DO YOU KNOW IF YOU WANT TO DO IT ON AN ELEVATOR?
OH, YOU JUST KNOW.
SHOOT! WE GOT TO GO.
WE GOT A RESERVATION IN 30 MINUTES.
OH, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
YOU SEE, WHAT I HAD PLANNED
SHOULDN'T TAKE MORE THAN TWO, THREE MINUTES, TOPS.
HMM... 200 SECONDS OF PASSION.
WE GOT TO GO.
BUT...
UM...
HERE'S AN IDEA.
HAVE YOU EVER WORN WOMEN'S UNDERWEAR?
WELL, YES, ACTUALLY.
BUT, UH... THEY WERE MY AUNT EDNA'S...
AND THERE WERE THREE OF US IN THERE.
WELL, I WAS THINKING IT WOULD BE KIND OF SEXY
IF YOU WORE MINE TONIGHT AT DINNER.
YOU WANT ME TO WEAR YOUR PANTIES?
COULD YOU?
WELL, IF I WAS WEARING YOUR UNDERWEAR
THEN WHAT WOULD YOU BE WEARING?
YOU'RE SWELL.
OKAY, GOT THE MUSIC.
GOT THE DINNER, OH, AND CHECK IT OUT.
I MADE MARCEL'S FAVORITE DISH-- BANANA CAKE...
OOH! WITH MEAL WORMS.
YARGHH!
OHH!
CANDLES.
WHAT DO YOU THINK IS GOING TO HAPPEN
HERE TONIGHT?
HELLO.
OH, HI. ARE YOU ON YOUR WAY OVER?
OH.
NO, NO, NO. I UNDERSTAND.
I MEAN, A MONKEY'S GOT TO WORK.
NO, IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
IT'S NOT LIKE I HAD ANYTHING SPECIAL PLANNED.
YOU KNOW.
YEAH. OKAY.
OKAY. OKAY, BYE.
OH...
I'M SORRY, MAN.
YEAH.
FEEL THAT?
WHAT?
WE PASSED THE MOMENT WHERE WE SHOULD'VE STOPPED
HOLDING HANDS. OH, YEAH.
YEAH.
OKAY, RACHEL, WHY DON'T YOU START TALKING FIRST?
ALL RIGHT.
I FEEL THAT THIS IS TOTALLY UNJUSTIFIED.
SHE GAVE ME THE GREEN LIGHT.
I DID NOTHING...
DO YOU THINK I CAN'T SEE YOU
IN THE TV SET?
ALL RIGHT, MONICA, IF THERE IS SOMETHING
THAT YOU WOULD LIKE TO SHARE...
YOU KNOW, YOU HAD NO RIGHT TO GO OUT WITH HIM.
THAT IS THE MOST RIDICULOUS...
YOU SOLD ME OUT!
I DID NOT SELL YOU OUT!
YES, YOU DID!
WOULD YOU LET ME TALK?!
DID YOU JUST FLICK ME?
OKAY, WELL, YOU WOULDN'T LET ME FINISH.
AND I...
WAS JUST...
OWW! THAT...
HURT!
QUIT FLICKING!
OW!YOU STOP FLICKING!
YOU FLICKED ME FIRST!
OW! STOP IT!
OW! OW!
OH! ALL RIGHT. OKAY.
LET'S NOT DO THIS!
STAY CALM!
HAPPY THOUGHTS!
COME ON, PEOPLE!
OKAY, NOW I'M GOING TO KICK SOME ASS!
OW!
OW! OW! OW! OW! OW! OW!
ALL RIGHT.
NOW, I WILL LET GO IF YOU BOTH STOP.
DO YOU WANT ME TO STOP SEEING HIM?
IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT?
UH HUH.
YOU WANT ME TO JUST CALL HIM UP
AND TELL HIM YOU'RE SEEING HIM INSTEAD?
IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT?
OKAY.
OH, THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT?
YES.
FINE.
THERE WE GO.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
IF WE WERE IN PRISON
YOU GUYS WOULD BE, LIKE, MY BITCHES.
THANKS FOR LETTING ME TAG ALONG TONIGHT, YOU GUYS.
FORGET ABOUT IT.
HOW YOU DOING THERE, SQUIRMY?
I'M HANGING IN...
AND A LITTLE OUT.
SO, ASSISTANT TO THE DIRECTOR.
THAT'S A REALLY EXCITING JOB.
I MEAN, YOU MUST HAVE A TON OF COOL RESPONSIBILITY.
I HAVE NOTHING TO DO WITH CASTING.
SO WHAT ARE YOU GUYS
GOING TO EAT?
HOW COME ALL I CAN THINK ABOUT
IS PUTTING THAT ICE IN MY MOUTH
AND LICKING YOU ALL OVER?
BECAUSE I WENT TO AN ALL BOYS HIGH SCHOOL
AND GOD IS MAKING UP FOR IT?
I WANT YOU RIGHT HERE, RIGHT NOW.
RIGHT NOW, RIGHT HERE?
DON'T YOU THINK WE'RE IN KIND OF A PUBLIC PLACE?
THEY DO HAVE THE SHRIMP.
MEET ME IN THE BATHROOM.
I'M GOING TO THE BATHROOM NOW.
HE LIKES TO KEEP US IN THE LOOP.
COME ON.
I CAN'T BELIEVE WE'RE DOING THIS.
ALL RIGHT, MISTER, LET'S SEE THOSE PANTIES.
ALL RIGHTY.
OOH, OOH, BUT YOU KNOW WHAT WOULD BE EVEN SEXIER?
WHAT?
IF YOU DIDN'T HAVE YOUR SHIRT TUCKED INTO THEM.
OH.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW, I WOULD LIKE TO SEE YOU WEARING NOTHING BUT THEM.
TAKE YOUR CLOTHES OFF.
OKAY, BUT I HOPE YOU REALIZE
THIS MEANS WE'RE GOING TO MISS
HEARING ABOUT THE SPECIALS.
COME ON. HURRY, HURRY.
HEY, DO YOU WANT THIS DONE QUICK
OR DO YOU WANT IT DONE RIGHT?
ALL RIGHT NOW, TURN AROUND.
I WANT TO SEE YOU FROM BEHIND.
OKAY.
SOMEBODY'S BEEN DOING
HIS BUNS OF STEEL VIDEO.
SAY, YOU WANT ME
TO CLENCH ANYTHING, OR..?
SUSIE?
SUSIE!
THIS... IS FOR THE FOURTH GRADE.
HUH? WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WHAT DO I MEAN?! WHAT DO YOU MEAN
"WHAT DO I MEAN?"
I MEAN UNDERPANTS, MISTER.
THAT'S WHAT I MEAN.
WHAT? WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
MY SKIRT!
YOU LIFTED, KIDS LAUGHING.
I WAS "SUSIE UNDERPANTS" TILL I WAS 18.
THAT WAS IN THE FOURTH GRADE!
HOW CAN YOU
STILL BE UPSET ABOUT THAT?
WELL, UM... WHY DON'T YOU CALL ME IN 20 YEARS
AND TELL ME IF YOU'RE STILL UPSET ABOUT THIS.
ALL RIGHT. I HOPE YOU REALIZE
YOU'RE NOT GETTING THESE UNDERPANTS BACK!
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
JUST LIKE, TWO WEEKS AGO, I WAS WATCHING SUDDEN DEATH
AND NOW I'M ON A DATE WITH JEAN CLAUDE VAN DAMME.
CAN YOU BEAT UP THAT GUY?
YEAH.
SURE.
THIS IS SO WILD.
YOU KNOW, I GOT TO ADMIT I WAS KIND OF SURPRISED
THAT YOU AGREED TO GO ON A BLIND DATE.
NORMALLY I WOULD NOT DO IT.
YEAH?
WELL, WHAT MADE YOU MAKE THE EXCEPTION FOR ME?
BECAUSE RACHEL TOLD ME
YOU WERE DYING TO HAVE A THREESOME
WITH ME AND DREW BARRYMORE.
OH, BY THE WAY
DREW HAS SOME GROUND RULES, AND, UH...
SAY YOU'RE SORRY!
NO!
SAY IT, RACHEL!
NO! NO! I'M NOT!
SAY IT! SAY IT!
GREAT.
RACHEL...
YOU SAY YOU'RE SORRY, OR YOUR SWEATER GETS IT.
OKAY, OKAY. THAT IS MY FAVORITE SWEATER.
THAT IS MY THIRD DATE SWEATER.
SAY YOU'RE SORRY.
OKAY. DO YOU WANT TO PLAY?
OKAY. LET'S PLAY.
LET'S PLAY.
WHAT ARE YOU
GOING TO DO?
YOU GIVE ME BACK MY SWEATER OR IT'S HANDBAG MARINARA.
YOU DON'T HAVE THE GUTS.
OH, YEAH? WELL, AT LEAST I WASN'T TOO CHICKEN
TO TELL SOME GUY I THOUGHT HE WAS CUTE.
OH!
OH!!
OH, ALL RIGHT.
STOP! STOP THE MADNESS!
THIS IS CRAZY.
WHO CAN EVEN REMEMBER
WHY YOU STARTED FIGHTING IN THE FIRST PLACE?
YES, THAT'S RIGHT.
BUT STILL...
LOOK AT YOUR PURSE.
LOOK AT YOUR SWEATER.
LOOK AT YOURSELVES.
I'LL HELP YOU FIX YOUR SWEATER.
I'LL HELP YOU...
THROW OUT YOUR PURSE.
I'M SORRY THAT I MADE YOU STOP SEEING HIM.
WELL, I'M SORRY I WENT OUT WITH HIM WHEN I KNEW YOU LIKED HIM.
I'M SORRY THAT I BORROWED YOUR GLOVES.
JOEY?
MA?
JOEY!
CHANDLER? WHAT ARE YOU STILL DOING HERE?
I THOUGHT YOU GUYS TOOK OFF.
OH, NO, NO. SHE TOOK OFF...
WITH MY CLOTHES!
ARE YOU NAKED IN THERE?
WELL, NOT EXACTLY.
I'M WEARING PANTIES.
HUH.
YOU, UH... YOU ALWAYS WEAR PANTIES?
NO, NO. THIS IS THE FIRST TIME.
WOW, TALK ABOUT YOUR BAD LUCK.
I MEAN, THE FIRST TIME YOU TRY PANTIES
AND SOMEONE WALKS OFF WITH YOUR CLOTHES.
I WAS NOT TRYING THEM OUT.
SUSIE ASKED ME TO WEAR THEM.
WELL, LET ME SEE.
NO. I'M NOT LETTING YOU OR ANYBODY ELSE SEEEVER.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
WHOA.
SOMEONE'S FLOSSING.
JOEY, SOME PEOPLE DON'T LIKE THAT.
? CHANDLER'S WEARING PANTIES. ?
WHAT?
LET ME SEE.
NO, NO. YOU DON'T HAVE TO SEE.
HI, TUSHIE.
ALL RIGHT. ONE OF YOU GIVE ME YOUR UNDERPANTS.
OH, NO.
CAN'T HELP YOU. I'M NOT WEARING ANY.
HOW CAN YOU NOT BE WEARING ANY UNDERWEAR?
OH, I'M GETTING HEAT FROM THE GUY
IN THE HOT PINK THONG.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK.
ROSS, I'LL GIVE YOU $50 FOR YOUR UNDERPANTS.
HEY. HEY. HEY.
HEY, PHEEBS, CAN I HAVE THE MILK AFTER YOU?
I'M ALMOST DONE WITH IT-- KEEP YOUR PANTIES ON.
HEY, HEY.
AND I'M IN THE MOVIE.
WHAT? WHAT HAPPENED?
ONE OF THE VIRUS VICTIMS CALLED IN SICK, SO CATHY RECOMMENDED ME
AND, BOOM! I'M DYING ON A GURNEY.
HEY!
OH, ROSS
MARCEL JUST FINISHED HIS LAST SCENE
IF YOU WANT TO GO DOWN THERE AND SAY GOOD BYE.
UH... NO, THAT'S OKAY.
I MEAN, HE'S PROBABLY GOT PARTIES TO GO TO AND STUFF.
YOU KNOW...
HE'S MOVED ON.
HEY, THAT'S THE WAY IT GOES, RIGHT?
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT?
? LOOKS LIKE WE MADE IT ?
? LEFT EACH OTHER ON THE WAY ?
? TO ANOTHER LOVE ?
? LOOKS LIKE WE MADE IT ?
? OR I THOUGHT SO TILL TODAY ?
? UNTIL YOU WERE THERE, EVERYWHERE ?
? AND ALL I COULD TASTE WAS LOVE THE WAY WE MADE IT ?
? LOOKS LIKE WE MADE IT... ?
I'M SORRY IT DIDN'T WORK OUT BETWEEN YOU AND ME.
OR YOU AND ME.
DREW WAS... VERY DISAPPOINTED.
OKAY. WELL, BYE.
GOOD BYE.
WELL, BYE FROM ME TOO.
OKAY. WELL, BYE BYE AGAIN.
OKAY.
PERHAPS THE THREE OF US JUST COULD...
OH, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
ARE YOU SURE?
I CAN CRUSH A WALNUT WITH MY BUTT.
OH, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
IMPRESSIVE. BUT NO.
MAYBE IF I WERE BAKING.
OKAY.
BYE BYE.
BYE, MARCEL.
SEE YOU ON THE BIG SCREEN.
YOU KEEP PEOPLE DRINKING THAT BEER, OKAY?
I'LL MISS YOU, BUDDY.
YOU KNOW, I THINK I WANT TO WRITE A SONG ABOUT ALL THIS.
OH, YEAH?
YEAH. OOH, EXCEPT ONE OF THE STRINGS
ON MY GUITAR IS BROKEN.
HEY, CHANDLER, CAN I BORROW YOUR "G" STRING?
HOW LONG YOU BEEN WAITING TO SAY THAT?
ABOUT 20 MINUTES.
CAN'T YOU SEE WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
THIS MAN IS DYING.
CUT.
CAN'T YOU SEE WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
THIS MAN IS DYING.
CUT!
CAN'T YOU SEE WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
THIS MAN IS DYING.
MOMMY.
CAN YOU SEE WHAT'S GOING ON?
THIS MAN IS DEAD.