HEY.
WHAT YOU GUYS DOING?
MONICA'S MAKING US WATCHOLD YELLER.
SO WHY ARE YOU GUYS SO UPSET?
IT'S OLD YELLER.
IT'S A HAPPY MOVIE.
WHAT?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
COME ON.
HAPPY FAMILY GETS A DOG.
FRONTIER FUN.
YEAH, BUT, PHEEBS, WHAT ABOUT THE END?
WHEN YELLER SAVES THE FAMILY FROM THE WOLF
AND EVERYONE'S HAPPY?
THAT'S NOT THE END.
YUH HUH. THAT'S WHEN MY MOTHER
WOULD SHUT OFF THE TV AND SAY "THE END."
WHAT ABOUT THE PART WHERE HE HAS RABIES?
HE DOESN'T HAVE RABIES. HE HAS BABIES.
THAT'S WHAT MY MOM SAID.
UH, PHOEBE, I DON'T THINK YOUR MOM
WOULD WANT YOU TO SEE WHAT'S ABOUT TO HAPPEN.
WHY? WHAT'S ABOUT TO HAPPEN?
I'VE NEVER SEEN THIS PART BEFORE.
HEY, TRAVIS, WHATCHA DOING WITH THAT GUN?
OH, NO.
NO, NO, TRAVIS, PUT DOWN THE GUN.
NO, NO, NO, HE'S YOUR BUDDY.
HE'S YOUR YELLER. NO.
NO, NO. THE END! THE END!
OKAY, WHAT KIND OF A SICK DOGGIE SNUFF FILM IS THIS?!
HEY, HAVE YOU GUYS EATEN?
BECAUSE RICHARD AND I JUST FINISHED
AND WE'VE GOT LEFTOVERS.
CHICKEN AND POTATOES.
WHAT AM I WEARING?
ACTUALLY, NOTHING BUT RUBBER GLOVES.
YOU KNOW, ONE OF THESE TIMES
YOU'RE GOING TO REALLY BE NAKED
AND WE'RE NOT GOING TO COME OVER.
OOH, THAT WOULD TEACH ME A LESSON.
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, I'VE GOT A LEG
THREE BREASTS AND A WING.
HOW DO YOU FIND CLOTHES THAT FIT?
OH, HEY, MONICA, WE GOT A QUESTION.
ALL RIGHT, FOR THE ZILLIONTH TIME
YES, I SEE OTHER WOMEN IN THE SHOWER AT THE GYM
AND, NO, I DON'T LOOK.
NO, NOT THAT ONE.
WE'RE TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHO TO BRING TO THE KNICKS GAME TONIGHT.
WE HAVE AN EXTRA TICKET.
YEAH, ROSS CAN'T GO.
SO IT'S BETWEEN MY FRIEND ERIC PROWER
WHO HAS BREATH ISSUES
AND DAN, WITH THE POKING.
"DID YOU SEE THAT PLAY?"
"DO YOU WANT
SOME MORE BEER?"
"IS THAT SPIKE LEE?"
OKAY.
HEY, WHY DON'T YOU ASK RICHARD?
OKAY. HEY, RICHARD.
IF YOU HAD AN EXTRA TICKET
TO THE KNICKS GAME...
AND YOU HAD TO CHOOSE BETWEEN A FRIEND
WHO SMELLED AND ONE WHO...
BRUISES YOU
WHO WOULD YOU PICK?
WOW.
WELL, BEING A HUGE KNICKS FAN MYSELF
I THINK YOU SHOULD TAKE SOMEONE
WHO'S A HUGE KNICKS FAN.
OKAY.
THAT'S ERIC.
GLAD TO BE OF HELP.
MATCHES.
I MEANT
WHY DON'T YOU TAKE RICHARD TO THE GAME?
WHAT?
I DON'T KNOW...
COME ON.
HE KEEPS HIS FINGERS TO HIMSELF
AND HE'S ALWAYS MINTY FRESH.
RICHARD'S REALLY NICE AND EVERYTHING.
IT'S JUST WE DON'T KNOW HIM REALLY WELL
YOU KNOW, AND PLUS, HE'S, YOU KNOW, OLD...
ERTHAN SOME PEOPLE
BUT, UH, YOUNGER THAN SOME BUILDINGS.
SO HE'S A LITTLE OLDER.
BIG DEAL.
I MEAN, HE'S IMPORTANT TO ME.
YOU KNOW, IF YOU ASK HIM, HE MIGHT TAKE YOU IN HIS JAG.
HOW DO WE SAY "YES" NOW
AND MAKE IT SEEM LIKE WE'RE NOT DOING IT
JUST TO RIDE IN THE COOL CAR?
OKAY, THIS COULD BE TOUGH.
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
MONICA, WE'LL BRING HIM
BUT ONLY IF HE TAKES THE JAGUAR.
OOH, YOU ALMOST HAD IT.
NO, NO. YOU'RE FINE.
YOU'RE FINE.
HELLO.
HI.
HI, HONEY.
YOU GUYS ARE NOT GOING TO BELIEVE WHAT HAPPENED.
WHAT? WHAT?
WE WERE SITTING OVER THERE
PLAYING ON THE FLOOR
AND HE GRABS THE TABLE AND HE PULLS HIMSELF UP.
HE PULLED HIMSELF UP.
STANDING MAN.
I'M SORRY YOU GUYS MISSED IT
BUT I DID TAPE IT
SO IF YOU GUYS WANT TO SEE IT...
UH, WE KNOW.
HE ALREADY DID IT LAST WEEK.
YOU CAN WATCH OUR TAPE IF YOU WANT.
SEE? I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
I MISSED... I MISSED THE FIRST TIME OF EVERYTHING.
I MISSED THE FIRST TIME HE ROLLED OVER
THE FIRST TIME HE CRAWLED.
WHAT ELSE DID I MISS?
HAS HE SPOKEN YET? IS HE DRIVING?
DOES HE HAVE A FAVORITE LIQUEUR?
YOU KNOW, ACTUALLY
HE'S GETTING CLOSER ON THE TALKING THING.
HE CAN'T QUITE SAY "MAMA" YET
BUT ONCE HE SAID "YEMEN."
SEE?
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M SO SICK OF MISSING STUFF.
I WANT HIM FOR MORE THAN A DAY.
I WANT HIM FOR A WHOLE WEEKEND.
NO, LISTEN...
THAT'LL BE FINE. THAT WILL BE GREAT.
REALLY?
I MEAN, I HAD A WHOLE SPEECH PREPARED.
OH, SHOOT. THAT WOULD HAVE BEEN FUN.
OH, LOOK, DID... DID YOU JUST SEE THAT?
DID YOU SEE? HE JUST WAVED. HE JUST WAVED!
HE'S NEVER WAVED BEFORE!
YOU'VE NEVER WAVED BEFORE!
YES, HE HAS.
VERY GOOD.
HEY.
HEY, PHEEBS.
WHAT YOU GOT THERE?
OKAY. LOVE STORY, BRIAN'S SONG
AND TERMS OF ENDEARMENT.
WOW. ALL YOU NEED NOW IS THE KILLING FIELDS
AND SOME GUACAMOLE
AND YOU GOT YOURSELF A PAR TAY.
YEAH. I TALKED TO MY GRANDMA ABOUT THE OLD YELLER INCIDENT
AND SHE TOLD ME THAT MY MOM USED TO NOT SHOW US
THE ENDS OF SAD MOVIES TO SHIELD US FROM THE PAIN AND SADNESS
YOU KNOW, BEFORE SHE KILLED HERSELF.
HEY.
WHERE IS HE? WHERE'S RICHARD?
DID YOU DITCH HIM?
YEAH, RIGHT AFTER WE STOLE HIS LUNCH MONEY
AND GAVE HIM A WEDGIE.
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU?
HE'S PARKING THE CAR.
DID YOU GUYS HAVE FUN?
YOUR BOYFRIEND IS SO COOL.
REALLY?
YEAH, HE LET US DRIVE HIS JAGUAR.
JOEY FOR 12 BLOCKS, ME FOR 15.
WOW.
HE MUST LIKE YOU THE BEST.
OH, AND WHAT ABOUT THAT THING HE DID
WHEN HE TIPPED THE GUY WHO SHOWED US TO OUR SEATS?
YOU NEVER EVEN SAW THE MONEY.
IT WAS LIKE THIS.
"HEY, CHANDLER
THANKS FOR SHOWING US TO OUR SEATS."
"YOU'RE WELCOME.
HEY, JOEY, THANKS FOR PARKING THE CAR."
"NO PROBLEM.
HEY, CHANDLER..."
I THINK THEY GET IT.
OKAY.
THERE'S THE MAN!
HEY!
HEY, YOU'RE GETTING BETTER.
I'M GOING TO KEEP THIS, BY THE WAY.
OKAY...
HE KEPT MY DOLLAR.
SO, YOUR FIRST WHOLE WEEKEND WITHOUT BEN.
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS GOING TO DO?
WE'RE GOING DOWN TO COLONIAL WILLIAMSBURG.
A WOMAN I WENT TO COLLEGE WITH
JUST BECAME THE FIRST FEMALE BLACKSMITH DOWN THERE.
WELL, YOU KNOW
THEY'RE A LITTLE BEHIND THE TIMES
IN COLONIAL WILLIAMSBURG.
OKAY, WELL, LOOK, I BETTER GO
BEFORE MOMMY STARTS WEEPING.
BYE.
WE LOVE YOU.
"BYE, MOMMY. BYE, MOMMY."
HAVE A GOOD TIME. BYE.
OKAY, BEN...
ROSS?
YEAH?
LOOK.
JOEY, DO YOU KNOW WE CAN SEE YOU FROM HERE?
HOW COME RICHARD LOOKS SO MUCH COOLER
WITH ONE OF THESE THAN ME?
FOR STARTERS, YOU MAY WANT TO LIGHT IT
AND LOSE THE SPATULA.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK IT'S CUTE--
YOU TRYING TO BE LIKE RICHARD.
NOT LIKE HIM, PER SE
JUST NOT UNLIKE HIM.
LOOK, IT'S THE ARTIST FORMALLY KNOWN AS CHANDLER.
I WAS JUST TRYING SOMETHING HERE, YOU KNOW?
JOEY, WHY DIDN'T YOU GROW A MUSTACHE?
OH, WE FLIPPED FOR IT.
I GOT THE CIGAR, HE GOT THE MUSTACHE.
WE FIGURED IF WE BOTH GREW THEM
WE'D LOOK LIKE DORKS.
YEAH, YOU REALLY SIDE STEPPED
THAT LAND MINE.
HEY, LISTEN, WE GOT TO GO.
I PROMISED RICHARD WE'D MEET HIM DOWNSTAIRS.
YOU'RE MEETING RICHARD?
YEAH, WE'RE GOING TO A RANGER GAME.
DIDN'T HE TELL YOU?
HE TOLD ME HE WAS
GOING OUT WITH THE GUYS.
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU WERE THE GUYS.
YOU HEAR THAT?
WE'RE "THE GUYS."
WITH THAT MUSTACHE
DOESN'T CHANDLER REMIND YOU OF AUNT SYLVIA?
THANK YOU!
HI. WE'RE VISITING.
YAY!
IT'S BEN AND HIS... DA DA.
DA DA.
CAN YOU SAY "DA DA"?
OH...
I'M GOING TO TELL YOUR MOMMIES YOU SAID IT ANYWAY
SO YOU MIGHT AS WELL TRY.
NO LUCK, HUH?
NO. A WHILE AGO, I GOT A "SEH" OUT OF HIM
WHICH I THOUGHT, YOU KNOW, MIGHT TURN INTO
"SEH CONDARY CAREGIVER," BUT...
HEY, WOULD YOU HOLD HIM FOR A SEC?
BECAUSE I GOT TO TAKE THIS OFF.
OH. YEAH.
SURE. OKAY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'M HOLDING BEN.
YEAH, WELL
HE'S A BABY, NOT A BOMB.
OKAY.
JUST HOLD HIM LIKE YOU'D HOLD A FOOTBALL.
THIS IS HOW I WOULD HOLD A FOOTBALL.
OKAY, HERE, HERE.
THERE WE GO.
OKAY. I'M SORRY.
I'M JUST NOT VERY GOOD WITH BABIES.
I MEAN, I HAVEN'T BEEN AROUND THEM.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW, SINCE I WAS ONE.
THAT'S ALL RIGHT. IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
REALLY? YEAH, DEFINITELY.
I'M SURE YOU'LL FEEL TOTALLY DIFFERENT
WHEN IT'S OUR BABY. WHAT?
WHAT?
YOU THINK ABOUT STUFF LIKE THAT?
UH... YEAH.
I MEAN, ACTUALLY, I KIND OF THINK
THAT WE'LL HAVE... WE'LL HAVE TWO BABIES.
TWO... TWO BABIES?
YEAH. YOU KNOW, A BOY AND A GIRL.
HOPEFULLY, THE GIRL WILL COME FIRST
SO BEN HERE WON'T FEEL TOO COMPETITIVE.
UM... TH THEN WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN?
WELL, WE WON'T WANT TO RAISE KIDS IN THE CITY
SO WE'LL PROBABLY MOVE TO SCARSDALE.
SCAR... UH HUH. THAT WAY, I FIGURE
WE'LL BE FAR ENOUGH AWAY FROM OUR PARENTS
THAT WE DON'T HAVE TO SEE THEM ALL THE TIME
BUT CLOSE ENOUGH THAT THEY CAN
COME OVER AND BABY SIT WHENEVER WE WANT.
AND, YES, I KNOW THE TAXES ARE A LITTLE HIGHER
THAN, LET'S SAY, NASSAU COUNTY
BUT THE SCHOOL SYSTEM'S SUPPOSEDLY GREAT.
WOW.
WOW, THAT'S GREAT.
GREAT.
OKAY, WOW, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M OFF MY BREAK NOW
SO, UH, UM, HERE--
YOU TAKE THIS
AND, UM...
I AM GOING TO GO POUR
THESE VERY NICE PEOPLE SOME COFFEE.
OKAY.
OH, LOOK AT THAT.
I DON'T HAVE A POT.
WELL, HEY, MAYBE I'VE GOT ONE AT HOME...
OR IN SCARSDALE.
HEY, IS THAT A DOOR?
RACH?
HEY.
HEY, PHEEBS, WHAT'S HAPPENING?
OH, OKAY, MURDER, CANCER
SOCCER TEAMS EATING EACH OTHER IN THE ANDES.
I WAS REALLY JUST MAKING SMALL TALK.
OKAY, WELL, I WAS JUST VENTING.
SO YOU WATCHED THE MOVIES, HUH?
UH HUH. WHAT IS HAPPENING TO THE WORLD?
I MEAN... NO, NO, NO.
BECAUSE E.T. LEAVES AND ROCKY LOSES.
CHARLOTTE DIES.
CHARLOTTE WHO?
WITH THE WEB. THE SPIDER.
SHE DIES.
SHE HAS BABIES AND DIES.
IT'S, LIKE, "HEY, WELCOME HOME FROM THE HOSPITAL." THUD.
ALL RIGHT, YOU WANT TO FEEL BETTER?
YEAH.
OKAY.
HERE. WATCH THIS.
IT'S A WONDERFUL LIFE.
YES, I'VE HEARD OF THIS.
SO YOU CAN'T LOSE.
IT'S THERE IN THE TITLE.
THE WONDERFULNESS IS BAKED RIGHT IN.
PLEASE, I ALMOST FELL FOR THAT WITH PRIDE OF THE YANKEES.
I THOUGHT I WAS GOING TO SEE A FILM ABOUT YANKEE PRIDE
AND THEN, BOOM, THE GUY GETS LOU GEHRIG'S DISEASE.
THE GUY WAS LOU GEHRIG.
DIDN'T YOU KIND OF SEE IT COMING?
PHOEBE, JUST WATCH THAT.
I PROMISE YOU IT WILL RESTORE ALL YOUR FAITH IN HUMANITY.
HEY, BIG GUY, GAME TIME.
HEY, BE RIGHT THERE.
THERE'S A GAME?
YEAH, I JUST GOT MY PICK UP STICKS
BACK FROM THE SHOP.
BRING YOUR NERVES OF STEEL.
IT'S THE BASKETBALL PLAY OFFS.
LISTEN, HONEY, I APPRECIATE THIS
BUT YOU DON'T HAVE TO KEEP HANGING OUT WITH THEM FOR ME.
I MEAN, THEY HAVE EACH OTHER.
OH, NO, HONEY, I MEAN, DON'T WORRY.
I LIKE HANGING OUT WITH THOSE GUYS.
IT'S FUN FOR ME.
THEY'RE DIFFERENT THAN MY OTHER FRIENDS.
THEY DON'T START SENTENCES
WITH, "YOU KNOW WHO JUST DIED SHOVELING SNOW?"
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S GREAT.
THEN JUST GO.
GO, KNICKS!
UH, IT'S THE COLLEGE PLAY OFFS.
OH. THEN... GO, VASSAR!
THEY'RE NOT IN IT.
OKAY, THEN JUST GO.
OKAY.
WHY DOES THIS BOTHER ME SO MUCH?
I MEAN, I DON'T WANT TO BE ONE OF THOSE PEOPLE
WHO TELLS THEIR BOYFRIEND
THEY WANT TO SPEND 24 HOURS A DAY WITH HIM.
SURE.
HE DOESN'T HAVE THAT MUCH FREE TIME.
I DON'T KNOW. WHAT DO I DO?
DOES IT MATTER?
YOU'RE ULTIMATELY JUST GOING TO DIE OR GET DIVORCED
OR HAVE TO BLOW YOUR PET'S HEAD OFF.
UCH!
ME, TOO.
RACHEL, I GOT A QUESTION.
RICHARD MADE PLANS AGAIN WITH THE GUYS.
YEAH, WELL, ROSS JUST MADE PLANS
FOR THE WHOLE CENTURY.
I THINK I'M GOING TO GO TO MY ROOM AND READ COSMO.
MAYBE THERE'S SOMETHING HELPFUL IN THERE.
IF NOT, AT LEAST MAYBE I CAN LEARN HOW
TO DO AN AT HOME BIKINI WAX WITH LEFTOVER CHRISTMAS CANDLES.
OKAY, WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED BACK THERE?
I DON'T KNOW. YOU TELL ME.
ONE MINUTE, I'M HOLDING BEN LIKE A FOOTBALL.
THE NEXT THING I KNOW, I'VE GOT TWO KIDS
I'M LIVING IN SCARSDALE COMPLAINING ABOUT THE TAXES.
WELL, I'M SORRY. I THINK ABOUT STUFF, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, YOU'RE AT WORK, YOU'RE ASSEMBLING BONES
YOUR MIND WANDERS.
ROSS, YOU HAVE PLANNED OUT
THE NEXT 20 YEARS OF OUR LIVES.
WE'VE BEEN DATING FOR SIX WEEKS.
OH, COME ON. WHAT?
YOU NEVER THINK ABOUT OUR FUTURE?
YES, BUT I THINK ABOUT WHOSE APARTMENT
WE'RE GOING TO SLEEP AT TOMORROW NIGHT
AND WHERE WE'RE GOING TO HAVE DINNER NEXT SATURDAY NIGHT.
I DO NOT THINK ABOUT WHAT OUR CHILDREN'S NAMES ARE GOING
TO BE.
YOU KNOW WHAT
OUR CHILDREN'S NAMES ARE GOING TO BE.
NO. NO. I MEAN, YOU KNOW, I READ A BOOK
AND THERE WAS A GIRL NAMED EMILY
AND I THOUGHT... I THOUGHT THAT MIGHT BE GOOD.
WHAT WAS THE BOOK?
"THE BIG BOOK OF CHILDREN'S NAMES."
OKAY, ROSS, ROSS, OKAY, LISTEN.
WHAT WE HAVE IS AMAZING.
YEAH.
BUT I DO NOT WANT TO HAVE EVERYTHING DECIDED FOR ME.
I SPENT MY WHOLE LIFE LIKE THAT.
THAT'S WHAT I HAD WITH BARRY.
THAT WAS ONE OF THE REASONS I LEFT.
I LIKE NOT KNOWING RIGHT NOW.
AND I'M SORRY IF THAT SCARES YOU
BUT IF YOU WANT TO BE WITH ME
YOU ARE GOING TO HAVE TO DEAL WITH THAT.
OKAY, FINE.
THANK YOU.
WE'RE NOT DONE.
I DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
THEN YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO UNDERSTAND
THAT YOU'RE WITH A GUY
WHO'S NOT GOING TO STOP PLANNING HIS FUTURE WITH YOU
BECAUSE HE KNOWS WE'RE GOING TO END UP TOGETHER
AND IF THAT SCARES YOU, TOUGH
BECAUSE YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO DEAL WITH THAT.
FINE. I WILL.
GOOD. BECAUSE I LOVE YOU.
YEAH. OH, YEAH? I LOVE YOU, TOO.
WELL, THAT'S THE FIRST TIME WE'VE SAID THAT.
YES, IT IS.
I'M GOING TO KISS YOU.
WELL, YOU BETTER.
HEY.
OH, THANKS FOR THE GREAT MOVIE TIP.
OH, YEAH. DID YOU LIKE IT?
I DON'T KNOW IF I WAS HAPPIER
WHEN GEORGE BAILEY DESTROYED THE FAMILY BUSINESS
OR DONNA REED CRIED
OR WHEN THE MEAN PHARMACIST MADE HIS EAR BLEED.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL GIVE YOU THE EAR THING
BUT DON'T YOU THINK THE ENDING WAS PRETTY WONDERFUL?
I DIDN'T WATCH THE ENDING.
I WAS TOO DEPRESSED.
IT JUST KEPT GETTING WORSE AND WORSE.
IT SHOULD HAVE BEEN CALLED IT'S A SUCKY LIFE
AND JUST WHEN YOU THINK IT CAN'T SUCK ANY MORE, IT DOES.
KICK SAVE
AND DENIED.
BUT HE GETS IT BACK
PASS TO THE MIDDLE, LINES IT UP
AND, BAM, YES!
COULD THAT SHOT BE ANY PRETTIER?
MAN, YOU ARE INCREDIBLE.
WELL, WE HAD A TABLE IN COLLEGE.
REALLY? I DIDN'T KNOW THEY HAD FOOSBALL IN THE 1800s.
NICE MUSTACHE, BY THE WAY.
WHEN PUBERTY HITS
THAT THING'S REALLY GOING TO KICK IN.
HONEY, NOT TO SOUND TOO FLORENCE HENDERSON
BUT DINNER'S ON THE TABLE.
OKAY, JUST ONE MORE POINT.
SCORE!
NOW CAN WE GO?
SEE, THAT'S WHY WE DON'T LET HER PLAY.
IS EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT?
MM HMM.
UH OH.
HEY, LISTEN, DON'T BE MAD AT HIM.
IT'S OUR FAULT.
I'M SORRY WE'VE BEEN HOGGING
SO MUCH OF HIS TIME.
YEAH, HE'S JUST REALLY GREAT TO HANG OUT WITH.
NO, SERIOUSLY. WELL...
CHANDLER AND I WERE JUST TALKING ABOUT THIS.
HE IS SO MUCH COOLER THAN OUR DADS.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW, OUR DADS ARE OKAY AND ALL
BUT RICHARD IS JUST... OW! OW!
WHAT ARE YOU KICKING ME FOR?
HUH?
I'M TRYING TO TALK HERE.
UH... YOU GUYS SEE ME AS A DAD?
OH, YEAH.
NO.
YOU'RE JUST CLEARLY NOT FAMILIAR
WITH OUR YOUNG PERSON'S VERNACULAR.
SEE, WHEN WE SAY "DAD," WE MEAN "BUDDY."
WE MEAN "PAL."
UH HUH. YEAH.
NO, SERIOUSLY, JOEY'S MY DAD.
MONICA'S MY DAD.
I'VE EVEN GOT SOME DADS DOWN AT WORK.
THAT'S FINE.
WELL, YOUR OTHER DAD AND I
ARE GOING TO GO HAVE A ROMANTIC EVENING
AND I GUESS I'LL JUST SEE YOU KIDS AROUND.
NIGHTY NIGHT.
YOU'RE NOT A DAD.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU GOT US INTO TROUBLE.
SO, ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH.
IT'S JUST I FEEL LIKE I'M ABOUT A HUNDRED.
I THOUGHT I WAS JUST ONE OF THE GUYS.
COME HERE.
I'LL MAKE YOU FEEL LIKE ONE OF THE GUYS.
YOU KNOW, FOR A REALLY COOL GUY
YOU SUCK AT FOOSBALL.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I WAS KILLING THEM.
YEAH, WELL, THEY SUCK, TOO.
THEN YOU TAKE THE POOPY DIAPER
AND YOU PUT IT IN THE POOPY DIAPER PAIL.
OKAY, ROSS, JUST SO YOU KNOW
CALLING IT A "POOPY DIAPER"
DOESN'T MAKE THIS PROCESS ANY CUTER.
HELLO.
It's us.
COME ON UP.
I'M GOING TO GET THE REST OF HIS STUFF TOGETHER.
OKAY, WE CAN DO THIS, NOW, CAN'T WE, BEN?
YES, WE CAN.
THERE. I DID IT.
OH HO! I DID IT.
OOH!
LOOK AT THAT.
OH! IT STAYS ON AND EVERYTHING.
HI.
I'M SORRY.
WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY?
DID YOU JUST SAY "HI"?
OH, MY GOD.
ROSS, ROSS, BEN JUST SAID "HI."
BEN JUST SAID "HI."
WHAT, THE WORD "HI"?
NO, MY UNCLE HY.
GREAT. GREAT. AND I MISSED THAT, TOO.
I MISS EVERYTHING.
OH, I'M SORRY.
I GUESS I JUST BRING IT OUT IN HIM.
HELLO. WHERE IS HE?
WE MISSED YOU SO MUCH.
COME HERE, BEN.
HI.
GUESS WHAT. BEN JUST SAID HIS FIRST WORD.
WHAT DID HE SAY?
SOMETHING ABOUT "HI."
OH, THAT'S SO EXCITING.
MOMMY'S SO PROUD OF YOU.
HI.
ACTUALLY, IT'S MORE LIKEHI!
OKAY, THIS COULD GO ON FOR A WHILE.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE'VE GOT A CAB WAITING DOWNSTAIRS.
THIS WAS FUN.
WE SHOULD REALLY DO IT AGAIN SOMETIME, BEN.
WHAT DO YOU SAY? OKAY.
SO I'VE GOT HIM... TUESDAY.
TUESDAY. RIGHT.
OKAY, BYE, YOU GUYS.
TAKE CARE.
BYE, BEN.
BYE.
DID HE JUST... DID HE JUST SAY "BYE"?
HE SAID "BYE."
HE SAID "BYE" TO ME!
YES, HE DID.
SUDDENLY I'M SEEING HIM GO OFF TO COLLEGE.
WE GOT TO GO.
WE GOT THAT CAB DOWNSTAIRS.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
SEE YOU LATER.
BYE.
BYE!
OHH!
Oh, wow. Look at this nice deep hole I've been digging.
Hey, Bert, isn't this a nice hole here?
OKAY, BEN, THIS IS THE PART
WHERE ERNIE BURIES BERT IN THE SAND AND CAN'T FIND HIM.
NOW, I'VE LOOKED AHEAD ON THE TAPE
AND HE DOES FIND HIM AGAIN.
BUT, OKAY, BEFORE THAT HAPPENS
THERE'S SOME PRETTY ROUGH GOING FOR A WHILE.
BUT I THINK WE CAN HANDLE IT.
AND THERE'S JUST THE ALPHABET, BUT WE KNOW THAT ENDS WELL.
SO... OKAY, HERE WE GO.
Bert? Bert? Bert?
Hey, what happened to my friend Bert?
He was here just a moment ago.
Oh, no, my old friend Bert is lost.
I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE HERE.