MAN, THIS IS WEIRD.
YOU EVER REALIZE
CAP'N CRUNCH'S EYEBROWS ARE ACTUALLY ON HIS HAT?
THAT'S WHAT'S WEIRD?
JOEY, THE MAN'S BEEN CAPTAIN OF A CEREAL
FOR THE LAST 40 YEARS.
BAH! LAH!
WHAT?
THE SPOON.
YOU LICKED AND AND YOU PUT.
YOU LICKED AND YOU PUT.
YEAH? SO?
WELL, DON'T YOU SEE HOW GROSS THAT IS?
I MEAN, THAT'S LIKE YOU'RE USING MY TOOTHBRUSH.
YOU USED MY TOOTHBRUSH?
WELL, THAT WAS ONLY BECAUSE I USED THE RED ONE
TO UNCLOG THE DRAIN.
MINE IS THE RED ONE!
OH, GOD.
CAN OPEN.
WORMS EVERYWHERE.
HEY, WHY CAN'T WE USE THE SAME TOOTHBRUSH
BUT WE CAN USE THE SAME SOAP?
BECAUSE SOAP IS SOAP.
IT'S SELF CLEANING.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, NEXT TIME YOU TAKE A SHOWER
THINK ABOUT THE LAST THING I WASH
AND THE FIRST THING YOU WASH.
HEY.
HEY. HEY.
OOH, LOOK AT YOU FANCY LADS.
WHAT'S THE OCCASION?
WELL, YOU KNOW THE GUY ON MY SHOW THAT'S IN A COMA?
HE'S HAVING A BRUNCH.
HEY. READY WHEN YOU ARE.
OKEY DOKE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU GUYS
ARE ACTUALLY GETTING TATTOOS.
EXCUSE ME. YOU GUYS ARE GETTING TATTOOS?
YES, BUT YOU CANNOT TELL ROSS
BECAUSE I WANT TO SURPRISE HIM.
WOW. THIS IS WILD.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO GET?
UM, I'M GETTING A LILY.
FOR MY MOM, BECAUSE HER NAME'S LILY.
WOW. THAT'S LUCKY.
WHAT IF HER NAME WAS "BIG UGLY SPLOTCH"?
SO WHERE YOU GETTING IT?
I THINK ON MY SHOULDER.
WHAT?
WHAT'S ON YOUR SHOULDER?
UM, A CHIP.
I'VE GOT A BIG ATTITUDE PROBLEM.
A TATTOO. I'M GETTING A TATTOO.
A TATTOO?
WHY? WHY WOULD YOU WANT TO DO THAT?
HI.
WELL, HEY, YOU DON'T THINK THEY'RE KIND OF COOL?
NO. SORRY. I DON'T.
I MEAN, WHY WOULD ANYONE PAY SOMEONE
TO SCAR THEIR BODY FOR LIFE?
AND WHAT IF IT DOESN'T COME OUT RIGHT, PHEEBS?
IT'S LIKE HAVING A BAD HAIRCUT ALL THE TIME.
WHY IS EVERYONE STARING AT ME?
ROSS, COME SIGN THIS BIRTHDAY CARD FOR DAD.
RICHARD'S GOING TO BE HERE ANY MINUTE.
OOH, RICH IS GOING TO THE PARTY, TOO, HUH?
WELL, HE'S MY PARENTS' BEST FRIEND.
HE HAS TO BE THERE.
SO, IS TODAY THE DAY
YOU'RE GOING TO TELL THEM ABOUT YOU TWO?
YEAH, FOR MY DAD'S BIRTHDAY, I DECIDED TO GIVE HIM A STROKE.
YOU KNOW, I THINK YOU SHOULD TELL THEM.
NO. I DON'T EVEN KNOW HOW SERIOUS HE IS ABOUT ME.
UNTIL I DO, I'M NOT TELLING THEM ANYTHING.
I DON'T KNOW. I DON'T THINK MOM AND DAD WOULD MIND.
REMEMBER WHEN YOU WERE NINE, AND RICHARD WAS 30
HOW DAD USED TO SAY, "GOD, I HOPE THEY GET TOGETHER"?
HELLO?
It's me. I'm double parked.
OKAY. COME ON, ROSS. BYE, GUYS.
SEE YOU. SEE YOU.
OKAY.
OH, BYE, YOU.
BYE.
HMM.
BYE, YOU.
OKAY, HERE WE GO.
HERE WE GO. HERE WE GO. HERE WE GO.
OKAY, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
IT'S GOING TO BE FINE.
HOW CAN YOU SAY THAT?
ARE YOU NOT NERVOUS?
I'M TERRIFIED.
THIS IS JUST A VERY ABSORBENT SUIT.
ALL RIGHT, SHALL WE, MONICA?
YES, YES.
NO. YOU KNOW WHAT?
ROSS, LET'S LET'S SWITCH PLACES.
YOU GET IN THE MIDDLE.
OKAY. YOU KNOW WHAT?
UNLESS THIS LOOKS LIKE WE'RE TRYING
TO COVER SOMETHING UP.
MONICA, MONICA, YOU COULD COME IN STRADDLING HIM.
THEY STILL WOULDN'T BELIEVE IT.
WE'RE HERE.
OH, HI, KIDS.
HI, DARLING.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, DAD.
OH, THANK YOU.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
SO, YOU KIDS THANK DR. BURKE FOR THE RIDE?
UH, ACTUALLY, MOM
I THINK MONICA THANKED HIM FOR THE BOTH OF US.
SO, YOU KIDS TAKE THE TRAIN IN?
NO. RICHARD BURKE GAVE THEM A RIDE.
OH. SPEAKING OF WHOM...
I HEAR HE'S GOT SOME 20 YEAR OLD TWINKIE
IN THE CITY.
OH, HONEY!
FINGER CRAMP.
OH, GOD.
SORRY.
HERE. LET ME GET THAT, MOM.
SO, RICHARD'S SHOPPING IN THE JUNIOR SECTION.
MM HMM.
ARE WE STILL ON THAT?
AND YOU JUST KNOW SHE'S GOT THE I.Q. OF A NAPKIN.
MM HMM.
SHE'S PROBABLY NOT EVEN VERY PRETTY-
JUST YOUNG ENOUGH SO THAT EVERYTHING IS STILL POINTING UP.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THIS PLACE?
I KNOW. THIS IS A GREAT APARTMENT.
OH! I WAS JUST IN THE BATHROOM
AND THERE'S MIRRORS ON BOTH SIDES OF YOU.
SO WHEN YOU'RE IN THERE
IT'S LIKE YOU'RE PEEING WITH THE ROCKETTES.
WELL, THERE'S MY FANTASY COME TRUE.
NO, SERIOUSLY.
HEY.
HEY. WE WERE JUST SAYING, GREAT APARTMENT, MAN.
THANKS. YOU WANT IT? HUH?
YEAH, I'M MOVING TO A BIGGER PLACE.
YOU SHOULD DEFINITELY TAKE THIS ONE.
YEAH. CAN YOU SEE ME IN A PLACE LIKE THIS?
WHY NOT? YOU HATE PARK VIEWS AND HIGH CEILINGS?
COME ON. I'LL SHOW YOU THE KITCHEN.
OH, THAT'S ALL RIGHT, FELLAS.
I SAW A KITCHEN THIS MORNING... ON TV.
STOP TALKING. OKAY.
COME ON, TELL US.
YEAH, IS SHE REALLY 2O?
I AM NOT TELLING YOU GUYS ANYTHING.
COME ON, RICH, IT'S MY BIRTHDAY.
LET ME LIVE VICARIOUSLY.
DAD, YOU REALLY DON'T WANT TO DO THAT.
AH, WHAT'S A LITTLE MIDLIFE CRISIS BETWEEN FRIENDS?
JACK, WOULD YOU LET IT GO?
LOOK, I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE GOING THROUGH.
WHEN I TURNED 50, I GOT THE PORSCHE.
YOU, YOU GOT YOUR OWN LITTLE SPEEDSTER.
GUYS, SERIOUSLY, IT IS NOT LIKE THAT.
TELL YOU WHAT.
MAYBE, ONE OF THESE WEEKENDS
YOU CAN BORROW THE CAR, AND I COULD...
DAD, I BEG YOU NOT TO FINISH THAT SENTENCE.
WHAT? I'M KIDDING.
YOU KNOW I'D NEVER LET HIM TOUCH THE PORSCHE.
OKAY, RACH
WHICH... WHICH LILY?
THIS LILY OR THAT LILY?
WELL, I... I LIKE THIS LILY.
IT'S MORE OPEN, YOU KNOW?
AND THAT'S LIKE MY MOM--
SHE HAD A MORE OPEN, GIVING SPIRIT.
OOH, FOGHORN LEGHORN! OH...
ALL RIGHT.
BLOND GIRL, YOU'RE IN ROOM TWO.
NOT SO BLOND GIRL, YOU'RE WITH ME.
OKAY, HERE WE GO.
UH HUH.
YOU'RE NOT GOING?
WHAT, IS IT... IS THIS BECAUSE OF WHAT ROSS SAID?
NO.
WELL, YEAH, MAYBE.
I DON'T BELIEVE THIS.
IS THIS HOW THIS RELATIONSHIP'S GOING TO WORK?
ROSS EQUALS BOSS?
I MEAN...
COME ON, WHAT IS THIS- 1922?
WHAT'S 1922?
JUST, YOU KNOW, A LONG TIME AGO.
WELL, WHEN MEN USED TO TELL WOMEN WHAT TO DO A LOT.
AND THEN THERE WAS SUFFRAGE
WHICH WAS A GOOD THING, BUT IT SOUNDS HORRIBLE.
DO YOU WANT TO GET THIS TATTOO?
YES, I DO. IT'S JUST THAT ROSS...
OKAY, HEY, HEY!
IS YOUR BOYFRIEND THE BOSS OF YOU?
NO.
OKAY, WHO IS THE BOSS OF YOU?
YOU?
NO. YOU ARE THE BOSS OF YOU.
NOW, YOU MARCH YOUR HEINIE IN THERE
AND GET THAT HEART TATTOOED ON YOUR HIP.
GO!
I HAVEN'T EVEN GOTTEN MY TATTOO YET
AND I'M ALREADY TOUGHER.
HOW YOU DOING?
I'M A TWINKIE.
REALLY? I'M A HERO.
OH...
AH...
THIS IS SO HARD.
YEAH, I KNOW.
I HATE IT, TOO.
LOOK, MAYBE WE SHOULD JUST TELL THEM.
MAYBE WE SHOULD JUST TELL YOUR PARENTS FIRST.
MY PARENTS ARE DEAD.
GOD, YOU ARE SO LUCKY.
NO, NO.
I MEAN, WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
I KNOW. I KNOW.
JUST HANG IN THERE, OKAY?
OKAY, I'LL GO OUT FIRST, ALL RIGHT?
ALL RIGHT.
JUDY. GOING TO THE BATHROOM!
GOOD FOR YOU!
THANK YOU, RICHARD.
I APPRECIATE THE SUPPORT.
HONEY, HAVE YOU SEEN
MY HARMON KILL EBREW BAT?
BOB DOESN'T BELIEVE I HAVE ONE.
I HAVE NO IDEA.
DID YOU KNOW RICHARD HAS A TWINKIE IN THE CITY?
I KNOW. HE'S LIKE A NEW MAN.
IT'S LIKE A SCENE FROM COCOON.
I JUST NEVER WOULD HAVE PICTURED RICHARD WITH A BIMBO.
APPARENTLY, HE TOLD JOHNNY SHAPIRO THAT SHE'S QUITE A GIRL.
IN FACT, HE TOLD JOHNNY
THAT HE THINKS HE'S FALLING IN LOVE WITH HER.
REALLY?
I TELL YOU, I'VE NEVER SEEN HIM THIS HAPPY.
SO, JACK, YOU EVER THINK
ABOUT TRADING ME IN FOR A YOUNGER MODEL?
OF COURSE NOT.
WITH YOU, IT'S LIKE I'VE GOT TWO 25 YEAR OLDS.
OH, JACK, STOP.
COME ON.
IT'S MY BIRTHDAY.
CAN WE DROP THIS?
I AM NOT INTERESTED IN THE GUY'S APARTMENT.
OH, PLEASE.
I SAW THE WAY YOU WERE CHECKING OUT HIS MOLDINGS.
YOU WANT IT.
WHY WOULD I WANT ANOTHER APARTMENT? HUH?
I'VE ALREADY GOT AN APARTMENT THAT I LOVE.
WELL, IT WOULDN'T KILL YOU TO SAY IT
ONCE IN A WHILE.
ALL RIGHT, YOU WANT THE TRUTH?
I'M THINKING ABOUT IT.
WHAT?
I'M SORRY. I'M 28 YEARS OLD.
I'VE NEVER LIVED ALONE
AND I'M FINALLY AT A PLACE WHERE I GOT ENOUGH MONEY
THAT I DON'T NEED A ROOMMATE ANYMORE.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
I DON'T NEED A ROOMMATE EITHER, OKAY?
I CAN AFFORD TO LIVE HERE BY MYSELF.
YOU KNOW, I MAY HAVE TO BRING IN SOMEBODY ONCE A WEEK
TO LICK THE SILVERWARE.
WHAT ARE YOU GETTING SO BENT OUT OF SHAPE FOR, HUH?
IT'S NOT LIKE WE AGREED TO LIVE TOGETHER FOREVER.
WE'RE NOT BERT AND ERNIE.
I'M AWARE THAT WE'RE NOT GAY PUPPETS, ALL RIGHT?
LOOK, YOU KNOW WHAT?
IF THIS IS THE WAY YOU FEEL
THEN MAYBE YOU SHOULD TAKE IT.
WELL, THAT'S HOW I FEEL.
WELL, THEN MAYBE I WILL!
FINE WITH ME.
GREAT.
THEN YOU'LL BE ABLE
TO SPEND MORE QUALITY TIME
WITH YOUR REAL FRIENDS-- THE SPOONS.
WHOSE DRINK CAN I FRESHEN?
ALMOST TIME FOR CAKE.
MON? :   YEAH?
MON, ARE YOU OKAY?
YOU REMEMBER THAT VIDEO I FOUND OF MOM AND DAD?
YEAH?
WELL, I JUST CAUGHT THE LIVE SHOW.
EWW.
HEY, THERE.
WHAT?
NOTHING.
I JUST...
HEARD SOMETHING NICE ABOUT YOU.
OH, REALLY?
MM HMM.
RICHARD?
RICHARD...
YOUR SON ISN'T SEEING ANYONE, IS HE?
UH, NOT THAT I KNOW OF.
WELL, I WAS THINKING
WHY DOESN'T HE GIVE MONICA A CALL?
THAT...
THAT'S AN IDEA.
WELL, ACTUALLY, I'M ALREADY SEEING SOMEONE.
OH?
OH...
SHE NEVER TELLS US ANYTHING.
ROSS, DID YOU KNOW MONICA'S SEEING SOMEONE?
MOM, THERE ARE SO MANY PEOPLE IN MY LIFE.
SOME OF THEM ARE SEEING PEOPLE
AND SOME OF THEM AREN'T.
IS THAT CRYSTAL?
SO, WHO'S THE MYSTERY MAN?
WELL, UH, HE'S A DOCTOR.
ARE AL DOCTOR?
NO, A DOCTOR OF MEAT.
OF COURSE HE'S A REAL DOCTOR.
AND HE'S HANDSOME...
AND HE'S SWEET
AND I KNOW YOU'D LIKE HIM.
WELL, THAT'S WONDERFUL. I...
OY.
MOM, IT'S OKAY.
IT IS, JUDY.
JACK...
COULD YOU COME IN HERE FOR A MOMENT?
NOW!
FOUND IT.
I'LL TAKE THAT, DAD.
IT SEEMS YOUR DAUGHTER AND RICHARD
ARE SOMETHING OF AN ITEM.
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
HE'S GOT A TWINKIE IN THE CITY.
DAD, I'M THE TWINKIE.
YOU'RE THE TWINKIE?
SHE'S NOT A TWINKIE.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, YOU GUYS
THIS IS THE BEST RELATIONSHIP I'VE BEEN IN...
OH, PLEASE! A RELATIONSHIP?
YES, A RELATIONSHIP.
FOR YOUR INFORMATION, I AM CRAZY ABOUT THIS MAN.
REALLY?
YES.
WOW.
AM I SUPPOSED TO STAND HERE
AND LISTEN TO THIS ON MY BIRTHDAY?
DAD... DAD, THIS IS A GOOD THING FOR ME.
YOU KNOW, AND YOU EVEN SAID YOURSELF
YOU'D NEVER SEEN RICHARD HAPPIER.
WHEN DID I SAY THAT?
UPSTAIRS IN THE BATHROOM
RIGHT BEFORE YOU FELT UP MOM.
? HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO YOU ?
? HAPPY BIRTHDAY, DEAR JACK ?
? HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO YOU. ?
OH, IT LOOKS SO GOOD.
OH, I LOVE IT.
I KNOW. SO DO I.
I'M SO GLAD YOU MADE ME DO THIS.
OKAY, LET ME SEE YOURS.
UH...
OKAY, LET'S SEE YOURS AGAIN.
PHOEBE, WE JUST SAW MINE. LET ME SEE YOURS.
OH, OKAY.
OH, NO!
OH, IT'S GONE.
THAT'S SO WEIRD.
I DON'T KNOW HOW... WHERE IT WENT.
YOU DIDN'T GET IT?
NO.
WHY DIDN'T YOU GET IT?
I'M SORRY, I'M SORRY.
PHOEBE, HOW COULD YOU DO THIS TO ME?!
THIS WAS ALL YOUR IDEA.
I KNOW, I KNOW, AND I WAS GOING TO GET IT
BUT THEN HE CAME IN WITH THIS NEEDLE.
DID YOU KNOW THEY DO THIS WITH NEEDLES?
REALLY? YOU DON'T SAY?
BECAUSE MINE WAS LICKED ON BY KITTENS!
I'M SORRY. I...
ALL RIGHT, SERIOUSLY... SERIOUSLY
DOES IT HURT A LOT?
NO. IT'S JUST LIKE A PINCH. LIKE THAT.
OW! OH! OW! OH, MY GOD!
OH, THAT'S...
OH, THAT REALLY HURT ME!
OH, THAT'S GOING TO LEAVE A MARK.
HEY.
HEY, LISTEN, I'M SORRY ABOUT WHAT...
YEAH, ME, TOO. I KNOW.
YEAH.
SO, DO WE NEED TO HUG HERE OR...?
NO. WE'RE ALL RIGHT.
YEAH. YEAH.
SO, I GOT YOU SOMETHING.
PLASTIC SPOONS.
GREAT.
LICK AWAY, MY MAN.
THESE WILL GO GREAT IN MY NEW PLACE.
YOU KNOW, TILL I GET REAL ONES.
WHAT?
WELL, I CAN'T USE THESE FOREVER.
I MEAN, LET'S FACE IT--
THEY'RE NO FRIEND OF THE ENVIRONMENT.
NO, NO, I MEAN, WHAT...
WHAT'S THIS ABOUT YOUR NEW PLACE?
I'M MOVING OUT, LIKE WE TALKED ABOUT.
WELL, I DIDN'T THINK THAT WAS SERIOUS.
YOU KNOW, I THOUGHT THAT WAS JUST A FIGHT.
WELL, IT WAS A FIGHT.
BASED ON SERIOUS STUFF, REMEMBER?
ABOUT HOW I NEVER LIVED ALONE OR ANYTHING?
I JUST THINK IT WOULD BE GOOD FOR ME--
YOU KNOW, HELP ME TO GROW OR... WHATEVER.
WELL, THERE YOU GO.
HEY, ARE YOU COOL WITH THIS?
I MEAN, I DON'T WANT TO LEAVE YOU HIGH AND DRY.
HEY, NO. I'VE NEVER BEEN LOWER OR WETTER.
I'LL BE FINE.
I'LL JUST TURN YOUR, UH, BEDROOM
INTO A GAME ROOM OR SOMETHING, YOU KNOW?
PUT THE FOOSBALL TABLE IN THERE.
WHOA. WHY DO YOU GET TO KEEP THE TABLE?
I DID PAY FOR HALF OF IT.
YEAH, AND, UH...
... I PAID FOR THE OTHER HALF.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
I'LL PLAY YOU FOR IT.
ALL RIGHT, YOU'RE ON.
I COULD TAKE TWO MINUTES OUT OF MY DAY TO KICK YOUR ASS.
YOUR LITTLE MEN ARE GOING TO GET SCORED ON MORE TIMES
THAN YOUR SISTER.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA,WHOA.
WHICH SISTER?
SO, ARE YOU SORRY THAT I TOLD THEM?
NO. IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME
SINCE YOUR DAD AND I WENT RUNNING.
OH.
OH. WELL, DID YOU GET IT? LET ME SEE?
IS ROSS HERE?
NO. HE WENT OUT TO GET PIZZA.
OKAY, REALLY QUICK, OKAY?
THAT'S GREAT.
VERY TASTEFUL.
THANK YOU.
WANT TO SEE MINE? WANT TO SEE MINE?
YES!
WHAT? YOU DIDN'T GET ONE.
OKAY, WELL, THEN WHAT IS THIS?
WHAT ARE WE LOOKING AT?
THAT BLUE FRECKLE?
OKAY, THAT'S MY TATTOO.
THAT IS NOT A TATTOO.
THAT IS A NOTHING.
I FINALLY GOT HER BACK IN THE CHAIR
HE BARELY TOUCHED HER WITH THE NEEDLE
SHE JUMPED UP SCREAMING
AND THAT WAS IT.
OKAY, HI.
FOR YOUR INFORMATION
THIS IS EXACTLY WHAT I WANTED.
THIS IS A TATTOO
OF THE EARTH AS SEEN FROM A GREAT, GREAT DISTANCE.
IT'S THE WAY MY MOTHER SEES ME FROM HEAVEN.
OH... OH...
OH, WHAT A LOAD OF CRAP.
THAT IS A DOT.
YOUR MOTHER IS UP IN HEAVEN GOING
"WHERE THE HELL IS MY LILY, YOU WUSS?!"
OKAY?
PHOEBE, THAT IS NOT A TATTOO.
THIS IS A TATTOO!
YOU GOT A TATTOO?
MAYBE.
BUT JUST A LITTLE ONE.
PHOEBE GOT THE WHOLE WORLD.
WELL, LET ME SEE.
WELL?
WELL, IT'S REALLY...
SEXY.
I WOULDN'T HAVE THOUGHT IT WOULD BE, BUT...
WOW.
REALLY?
YEAH. SO, UH...
IS IT SORE, OR CAN YOU DO STUFF?
I GUESS.
HEY, SAVE US SOME PIZZA.
GET IT OUT OF THE CORNER!
CENTER IT.
PASS IT.
PASS IT!
STOP TALKING TO YOUR MEN.
YES!
AND THE TABLE IS MINE.
CONGRATULATIONS.
HEY, YOU GUYS ARE STILL GOING TO COME VISIT ME, RIGHT?
OH, YEAH. YOU GOT THE BIG TV.
WE'LL BE OVER THERE ALL THE TIME.
EXCEPT WHEN WE ARE HERE.
I KNOW YOU'RE JUST MOVING UPTOWN
BUT I'M REALLY GOING TO MISS YOU.
I KNOW. HOW CAN YOU NOT BE ACROSS THE HALL ANYMORE?
YEAH. WHO'S GOING TO EAT ALL OUR FOOD
AND TIE UP OUR PHONE LINES, AND...?
IS THAT MY BRA?
WHAT THE HELL YOU DOING WITH MY BRA?
OH, NO, NO, IT'S, UH, IT'S NOT WHAT YOU THINK.
WE, UH.... WE USED IT TO, YOU KNOW
FLING WATER BALLOONS OFF THE ROOF.
REMEMBER THAT?
THOSE JUNIOR HIGH KIDS
COULDN'T EVEN GET THEIRS ACROSS THE STREET.
YEAH, I REMEMBER.
HEY, LET'S BRING THE REST OF THESE DOWN TO THE TRUCK.
OKAY.
THANKS.
SO, UH... YOU WANT ME TO, UH, GIVE YOU A HAND
WITH THE FOOSBALL TABLE?
NAH.
YOU KEEP IT.
YOU NEED THE PRACTICE.
THANKS.
SO...
I GUESS THIS IS IT.
YEAH. RIGHT. YEAH.
I GUESS SO.
LISTEN, UH...
I DON'T KNOW WHEN I'M GOING TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
WELL, I'M GUESSING, UH, TONIGHT AT THE COFFEE HOUSE.
RIGHT. YEAH.
OKAY.
UH... TAKE CARE.
YEAH.
HEY, DAD. WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I JUST STOPPED BY YOUR BOYFRIEND'S
TO GIVE HIM A PIECE OF MY MIND.
AND...?
AND I WAS GOING
TO PUNCH HIM IN THE NOSE
BUT HE HAD THE GAME ON, SO WE STARTED WATCHING.
UH HUH.
WELL, THEN, AT HALFTIME, I WAS GOING TO GIVE HIM WHAT FOR
BUT HE OFFERED ME A BEER, AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
WHAT?
HE'S GOT IT ON TAP!
RIGHT IN HIS APARTMENT!
THE DAMN THING IS BUILT RIGHT INTO HIS BAR.
IT'S UNBELIEVABLE.
DAD, DID YOU TALK ABOUT ME?
OH, RIGHT. WELL...
ACTUALLY, WE NEVER GOT TO YOU.
LOOK...
YOU'RE A BIG GIRL.
I JUST HOPE YOU KNOW WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
I DO.
DAD, YOU'RE WEARING
THE TIE THAT I GOT YOU.
YEAH.
SO, WHERE DID YOU GET THE HAT?
I DON'T KNOW.