It's not fair.
It's my money!
I know, but it's what Brad wanted.
OKAY, WHICH ONE IS SHE?
THAT'S BRAD'S WIDOW.
WHY IS SHE SO UPSET?
BECAUSE SHE JUST FOUND OUT
SHE WAS CUT OUT OF THE WILL.
OH, DOESN'T SHE KNOW
YOU CAN'T DEFINE YOURSELF IN TERMS OF MONEY.
THAT IT'S ABOUT VALUES AND MORALS
AND YOUR ABILITY TO GIVE AND RECEIVE LOVE.
NO.
Oh, Drake.
I'm sorry, Amber.
It's just like Brad to have to have the last word.
I'M SORRY I'M LATE. WHAT HAPPENED?
WE JUST WANT TO SEE THE END.
I want you, Drake.
I know you do.
But you and I can never be together that way.
What?
There's something I never told you, Amber.
I'm actually... your half brother.
SO WHAT HAPPENS NEXT?
WELL, I GET THE MEDICAL AWARD
FOR SEPARATING THE SIAMESE TWINS.
THEN AMBER AND I GO TO VENEZUELA
TO MEET OUR OTHER HALF BROTHER, RAMON.
AND THAT'S WHERE I FIND THE WORLD'S BIGGEST EMERALD.
IT'S REALLY BIG...
BUT IT'S CURSED.
THAT'S SO COOL.
GOD, THAT IS GOOD TV.
? BECAUSE YOU'RE THERE FOR ME TOO. ?
COME ON, PHEEBS, PLAY WITH ME.
NO.
THIS GAME IS GROTESQUE.
20 ARMLESS GUYS JOINED AT THE WAIST BY A STEEL BAR.
FORCED TO PLAY SOCCER FOREVER?
HELLO? HUMAN RIGHTS VIOLATION.
DON'T FEEL SO BAD FOR THEM.
AFTER THEY'RE DONE PLAYING
I BREAK OUT THE LITTLE PLASTIC WOMEN
AND EVERYBODY HAS A PRETTY GOOD TIME.
WHY DON'T YOU PLAY WITH YOUR ROOMMATE?
HE'S, UH...
HE'S NOT A BIG FAN OF FOOSBALL.
UH OH. ARE WE NOT GETTING ALONG WITH THE NEW BOY?
NO, HE'S ALL RIGHT.
HE JUST... HE SPENDS MOST OF HIS TIME IN HIS ROOM.
MAYBE THAT'S BECAUSE
YOU HAVEN'T TAKEN TIME TO GET TO KNOW HIM.
LET'S REMEDY THAT, SHALL WE?
WE DON'T NEED TO REMEDY THAT.
OH, YEAH. IT'LL BE FUN.
WHAT WAS THAT?
HI. I JUST THOUGHT THAT IT WOULD BE FUN
IF THE THREE OF US HAD SOME BEERS
AND GOT TO KNOW EACH OTHER.
ALL RIGHT. THAT SOUNDS ALL RIGHT.
OH, GOOD. OKAY.
OH, NO, I HAVE TO GO
BECAUSE I'M LATE FOR MY, UM...
GREEN EGGS AND HAM DISCUSSION GROUP.
TONIGHT IT'S
WHY HE WOULD NOT EAT THEM ON A TRAIN.
HAVE FUN. BYE.
THAT WAS SO LAME.
I KNOW, YEAH.
OKAY, TALK TO HIM.
SO YOU THINK THAT SPEED RACER GUY GETS A LOT OF TICKETS OR...?
THAT'S GOOD. THAT'S GOOD.
SO WHO BROKE UP WITH WHO?
WHAT, ARE YOU KIDDING?
I BROKE UP WITH HER.
SHE ACTUALLY THOUGHT THAT SEAN PENN
WAS THE CAPITAL OF CAMBODIA.
THAT'S GOOD, MAN.
WHEN EVERYBODY KNOWS THAT THE CAPITAL OF CAMBODIA...
IS, UH...
IT'S NOT SEAN PENN. NOT SEAN PENN.
ALL RIGHT, I GOT A FUNNY ONE.
MY LAST GIRLFRIEND, TILLY
OKAY, WE'RE EATING BREAKFAST, RIGHT?
I MADE ALL THESE PANCAKES.
THERE WAS, LIKE, 50 PANCAKES.
ALL OF A SUDDEN, SHE TURNS TO ME, ALL RIGHT?
SHE SAYS, "EDDIE, I DON'T WANT TO SEE YOU ANYMORE."
IT WAS LITERALLY LIKE SHE HAD REACHED INTO MY CHEST
RIPPED OUT MY HEART AND SMEARED IT ALL OVER MY LIFE.
NOW THERE'S LIKE THIS
INCREDIBLE ABYSS
AND I'M FALLING
AND I KEEP FALLING
AND I DON'T THINK I'M EVER GOING TO STOP.
THAT WASN'T SUCH A FUNNY STORY, WAS IT?
? AND A CRUSTY OLD MAN SAID, "I'LL DO WHAT I CAN" ?
? AND THE REST OF THE RATS PLAYED MARACAS. ?
THAT'S IT. THANKS.
GOOD NIGHT.
PHOEBE'S GOT ANOTHER JOB, RIGHT?
GREAT SET TONIGHT, PHEEBS.
I KNOW.
WELL, WE SHOULD PROBABLY GET GOING.
WE SHOULD GO, TOO.
I'VE GOT PATIENTS AT 8:00 IN THE MORNING.
YOU KNOW, I WAS THINKING.
YOU KNOW HOW WE ALWAYS STAY AT YOUR APARTMENT?
I THOUGHT MAYBE TONIGHT WE'D STAY AT MY PLACE.
I DON'T KNOW. I DON'T HAVE MY JAMMIES.
WELL, MAYBE YOU DON'T NEED THEM.
MY BABY SISTER, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN.
SHUT UP. I'M HAPPY.
OH, THIS IS SO NICE.
ALL RIGHT, I HAVE TO MAKE A SPEECH.
I JUST WANT TO SAY
THAT OF ALL THE GUYS THAT MONICA'S BEEN WITH
AND THAT IS A LOT
I LIKE YOU THE BEST.
OH, THANK YOU, PHEEBS.
THAT'S VERY SWEET.
DID YOU HEAR THAT?
SHE LIKES ME BEST.
AND APPARENTLY THERE HAVE BEEN A LOT.
NOT A LOT.
PHOEBE'S KIDDING.
PHOEBE'S CRAZY.
PHOEBE'S DEAD.
HI.
I'M LOOKING FOR EDDIE MANOACK.
HE'S NOT HERE RIGHT NOW.
I'M CHANDLER. CAN I TAKE A MESSAGE
OR A FISH TANK?
THANKS.
COME ON IN.
I'M TILLY.
OH.
I GATHER BY THAT "OH," THAT HE TOLD YOU ABOUT ME.
YEAH, YOUR NAME CAME UP IN A CONVERSATION
THAT TERRIFIED ME TO MY VERY SOUL.
HE'S KIND OF INTENSE, HUH?
YES! HEY, CAN I ASK YOU, IS EDDIE A LITTLE...?
A LITTLE WHAT?
BIT COUNTRY?
OR, UH... YOU KNOW, A LITTLE ROCK 'N' ROLL?
COME ON IN HERE, YOU ROOMIE.
HELLO, TILLY.
EDDIE, I JUST CAME BY TO DROP OFF YOUR TANK.
THAT WAS VERY THOUGHTFUL OF YOU.
IT WAS VERY THOUGHTFUL.
WELL, OKAY, THEN.
I'M GOING TO GO.
BYE.
BYE BYE.
SO WE GETTING A FISH?
YOU HAD SEX WITH HER, DIDN'T YOU?
PHEEBS, CHECK IT OUT, CHECK IT OUT, CHECK IT OUT.
OH, SOAP OPERA DIGEST.
THAT'S ONE OF MY FAVORITE DIGESTS.
PAGE 42, PAGE 42.
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
HEY! "NEW DOG ON THE BLOCK.
DAYS OF OUR LIVES, JOEY TRIBBIANI."
OOH, COOL PICTURE.
YEAH.
OH, I LOOK GOOD.
HEY, IS THIS TRUE?
THAT YOU WRITE A LOT OF YOUR OWN LINES?
WELL, KIND OF, YEAH.
LIKE REMEMBER LAST WEEK WHEN ALEX WAS IN THE ACCIDENT?
THE LINE IN THE SCRIPT WAS
"IF WE DON'T GET THIS WOMAN TO A HOSPITAL
SHE'S GOING TO DIE."
BUT I MADE IT, "IF THIS WOMAN DOESN'T GET TO A HOSPITAL
SHE'S NOT GOING TO LIVE."
SEE?
OH, OKAY, I SEE WHAT YOU DID THERE.
AREN'T YOU AFRAID, THOUGH, THAT THE WRITERS
ARE GOING TO BE KIND OF MAD WHEN THEY READ THIS?
HUH. I NEVER REALLY THOUGHT ABOUT THE WRITERS.
THE SCRIPTS JUST KIND OF COME TO MY HOUSE.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
THIS MAKES ME LOOK GOOD, WHICH MAKES THE SHOW LOOK GOOD
WHICH MAKES THE WRITERS LOOK GOOD.
SO HOW COULD THEY BE MAD ABOUT THAT?
MAKES UP MOST OF HIS OWN LINES.
SON OF A...
YEAH. WRITE THIS, JERKWEED.
I FALL DOWN AN ELEVATOR SHAFT?
WHAT THE HELL DOES THIS MEAN?
UH... I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST BRING THE SCRIPTS.
THEY CAN'T KILL ME.
I'M FRANCESCA'S LONG LOST SON!
RIGHT.
COULD YOU SIGN THIS?
NO. NO WAY.
I'M NOT SIGNING THAT.
I DON'T THINK THAT'S GOING TO AFFECT THE PLOT OF THE SHOW.
HOW CAN THEY DO THIS TO ME?
ALL RIGHT, I'M JUST GOING TO GO.
SORRY.
WELL, IT WASN'T THAT MANY GUYS.
IF YOU CONSIDER HOW MANY GUYS THERE ACTUALLY ARE
IT'S A VERY SMALL PERCENTAGE.
HEY, IT'S NOT THAT BIG A DEAL.
I WAS JUST CURIOUS.
GOOD NIGHT.
GOOD NIGHT, RICHARD.
GOOD LUCK, MON.
BEFORE I TELL YOU
WHY DON'T YOU TELL ME HOW MANY WOMEN
YOU'VE BEEN WITH.
TWO.
TWO? TWO?
HOW IS THAT POSSIBLE?
I MEAN, HAVE YOU SEEN YOU?
WELL, WHAT CAN I SAY?
I WAS MARRIED TO BARBARA FOR 30 YEARS.
SHE WAS MY HIGH SCHOOL SWEETHEART.
NOW YOU.
THAT'S TWO.
TWO IT IS.
OKAY, TIME FOR BED.
I'M GOING TO GO BRUSH MY TEETH.
WHOA, WHOA, NOW, WAIT A MINUTE, NOW.
COME ON, IT'S YOUR TURN.
OH, COME ON.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T NEED THE ACTUAL NUMBER
JUST A BALLPARK.
OKAY, IT IS DEFINITELY LESS THAN A BALLPARK.
WOW, I AM SO GLAD I'M NOT MONICA RIGHT NOW.
TELL ME ABOUT IT.
SO WHAT'S... WHAT'S YOUR MAGIC NUMBER?
AH...
COME ON, YOU KNOW EVERYONE I'VE BEEN WITH.
ALL BOTH OF THEM.
WELL, THERE'S YOU...
BETTER NOT BE DOING THESE IN ORDER.
OKAY, BILLY DRESKIN...
PETE CARNEY...
BARRY...
AND UH... OH, PAOLO.
OH, YES, THE WIENIE FROM TURINI.
OH, HONEY, ARE YOU JEALOUS OF PAOLO?
OH, COME ON, I'M SO MUCH HAPPIER WITH YOU
THAN I EVER WAS WITH HIM.
REALLY?
OH, PLEASE.
THAT PAOLO THING WAS BARELY A RELATIONSHIP.
ALL IT REALLY WAS
WAS, YOU KNOW, MEANINGLESS ANIMAL SEX.
OKAY, YOU KNOW, THAT SOUNDED SO MUCH BETTER IN MY HEAD.
EDDIE, I DIDN'T SLEEP WITH YOUR EX GIRLFRIEND.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT SOMEONE
WHO SLEPT WITH HER WOULD SAY.
THIS IS NUTS. THIS IS CRAZY.
SHE CAME OVER FOR, LIKE, TWO MINUTES
DROPPED OFF A FISH TANK AND LEFT-- END OF STORY.
WHERE'S BUDDY?
BUDDY?
MY FISH, BUDDY.
THERE WAS NO FISH WHEN SHE DROPPED IT OFF.
THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE.
YOU SLEEP
WITH MY EX GIRLFRIEND.
THEN YOU INSULT MY INTELLIGENCE BY LYING ABOUT IT
AND THEN YOU KILL MY FISH? MY BUDDY?
HEY, I DIDN'T KILL YOUR FISH.
LOOK, EDDIE...
WOULD YOU LOOK AT WHAT I'M DOING HERE.
NOW THAT CAN'T BE SMART.
SO WE'RE JUST GOING TO TAKE THIS GUY RIGHT OFF YOU
AND PUT HIM HERE IN MR. POCKET.
TANGELO?
THAT'S IT? THAT'S THE GIANT NUMBER
YOU WERE AFRAID TO TELL ME?
WELL, YEAH.
WELL, THAT'S NOT BAD AT ALL.
YOU HAD ME THINKING IT WAS LIKE A... FLEET.
ARE YOU REALLY OKAY WITH IT?
OH, HONEY, I'M FINE.
OH, YAY.
OKAY, ABOUT THAT TWO...
WHAT?
ALL RIGHT.
WHAT ABOUT MY TWO?
WELL, THAT JUST SEEMS LIKE A REALLY SMALL NUMBER.
RIGHT.
AND...?
AND, WELL, DON'T YOU HAVE A LOT OF WILD OATS TO SOW?
OR IS THAT WHAT YOU'RE DOING WITH ME?
OH, MY GOD!
AM I AN OAT?
OH, HONEY, YOU ARE NOT AN OAT.
I I MEAN, I DON'T KNOW.
I GUESS I'M JUST NOT... AN OAT GUY.
I'VE ONLY SLEPT WITH WOMEN I'VE BEEN IN LOVE WITH.
BUT YOU'VE ONLY SLEPT WITH TWO PEOPLE.
RIGHT.
WOW.
OH, WOW.
YOU KNOW I LOVE YOU, TOO, RIGHT?
NOW I DO.
OH! ROSS...
ROSS, PLEASE LISTEN TO ME.
ROSS, YOU ARE SO MUCH BETTER
FOR ME THAN PAOLO EVER WAS.
YOU CARE ABOUT ME, YOU'RE LOVING
YOU MAKE ME LAUGH.
IF I MAKE YOU LAUGH, HERE'S AN IDEA:
WHY DON'T YOU INVITE PAOLO OVER
TO HAVE A LITTLE ROMP IN THE SACK
AND I'LL JUST STAND IN THE CORNER
AND TELL KNOCK KNOCK JOKES?
STOP! GOD!
ROSS, WHAT YOU AND I HAVE
IS SPECIAL.
ALL PAOLO AND I EVER HAD WAS...
ANIMAL SEX? ANIMAL SEX?
SO WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
YOU'RE SAYING THAT, LIKE
THERE'S NOTHING BETWEEN US ANIMAL AT ALL?
I MEAN, THERE'S NOT EVEN, LIKE, UM... A LITTLE ANIMAL?
NOT EVEN... NOT EVEN, LIKE, LIKE... CHIPMUNK SEX?
OKAY, ROSS, TRY TO HEAR ME, OKAY?
HEY, I'M NOT GOING TO LIE TO YOU, OKAY?
IT WAS GOOD WITH PAOLO...
KNOCK, KNOCK.
BUT...
WHAT YOU AND I HAVE IS SO MUCH BETTER, OKAY?
WE HAVE TENDERNESS.
WE HAVE INTIMACY.
WE CONNECT.
YOU KNOW, I SWEAR
THIS IS THE BEST I HAVE EVER HAD.
UNTIL NOW.
OH, DON'T!
OH, HI.
HI.
RICHARD JUST TOLD ME HE LOVED ME.
OH, MY GOD! I KNOW.
HONEY, THAT'S GREAT!
I KNOW.
I JUST CAN'T FIND...
THEY'RE IN THE TOP DRAWER.
HURRY.
YOU NEED ONE, TOO?
OH... YEAH.
I FOUND THEM!
THERE'S ONLY ONE.
MONICA?
HI.
BE RIGHT THERE.
WE'RE JUST, UM...
WE'RE TRYING TO DECIDE SOMETHING.
RACHEL?
HEY.
THEY'RE JUST TRYING TO DECIDE SOMETHING.
OH, GOOD. GOOD, GOOD.
SO, IS, UM... WAS YOUR MUSTACHE
DID DID IT USE TO BE DIFFERENT?
NO.
OH.
HOW DO YOU, YOU KNOW, KEEP IT SO NEAT?
I HAVE A LITTLE COMB.
OH.
AND WHAT DO YOU CALL THAT?
A MUSTACHE COMB.
INTERESTING.
OKAY, I I WILL DO YOUR LAUNDRY FOR ONE MONTH.
NO!
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY!
I WILL I WILL I WILL...
HEY, I WILL CLEAN THE APARTMENT FOR TWO MONTHS.
I'LL GIVE THIS TO YOU NOW
IF YOU CAN TELL ME WHERE WE KEEP THE DUSTPAN.
SO, WERE YOU IN 'NAM?
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT? YOU KNOW WHAT?
WE ARE BOTH ADULTS HERE, RIGHT?
WELL, THERE'S GOT TO BE A MATURE WAY
TO HANDLE THIS.
ROCK, PAPER, SCISSORS?
GOT YOU.
ONE, TWO, THREE.
YES!
FINE. GO HAVE SEX.
THANK YOU.
NO! YOU HAVE GOT IT COMPLETELY WRONG.
JOHN SAVAGE WAS DEER HUNTER, NO LEGS.
JON VOIGHT WAS COMING HOME, COULDN'T FEEL HIS LEGS.
NO. NO WAY.
YOU'VE GOT IT TOTALLY
THE OTHER WAY AROUND, MY FRIEND.
JON VOIGHT...
HONEY.
WHAT?
SHALL WE?
IT'S NOT GOING TO HAPPEN.
THEY'RE DOING IT TONIGHT.
WE CAN DO IT TOMORROW.
UH, IN THE FUTURE
IF I COULD SEE THE SCHEDULE BEFOREHAND...
SO, WHEN I WOKE UP THIS MORNING
HE HAD STOLEN ALL THE INSOLES OUT OF MY SHOES.
WHY?
BECAUSE HE THINKS I SLEPT WITH HIS EX GIRLFRIEND
AND KILLED HIS FISH.
WHY WOULD YOU KILL HIS FISH?
BECAUSE SOMETIMES, PHOEBE, AFTER YOU SLEEP WITH SOMEONE
YOU HAVE TO KILL A FISH.
CHANDLER, HONEY, I'M SORRY.
CAN WE WATCH JOEY'S SHOW NOW, PLEASE?
YEAH.
HE'S NOT HERE YET.
SO? HE'S ON THE SHOW.
HE KNOWS WHAT HAPPENS.
OH, I'M FINE ABOUT MY PROBLEM NOW, BY THE WAY.
OH, GOOD.
Amber...
I want you to know that I will always be there for you--
as a friend and as your brother.
Oh, Drake.
What a day, huh?
FIRST, THE MEDICAL AWARD, NOW THIS.
YEAH, SOME GUYS ARE JUST LUCKY, I GUESS.
Dr. Ramoray, report to first floor Emergency, stat.
WELL, THEN, UH...
I, UH... GUESS THAT'S ME.
ANYONE ELSE NEED TO GO ON THE ELEVATOR?
DR. HORTON?
DR. WONG?
NO, NO.
THEY ONLY SAID YOU.
WELL, OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
I LOVE YOU, DRAKE.
YEAH, WHATEVER.
OH, NO!
DRAKE! LOOK OUT!
DRAKE!
DID THEY JUST KILL OFF JOEY?
NO.
NOW, MAYBE.
COME ON! OPEN UP!
WE WANT TO TALK TO YOU.
I DON'T FEEL LIKE TALKING.
COME ON, JOEY. WE CARE ABOUT YOU.
WE'RE WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
AND SOME OF US REALLY HAVE TO PEE.
SORRY, JOEY.
HEY...
LISTEN, SORRY ABOUT YOUR DEATH.
THAT REALLY SUCKS.
WE CAME OVER AS SOON AS WE SAW.
HOW COULD YOU NOT TELL US?
I DON'T KNOW. I WAS... KIND OF HOPING
NO ONE WOULD EVER FIND OUT.
WELL, MAYBE THEY COULD FIND A WAY
TO BRING YOU BACK.
NAH. THEY SAID THAT WHEN THEY FOUND MY BODY
MY BRAIN WAS SO SMASHED IN
THAT THE ONLY DOCTOR WHO COULD HAVE SAVED ME WAS ME.
THAT'S SUPPOSED TO BE SOME KIND OF IRONY OR SOMETHING.
BUT, JOEY, YOU'RE GOING TO BE FINE.
YOU DON'T NEED THAT SHOW.
IT WAS JUST A DUMB SOAP OPERA.
PHOEBE, THIS WAS THE GREATEST THING THAT EVER HAPPENED TO ME.
YES. I WAS GOING TO INCORPORATE THAT.
OH, GOOD. HERE'S MONICA.
SHE'LL HAVE SOMETHING NICE TO SAY.
UM, I STRAIGHTENED OUT YOUR SHOWER CURTAIN
SO YOU WON'T GET MILDEW.
WHAT? TO ME, THAT'S NICE.
IT'S GOING TO BE OKAY.
YOU KNOW THAT.
NO, I DON'T.
IT'S LIKE, YOU KNOW, YOU WORK YOUR WHOLE LIFE FOR SOMETHING
AND YOU THINK THAT WHEN YOU GET IT
IT'S NEVER GOING TO BE AS GOOD AS YOU THOUGHT IT WOULD BE
BUT THIS SO WAS.
YOU KNOW, IT CHANGED EVERYTHING.
LIKE, THE OTHER DAY I GOT THIS CREDIT CARD APPLICATION
AND I WAS PREAPPROVED.
HUH?
I'VE NEVER BEEN PREAPPROVED FOR ANYTHING IN MY LIFE.
I'M SORRY, MAN.
YEAH. JOEY, HONEY, I DON'T KNOW
IF THIS WILL MEAN ANYTHING TO YOU
BUT YOU'LL ALWAYS BE PREAPPROVED WITH US.
NO, THAT MEANS NOTHING TO ME.
PECAN SANDIE? JUST MADE THEM.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
WHAT ARE THESE, RAISINS?
UH... SURE. WHY NOT?
LISTEN, EDDIE, UH...
I'VE BEEN THINKING ABOUT OUR CURRENT LIVING SITUATION
AND, UH... WHY ARE YOU SMILING?
I GOT A LITTLE SURPRISE.
LOOK, I GOT US A NEW FISHIE.
I NAMED HIM, UH...
"CHANDLER," YOU KNOW, AFTER... AFTER YOU.
WELL, THAT'S NOT EVEN A REAL FISH.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S A GOLDFISH CRACKER.
SO WHAT'S YOUR POINT, MAN?
OKAY, GOOD NIGHT...
YOU BIG FREAK OF NATURE.
HEY.
OOH!
BRISK TONIGHT.
OH, MAN.
LET'S NEVER SPEAK OF THIS.
YOU GOT IT.