JOEY, WOULD YOU SLOW DOWN?
THEY'RE NOT GOING TO BE SOLD OUT OF PAPERS
AT 1:00 IN THE MORNING.
I'M EXCITED.
I'VE NEVER GOTTEN REVIEWED BEFORE.
YOU WERE SO AMAZING AS THE KING.
I WAS REALLY IMPRESSED. I WAS.
ALTHOUGH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU MIGHT WANT TO CONSIDER WEARING UNDERWEAR NEXT TIME.
YEAH, BECAUSE WHEN
YOU SAT DOWN ON YOUR THRONE
YOU COULD KIND OF SEE YOUR... ROYAL SUBJECTS.
COME ON, NO ONE WORE UNDERWEAR BACK THEN.
I'M SURE THE CRITICS APPRECIATED YOUR AUTHENTICITY.
NICE GENITALS, BY THE WAY.
THANKS, MAN.
HERE IT IS, HERE IT IS!
"THE ONLY THING WORSE
"THAN THE MINDLESS, ADOLESCENT DIRECTION
"WAS JOSEPH TRIBBIANI'S DISTURBINGLY UNSKILLED PORTRAYAL OF THE KING."
OKAY, LOOK, THAT IS ONE GUY'S OPINION.
ALL RIGHT?
PHEEBS, READ YOURS.
"THE ONLY THING WORSE
"THAN THE MINDLESS, ADOLESCENT DIRECTION..."
DOES ANYBODY HAVE ONE FROM A DIFFERENT PAPER?
ROSS, READ YOURS.
I DON'T WANT TO.
"THE ONLY ENJOYABLE MOMENT
IS WHEN THE KING IS BEHEADED AND HE CAN SPEAK NO MORE."
OH...!
JOEY, HONEY, THEY DON'T KNOW WHAT THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT.
MAYBE THEY DO.
I'VE BEEN DOING THIS TEN YEARS
AND I HAVEN'T GOTTEN ANYWHERE.
THERE'S GOT TO BE A REASON.
COME ON, MAN, YOU'RE JUST PAYING YOUR DUES.
NO, NO. IT'S TOO HARD.
IT'S NOT WORTH IT.
I QUIT.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT ONE MINUTE.
WAIT A MINUTE.
I BELIEVE THIS WILL CHANGE YOUR MIND.
"IN A MEDIOCRE PLAY, JOSEPH TRIBBIANI
"WAS ABLE TO ACHIEVE BRILLIANT NEW LEVELS OF...
"CONTINUED ON PAGE 153.
SUCKING."
WELL, WAS THERE ANYTHING ELSE YOU EVER WANTED TO BE?
I DON'T KNOW.
WHEN I WAS LITTLE, I WANTED TO BE A VETERINARIAN
BUT THEN I FOUND OUT YOU HAVE TO PUT YOUR HANDS
INTO COWS AND STUFF.
HI.
HEY.
ARE ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH, YEAH, JUST A TOUGH DAY AT WORK.
A STEGOSAURUS FELL OVER AND TRAPPED A KID.
WHOA, WHOA... I KNOW THIS JACKET.
THIS IS FUN BOBBY'S JACKET.
WHERE IS HE? WHAT?
HE'S HERE, ISN'T HE?
MAYBE.
DON'T TOY WITH ME.
GELLER!
FUN BOBBY!
HEY! WHOA, YOU BEEN WORKING OUT, HUH?
NOT AT ALL.
I LOVE THIS GUY.
HEY, I WAS SO PSYCHED
TO HEAR YOU'RE BACK WITH MY SISTER.
YOU AND ME BOTH.
HEY, SO WHAT DID I MISS? WHAT DID I MISS? COME ON.
WE WERE JUST TRYING TO MAKE JOEY FEEL BETTER.
HEY, DO YOU NEED ME TO PICK YOU UP?
NO, I'M ALL RIGHT, MAN, REALLY.
NO, I'M PICKING YOU UP.
HEY, NO, SERIOUSLY, I DON'T NEED YOU TO...
ALL RIGHT!
IT STILL WORKS.
OKAY. NOW, BEFORE I GO, DOES ANYBODY ELSE NEED
TO BE PICKED UP?
I'M STILL GOING TO GO.
OKAY, I'LL SEE YOU LATER, BABE.
PUBLIC DISPLAY OF AFFECTION COMING UP.
YOU CAN AVERT YOUR EYES.
SEE YA.
GOOD BYE.
FUN BOBBY IS SO GREAT.
OH, ISN'T HE?
I REALLY THINK, THIS TIME, IT MAY WORK WITH HIM.
I MEAN, HE JUST MAKES ME FEEL SO GOOD
AND I'VE BEEN FEELING SO LOUSY
THE LAST COUPLE OF MONTHS-- NO JOB, NO BOYFRIEND.
WELL, AT LEAST MY CUP IS HALF FULL.
HALF FULL OF LOVE.
AND FOR OUR TWO WEEK ANNIVERSARY HE'S GOING TO TAKE ME
TO HIS COUSIN'S CABIN FOR THE WEEKEND.
CABIN OF LOVE.
WE WENT THROUGH A LOT OF WINE TONIGHT, YOU GUYS.
REALLY? I ONLY HAD TWO GLASSES.
I JUST HAD A GLASS.
TWO.
I HAD ONE GLASS.
I HAD ABOUT A MUGFUL IN THIS LOVELY
"I GOT BONED AT THE MUSEUM OF NATURAL HISTORY" MUG.
OKAY, SO THAT'S...
THAT'S, WHAT, TWO BOTTLES
AND YET, SOMEHOW WE WENT THROUGH FIVE?
OH. OOH.
OH.
SO WHAT?
SO HE DRANK A LOT TONIGHT.
YEAH, BUT
YOU KNOW, NOW THAT I THINK ABOUT IT, I DON'T THINK
I'VE EVER SEEN FUN BOBBY WITHOUT A DRINK IN HIS HAND.
YEAH, AND OOH
YEAH, YOU KNOW, DID YOU NOTICE
HOW HE ALWAYS STARTS HIS STORIES WITH, "OKAY, I WAS SO WASTED"
OR, "WE WERE SO BOMBED," OR, "SO I WAKE UP
AND I'M IN THIS DUMPSTER IN CONNECTICUT."
MONICA, HAVE YOU
EVER BEEN WITH HIM WHEN HE WASN'T DRINKING?
WELL, WE JUST HAPPEN TO GO TO A LOT OF PLACES
WHERE YOU MIGHT DRINK.
I MEAN, HOW DO YOU GO TO A WINE TASTING
WITHOUT HAVING A DRINK?
OR TO A CLUB, OR TO THE... ZOO?
RACH, DOES THIS HAVE NON FAT MILK?
UM...
I DON'T KNOW. WHY DON'T YOU TASTE IT?
MMM. NO.
OH, WELL, TOO LATE. SORRY.
YOU ALREADY HAD SOME.
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE MAKE THESE COFFEES IRISH?
UM...
CAKE!
YEAH, WE'RE GOING TO GET SOME CAKE.
YOU KNOW, IT SEEMS LIKE YOU'VE BEEN MAKING
AN AWFUL LOT OF STUFF "IRISH" LATELY.
WELL, I WOULD MAKE THEM BELGIAN, BUT THE WAFFLES
ARE HARD TO GET INTO THAT FLASK.
BOBBY.
YEAH, OKAY.
LOOK, MAYBE THIS IS NONE OF MY BUSINESS
OR MAYBE IT IS, I DON'T KNOW
BUT, UM, I'M KIND OF WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
OKAY, LOOK, THIS ISN'T THE FIRST TIME SOMEBODY'S
SAID SOMETHING TO ME ABOUT THIS
BUT I DON'T KNOW.
I ALWAYS MADE EXCUSES ABOUT IT
LIKE "I'M JUST A SOCIAL DRINKER."
OR "HEY, COME ON, IT'S FLAG DAY."
SO, WHAT ARE YOU SAYING NOW?
I GUESS I'M SAYING I'LL TRY AND QUIT.
I KIND OF LIKE THAT YOU WORRY ABOUT ME.
SO, WHAT'S GOING ON, HUH?
I AM GOING TO TRY AND QUIT DRINKING.
OH, WHY?
HEY.
HEY. HEY.
GUESS WHO'S BACK IN SHOW BUSINESS?
OOH! OOH! LORNE GREENE?
NO. NO, PHEEBS. YOU KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE HE'S DEAD.
OH, NO.
OKAY, I GUESS IT'S GOING TO SEEM KIND OF BITTERSWEET NOW
BUT JOEY, THAT'S WHO.
OH! REALLY? MY AGENT
JUST CALLED ME WITH AN AUDITION FOR DAYS OF OUR LIVES.
YES!
HERE'S TO JOEY!
HERE, JOEY!
OH, WELL, WE HAVE TO CELEBRATE.
YOU KNOW WHAT WE SHOULD DO?
WE SHOULD DO, LIKE, A SOAP OPERA THEME.
HEY, YEAH. WE COULD ALL SLEEP TOGETHER, AND THEN ONE OF US
COULD GET AMNESIA.
HEY, RACH, WHAT TIME DO YOU GET OFF?
WE'RE ALL GOING TO DO SOMETHING TONIGHT.
UM, WELL, ACTUALLY, I'M ALREADY DONE
BUT I'VE KIND OF GOT PLANS.
YOU HAVE OTHER FRIENDS?
YEAH. I, UH, I HAVE... I HAVE A DATE.
WHAT?
YOU HAVE A DATE?
YES.I HAVE A DATE.
WITH A MAN?
NO. WITH A CROUTON.
WHAT?
WHAT IS SO STRANGE ABOUT ME HAVING A DATE?
WITH A CROUTON?
RACH...
WHAT ABOUT ROSS?
ARE YOU STILL MAD AT HIM BECAUSE HE MADE THAT LIST ABOUT YOU?
NO, NO, I'M NOT MAD AT HIM.
I'M NOT REALLY ANYTHING AT HIM ANYMORE.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I DON'T KNOW.
I... WHATEVER I WAS FEELING, I'M... NOT.
BUT YOU GUYS CAME SO CLOSE.
OH, I KNOW. I'M SORRY, YOU GUYS.
YOU'RE JUST GOING TO HAVE TO GET USED TO THE FACT
THAT I WILL NOT BE DATING ROSS.
HERE HE IS.
HI.
GUYS, THIS IS RUSS.
ESTELLE LEONARD TALENT AGENCY.
OH, SAMMY, WOULD YOU STOP CALLING ME ALREADY?
NO... NO, NO, NO, NO.
I'M NOT SAYING YOU'RE NOT TALENTED.
YOU'RE VERY TALENTED.
IT'S JUST THAT WITH THE BIRD DEAD AND ALL
THERE'S VERY LITTLE ACT LEFT.
OH, HONEY, GIVE ME A BREAK.
OH. I'LL TALK TO YOU LATER.
WELL, THERE'S MY FAVORITE CLIENT.
SO, TELL ME, DARLING, HOW WAS THE AUDITION?
WELL, I THINK IT WENT PRETTY WELL.
I GOT A CALLBACK FOR THURSDAY.
JOEY, HAVE YOU EVER SEEN ME ECSTATIC?
NO.
WELL, HERE IT IS.
OKAY.
LISTEN, THERE'S SOMETHING I WANT TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT.
THE NETWORK CASTING LADY...
OH, ISN'T LORI A DOLL?
YEAH, YEAH, SHE'S GREAT
BUT I KIND OF GOT THE FEELING
THAT SHE WAS SORT OF COMING ONTO ME
AND I DEFINITELY WOULD GET THE PART
IF I WOULD HAVE, YOU KNOW...
IF I WOULD HAVE SENT THE LITTLE GENERAL IN.
OH.
I SEE.
WELL, I'M JUST GOING TO PUT IN A CALL HERE
AND WE'LL FIND OUT WHAT'S GOING ON
AND STRAIGHTEN IT OUT.
YEAH, HI.
LORI, PLEASE.
HI, DARLING.
SO, HOW ABOUT JOEY TRIBBIANI FOR THE PART OF THE CAB DRIVER?
ISN'T HE TERRIFIC?
UH HUH.
OKAY, DOLL, I'LL TALK TO YOU LATER.
YEAH, YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO SLEEP WITH HER.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
FUN BOBBY.
WHAT? ISN'T HE SOBER?
OH, HE'S SOBER, ALL RIGHT.
JUST TURNS OUT THAT FUN BOBBY WAS FUN FOR A REASON.
OH.
THANKS.
ALL RIGHT, HERE YOU GO, SWEETIE.
YOU WANT TO HEAR SOMETHING FUNNY?
OH, GOD, YES.
THERE ARE NO HARDWARE STORES OPEN PAST MIDNIGHT
IN THE VILLAGE.
THAT IS FUNNY.
I NEEDED TO BUY A HAMMER THE OTHER NIGHT
AND I'M OUT WALKING AROUND THE NEIGHBORHOOD
AND I'M WALKING AND I'M WALKING AND I'M WALKING...
OKAY...
SO YOU'RE SAYING YOU WERE WALKING.
BUT APPARENTLY, THERE ARE NO HARDWARE STORES
OPEN PAST MIDNIGHT IN THE VILLAGE.
HUH.
SO... SO, IT'S A HELPFUL FACT
AS WELL AS FUNNY.
GOOD JOB.
SAY, HONEY, DON'T YOU HAVE TO BE AT YOUR INTERVIEW NOW?
OH, YEAH.
SEE YOU GUYS.
BYE...
RIDICULOUSLY DULL BOBBY.
OH, MY GOD.
IT'S NOT THAT BAD.
NOT THAT BAD?
DID YOU NOT HEAR THE HAMMER STORY?
OKAY, OKAY. DON'T GET ALL SQUINKY.
MAYBE IT WAS JUST THE KIND OF STORY WHERE YOU HAD TO BE THERE.
BUT I'M GOING TO BE THERE, FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE.
I MEAN, I CAN'T BREAK UP
WITH HIM. I'M THE ONE WHO MADE HIM QUIT DRINKING.
HE'S DULL BECAUSE OF ME.
DON'T SAY THAT.
HE'S PROBABLY ALWAYS BEEN DULL.
YOU JUST, YOU KNOW, SET IT FREE.
HI.
HEY, ROSS. BAH!
HI, RUSS.
I'VE JUST GOT TWO MORE TABLES TO CLEAN
AND THEN WE'LL GO, OKAY?
OKAY. I'LL JUST SIT HERE
AND CHAT WITH YOUR, UH, FRIEND TYPE PEOPLE.
RACHEL.
YEAH.
UM, HI. HI.
OKAY, SO, YOU KNOW WHAT YOU'RE DOING, RIGHT?
WAITRESSING?
WELL, YEAH, BUT NO.
I MEAN, UM, OKAY.
DOESN'T RUSS JUST REMIND YOU OF SOMEONE?
HUH.
BOB SAGET?
OH, YEAH.
NO, NO, NO. OH, OH.
HI.
OH, MY, OH.
WHAT'S WRONG?
OKAY.
SHE'S JUST UPSET
BECAUSE SHE BUTTERED A SPIDER INTO HER TOAST THIS MORNING.
ALL RIGHT.
LISTEN, PHEEBS, THIS IS GOING TO BE OKAY.
ROSS, RUSS. RUSS, ROSS.
HI.
ARE YOU A, UH, FRIEND OF RACHEL'S?
YES. YES, I AM.
ARE YOU A, UH, A FRIEND OF RACHEL'S?
ACTUALLY, I'M, UH, KIND OF, UH
YOU KNOW, UH, A DATE TYPE.... THING
OF RACHEL'S.
A DATE?
YEAH.
I'M HER DATE.
OH. OH, YOU'RE, UH...
OH, YOU'RE THE DATE?
YOU KNOW, THIS IS ACTUALLY GOOD
BECAUSE IF WE EVER LOSE ROSS, WE HAVE A SPARE.
OH, YOU ARE THE, UH, PALEONTOLOGIST.
YES. YES, I AM.
AND YOU ARE A...
PERIODONTIST.
SEE, THEY'RE AS DIFFERENT AS NIGHT AND...
LATER THAT NIGHT.
WELL, I AM GOING TO, UH... GET A BEVERAGE.
IT WAS NICE, NICE, UH, MEETING YOU.
DITTO.
I, UH, WELL, I MET RUSS.
OH.
HEY, I DIDN'T KNOW WE WERE SEEING OTHER PEOPLE.
WELL, WE'RE NOT SEEING EACH OTHER, SO...
WELL, FOR YOUR INFORMATION, THERE'S A WOMAN AT THE MUSEUM
WHO'S CURATOR OF MOTHS AND OTHER WINGED THINGS
WHO'S, UH...
LET IT BE KNOWN THAT SHE IS DRAWN TO ME
MUCH LIKE A... WELL, YOU KNOW.
WELL, SO FAR I'VE BEEN KEEPING HER AT BAY
BUT, UH, IF THIS IS THE DEAL, THEN...
WELL, YEAH, THIS IS THE DEAL.
OKAY, WELL, UM... HAVE A NICE EVENING.
THANK YOU.
RUSS, YOU READY?
YEAH.
BYE.
SHE'S DATING?
YES. YES, BUT DID YOU SEE WHO SHE WAS DATING?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
DO YOU NOT SEE IT?
SEE WHAT? I DON'T KNOW WHAT SHE SEES IN... THAT GOOBER.
AND IT... AND IT TAKES HIM, WHAT?
LIKE, I DON'T KNOW, UH, UH, HELLO
A WEEK TO GET OUT A SENTENCE?
YEAH, IT'S ANNOYING, ISN'T IT?
YEAH.
HEY.
WHOA, WHOA. SO I'M GUESSING YOU DIDN'T GET THE PART.
OR ITALY CALLED AND SAID IT WAS HUNGRY.
THE PART'S MINE IF I WANT IT.
OH, MY GOD!
YEAH, IF I'M WILLING TO SLEEP WITH THE CASTING LADY.
OH, MY...
GOD.
TEN YEARS I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR A BREAK
LIKE THIS, CHANDLER-- TEN YEARS.
I MEAN, DAYS OF OUR LIVES--
THAT'S ACTUALLY ON TELEVISION.
SO WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
I GUESS I COULD SLEEP WITH HER.
BUT HOW CAN I DO THAT?
WELL, I'VE GOT A POP UP BOOK
THAT TOLD ME EVERYTHING I NEED TO KNOW.
I'VE NEVER SLEPT WITH SOMEONE FOR A PART.
WELL, IS SHE..?
SORRY.
IS SHE GOOD LOOKING?
YEAH, SHE'S TOTALLY GOOD LOOKING.
I MEAN, IF I MET HER IN A BAR OR SOMETHING
I'D BE BUYING HER BREAKFAST.
YOU KNOW, AFTER HAVING SLEPT WITH HER.
YOU KNOW, MAYBE THIS ISN'T SUCH A BIG DEAL.
I MEAN, THE WAY THAT I SEE IT
IS YOU GET A GREAT JOB AND YOU GET TO HAVE SEX.
THROW IN A TREE AND A FAT GUY
AND YOU'VE GOT CHRISTMAS.
I JUST DON'T THINK THAT I WANT IT THAT WAY THOUGH, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, LET'S SAY I DO MAKE IT, ALL RIGHT?
I'M ALWAYS GOING TO LOOK BACK AND WONDER
IF IT WAS BECAUSE OF MY TALENT
OR BECAUSE OF, YOU KNOW...
THE LITTLE GENERAL.
DIDN'T YOU USED TO CALL IT THE "LITTLE MAJOR"?
YEAH, BUT AFTER DENISE DiMARCO, I HAD TO PROMOTE IT.
CAN I GET YOU SOMETHING FROM THE BAR?
YES, I WOULD LIKE SOMETHING.
NO. NO, THANK YOU.
IF YOU WANT A DRINK, IT'S OKAY WITH ME.
I'VE GOT TO GET USED TO IT.
NO, REALLY, I WOULDN'T FEEL RIGHT ABOUT IT.
JUST SOME WATER, PLEASE.
THE LIGHT WENT OUT IN MY REFRIGERATOR.
I'D LIKE A SCOTCH ON THE ROCKS WITH A TWIST.
I'M SORRY.
HEY, WE'RE HAVING SOME FUN NOW, HUH, ROSS?
WANT TO DO ANOTHER ONE, HUH, RUSS?
OKAY, 11 LETTERS.
"ATOMIC ELEMENT NUMBER 101."
ENDS IN "IUM".
DYSPROSIUM?
TRY MENDELEVIUM.
AND WEENIE NUMBER TWO HAS IT.
UNLESS, OF COURSE, NINE DOWN-- "KNIGHTS IN WHITE SATIN"
WAS SUNG BY THE DOODY BLUES.
YOU DON'T SEE IT?
YOU ACTUALLY DON'T SEE IT?
WHAT?
OKAY, HONEY, YOU'RE DATING ROSS.
NO, PHEEBS, I'M DATING RUSS.
RUSS IS ROSS.
RUSS, ROSS.
STEVE, SLEEVE.
OKAY, NO ONE IS NAMED SLEEVE.
PHOEBE, WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
OTHER THAN THEIR NAMES BEING SIMILAR
I'M SORRY, I DO NOT SEE WHAT YOU'RE SEEING.
FOR YOUR INFORMATION
IT'S A CARD SHARP, NOT A CARD SHARK.
YOU COULD NOT BE MORE WRONG.
YOU COULD TRY, BUT YOU WOULD NOT BE SUCCESSFUL.
OKAY, I'M GOING TO GET SOME MORE COFFEE
BEFORE THE PINCHING AND EYE POKING BEGINS.
I KNOW WHAT YOUR PROBLEM IS.
OH, YOU DO, DO YOU?
MM HMM. YOU'RE JEALOUS.
UH... OF WHAT?
YOU'RE JEALOUS
BECAUSE I'M A REAL DOCTOR.
HEY, YOU'RE A DOCTOR OF GUMS.
THAT'S THE SMALLEST BODY PART YOU CAN MAJOR IN.
IT'S LIKE, DAY ONE: FLOSS.
DAY TWO: HERE'S YOUR DIPLOMA.
YOU LISTEN...
NO, NO, LET ME FINISH.
NO, LET ME FINISH.
NO, YOU LET ME FINISH.
HI.
EW.
EW, EW, EW, EW, EW, EW, EW...
DID JOEY SAY WHAT HE WAS GOING TO DO WHEN HE LEFT?
NO. I DON'T EVEN THINK HE KNEW.
HEY, WOULD YOU SLEEP WITH SOMEBODY TO GET A GREAT JOB?
I DON'T KNOW. WHO WOULD I HAVE TO SLEEP WITH?
ME.
WHY WOULD I HAVE TO SLEEP WITH YOU?
IT'S MY GAME. YOU WANT THE JOB, OR NOT?
HI.
HEY.
GOOD MORNING.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
BOBBY AND I ARE GOING AWAY FOR THE WEEKEND, REMEMBER?
OH!
WHAT'S WITH ALL THE BOTTLES OF LIQUOR?
EXCUSE ME, MISS
IN THE EVENT OF A WATER LANDING
CAN THIS SEAT BE USED AS A FLOATATION DEVICE?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
IS BOBBY DRINKING AGAIN?
NO, THIS IS NOT FOR HIM; THIS IS FOR ME.
THAT WAY
HE'S STILL SOBER
BUT I FIND HIS STORIES ABOUT SHOELACES MUCH MORE AMUSING.
GOD, EVEN HIS KNOCK IS BORING.
HI. I'LL BE READY IN A SECOND.
COULD I TALK TO YOU A MINUTE?
SURE.
THIS IS REALLY HARD FOR ME TO SAY.
OH, GOD! YOU FELL OFF THE WAGON.
NO, NO.
IT'S ABOUT YOU.
WHAT ABOUT ME?
I THINK YOU MAY HAVE A DRINKING PROBLEM.
WHAT? THESE?
NO, THESE ARE, UM... FOR CUTS AND SCRAPES.
LOOK, I AM JUST NOT STRONG ENOUGH
TO BE IN A CO DEPENDENT RELATIONSHIP RIGHT NOW, OKAY?
OH, SHOOT.
WELL, ANYWAY, I HOPE WE CAN BE FRIENDS.
OKAY.
TAKE CARE.
OKAY, YOU TOO.
BYE.
WHAT HAPPENED?
WELL, WE KIND OF BROKE UP.
OH...
DOES ANYBODY WANT THESE?
I'LL TAKE ONE.
SOMETIMES I LIKE TO HOLD STUFF LIKE THIS
AND PRETEND I'M A GIANT.
HEY.
HOW'D THE CALLBACK GO?
IT WAS UNBELIEVABLE.
I WALKED IN THERE, AND SHE WAS ALL OVER ME.
SO, WHAT'D YOU DO?
WELL, I COULDN'T DO IT.
I TOLD HER I DIDN'T WANT TO GET THE PART THAT WAY.
GOOD FOR YOU. WOW.
BUT WAIT, WAIT. BUT THEN AFTER I LEFT
HER OFFICE, SHE CAUGHT UP WITH ME AT THE ELEVATOR
AND OFFERED ME AN EVEN BIGGER PART.
SO, AND?
SO, YOU ARE NOW LOOKING
AT DR. DRAKE RAMORAY, NEUROSURGEON
RECURRING IN AT LEAST FOUR EPISODES!
ALL RIGHT, I GOT TO GO SHOWER.
HI.
OH, HEY.
I GUESS YOU GUYS HEARD RACHEL DUMPED ME.
YEAH, I'M SORRY, MAN.
ALL SHE SAID WAS THAT I REMIND HER TOO MUCH OF SOMEBODY.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA WHO SHE'S TALKING ABOUT?
UM... OH, I DO.
IT'S BOB SAGET.
SHE HATES HIM.
HEY.
HEY, JULIE.
HEY, HOW ARE YOU DOING?
OH... OH, I DON'T KNOW.
I MEAN, IT'S DEFINITELY WEIRD NOT BEING WITH ROSS
BUT I GUESS I'M DOING OKAY.
ACTUALLY, I'VE GOT
SOME OF HIS STUFF THAT HE, UM...
HAVE WE MET?
I DON'T THINK SO.
YOU LOOK SO FAMILIAR.
WELL, MAYBE, UH...
MAYBE WE COULD TALK ABOUT IT OVER A CUP OF COFFEE.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M SICK OF COFFEE.
LET'S GO GET US SOME JUICE.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY. BYE.
BYE. OKAY.