HEY.
HOLD ON A SECOND.
HUH?
NICE.
HEY, I GOT SOMETHING FOR YOU.
WHAT'S THIS?
812 BUCKS.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW WHAT BIG LEON TOLD YOU
BUT IT'S AN EVEN THOUSAND IF YOU WANT ME
FOR THE WHOLE NIGHT.
WHAT IS THIS FOR?
WELL, I'M MAKING MONEY NOW
AND THIS IS PAYING YOU BACK
FOR HEAD SHOTS, ELECTRIC BILLS
AND SO MANY SLICES OF PIZZA, I CAN'T EVEN COUNT.
I LOVE YOU, MAN.
WELL, THANKS, MAN.
NOW I CAN GET MY PONY.
HEY, THIS IS A LITTLE EXTRA SOMETHING
FOR, YOU KNOW, ALWAYS BEING THERE FOR ME.
WOW. I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
HUH? WHAT DO YOU SAY?
I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S A BRACELET.
ISN'T IT?
AND IT'S ENGRAVED, TOO.
CHECK IT OUT.
"TO MY BEST BUD."
THANKS, BEST BUD.
PUT IT ON.
OH, NOW?
NO, NO, I THINK SOMETHING THIS NICE
SHOULD BE SAVED FOR A SPECIAL OCCASION.
OH, NO, NO, THAT'S THE BEAUTY PART.
IT GOES WITH EVERYTHING.
YOU PUT THIS ON... YOU'RE GOOD TO GO.
WELL, I'VE NEVER BEEN GOOD TO GO
SO WHAT THE HELL?
WHY NOT TRY SOME JEWELRY, HUH?
YEAH.
OH HO HO, MAN.
YOU ARE SO WEARING THAT BRACELET. WHOO.
I SO AM.
WHOA, YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT THIS WILL DO FOR YOUR SEX LIFE?
IT'LL PROBABLY SLOW IT DOWN AT FIRST
BUT, ONCE I GET USED TO THE EXTRA WEIGHT
I'LL BE BACK ON TRACK.
WELL, THIS ALL LOOKS GOOD.
GREAT.
IF I WANT TO CALL FOR A REFERENCE ON YOUR LAST JOB?
OH, THAT'S THERE ON THE BOTTOM.
"SEE THE MANAGER-- CHANDLER BING."
ALL RIGHT, LET'S SEE IF YOU'RE
AS GOOD IN PERSON AS YOU ARE ON PAPER.
MAKE ME A SALAD.
A SALAD? REALLY?
I COULD DO SOMETHING A LITTLE MORE COMPLICATED, IF YOU LIKE.
NO, JUST A SALAD WILL BE FINE.
ALL RIGHT, YOU GOT IT.
NOW, I WANT YOU TO TELL ME
WHAT YOU'RE DOING WHILE YOU'RE DOING IT.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, I'M TEARING THE LETTUCE.
UH HUH. IS IT DIRTY?
NO, DON'T WORRY. I'LL WASH IT.
DON'T. I LIKE IT DIRTY.
IT'S... YOUR CALL.
SO, UH... WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO NEXT?
WELL, I THOUGHT THAT I WOULD CUT UP THE TOMATOES.
ARE THEY, UH, FIRM?
THEY'RE ALL RIGHT.
YOU SURE THEY HAVEN'T GONE BAD?
YOU SURE THEY'RE NOT VERY, VERY BAD?
NO, REALLY, THEY'RE OKAY.
YOU GOING TO SLICE THEM UP REAL NICE?
ACTUALLY, I WAS GOING TO DO THEM JULIENNE.
I'M OUT OF HERE.
HELLO.
NO, RACHEL'S NOT HERE RIGHT NOW.
CAN I TAKE A MESSAGE?
AND HOW DO WE SPELL CASEY?
IS IT LIKE "AT THE BAT" OR "AND THE SUNSHINE BAND"?
OKAY.
BYE BYE.
HEY, WHO'S THIS, UH, THIS CASEY?
OH, SOME GUY SHE MET AT THE MOVIES.
OH, REALLY? WHAT DOES HE WANT WITH HER?
WELL, I'M GUESSING HE WANTS TO
DO A LITTLE DANCE...
YOU KNOW, MAKE A LITTLE LOVE.
WELL, PRETTY MUCH GET DOWN TONIGHT.
I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T GET IT.
TWO MONTHS AGO, RACHEL AND I WERE THIS CLOSE, RIGHT?
NOW I'M TAKING MESSAGES
FROM GUYS SHE... SHE MEETS AT THE MOVIES?
I MEAN, THIS CASEY SHOULD BE
TAKING DOWN MY MESSAGES, YOU KNOW?
OR, OR... RACHEL AND I SHOULD BE TOGETHER
AND WE SHOULD GET...
SOME KIND OF MESSAGE SERVICE.
HANG IN THERE.
IT'S GOING TO HAPPEN.
NOW HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT?
BECAUSE SHE'S YOUR LOBSTER.
OH, SHE'S GOING SOMEWHERE.
COME ON, YOU GUYS.
IT'S A KNOWN FACT THAT LOBSTERS
FALL IN LOVE AND MATE FOR LIFE.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU CAN ACTUALLY SEE OLD LOBSTER COUPLES
WALKING AROUND THEIR TANK
YOU KNOW, HOLDING CLAWS, LIKE...
YOU HAVE... YOU HAVE TO PICTURE LOBSTERS.
HEY, YOU FEELING BETTER?
YEAH, I THINK THAT FIFTH SHOWER
ACTUALLY GOT THE INTERVIEW OFF ME.
SO, DO YOU HAVE ANY OTHER POSSIBILITIES?
YEAH, WELL, THERE IS THE POSSIBILITY
THAT I WON'T MAKE RENT.
MONICA, IF YOU WANT, I CAN LEND YOU SOME MONEY.
NO, NO, BECAUSE IF I COULDN'T PAY YOU BACK RIGHT AWAY
I'D FEEL GUILTY AND TENSE EVERY TIME I SAW YOU.
OH, OKAY. WELL, WHY DON'T YOU BORROW IT FROM MOM AND DAD?
YOU FEEL GUILTY AND TENSE AROUND THEM ALREADY.
YOU MIGHT AS WELL MAKE SOME MONEY
OFF OF THEM.
YOU KNOW, THE MAN'S GOT A POINT.
OOH.
WHAT IS THAT SPARKLY THING?
THAT THING?
IT'S A, UH...
YEAH, IT'S...
IT'S A LITTLE FLASHY.
NO, NO. NO, NO.
IT'S NOT FLASHY-- NOT FOR A GOODFELLA.
MAN!
MAN, THAT IS SHARP.
THAT MUST HAVE COST YOU QUITE A FEW DOUBLOONS.
NO, IT'S FUN. IT'S FUN.
IT'S KIND OF LIKE KNOWING ONE OF THE GABOR SISTERS.
HI.
HI. HI, DARLING.
SO, WHAT'S THIS?
SOME OF YOUR OLD STUFF.
WELL, SWEETIE, WE HAVE A SURPRISE FOR YOU.
WE'RE TURNING YOUR ROOM INTO A GYM.
WOW, THAT IS A SURPRISE.
JUST ONE LITTLE QUESTION.
UH, WHY NOT ROSS' ROOM?
GOSH, WE TALKED ABOUT THAT
BUT YOUR BROTHER HAS SO MANY SCIENCE TROPHIES
AND PLAQUES AND MERIT BADGES...
WELL, WE DIDN'T WANT TO DISTURB THEM.
OH, GOD FORBID.
SO, WHAT'S NEW WITH YOU?
WHAT CAN YOU TELL US?
HOW'S YOUR JOB?
MY JOB?
WELL, UH... DID I MENTION
I STILL DON'T HAVE A BOYFRIEND?
OH, WELL, I JUST ASSUMED.
OH, HI.
HELLO.
RACHEL, OH...
WE WERE SO SORRY TO HEAR
ABOUT YOUR PARENTS SPLITTING UP, DEAR.
WELL, YOU KNOW, THEY'RE JUST SEPARATED
SO, YOU NEVER KNOW. WE'LL SEE.
WELL, I CAN'T SAY ANY OF US WERE SURPRISED.
YOUR PARENTS HAVE BEEN UNHAPPY EVER SINCE
WE'VE KNOWN THEM...
ESPECIALLY AFTER THAT INCIDENT
IN HAWAII.
WHAT...
WHAT INCIDENT?
UH, NO. NO, NO, NO, NO
I MUST BE THINKING OF SOMEONE ELSE.
MAYBE ME. HA!
DON'T YOU HAVE SOME FOLDING TO DO?
GO FOLD, DEAR, FOLD.
YOU FOLD. GO AHEAD.
DO YOU WANT A REFILL?
NO, I'M ALL RIGHT. THANKS.
OKAY. OOH.
OKAY, YOU GOT TO GIVE ME A SECOND.
I WANT TO GET THIS JUST RIGHT.
DUDE-- 11:00, TOTALLY HOT BABE CHECKING YOU OUT.
THAT WAS REALLY GOOD.
THINK I'M READY FOR MY PENIS NOW.
I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE THINKING--
DAVE THOMAS, FOUNDER OF WENDY'S.
I'M GAIL.
CHANDLER.
I... I, I REALLY HAVE TO BE SOMEWHERE
BUT IT WAS NICE MEETING YOU.
WHA...
OH, THIS IS EXCELLENT.
YOU KNOW, HE COULD HAVE GOT ME A V.C.R.
HE COULD HAVE GOT ME A SET OF GOLF CLUBS
BUT NO, HE HAS TO GET ME "THE WOMAN REPELLER."
THE EYESORE FROM THE LIBERACE HOUSE OF CRAP!
IT'S NOT THAT BAD.
OH, EASY FOR YOU TO SAY. YOU DON'T HAVE TO WALK AROUND
SPORTING SOME REJECT FROM THE MR. "T" COLLECTION.
CHANDLER... CHANDLER.
"I PITY THE FOOL THAT PUTS ON MY JEWELRY!
"I DO! I DO!
I PITY THE FOOL THAT--" HI.
HEY, MAN, WE WERE JUST DOING
SOME IMPRESSIONS OVER HERE.
DO YOUR MARCEL MARCEAU.
THAT'S ACTUALLY GOOD.
WOULD YOU LOOK AT THAT GUY?
HOW LONG HAS HE BEEN TALKING TO HER?
I DON'T KNOW. COUPLE OF MINUTES.
YEAH? TRY DOUBLING THAT.
IT'S LIKE, BACK OFF, BUDDY.
SHE'S A WAITRESS, NOT A GEISHA.
I THINK SHE'S OKAY.
LOOK AT THAT. LOOK AT THAT.
SEE HOW SHE'S PUSHING HIM AWAY, AND HE WON'T BUDGE?
ALL RIGHT, I'M GOING TO DO SOMETHING.
YEAH, YOU CAN GET A CONDO
RIGHT ON THE MOUNTAIN SIDE.
YOU SKI IN, SKI OUT. IT'S GREAT.
I LOVE IT.
EXCUSE ME? ARE YOU RACHEL?
WHAT?
ROSS GELLER.
GOD, IN YOUR AD YOU SAID YOU WERE PRETTY...
BUT WOW.
WHAT ARE YOU... WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
OH, MY GOD. IS THIS... IS THIS THE WRONG DAY?
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
I GUESS, IF IT WORKS OUT
WE'LL HAVE SOMETHING TO TELL THE GRANDKIDS.
YOU SURE WILL.
I'VE, UH... GOT TO GO.
WAIT... WHAT...
TAKE CARE.
OKAY. SEE YOU LATER.
NICE MEETING YOU.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
WHAT?
I WAS SAVING YOU.
SAVE ME FROM THE PLEASANT CONVERSATION
WITH THE INTERESTING MAN?
OH, SEE, FROM WHERE I WAS SITTING...
OKAY, ROSS, LISTEN TO ME.
I AM NOT YOURS TO SAVE.
BUT, YOU ARE.
WHAT?
WELL, YOU, UM...
YOU'RE MY LOBSTER.
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
ARE YOU BEING, LIKE, THE BLIND DATE GUY AGAIN?
NO, NO.
YOU'RE MY LOBSTER.
SEE, UM... LOBSTERS, UH...
IN THE TANK, WHEN THEY'RE OLD, UH...
THEY GET WITH THE...
THEY WALK AROUND HOLDING THE CLAWS.
IN THE TANK, YOU KNOW?
WITH... WITH THE HOLDING? AND...
PHEEBS, YOU WANT TO HELP ME OUT
WITH THE WHOLE LOBSTER THING?
DO THE CLAWS AGAIN.
RACH... OKAY, FORGET THE LOBSTERS, OKAY?
WE'RE... LET'S TALK... WHAT ABOUT US?
ROSS, THERE IS NO US.
OKAY?
NO, BUT...
NO, LISTEN TO ME.
I FELL FOR YOU, AND I GET CLOBBERED.
YOU, THEN, FALL FOR ME
AND I, AGAIN, SOMEHOW GET CLOBBERED.
I'M TIRED OF BEING CLOBBERED, YOU KNOW?
IT'S... IT'S JUST NOT WORTH IT.
WELL, BUT... BUT...
NO "BUT," ROSS.
WE ARE NEVER GOING TO HAPPEN, OKAY?
ACCEPT THAT.
EX... EXCEPT...
EXCEPT THAT WHAT?
NO.
ACCEPT... THAT.
OH.
I GOT TO GO.
HEY, MAN. LOOK, IT'S MY BEST BUD.
HOW YOU DOING?
WOW. YOU ARE REALLY GETTING GOOD
AT THAT MARCEL MARCEAU THING.
HEY, LISTEN, WHAT DO YOU SAY WE PLAY SOME BALL?
YOU AND ME. HUH?
OKAY, THAT'S MY BAD.
IF YOU HATED THE BRACELET SO MUCH, CHANDLER
YOU SHOULD'VE JUST SAID SO.
WELL, DOESN'T THE FACT THAT I WORE THE BRACELET
EVEN THOUGH I HATED IT SAY SOMETHING
ABOUT OUR FRIENDSHIP AND HOW MUCH IT MEANS TO ME?
WELL, WHAT ABOUT THE FACT THAT YOU INSULTED THE BRACELET
AND YOU MADE FUN OF ME?
OKAY, WELL, THAT'S THE PART WHERE I'M A WANK...
BUT I WAS HOPING, YOU KNOW, WE WOULDN'T FOCUS ON THAT.
OH, YEAH?
WELL, FOCUS ON THIS.
HARD TO ARGUE WITH THAT.
COME ON, MAN. I SAID I WAS SORRY, LIKE, A HUNDRED TIMES.
I PROMISE, I WILL NEVER TAKE IT OFF MY...
WRIST.
BUT IF YOU WANT TO STAY IN THERE AND BE MAD
YOU JUST, UH, YOU STAY IN THERE.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I AM HERE ON MY KNEES...
HOLDING UP THESE COUCH CUSHIONS...
AS A SYMBOL OF MY SORROW AND REGRET...
MUCH LIKE THEY DID IN BIBLICAL TIMES.
THOUGH YOU MAY HAVE THE ANGER NOW...
YOU'RE GOING TO GRAB YOURSELF AGAIN, AREN'T YOU?
YOU KNOW, THAT STEFFI GRAF HAS QUITE A TUSH.
I'M JUST SAYING.
IT'S RIGHT THERE.
HEY, GUYS.
HI, DARLING.
WHERE'S MY GRANDSON?
YOU DIDN'T BRING HIM?
NO, HE'S AT CAROL'S AND SUSAN'S TODAY.
A WOMAN IN MY OFFICE IS A LESBIAN.
I'M JUST SAYING.
OH, JACK, LOOK.
THERE'S THAT HOUSE PAINT COMMERCIAL
THAT CRACKS YOU UP.
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
EMOTIONAL HELL.
SO, DID THEY LEND YOU THE MONEY YET?
NO, BUT THAT'S PROBABLY BECAUSE I HAVEN'T ASKED THEM YET.
COME ON, MONICA, DO IT.
HEY, YOU GUYS.
UM, MONICA HAS SOME NEWS.
UM, YEAH, UH...
LISTEN, I'M SORRY I DIDN'T TELL YOU THIS BEFORE
BUT, UM, I'M NO LONGER AT MY JOB.
I HAD TO LEAVE IT.
WHY?
BECAUSE THEY MADE ME.
YOU WERE... FIRED?
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
JUDY, JUDY, RELAX.
THIS IS OUR LITTLE HARMONICA WE'RE TALKING ABOUT.
WE TAUGHT HER WELL.
TEN PERCENT OF YOUR PAYCHECK-- WHERE DOES IT GO?
IN THE BANK. IN THE BANK.
THERE YOU GO. SO SHE DIPS INTO HER SAVINGS.
THAT'S WHAT IT'S THERE FOR.
SHE'S GOING TO BE FINE.
AREN'T YOU, SWEETIE?
IN THE BANK.
AND IF YOU NEED A LITTLE EXTRA
YOU KNOW WHERE TO FIND IT.
ANYTHING LARGER BACK THERE?
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
WOULD YOU STOP ALREADY?
GET OUT OF THE BITTER BARN
AND PLAY IN THE HAY.
OH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I SHOULD PLAY IN THE HAY.
FORGET ABOUT THE FACT THAT I JUST DROPPED $400 DOLLAR
TO REPLACE A BRACELET THAT I HATED TO BEGIN WITH.
BRING ON THE HAY.
HEY.
I'VE GOT SOMETHING
THAT'S GOING TO MAKE YOU HAPPY.
GUESS WHAT GUNTHER FOUND.
OH!
HEY, NOW YOU HAVE TWO.
OH.
NOW YOU HAVE TWO.
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO, HUH?
HEY.
HOW COME YOU HAVE TWO?
WELL, THIS ONE'S FOR YOU.
GET OUT.
NO, I CAN'T.
I KNOW HOW MUCH THIS MEANS TO YOU
AND I ALSO KNOW
THAT THIS IS ABOUT MORE THAN JUST JEWELRY.
IT'S ABOUT YOU AND ME
AND THE FACT THAT WE'RE BEST BUDS.
WOW.
IS THIS FRIENDSHIP?
I THINK SO.
CHECK IT OUT.
WE'RE BRACELET BUDDIES.
THAT'S WHAT THEY'LL CALL US.
OKAY, HERE YOU GO.
YOU CAN PAY ME BACK WHENEVER YOU LIKE.
YOU HAVE DINOSAUR CHECKS?
YEAH. YEAH, I MEAN, YOU GET YOUR MONEY
AND YOU LEARN A LITTLE SOMETHING.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH THAT?
NOTHING. NOTHING.
HEY, YOU'RE A CHEAP ASAURUS.
I'M KIDDING. I'M KIDDING.
THANK YOU. I'M VERY GRATEFUL.
HEY, MON, WHAT IS THIS?
OH, UM, THAT WAS MY BATHING SUIT FROM HIGH SCHOOL.
I WAS A LITTLE BIGGER THEN.
I THOUGHT THAT'S WHAT THEY USED
TO COVER CONNECTICUT
WHEN IT RAINS.
HEY, MONICA, WHAT'S ON THIS VIDEOTAPE?
I DON'T KNOW. YOU GOT ME.
LET'S PUT IT IN.
HELLO.
HI.
HEY.
MMM...
Over here, Jack.
Okay.
I see Rachel's coming up the path.
Oh, doesn't she look pretty?
Jack, can you get this?
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT IS WITH YOUR NOSE?
THEY HAD TO REDUCE IT BECAUSE OF MY DEVIATED SEPTUM.
OKAY, I WAS WRONG.
THAT'S WHAT THEY USE TO COVER CONNECTICUT.
YOU KNOW WHAT THIS IS?
THIS IS US GETTING READY FOR THE PROM.
OH.
YOU KNOW WHAT, GUYS?
WE DON'T HAVE TO WATCH THIS.
YEAH, WE DO.
IT'LL BE FUN.
Did you get a shot of Monica?
WHERE'S MONICA?
OVER HERE, DAD.
WAIT. HOW DO YOU ZOOM OUT?
THERE SHE IS.
SOME GIRL ATE MONICA.
SHUT UP.
THE CAMERA ADDS TEN POUNDS.
SO, HOW MANY CAMERAS ARE ACTUALLY ON YOU?
Oh, you look so great.
So do you. Beautiful.
Oops.
Shoot. I got mayonnaise on you.
Oh, that's okay.
It's just the shoulder, not my dress.
EVERYBODY SMILE.
OH.
DAD, TURN IT OFF.
IT IS OFF.
IT IS NOT.
WHAT'S WITH THE RED LIGHT?
THAT'S THE "OFF" LIGHT.
RIGHT, ROSS?
LOOKING GOOD, MR. KOTTER.
YOU LOOK REALLY PRETTY TONIGHT.
OH, THANKS.
SO, WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO THIS SUMMER?
OH, YOU KNOW, I'M GOING TO HANG OUT AND WORK ON MY MUSIC.
OH.
IS MY HOOK UNHOOKED?
THESE THINGS KEEP FALLING DOWN.
I CAN'T...
KEEP THEM UP.
Uh, let me see.
I don't know.
So, what are you going to do...
Oh, the guys are here!
...this summer?
WORK ON YOUR MUSIC?
OH, MY GOD!
THERE'S ROY GUBLICK!
YOU KNOW, ROY SAW STAR WARS 317 TIMES.
HIS NAME WAS IN THE PAPER.
WHERE'S CHIP?
WHY ISN'T HE HERE YET?
HE'LL BE HERE, OKAY?
TAKE A CHILL PILL.
THERE.
I JUST TOLD RACHEL
THAT ROY TOUCHED MY BOOB.
I CAN'T GO TO MY OWN PROM WITHOUT A DATE.
I CAN'T. IT'S TOO LATE.
IF YOU'RE NOT GOING, I DON'T WANT TO GO EITHER.
OH, I'M GOING TO KICK CHIP'S ASS.
I HAVE A WONDERFUL IDEA.
YOU SHOULD TAKE RACHEL TO THE PROM.
DOUBTFUL.
JACK, GIVE ME THAT.
TALK TO YOUR SON.
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
YOUR MOTHER'S RIGHT. TAKE HER.
YOU COULD WEAR MY TUX.
DAD, SHE WON'T WANT TO GO WITH ME.
Of course, she would.
You're a college man.
I DON'T KNOW.
WELL, COME ON.
DON'T YOU WANT TO FIND OUT?
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I DON'T GET TO GO TO MY OWN PROM.
THIS IS SO HARSH.
OKAY.
HOLD MY BOARD.
ATTABOY.
OKAY, YOU GUYS, I THINK WE'VE SEEN ENOUGH.
NO, NO, NO.
NO.
OKAY, FINE. WELL, I'M NOT GOING TO WATCH, ALL RIGHT?
Come on, kid.
LET'S GO.
ARE YOU HANDSOME.
LET'S SHOW THEM.
JUST A SEC, DAD.
JUST BE COOL.
OKAY, DAD.
RACHEL, READY OR NOT
HERE COMES YOUR KNIGHT IN SHINING...
OH, NO.
BYE, YOU GUYS!
DON'T WAIT UP!
CHIP!
OH, DEAR.
JACK, HOW DO I TURN THIS OFF?
Press the button.
Which one? Which button? Jack...
The button. The button.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU DID THAT.
YEAH, WELL...
SEE?
HE'S HER LOBSTER.
Dance with him.
Mom, I'm hungry.
Dance with your father.
I MAY NOT KNOW ANY OF YOUR FLASH DANCES
BUT I'M NO SLOUCH ON THE DANCE FLOOR.
ALL RIGHT.
OH, JACK.
OH, JUDY.
Oh, Jack.
Judith...
Oh, Judy... Yes... Yes...