MOM, WOULD YOU RELAX?
THAT WAS TEN BLOCKS FROM HERE
AND THE WOMAN WAS WALKING ALONE AT NIGHT.
I WOULD NEVER DO THAT.
MOM, COME ON, STOP WORRYING.
THIS IS A SAFE STREET.
THIS IS A SAFE BUILDING.
THERE'S NOTHING... OH, MY GOD!
OH, WHAT ARE YOU DOING IN HERE?!
OH, GOD, MOM, I GOT TO GO!
I GOT TO GO.
OH, MY GOD.
OKAY.
THAT'S FINE.
YOU JUST READ THE PAPER.
I'M GOING TO GET A POT.
IT'S NOT FOR YOU.
OKAY, THAT'S FINE.
READ "THE FAMILY CIRCUS."
ENJOY THE GENTLE COMEDY.
OH, MY GOD. OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD... OH, GOD... OH... OH...
IT'S OPEN, YOU GUYS.
HI.
HI. HEY, CAN I HELP YOU?
YEAH, I'M LOOKING FOR PHOEBE.
DOES SHE STILL LIVE HERE?
UH, NO, SHE DOESN'T
BUT I CAN GET A MESSAGE TO HER.
GREAT. JUST TELL HER HER HUSBAND STOPPED BY.
HER WHAT?
HEY, HOW... HOW DID YOU DO THAT?
THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE, PHEEBS.
HOW CAN YOU BE MARRIED?
WELL, I'M NOT MARRIED MARRIED.
HE WAS JUST A FRIEND, AND HE'S GAY
AND HE'S FROM CANADA, AND HE JUST NEEDED A GREEN CARD.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU MARRIED DUNCAN.
I MEAN, HOW COULD YOU NOT TELL ME?
WE LIVED TOGETHER.
WE TOLD EACH OTHER EVERYTHING.
I'M SORRY, MONICA, BUT I KNEW IF I TOLD YOU
YOU'D GET REALLY, LIKE, JUDGMENTAL
AND YOU WOULD NOT APPROVE.
OF COURSE I WOULDN'T APPROVE.
I MEAN, YOU WERE TOTALLY IN LOVE
WITH THIS GUY WHO-- HELLO-- WAS GAY.
I MEAN, WHAT THE HELL WERE YOU THINKING?
SEE, AND YOU THOUGHT SHE'D BE JUDGMENTAL.
OKAY, I WASN'T "IN LOVE"
WITH HIM, AND I WAS JUST HELPING OUT A FRIEND.
PLEASE.
WHEN HE LEFT TOWN, YOU STAYED IN YOUR PAJAMAS FOR A MONTH
AND I SAW YOU EAT A CHEESEBURGER.
WELL, DIDN'T YOU?
I MIGHT HAVE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU DIDN'T TELL ME.
OH, COME ON. LIKE YOU TELL ME EVERYTHING?
WHAT HAVE I NOT TOLD YOU?
OH, I DON'T KNOW.
UM, HOW ABOUT THE FACT
THAT THE UNDERWEAR OUT THERE ON THE TELEPHONE POLE IS YOURS
FROM WHEN YOU WERE HAVING SEX WITH FUN BOBBY
OUT ON THE TERRACE.
WHAT?!
WAIT A MINUTE... WHO TOLD YOU?
YOU ARE DEAD MEAT.
I DIDN'T KNOW IT WAS A BIG SECRET.
OH, IT'S NOT BIG, NOT AT ALL.
YOU KNOW, KIND OF ON THE SAME LINES AS, SAY
OH, I DON'T KNOW, HAVING A THIRD NIPPLE!
YOU HAVE A THIRD NIPPLE?
YOU BITCH.
WHIP IT OUT! WHIP IT OUT!
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
COME ON.
THERE'S NOTHING TO SEE.
IT'S JUST A TINY BUMP.
IT'S TOTALLY USELESS.
OH, AS OPPOSED TO YOUR OTHER
MULTIFUNCTIONAL NIPPLES.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU.
YOU TOLD ME IT WAS A NUBBIN.
JOEY, WHAT DID YOU THINK A NUBBIN WAS?
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU SEE SOMETHING.
YOU HEAR A WORD.
I THOUGHT THAT'S WHAT IT WAS.
LET ME SEE IT AGAIN.
YEAH, SHOW IT TO US.
JOEY WAS IN A PORNO MOVIE.
IF I'M GOING DOWN, I'M TAKING EVERYBODY WITH ME.
OH, MY GOD!
A PORNO MOVIE?
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
I WAS YOUNG, AND I JUST WANTED A JOB, OKAY?
BUT, AT THE LAST MINUTE, I COULDN'T GO THROUGH WITH IT
SO THEY LET ME BE THE GUY WHO COMES IN TO FIX THE COPIER
BUT CAN'T, BECAUSE THERE'S PEOPLE HAVING SEX ON IT.
THAT IS WILD!
SO WHAT'S IT SHAPED LIKE?
IS THERE A HAIR ON IT?
WHAT HAPPENS
IF YOU FLICK IT?
SO, UH, DOES IT DO ANYTHING, YOU KNOW, SPECIAL?
WELL, YES, ROSS.
PRESSING MY THIRD NIPPLE OPENS THE DELIVERY ENTRANCE
TO THE MAGICAL LAND OF NARNIA.
YOU KNOW, IN SOME CULTURES, HAVING A THIRD NIPPLE
IS ACTUALLY A SIGN OF VIRILITY.
YOU GET THE BEST HUTS
AND WOMEN DANCE NAKED AROUND YOU.
HUH. ARE ANY OF THESE CULTURES PERCHANCE IN THE TRISTATE AREA?
YOU KNOW, YOU ARE SO AMAZING.
IS THERE ANYTHING YOU DON'T KNOW?
OOH, JULIE'S SO SMART.
JULIE'S SO SPECIAL.
WHAT, DOES SHE GO PUT AN OUTFIT ON AT NIGHT
AND GO OUT AND FIGHT CRIME?
LOOK, HONEY, I WANTED YOU TO HOOK UP WITH ROSS
AS MUCH AS YOU DID, BUT HE'S WITH HER NOW.
YOU'RE JUST GOING TO HAVE TO GET OVER IT.
OH, I'M GOING TO HAVE TO GET OVER IT.
GOD, SEE, I DIDN'T KNOW THAT'S WHAT I HAD TO DO.
I JUST HAVE TO GET OVER IT.
OH! I'M GOING
TO HAVE TO WRITE THAT DOWN ON MY HAND.
WHOA!
FOXY LADY!
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
I'M GOING TO GO MEET DUNCAN.
HE'S SKATING TONIGHT AT THE GARDEN.
HE'S IN THE CAPADES.
THE ICE CAPADES?
NO, NO. THE GRAVEL CAPADES.
YEAH, THE TURNS AREN'T AS FAST, BUT WHEN SNOOPY FALLS-- FUNNY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE DRESSING UP FOR HIM.
YOU'RE SETTING YOURSELF UP ALL OVER AGAIN.
OKAY, NO.
FOR YOUR INFORMATION, I'M GOING TO SEE HIM
SO I CAN PUT ALL THOSE FEELINGS BEHIND ME, OKAY?
AND THE REASON
I'M DRESSED LIKE THIS
IS BECAUSE I THINK IT'S NICE TO LOOK NICE
FOR YOUR GAY HUSBAND.
OH, DARN IT, WE'RE ALL OUT OF MILK.
HEY, CHANDLER
WILL YOU FILL ME UP HERE?
OH, I SEE... I SEE... BECAUSE OF THE THIRD NIPPLE THING.
OKAY, SWEETIE, I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
BYE.
SEE YOU LATER, RACH.
BYE BYE, JULIE.
HEY!
HEY.
HEY, COME ON, CUT IT OUT.
HEY...
WHAT?
CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
SURE.
WHAT?
COME ON, TALK TO ME.
OKAY.
WHAT'S THE LONGEST
YOU'VE BEEN IN A RELATIONSHIP BEFORE...
HA HAVING...?
HAVING HAD SEX?
WHY? WHO'S NOT HAVING...?
ARE YOU AND JULIE NOT.... OR ARE AND...
ARE YOU AND JULIE NOT HAVING SEX?
WELL... TECHNICALLY?
NO.
WOW.
IS IT BECAUSE SHE'S SO COLD IN BED?
OR IS IT BECAUSE SHE'S
LIKE, KIND OF BOSSY?
MAKES IT FEEL LIKE SCHOOL?
NO... NO, SHE'S GREAT
AND IT'S NOT LIKE WE HAVEN'T DONE... ANYTHING.
I MEAN, UH, WE... WE DO PLENTY OF OTHER STUFF...
LOTS OF OTHER STUFF, LIKE...
NO, NO, NO, NO.
DON'T NEED TO KNOW THE DETAILS.
THAT'S OKAY.
IT'S JUST... IT'S... IT'S ME.
YOU KNOW, I'VE ONLY BEEN WITH ONE WOMAN
MY WHOLE LIFE, AND SHE TURNED OUT TO BE A LESBIAN.
UH HUH.
SO NOW, I'VE GOT MYSELF ALL PSYCHED OUT, YOU KNOW
AND IT'S BECOME LIKE THIS... THIS THING, AND I...
YOU MUST JUST THINK I'M WEIRD.
NO. NO, NO, NO, I DON'T THINK IT'S WEIRD.
I THINK... I THINK, UM, IN FACT...
IN FACT, YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK?
WHAT?
I THINK IT'S SEXY.
SEXY?
LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING.
AS A WOMAN...
MM HMM?
... THERE IS NOTHING SEXIER THAN A MAN
WHO DOES NOT WANT TO HAVE SEX.
NO KIDDING?
OH, YEAH. IN FACT, YOU KNOW WHAT I'D DO?
WHAT?
I'D WAIT.
YOU'D WAIT?
YES, ABSOLUTELY.
I WOULD WAIT, AND WAIT.
THEN I'D WAIT
SOME MORE.
REALLY?
OH, YEAH.
I DON'T CARE HOW MUCH SHE TELLS YOU SHE WANTS IT.
I DON'T CARE IF SHE BEGS, SHE PLEADS, SHE TELLS YOU
SHE'S GOING TO HAVE SEX WITH... WITH ANOTHER MAN.
THAT JUST MEANS IT'S WORKING.
WOMEN REALLY WANT THIS?
MM HMM. MORE THAN JEWELRY.
HI.
PHOEBE...
? TA DAH! ?
HEY.
HI.
AH, LOOK AT YOU.
YOU LOOK GREAT.
DO I?
YEAH.
THANK YOU. SO DO YOU.
THANKS.
SPARKLY.
YEAH.
SO... WOW.
THIS IS... THIS IS PRETTY WONDERFUL, HUH?
MR. MAJOR CAPADES GUY.
GOD, I... I REMEMBER
WHEN YOU WERE JUST LIKE KING FRIDAY
INMR. ROGER'S ICE IS NICE.
YEAH, YOU ALWAYS SAID I'D MAKE IT.
YEAH, WELL, YOU KNOW, I'M KIND OF SPOOKY THAT WAY.
GOD, I MISSED YOU.
I'M GOING TO GET CHANGED.
OKAY.
UM... NOW.
WHAT?
PHEEBS?
OH, RIGHT. OKAY.
OLE.
WHAT?
UM... THE MATADOR, SO...
OLE.
SWEET, CAN YOU HOLD THIS FOR A SECOND?
SURE.
THANKS.
UH, JULIE?
YEAH.
SORRY. YOU HAD A PALEONTOLOGIST ON YOUR FACE.
BUT IT'S GONE NOW.
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
GOOD NIGHT, EVERYONE.
GOOD NIGHT.
GOOD BYE.
OH, LISTEN...
I JUST... I WANTED TO THANK YOU FOR, UH...
OUR LITTLE TALK BEFORE.
OH, GOD, NO PROBLEM.
SO YOU'RE GOING TO GO WITH THE WAITING THING?
WELL, I WAS GOING TO
BUT AFTER I TALKED TO YOU, I TALKED TO JOEY.
WHAT... WHAT DID HE SAY?
BASICALLY, HE TOLD ME
TO GET OVER MYSELF AND JUST DO IT.
SO I THOUGHT ABOUT WHAT YOU SAID
AND I THOUGHT ABOUT WHAT HE SAID
AND, WELL, HIS WAY I GET TO HAVE SEX TONIGHT, SO...
OH, GOD.
HMM.
WHAT IS THIS IN MY POCKET?
WHY, IT'S JOEY'S PORNO MOVIE.
HEY.
POP IT IN.
I'M FINE WITH IT.
I MEAN, IF YOU'RE OKAY WATCHING A VIDEO
FILLED WITH TWO NIPPLED PEOPLE.
GREAT.
PEOPLE HAVING SEX-- THAT'S JUST WHAT I NEED TO SEE.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH PEOPLE HAVING SEX?
WELL...
WELL, UM, YOU KNOW
THESE MOVIES ARE OFFENSIVE...
AND, UH, DEGRADING TO WOMEN...
AND FEMALES...
AND, UH...
AND THE LIGHTING'S ALWAYS UNFLATTERING.
AND...
MONICA, HELP ME OUT HERE.
HELL, I WANT TO SEE JOEY!
SO, IS THERE, LIKE, A STORY
OR DO THEY JUST START DOING IT RIGHT...?
OH. NEVER MIND.
OKAY, NOW, WAIT A MINUTE.
THAT IS THE CRAZIEST TYPING TEST
I'VE EVER SEEN.
ALL I SAY IS, SHE BETTER GET THE JOB.
LOOKS TO ME LIKE HE'S THE ONE GETTING
THE JOB.
SHH!
OKAY, HERE I COME. HERE I COME.
SEE, I'M COMING TO FIX THE COPIER.
I CAN'T GET TO THE COPIER.
I'M THINKING, "WHAT DO I DO? WHAT DO I DO?"
SO I JUST WATCH THEM HAVE SEX.
AND THEN I SAY... WAIT, HERE'S MY LINE.
You know, that's bad for the paper tray.
NICE WORK, MY FRIEND.
THANK YOU.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT. YOU SEE ME AGAIN.
HANG ON. THE GUY'S BUTT'S BLOCKING ME.
THERE I AM.
SO, UM... SO WHAT'S UP?
YOU CAME TO SEE ME YESTERDAY.
OH, YEAH, UM...
ALL RIGHT.
I KIND OF NEED A DIVORCE.
O... KAY.
H HOW COME?
UM, ACTUALLY, I'M GETTING MARRIED AGAIN.
WHAT?
OH, GOD, I DON'T KNOW HOW TO TELL YOU THIS.
I'M STRAIGHT.
YEAH, I KNOW. I...
I... I DON'T... I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
HOW CAN YOU BE STRAIGHT?
I MEAN, YOU'RE SO SMART AND FUNNY
AND YOU THROW SUCH GREAT ACADEMY AWARD PARTIES.
I KNOW. I KNOW.
THAT'S WHAT I KEPT TELLING MYSELF.
BUT YOU JUST REACH A POINT WHERE YOU CAN'T
LIVE A LIE ANYMORE.
SO HOW LONG HAVE YOU KNOWN?
WELL, I GUESS ON SOME LEVEL I ALWAYS KNEW I WAS STRAIGHT.
I THOUGHT I WAS SUPPOSED
TO BE SOMETHING ELSE.
YOU KNOW, I'M AN ICE DANCER.
ALL MY FRIENDS ARE GAY.
I WAS JUST TRYING TO FIT IN.
AND, UM...
AND THERE'S ACTUALLY A... A WOMAN?
HER NAME'S DEBORAH.
OH.
WELL, IS... IS SHE THE FIRST THAT YOU'VE BEEN WITH?
WELL, I'VE NEVER TOLD YOU THIS, BUT...
THERE WERE ONE OR TWO TIMES BACK IN COLLEGE
WHEN I'D GET REALLY DRUNK, GO TO A STRAIGHT BAR
AND WAKE UP WITH A WOMAN NEXT TO ME.
BUT, I, I...
I TOLD MYSELF IT WAS THE LIQUOR
AND EVERYONE EXPERIMENTS IN COLLEGE.
SURE.
BUT NOW
I KNOW I DON'T HAVE A CHOICE ABOUT THIS.
I WAS BORN THIS WAY.
I, I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW
YOU'RE MARRIED TO SOMEONE FOR SIX YEARS
AND YOU THINK YOU KNOW HIM
AND THEN ONE DAY HE SAYS, "OH, I'M NOT GAY."
I'M... I'M STILL ME.
WHY COULDN'T YOU JUST HAVE FIGURED THIS OUT
SIX YEARS AGO?
YOU KNOW, IT STILL SMELLS LIKE MONKEY IN THERE?
WELL, THAT SAVES US A CONVERSATION.
WELL, LISTEN, THIS HAS BEEN GREAT
BUT I'M OFFICIALLY WIPED.
ME, TOO. WE SHOULD GET GOING.
NO!
NO, I MEAN... NO.
COME ON, YOU GUYS.
I MEAN...
COME ON. LOOK, IT'S ONLY 11:30.
LET'S JUST TALK.
WE NEVER JUST HANG OUT AND TALK ANYMORE.
RACHEL
THAT'S ALL WE DO.
OKAY, MAYBE THAT'S ALL WE DO.
WHAT ABOUT JULIE?
WELL, YOU HAVE BEEN IN OUR LIVES
FOR NEARLY TWO MONTHS NOW
AND WE DON'T REALLY KNOW YOU.
I MEAN, WHO IS JULIE?
I MEAN
WHAT DO YOU LIKE?
WHAT DON'T YOU LIKE?
WE WANT TO KNOW EVERYTHING.
WELL, THAT COULD TAKE A WHILE.
SO?
I MEAN, WHO HERE DOES NOT HAVE THE TIME
TO GET TO KNOW JULIE?
I GOT THE TIME TO GET TO KNOW JULIE.
I GOT TIME.
UH, RACH?
I KNOW HER PRETTY WELL.
CAN I GO?
THAT'S FINE.
OKAY, JULIE, SO NOW LET'S START WITH YOUR CHILDHOOD.
WHAT WAS THAT LIKE?
WELL, IN A NUTSHELL...
UH, UH, UH, UH.
SO, UM, HAVE YOU TOLD YOUR PARENTS?
NO, BUT IT'LL BE OKAY.
THEY'RE PRETTY COOL.
MY BROTHER'S STRAIGHT, SO...
HERE YOU GO.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I JUST HAVE ONE MORE QUESTION.
UM, IF YOU HAD FIGURED THIS OUT SOONER
AND, UM... I HAD BEEN AROUND
DO YOU THINK THAT
I WOULD HAVE BEEN THE ONE WHO...?
NO, NO. THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
DON'T TELL ME.
I DON'T THINK EITHER ANSWER WOULD MAKE ME FEEL BETTER.
HERE.
I LOVE YOU, PHOEBE.
SO YOUR BROTHER'S STRAIGHT, HUH?
SERIOUSLY.
AND MY SECOND GRADE TEACHER WAS MISS THOMAS.
AND MY FIRST GRADE TEACHER WAS MRS. COBB.
MRS.... MRS. GOB?
NO, COBB.
LIKE COBB SALAD.
HMM. OKAY.
NOW, WHAT EXACTLY IS IN A COBB SALAD?
I'M GOING HOME.
WHY?
THAT JULIE'S A TALKER, HUH?
GOOD NIGHT.
WHEW!
IT'S PRETTY LATE.
YOU'RE PROBABLY NOT STILL PLANNING ON...
OH... NO, NO, I AM.
OH. OH, WELL...
OH, HEY, ARE YOU NERVOUS?
NO.
NO, I, UH...
I HAVE DONE IT BEFORE.
WELL, OKAY, I MEAN...
HOW ARE YOU GOING TO HANDLE IT?
ARE YOU GOING TO TALK ABOUT IT BEFOREHAND?
ARE YOU JUST GOING TO POUNCE?
I, UH... I DON'T KNOW.
I GUESS I'M JUST GOING TO...
SEE... SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
OKAY.
GOOD LUCK.
WHAT, UH...?
WHAT?
WELL, NOTHING.
I MEAN, UM...
IT IS YOUR FIRST TIME WITH HER
AND, YOU KNOW
IF THE FIRST TIME DOESN'T GO WELL
WELL, THEN, THAT'S PRETTY DARN HARD
TO RECOVER FROM.
OKAY, NOW I'M NERVOUS.
WELL, MAYBE YOU SHOULD PUT IT OFF.
NO, I DON'T WANT TO PUT IT OFF.
I...
GOD, I'M JUST...
I SPENT LAST YEAR BEING SO UNBELIEVABLY MISERABLE.
AND NOW, NOW... I'M ACTUALLY HAPPY.
YOU KNOW, I MEAN, REALLY HAPPY.
I JUST, I JUST...
DON'T WANT TO...
I DON'T WANT TO MESS IT UP.
YOU KNOW?
I KNOW.
YEAH.
I'M SORRY.
NO, IT'S...
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
RIGHT.
MAYBE IT DOESN'T HAVE TO BE THIS TOUGH.
MAYBE YOU WERE ON THE RIGHT TRACK
WITH THAT WHOLE, YOU KNOW, SPONTANEOUS THING.
I MEAN, WOMEN REALLY LIKE THAT.
REALLY?
YEAH.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW...
I MEAN, IF IT WERE ME...
YEAH.
I'D WANT YOU TO...
WHAT?
I DON'T KNOW... CATCH ME OFF GUARD
YOU KNOW, WITH, LIKE, A REALLY GOOD KISS.
YOU KNOW, REALLY...
SORT OF, UM, SOFT... AT FIRST.
AND THEN MAYBE, UM...
BRUSH THE HAIR AWAY FROM MY FACE.
YEAH.
AND THEN LOOK
FAR INTO MY EYES...
IN A WAY THAT LET'S ME KNOW SOMETHING...
AMAZING IS ABOUT TO HAPPEN.
UH HUH.
AND THEN, I DON'T KNOW--
THEN YOU'D PULL ME REALLY CLOSE TO YOU
SO THAT, SO THAT I'D BE PRESSED UP
YOU KNOW, RIGHT AGAINST YOU.
AND, UM...
IT WOULD GET KIND OF...
SWEATY...
AND, UH, AND BLURRY...
AND THEN IT'S JUST HAPPENING.
THANKS, RACH.
GOOD NIGHT.
OH...
OH, GOD.
? I'M SINGING IN THE RAIN ?
? JUST SINGING IN THE RAIN ?
? WHAT A GLORIOUS FEELING ?
? I'M HAPPY AGAIN ?
GOOD MORNING.
WELL, SOMEBODY GOT SOME LAST NIGHT.
TWICE.
? I'M READY FOR LOVE ?
? JUST SINGING ?
? SINGING IN THE RAIN. ?