SO, I'LL GET CANDLES
AND MY MOM'S LACE TABLECLOTH.
AND, SINCE IT'S RACHEL'S BIRTHDAY
AND WE WANT  IT TO BE SPECIAL
I THOUGHT I'D POACH A SALMON.
WHAT?
QUESTION: WHY DO WE ALWAYS HAVE TO HAVE PARTIES
WHERE YOU POACH THINGS?
YOU WANT TO BE IN CHARGE OF THE FOOD COMMITTEE?
QUESTION TWO: WHY DO WE ALWAYS HAVE TO HAVE PARTIES WITH COMMITTEES?
YEAH, WHY CAN'T WE JUST GET
SOME PIZZAS AND GET SOME BEERS AND HAVE FUN?
YEAH, I AGREE.
I THINK FANCY PARTIES ARE ONLY FUN
IF YOU'RE FANCY ON THE INSIDE
AND I'M JUST NOT SURE WE ARE.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU GUYS DON'T WANT IT TO BE SPECIAL.
FINE. YOU CAN THROW ANY KIND OF PARTY YOU WANT.
JOEY, THEY'RE NOT REAL.
HUH? WHAT?
I START MILES BENEATH THE SURFACE OF THESE THINGS, OKAY?
THEY'RE FAKE. SEE? HONK, HONK.
WOW, IT'S...
IT'S LIKE PORNO FOR CLOWNS.
I TALKED TO RACHEL'S SISTERS.
NEITHER OF THEM CAN COME.
OKAY. SO I STILL HAVE TO INVITE DYLAN
AND EMMA AND SHANNON COOPER.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
UH, NO SHANNON COOPER.
WHY NOT HER?
BECAUSE SHE, UH...
SHE STEALS STUFF.
OR MAYBE SHE DOESN'T STEAL STUFF AND JOEY JUST SLEPT WITH HER
AND NEVER CALLED HER BACK.
JOEY, THAT IS HORRIBLE.
HEY, I LIKED HER, ALL RIGHT?
MAYBE TOO MUCH.
I DON'T KNOW. I...
GUESS I JUST GOT SCARED.
OH, MY GOD.
I'M SORRY. I DIDN'T KNOW.
I DIDN'T THINK ANYONE WOULD BUY THAT. OKAY.
HI, HONEY. HOW DID IT GO?
OH! IT WAS THE GRADUATION FROM HELL.
YOU KNOW, MY COUSIN WENT TO HELL
ON A FOOTBALL SCHOLARSHIP.
YOU KNOW, I MEAN
THIS IS SUPPOSED TO BE A JOYOUS OCCASION.
MY SISTER'S GRADUATED FROM COLLEGE.
NOBODY THOUGHT SHE WOULD.
IT'S A TRUE TESTAMENT TO WHAT A GIRL FROM LONG ISLAND
WOULD DO FOR A CELICA.
SO WHAT HAPPENED?
MY PARENTS HAPPENED.
ALL THEY HAD TO DO WAS SIT IN THE SAME STADIUM
SMILE PROUDLY AND NOT TALK ABOUT THE DIVORCE
BUT NO O O O.
THEY GOT INTO A HUGE FIGHT
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE COMMENCEMENT ADDRESS.
BISHOP TUTU ACTUALLY HAD TO STOP AND SHUSH THEM.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU KNOW WHAT THE GOOD NEWS IS?
I GET TO SERVE COFFEE FOR THE NEXT EIGHT HOURS.
OKAY, SO I GUESS WE DON'T INVITE HER PARENTS.
WELL, HOW ABOUT JUST HER MOM?
WHY HER MOM?
BECAUSE I ALREADY INVITED HER.
OOH, OOH, DID YOU ASK STACEY ROTH?
OH, CAN'T INVITE HER.
SHE ALSO STEALS.
SO DOES HER ROOMMATE.
OKAY, HERE ARE THE BIRTHDAY CANDLES.
WHERE'S THE BIRTHDAY CAKE?
WE'RE NOT HAVING BIRTHDAY CAKE.
WE'RE HAVING BIRTHDAY FLAN.
EXCUSE ME?
IT'S A TRADITIONAL MEXICAN CUSTARD DESSERT.
OH, THAT'S NICE.
"HAPPY BIRTHDAY, RACHEL.
HERE'S SOME GOO."
DR. GREEN.
OH, MY GOD, IT'S RACHEL'S DAD.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
WHAT, THE FATHER CAN'T DROP BY
TO SEE THE DAUGHTER ON HER BIRTHDAY?
NO, NO. THE FATHER CAN.
BUT, UM...
SINCE I AM THE ROOMMATE
I CAN TELL YOU THAT SHE'S NOT HERE
AND I'LL PASS ALONG THE MESSAGE, OKAY?
SO BYE BYE.
OH! YOU'RE HAVING A PAR TY.
NO, NO, NOT A PARTY.
JUST A SURPRISE GATHERING OF SOME PEOPLE RACHEL KNOWS.
THIS IS PHOEBE AND CHANDLER AND JOEY.
I'LL NEVER REMEMBER ALL OF THAT.
SO, UH... WHAT'S THE DEAL?
RACHEL COMES HOME
PEOPLE POP OUT AND YELL STUFF?
IS THAT IT?
THIS ISN'T YOUR FIRST SURPRISE PARTY, IS IT, SIR?
HI, MONICA.
CHINESE MENU GUY.
FORGOT THE MENUS.
SO, BASICALLY, JUST A CHINESE GUY.
UH, HEY, DR. GREEN, WHY DON'T YOU COME WITH ME.
WE'LL PUT YOUR JACKET ON RACHEL'S BED.
ALL RIGHT.
THAT SOUNDS LIKE A TWO PERSON JOB.
WELL, MY GOODNESS, WHAT WAS THAT?
SANDRA, I AM SO SORRY.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE RACHEL
AND WE JUST WEREN'T READY FOR YOU YET.
YOU THOUGHT I WAS RACHEL?
YES, BECAUSE YOU LOOK SO YOUNG.
AND BECAUSE YOU'RE BOTH, YOU KNOW, WHITE WOMEN.
OH, I MISSED YOU KIDS.
WELL, SHOULD I PUT MY COAT IN THE BEDROOM?
NO!
NO. I'LL TAKE THAT FOR YOU.
OH, WELL, THANK YOU.
SUCH A GENTLEMAN.
THANK YOU.
OH...
IT ALL LOOKS SO NICE.
SO FESTIVE, ALL THE BALLOONS.
OH, THE FUNNIEST THING HAPPENED TO ME ON THE WAY HERE.
I WAS DRI...
THAT'S GREAT.
I CAN'T WAIT
TO HEAR THE REST OF IT
BUT I REALLY HAVE TO GO TO THE BATHROOM, SO...
HEY, COME WITH ME.
WHAT?
YEAH, YEAH, IT'LL BE LIKE WE'RE GAL PALS
LIKE AT A RESTAURANT  OH, IT'LL BE FUN.
COME ON, COME ON.
OH, MY GOD, OH, MY GOD, OH, MY GOD.
OKAY, THINK.
THINK.
WHAT WOULD JACK AND CHRISSY DO?
OKAY, NOW THAT YOUR COAT
IS SAFELY IN THE BED...
OKAY, WE CAN COME BACK OUT IN THE LIVING ROOM.
SO, JOEY AND CHANDLER
IT'S TIME THAT YOU TAKE DR. GREEN OVER TO YOUR PLACE.
UH, YES. ABSOLUTELY.
UM...
WHY, AGAIN?
BECAUSE THAT'S WHERE THE PARTY IS, YOU GOON.
SEE, THIS IS JUST THE STAGING AREA.
IT'S THE STAGING AREA.
YEAH, THIS MORE THAN ANYTHING ELSE
IS THE STAGING AREA.
THIS IS CLEARLY IN THE WRONG APARTMENT.
ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS ARE OFF TO PARTY NUMBER ONE.
AND YOU... OOH, YOU
ARE OFF TO PARTY NUMBER TWO.
ALL RIGHT, FELLAS, LET'S KEEP IT MOVING.
LET'S KEEP IT MOVING.
CHANDLER, COULD YOU
AT LEAST SEND SOME WOMEN TO MY PARTY?
OKAY, THAT'S ROSS.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, THEY'RE COMING. SHH!
OH... THANK YOU FOR SUCH A WONDERFUL DINNER.
THANKS FOR BEING BORN.
OH... THANK YOU FOR MY BEAUTIFUL EARRINGS.
THEY'RE PERFECT.
OH...
I LOVE YOU.
OH... NOW, YOU CAN EXCHANGE THEM
IF YOU WANT, OKAY?
NOW I LOVE YOU EVEN MORE.
SURPRISE!
OH, MY GOSH!
WOW!
MONICA...
OH, MY GOD!
MOM!
THIS IS SO GREAT!
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, SWEETIE.
WOW, YOU...
YOU!
I HAD NO IDEA.
REALLY?
NO, I KNEW.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, EVERYBODY, THERE'S FOOD AND DRINKS ON THE TABLE.
GO ACROSS THE HALL.
WHAT?
RIGHT NOW JOEY AND CHANDLER'S.
WHY? JUST GO.
SURPRISE!
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, SWEET PEA.
DADDY!
BOTH OF THEM ARE HERE?!
BOTH OF THEM?! BOTH OF THEM ARE HERE?!
WELL, WE COULD COUNT AGAIN.
OH, GOD. I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS IS HAPPENING.
YOU KNOW WHAT? THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
THIS IS YOUR BIRTHDAY, THIS IS YOUR PARTY.
I SAY WE JUST PUT THEM ALL TOGETHER
AND IF THEY CAN'T DEAL WITH IT, WHO CARES?
I DO!
THAT'S WHO.
LOOK, ARE YOU GOING TO BE OKAY?
WELL, I HAVE TO BE.
I DON'T REALLY HAVE A CHOICE.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW, I COULD LOOK AT THE BRIGHT SIDE.
I GET TWO BIRTHDAY PARTIES AND TWO BIRTHDAY CAKES.
WELL, ACTUALLY...
JUST ONE BIRTHDAY FLAN.
WHAT?
IT'S A TRADITIONAL MEXICAN CUSTARD DESSERT.
LOOK, TALK TO MONICA.
SHE'S ON THE FOOD COMMITTEE.
I CAN'T...
JOE! JOE!
HEY, SOME GIRL JUST WALKED UP TO ME
AND SAID, "I WANT YOU, DENNIS"
AND STUCK HER TONGUE DOWN MY THROAT.
I LOVE THIS PARTY.
NICE!
QUICK VOLLEYBALL QUESTION.
VOLLEYBALL.
YEAH, WE SET UP A COURT IN YOUR ROOM.
UH, YOU DIDN'T REALLY LIKE THAT GRAY LAMP, DID YOU?
JOEY, A WOMAN JUST STUCK HER TONGUE DOWN MY THROAT.
I'M NOT EVENS LISTENING TO YOU.
DENNIS!
OKAY, THAT'S ME.
LISTEN, HONEY, CAN YOU KEEP DAD OCCUPIED?
I'M GOING TO GO TALK TO MOM FOR A WHILE.
OKAY. DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEAS FOR ANY OPENERS?
UH, LET'S JUST STAY CLEAR
OF "I'M THE GUY THAT'S DOING YOUR DAUGHTER"
AND YOU SHOULD BE OKAY.
RIGHT.
OKAY, PEOPLE, I WANT YOU TO TAKE A PIECE OF PAPER
HERE YOU GO
AND WRITE DOWN YOUR MOST EMBARRASSING MEMORY
AND I DO ASK THAT WHEN YOU'RE NOT USING THE MARKERS
YOU PUT THE CAPS BACK ON THEM BECAUSE THEY WILL DRY OUT.
HI, DR. GREEN.
SO... HOW'S EVERYTHING
IN THE, UH... VASCULAR SURGERY...
GAME?
IT'S NOT A GAME, ROSS.
A WOMAN DIED ON MY TABLE TODAY.
I'M SORRY.
SEE, THAT'S THE GOOD THING ABOUT MY JOB.
ALL THE DINOSAURS ON MY TABLE
ARE ALREADY DEAD.
LISTEN, YOU GUYS
I DON'T MEAN TO BE A PAIN ABOUT THIS
BUT I'VE NOTICED THAT SOME OF YOU
ARE JUST PLACING THEM ON.
YOU WANT TO PUSH THE CAPS...
UNTIL YOU HEAR THEM CLICK.
GUNTHER?
WHERE YOU GOING?
I WAS SORT OF THINKING ABOUT MAYBE...
NO! NO, YOU CAN'T GO!
NO, THIS IS FUN.
COME ON. WE'RE JUST GETTING STARTED.
HERE. HERE'S YOUR MARKER.
LISTEN, IF YOU WANT TO GO, JUST GO.
NO. SHE'LL YELL AT ME AGAIN.
ALL RIGHT.
I CAN GET YOU OUT.
WHAT?
SHH.
IN A MINUTE, I'M GOING TO CREATE A DIVERSION.
WHEN I DO, WALK QUICKLY TO THE DOOR
AND DON'T LOOK BACK.
I THINK I NEED A DRINK.
I'LL GET IT FOR YOU.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
SCOTCH.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL BE BACK IN TEN SECONDS
WITH YOUR SCOTCH ON THE ROCKS IN A GLASS.
NEAT.
COOL.
NO, NO, NO. NO, NO, NO.
"NEAT," AS IN "NO ROCKS."
I KNOW.
OH, HELLO, ROSS.
NOW, WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
HI.
I HAVE BEEN IN THE BATHROOM.
STAY CLEAR OF THE SALMON MOUSSE.
OH... SCOTCH, NEAT.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S RACHEL'S FATHER'S DRINK.
WHOA. MINE, TOO.
ISN'T THAT NEAT?
SCOTCH NEAT.
WOULD YOU EXCUSE ME?
HEY EY. HEY.
WHERE YOU SNEAKING OFF TO, MISTER?
I'M GETTING MY CIGARETTES OUT OF MY JACKET.
NO, NO.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, "NO?"
NO. UM, SEE, BECAUSE... THAT'S THE STAGING AREA.
YOU GO IN THERE, IT'LL RUIN
THE WHOLE ILLUSION OF THE PARTY.
YEAH.
I THINK YOU TAKE YOUR SCOTCH BACK IN THERE
AND I WILL GET YOUR CIGARETTES FOR YOU, SIR.
GET MY GLASSES, TOO.
ALL RIGHTY ROO.
WHAT A GREAT MOMENT TO SAY THAT FOR THE FIRST TIME.
OKAY, AND THE FIRST PERSON'S
MOST EMBARRASS ING MEMORY IS:
"MONICA, YOUR PARTY SUCKS."
ALL RIGHT. VERY FUNNY.
OH, NO! OOH, OOH.
DID SOMEONE FORGET TO USE A COASTER?
WHAT?!
I DON'T SEE ANYTHING.
GREAT! I'M SEEING WATER RINGS AGAIN.
ROSS... WHOSE GLASSES ARE THOSE?
MINE.
YOU WEAR BIFOCALS?
MM HMM.
I HAVE A CONDITION...
APPARENTLY
THAT I REQUIRE
TWO DIFFERENT SETS OF FOCALS.
DO YOU KNOW MY HUSBAND HAS GLASSES
JUST LIKE THAT?
WELL, THOSE ARE VERY POPULAR FRAMES.
NEIL SEDAKA WEARS THEM.
I HEAR YOU CAN GET PEOPLE OUT OF HERE.
RACHEL?
YEAH?
YOU DIDN'T TELL ME YOUR BOYFRIEND SMOKES.
YEAH, LIKE A CHIMNEY.
OH, BIG SMOKER.
BIG, BIG SMOKER.
IN FACT, I'M GOING TO GO OUT INTO THE HALLWAY
AND FIRE UP THIS BAD BOY.
ARE YOU WEARING MY GLASSES?
YES.
I WAS JUST WARMING UP THE EARPIECES FOR YOU.
THANK YOU.
IS THAT ONE OF MY CIGARETTES?
YEAH.
YES, IT IS.
I WAS JUST MOISTENING THE TIP.
OKAY, SHE'S TAKING THE TRASH OUT
SO I CAN GET YOU OUT OF HERE
BUT IT HAS TO BE NOW.
SHE'LL BE BACK ANY MINUTE.
WHAT ABOUT MY FRIEND VICTOR?
NOPE. ONLY THE THREE OF YOU.
ANY MORE THAN THAT, SHE'LL GET SUSPICIOUS.
LET ME JUST GET MY COAT.
THERE ISN'T TIME.
YOU MUST LEAVE EVERYTHING.
THEY'LL TAKE CARE OF YOU NEXT DOOR.
IS IT TRUE THEY HAVE BEER?
EVERYTHING YOU'VE HEARD IS TRUE.
COULD YOU GUYS
PLEASE TRY TO KEEP IT DOWN?
WE'RE TRYING TO START A BOGGLE TOURNAMENT.
JOE, IF THESE PEOPLE FIND OUT
THEY'RE PLAYING SPELLING GAMES OVER THERE
THERE'LL BE NOBODY LEFT AT OUR PARTY.
YOU!
AND YOU!
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
AT MY PARTY!
AND GUNTHER!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
UM...
OKAY, WELCOME TO THE FUN...
PHOEBE.
ALL RIGHT, I'M SORRY
BUT THESE PEOPLE NEEDED ME.
THEY WORK HARD ALL WEEK.
IT'S SATURDAY NIGHT.
THEY DESERVE TO HAVE A LITTLE FUN. GO!
YOU KNOW, MY PARTY IS FUN.
MAYBE IT'S A LITTLE QUIETER, LESS OBVIOUS SORT OF FUN
BUT YOU KNOW, IF PEOPLE WOULD JUST GIVE IT A CHANCE, IT'S...
YOU WANT ME TO SEE A THERAPIST?
SWEETHEART, YOU OBVIOUSLY HAVE A PROBLEM.
YOU'VE CHOSEN A BOYFRIEND EXACTLY LIKE YOUR FATHER.
OKAY, MOM. YOU KNOW WHAT? FINE.
I'LL MAKE AN APPOINTMENT
OKAY, BUT, YOU KNOW WHAT? RIGHT NOW, I GOT TO GO...
I GOT TO GO DO A THING.
DID YOU KNOW YOUR MOTHER SPENT
$1,200 ON BONSAI TREES?
I FELT LIKE GULLIVER AROUND THAT PLACE.
OH, DADDY, I REALLY WANT TO HEAR MORE ABOUT THIS
I REALLY DO, BUT I JUST HAVE TO...
I JUST HAVE TO DO SOME... SOME STUFF.
YOU WORK AND YOU WORK AND YOU WORK AT A MARRIAGE
BUT ALL HE CARES ABOUT IS HIS STUPID BOAT.
YOU WORK AND YOU WORK AND YOU WORK ON A BOAT...
HE ALWAYS RIDICULED MY POTTERY CLASSES...
AND YOU SAND IT AND YOU VARNISH IT...
BUT WHEN ALL IS SAID AND DONE
HE STILL DRINKS OUT OF THE MUGS.
ONE NIGHT, WITH HER YOGA
AND HERBRIDGES OF MADISON COUNTY...
THE SCOTCH, THE CIGARETTES...
THE BONSAIS AND THE CHIHUAHUA...
I MAY HAVE ONLY BEEN IN THERAPY
FOR THREE WEEKS NOW, DEAR, BUT...
WHAT THE HELL DOES SHE WANT
WITH HALF A BOAT?
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
YOU CAN BE SHIRTS AND I'LL BE SKINS.
I'LL BE SKINS!
HEY.
HOW YOU HOLDING UP, THERE, TIGER?
OH.
SORRY. WHEN MY PAREN TS WERE GETTING DIVORCED
I GOT A LOT OF "TIGERS."
GOT A LOT OF "CHAMPS ," "CHIEFS," "SPORTS."
I EVEN GOT A "GOVERNOR."
THIS IS IT, ISN'T IT?
I MEAN, THIS IS WHAT
MY LIFE'S GOING TO BE LIKE.
MY MOM THERE, MY DAD THERE.
THANKSGIVING, CHRISTMAS.
SHE GETS THE HOUSE
HE'S IN SOME CONDO
MY SISTER'S GOING TO DECORATE WITH WICKER.
OH, CHANDLER, HOW DID YOU GET THROUGH THIS?
WELL, I RELIED
ON A CAREFULLY REGIMENTED PROGRAM OF DENIAL...
AND WETTING THE BED.
YOU KNOW, I JUST... IT'S SO WEIRD.
I WAS IN THERE JUST LISTENING TO THEM
BITCH ABOUT EACH OTHER.
ALL I KEPT THINKING ABOUT WAS THE FOURTH OF JULY.
BECAUSE IT REMINDED YOU OF THE WAY
OUR FOREFATHERS USED TO BITCH AT EACH OTHER?
IT'S JUST THIS THING.
EVERY YEAR, WE WOULD GO OUT ON MY DAD'S BOAT
AND WATCH THE FIREWORKS.
MOM ALWAYS HATED IT BECAUSE THE OCEAN AIR
MADE HER HAIR ALL BIG
MY SISTER, JILL, WOULD BE THROWING UP OVER THE SIDE
AND MY DAD WOULD BE UPSET BECAUSE NOBODY WAS HELPING
AND THEN WHEN WE DID HELP
HE WOULD SCREAM AT US FOR DOING IT WRONG...
BUT THEN, WHEN THE FIREWORKS STARTED
EVERYBODY JUST SHUT UP.
YOU KNOW? AND IT'D GET REALLY COLD
AND WE WOULD ALL JUST SORT OF SMUSH UNDER THIS ONE BLANKET...
IT NEVER OCCURRED TO ANYBODY TO BRING ANOTHER ONE.
AND NOW, IT'S...
YEAH, I I KNOW.
OKAY, THANKS FOR COMING.
I HOPE YOU GUYS HAD FUN.
ALL RIGHT, MONICA, DEAR, I'M GOING TO HIT THE ROAD.
NOW, I'VE LEFT MY TEN VERBS ON THE TABLE.
YOU BE SURE AND SEND ME THAT FINISHED POEM.
OKAY. WILL DO. I'M SO GLAD YOU CAME.
I THINK I SAW RACHEL OUT IN THE HALL?
OKAY, LET ME GO CHECK.
ALL RIGHT.
YOUR MOM WANTS TO SAY GOOD BYE.
OH, OKAY.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, SWEETIE.
OKAY.
UH... YOU DRIVE SAFE.
ROSS, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'M GETTING READY
FOR THE WATER... SKIING.
BIG HUG. ONE MORE BIG HUG. COME ON.
ALL RIGHT, DARLING.
HOW ARE YOU?
DR. GREEN, WHERE YOU GOING?
TO GET MY COAT.
NO, NO, NO! I'LL GET THAT!
ALL RIGHT! ALL RIGHT! I CAN GET MY OWN COAT!
SORRY. WE'RE ON A MAJOR FLAN HIGH.
OH, NO.
NO, YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO BE HERE...
BECAUSE THIS IS THE STAGING AREA.
IT'S ALL WRONG. YOU SHOULD LEAVE.
YOU KNOW, JUST...
GET OUT.
OR PERHAPS YOU'D LIKE A CREME DE MENTHE.
I HAVE TO BE HEADING
TOWARD MY CHATEAU. THANK YOU.
THEN I GUESS WE'RE GOING
BACK INTO THE HALLWAY.
THANKS FOR COMING, MRS. GREEN.
OKAY.
YOU TAKE CARE.
OH, YOU KIDS!
WELL...
THIS IS THE BEST PARTY I'VE BEEN TO IN YEARS.
THANK YOU!
OKAY, EVERYBODY, IT'S TIME FOR FLAN.
YEP. GET READY FOR THE GELATINOUS FUN.
KIND OF LOOKS LIKE THAT STUFF YOU GET
WHEN YOU GET A BAD INFECTION.
OKAY, THAT'S ENOUGH.
OKAY, RACHEL, MAKE A SPECIAL FLAN WISH.
OKAY, I'VE GOT ONE.
HEADS UP!
WOW! THOSE THINGS ALMOST NEVER COME TRUE.