CHANDLER, MON, THERE'S ONLY ONE BANANA NUT MUFFIN LEFT.
I ORDERED MINE FIRST.
YEAH, BUT I'M SO MUCH FASTER.
GIVE IT TO ME.
NO.
GIVE IT TO ME!
OKAY, YOU CAN HAVE IT.
THERE YOU GO.
ENJOY YOUR COFFEE.
THAT WAS THERE WHEN I GOT HERE.
HEY, YOU GUYS, YOU WILL NEVER GUESS
WHO'S COMING TO NEW YORK.
QUICK, PHOEBE, TELL US BEFORE HE CAN SWALLOW.
RYAN, THAT GUY I WENT OUT WITH
WHO'S IN THE NAVY.
YOU WENT OUT WITH A GUY IN THE NAVY?
I MET HIM WHEN I WAS PLAYING GUITAR
IN WASHINGTON SQUARE PARK.
RYAN THREW IN SALTWATER TAFFY
BECAUSE HE DIDN'T HAVE ANY CHANGE.
IS THAT WHEN YOU WROTE "SALTWATER TAFFY MAN"?
NO.
NO. HE IS MY SUBMARINE GUY.
HE RESURFACES, LIKE, EVERY COUPLE YEARS
AND WE HAVE THE MOST AMAZING THREE DAYS TOGETHER.
ONLY, THIS TIME, HE'S COMING FOR TWO WEEKS.
TWO WHOLE WEEKS-- WHICH MEANS YAY!
THIS GUY GOES DOWN FOR, LIKE, TWO YEARS AT A TIME?
THAT WILL TEACH YOU TO LICK MY MUFFIN.
HI.
OH, NO. WHAT HAPPENED?
I JUST SPOKE TO CAROL.
BEN'S GOT THE CHICKEN POX.
YOU'RE KIDDING. OH, NO.
SO IF YOU HAVEN'T ALREADY HAD IT
CHANCES ARE YOU'RE GOING TO GET IT.
I'VE HAD IT. I'VE HAD IT.
HAD IT. HAD IT.
I'VE NEVER HAD IT. I FEEL SO LEFT OUT.
HONEY, YOU MADE THE BED AGAIN.
I TOLD YOU, YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO THAT.
THIS ISN'T CAMP.
OH. THEN I GUESS THE PANTY RAID LAST NIGHT
WAS TOTALLY UNCALLED FOR.
OKAY.
I AM GOING TO TAKE A SHOWER
AND TODAY I WILL BE SINGING
JIM CROCE'S "LEROY BROWN."
MONICA?
HEY, MON, I HAVE A QUESTION.
IS LEROY
THE "BADDEST" MAN IN THE WHOLE DAMN TOWN
OR THE "FATTEST" MAN IN THE WHOLE DAMN TOWN?
THE BADDEST.
OTHERWISE THE SONG WOULD BE "FAT, FAT LEROY BROWN."
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'M JUST WAITING FOR YOU, SWEETIE.
ARE YOU REMAKING THE BED?
I'M SORRY, I'M SORRY.
THE WAY YOU DID IT, IT WAS JUST FINE.
THEN YOU'RE REDOING IT BECAUSE...?
IF I TELL YOU, YOU'LL THINK I'M CRAZY.
YOU'RE PRETTY MUCH RUNNING THAT RISK EITHER WAY.
OKAY, YOU SEE...
THE DUVET TAG SHOULDN'T BE AT THE TOP LEFT CORNER.
IT SHOULD BE AT THE BOTTOM RIGHT CORNER.
WELL, THAT'S NOT SO CRAZY.
I'M JUST EASING YOU IN.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU SEE THESE LITTLE FLOWER BLOSSOMS?
THEY SHOULD BE FACING UP, NOT DOWN
BECAUSE THE HEAD OF THE BED IS WHERE THE SUN WOULD BE.
YOU DON'T LOVE ME ANYMORE, DO YOU?
ACTUALLY, IF IT'S POSSIBLE, I LOVE YOU MORE.
REALLY?
MM HMM.
WOW.
THEN COME ON, I WANT TO SHOW YOU
HOW TO FOLD THE TOILET PAPER INTO A POINT.
HEY, LOOK, JOEY, I'M JUST SAYING
IF YOU NEED SOMETHING TO HOLD YOU OVER
I CAN GET YOU A JOB RIGHT HERE AS AN ENTRY LEVEL PROCESSOR.
BUT DON'T YOU NEED EXPERIENCE FOR A JOB LIKE THAT?
IT'S NOT THAT HARD TO LEARN, AND AS FOR PEOPLE REALIZING
THAT YOU HAVE NO IDEA WHAT YOU'RE DOING
HEY, YOU'RE AN ACTOR.
ACT LIKE A PROCESSOR, PEOPLE WILL THINK
YOU'RE A PROCESSOR.
HEY, CHANDLER, HERE'S
THIS MORNING'S PROJECTIONS.
THANKS. SCOTT ALEXANDER, JOEY TRIBBIANI.
JOEY IS A, UH, FELLOW PROCESSOR.
NO KIDDING?
OH, YEAH.
I PROCESS.
PEOPLE WANT THE PROCESSING, I'M THE ONE THEY CALL.
WHERE DO YOU WORK?
UH... RIGHT NOW, I'M IN BETWEEN THINGS.
YOU KNOW HOW IT IS.
ONE DAY, YOU'RE PROCESSING.
THE NEXT DAY, YOU'RE...
NOT SO MUCH PROCESSING ANYMORE.
I WAS JUST TELLING JOEY
ABOUT THE OPENING IN FLEISCHMAN'S GROUP.
FLEISCHMAN'S GROUP?
WHATEVER YOU DO, DON'T TOUCH HIS SANDWICHES.
ARE ALL YOU PROCESSORS DORKS?
UCH, THIS LIPSTICK LOOKS JUST GREAT ON YOU.
YOU LOOK FABULOUS, HONEY, YOU REALLY DO.
ARE YOU SURE? REALLY?
SEE? YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL.
FOR GOD SAKES, DIM THE LIGHTS.
I... I... I... I'M HIDEOUS.
IT'S GOING TO BE OKAY.
RYAN'S BEEN UNDERWATER.
HE'S JUST GOING TO BE SO GLAD
THAT YOU DON'T HAVE BARNACLES ON YOUR BUTT.
COME IN.
HEY, BABY, I'M BA...
HEY, RYAN, WHAT'S UP?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
NO, YOU HAVE TO STAY BACK.
I... I HAVE THE POX.
CHICKEN OR SMALL?
CHICKEN, WHICH IS SO IRONIC, CONSIDERING I'M A VEGETARIAN.
WHY AREN'T YOU AT HOME IN BED?
BECAUSE MY GRANDMOTHER'S NEVER HAD CHICKEN POX.
PLEASE, PLEASE TELL ME YOU HAVE
BECAUSE, OH, MY GOD, I FORGOT HOW CUTE YOU ARE.
I'M SORRY. I NEVER HAD THEM.
OH! OH!
IF I HAD ONE WISH
IT WOULD BE TO BUILD A TIME MACHINE
GO BACK TO WHEN I WAS SEVEN
WHEN JIMMY HAUSER HAD THE CHICKEN POX.
I WOULD GRAB THAT KID AND RUB HIM ALL OVER MY FACE.
OR YOU COULD JUST WISH
THAT I DIDN'T HAVE THEM NOW.
CAN I PLEASE SEE YOUR FACE?
NO. YOU DON'T WANT TO SEE A FACE COVERED WITH POX.
YOUR FACE COULD BE COVERED WITH LOX
I WOULDN'T CARE.
AND YOU HATE FISH.
THAT'S SO SWEET.
ALL RIGHT, OKAY, YOU CAN SEE.
THIS... IS ME.
OH, SORRY.
OH, I AM SCARY.
NO, THE LIGHTNING.
IT WAS AN UNFORTUNATE COINCIDENCE.
YOU LOOK LOVELY.
LOVELY.
I HATE THIS.
I HAD THE MOST AMAZING TWO WEEKS PLANNED FOR US.
AND ALMOST EVERYTHING I HAD IN MIND
WE HAD TO BE A LOT CLOSER THAN THIS.
PHOEBE, I HAVE SPENT THE LAST EIGHT MONTHS
IN A STEEL TUBE WITH MEN...
THINKING ABOUT THIS MOMENT.
I AM NOT GOING TO LET A BUNCH OF ITCHY SPOTS STAND BETWEEN US.
OKAY, THIS IS THE MOST ROMANTIC DISEASE
I'VE EVER HAD.
HEY.
HEY. HOW'S THE FIRST DAY GOING?
PRETTY GOOD. IT'S LIKE YOU SAID--
IT'S MOSTLY JUST PUTTING NUMBERS FROM ONE COLUMN
INTO ANOTHER COLUMN.
WELL, THERE YOU GO.
HEY, EVERYBODY IS SO NICE.
I HAD A GOOD TALK WITH THAT LADY WITH THE RED HAIR, JEANNIE.
JEANNIE, THE HEAD OF EAST COAST OPERATIONS JEANNIE?
YEAH. TURNS OUT OUR KIDS GO TO THE SAME SCHOOL.
SMALL WORLD, HUH?
WEIRD WORLD.
YOUR KIDS?
I FIGURE MY CHARACTER HAS KIDS.
YOU KNOW, THERE ISN'T A PART OF THAT SENTENCE
THAT I DON'T NEED EXPLAINED.
WELL, SEE, WHEN YOU'RE ACTING
YOU NEED TO THINK ABOUT STUFF LIKE THAT.
MY CHARACTER-- JOSEPH THE PROCESSING GUY--
HAS TWO LITTLE GIRLS
ASHLEY AND BRITTANY.
ASHLEY COPIES EVERYTHING BRITTANY DOES.
OH, WELL, INVISIBLE KIDS CAN BE THAT WAY SOMETIMES.
YOU KNOW, JOSEPH AND HIS WIFE, KAREN
ARE THINKING OF HAVING A THIRD KID.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
JUST DID.
REALLY? WOW.
THAT'S SOME PRETTY POWERFUL IMAGINARY SPERM
YOU MUST HAVE THERE.
YOU KNOW WHAT MAKES THE ITCHING EVEN WORSE?
THAT YOU DON'T STOP TALKING ABOUT IT?
FINE.
LET'S JUST PLAY, OKAY?
GOOD. OKAY.
HERE WE GO, DOUBLE SIXES.
HERE WE GO.
COME TO MAMA.
GETTING READY TO ROLL THE DICE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
ARE YOU SCRATCHING?
NO. THIS IS WHAT I DO FOR LUCK, OKAY?
YOU'RE SCRATCHING.
GIVE ME THE DICE.
NO!
GIVE ME THE DICE!
NO! HERE! THERE!
OOH! DOUBLE SIXES!
WE CAN'T SCRATCH.
YOU KNOW WE CAN'T.
WE'LL SCAR.
I CAN'T STOP THINKING ABOUT IT.
IT'S JUST SO HARD.
I JUST WANT TO GRAB ALL THESE HOUSES
AND RUB THEM ALL OVER MY BODY.
NO!
YES.
COME ON!
YOU KNOW YOU WANT IT.
YOU KNOW YOU WANT IT, TOO.
LET'S JUST BE BAD.
IT'LL FEEL SO GOOD.
OH, COME ON.
COME ON.
OH, GOD, HELP ME.
UH HUH.
GOOD, HUH?
OH, YEAH.
NOW DO ME.
DO MY BACK.
OH, COME ON, HARDER.
THERE YOU GO.
DON'T MOVE.
WHY? WHY?
OH! OH!
STOP THAT! STOP THAT RIGHT NOW!
YOU KNOW, I MIGHT OF EXPECTED THIS OF YOU, PHOEBE
BUT, RYAN, YOU'RE A MILITARY MAN.
SHE MADE ME DO IT.
THAT'S A NICE COLOR ON YOU.
YEAH? WELL, IT COMES IN PINK AND BLOTCHY, BABY.
I HOPE YOU GET A WEENIE POCK.
YOU AND MILTON HAVE TO JOIN US ON THE BOAT.
KAREN'LL PACK A LUNCH.
YOU'LL BRING THE KIDS.
WE'LL MAKE A DAY OF IT.
WE'LL HAVE TO SET THAT UP.
OH, I BETTER GET BACK.
HOPE THE BABY FEELS BETTER.
OH, THANKS. THANKS.
BYE BYE, JEANNIE.
BYE BYE, JOSEPH.
WHAT A PHONY.
WELL, I'M SURE YOU'LL TEACH HER A LESSON
WHEN SHE STEPS OFF THE DOCK ONTO NOTHING.
HEY, MR. DOUGLAS.
LISTEN, BING, I RECEIVED YOUR MEMO.
SO WE'RE NOT GOING TO SEE THE SYSTEMS REPORT
UNTIL NEXT FRIDAY?
MY GROUP WANT TO SPEND
THE HOLIDAY WEEKEND WITH THEIR FAMILIES.
I HAVE A FAMILY.
I'M GOING TO BE HERE.
YEAH, BING, WHAT'S THAT ABOUT?
IT'S ABOUT CUTTING MY PEOPLE A LITTLE SLACK
YOU KNOW, FOR MORALE.
LOOK, IF YOU WANT TO SEE SOME ROUGH NUMBERS
I CAN GET THEM TO YOU BY WEDNESDAY.
"ROUGH NUMBERS"?
THIS COMPANY WAS NOT BUILT ON ROUGH NUMBERS.
AM I RIGHT, MR. DOUGLAS?
HAVE THE FINAL NUMBERS ON MY DESK BY TUESDAY.
IF YOU SAY SO, SIR.
JOSEPH'S GOOD, ISN'T HE?
WELL, I'M GOING TO KILL YOU.
HEY, HEY.
I JUST FIGURED JOSEPH'S THE KIND OF GUY
WHO LIKES TO MIX IT UP
YOU KNOW, GET IN THERE, RUFFLE SOME FEATHERS.
WHY?
LOOK, I'M SORRY, BUT THAT'S WHAT JOSEPH DOES.
OKAY?
IF YOU TRY TO PULL SOMETHING
HE'LL CALL YOU ON IT.
"WHAT ARE YOU TRYING TO PULL?"
HE'LL SAY.
OOH, DUCT TAPE.
WAS I SUPPOSED TO BRING SOMETHING, TOO?
THIS IS FOR THE SCRATCHY TWINS OUT THERE.
I TAPED OVEN MITTS TO THEIR HANDS.
YOU'RE STRICT.
YEAH, WELL, IT'S FOR THEIR OWN GOOD.
YOU KNOW, I LIKE
THE WAY YOU HAVE EFFICIENTLY FOLDED THIS TAB UNDER.
SEE, IN A TAPE EMERGENCY
YOU COULD SHAVE VALUABLE SECONDS OFF YOUR TIME.
EXACTLY.
OH.
I LOVE THAT I CAN BE TOTALLY NEUROTIC AROUND YOU NOW.
TELL ME THE TRUTH.
DON'T YOU LIKE IT BETTER
NOW THAT EVERYTHING ON YOUR DESK IS PERPENDICULAR?
IT IT'S NOT A RIGHT ANGLE, IT IS A WRONG ANGLE.
VERY GOOD.
THANK YOU.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
TOMORROW, I'M GOING TO DO YOUR CLOCKS.
YOU'RE GOING TO DO WHAT TO MY CLOCKS?
I'M GOING TO SET THEM TO MY TIME.
WELL, I'M CONFUSED.
I THOUGHT WE SHARED TIME.
NO, NO.
SEE, IN MY BEDROOM, I SET MY CLOCK SIX MINUTES FAST.
YOU WANT TO KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE IT'S IN A SLIGHTLY DIFFERENT TIME ZONE
THAN THE KITCHEN?
YOU KNOW WHAT? FORGET IT.
NO, COME ON, TELL ME.
NO, BECAUSE YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
YOU DON'T HAVE ANY
OF THESE CUTE LITTLE OBSESSIVE THINGS.
NO, THAT'S NOT TRUE. THAT IS NOT TRUE.
OH, YEAH? WELL, TELL ME ONE OF YOURS.
OKAY.
AH!
ONE OF MY THINGS IS
I ALWAYS SEPARATE MY SWEAT SOCKS FROM MY DRESS SOCKS.
YEAH.
WHAT IF THEY GET MIXED UP?
BOY, I WOULD JUST, UH...
I WOULD FREAK OUT.
YOU WOULD NOT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
I HATE THIS.
YOU'RE TOO NORMAL.
CAN'T BELIEVE MY BOYFRIEND DOESN'T HAVE A THING.
MY BOYFRIEND DOESN'T HAVE A THING.
SEE, IF ANYONE OVERHEARD THAT, I DIDN'T COME OFF WELL THERE.
HEY!
MR. DOUGLAS IS LOOKING FOR YOU.
WHY? W W WHY?
WHY IS MR. DOUGLAS LOOKING FOR ME?
BECAUSE HE HAS A STRONG SUSPICION
THAT YOU DROPPED THE BALL ON THE LENDER PROJECT.
WHAT... W WHY...
WHY DOES HE SUSPECT THAT?
BECAUSE, AT FIRST, HE THOUGHT IT WAS JOSEPH.
BUT AFTER HE ASKED JOSEPH ABOUT IT
TURNS OUT IT WAS YOU.
ANYWAY, I JUST THOUGHT
YOU SHOULD KNOW.
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S IT!
LOOK, JOEY, I'M SORRY.
I REALIZE THIS IS THE ROLE OF A LIFETIME FOR YOU
AND IF I COULD JUST FIRE JOSEPH, I WOULD
BUT THAT'S NOT POSSIBLE.
SO I'M GOING TO HAVE TO LET BOTH OF YOU GO.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
EVERYBODY LOVES JOSEPH.
I DON'T.
I HATE JOSEPH.
OKAY?
I THINK HE'S A BROWN NOSING SUCK UP.
OH, YEAH?
WELL, YOU CAN'T FIRE JOSEPH.
YOU KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE HE'S NOT IN YOUR DEPARTMENT.
HAA.
ALL RIGHT, OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, SO I CAN'T FIRE JOSEPH
BUT I CAN SLEEP WITH HIS WIFE.
NOT KAREN?
YEAH, KAREN.
I'M THINKING ABOUT HAVING AN AFFAIR WITH HER.
OH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I JUST DID.
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING TO ME, MAN?
OH. WELL, IT'S NOT ME.
IT'S MY CHARACTER.
"CHANDY."
THE ROGUE PROCESSOR
WHO SEDUCES HIS COWORKERS' WIVES FOR SPORT
AND LAUGHS ABOUT IT
THE NEXT DAY AT THE WATER COOLER.
IN FACT, I HAVE HER PANTIES RIGHT THERE IN MY DRAWER.
REALLY?
NO, FREAK SHOW! SHE'S FICTIONAL!
ALL RIGHT!
HEY, TAKE IT EASY.
IF IT MEANS THAT MUCH TO YOU
I'LL, UH... I'LL GO FIND SOMETHING ELSE.
THANK YOU.
IT'S JUST THAT...
I'M GOING TO MISS JOSEPH.
I LIKED HIM.
HIS WIFE... SHE WAS HOT.
AND THE KIDS...
YOU KNOW, HE WAS GOING
TO PUT IN A POOL NEXT SUMMER.
OW!
CAN I PLEASE TAKE THESE OFF?
I SWEAR I WON'T SCRATCH.
SORRY, HON.
MONICA'S ORDERS.
WELL, THAT WASN'T EASY.
OKAY, DINNER'S ON.
AND THERE'S A PEACH COBBLER WARMING IN THE OVEN.
SO THE PLATE'S GOING TO BE HOT
BUT THAT SHOULDN'T BE A PROBLEM FOR YOU.
ALL RIGHT, YOU KIDS.
BYE, NOW.
BYE.
LOOK.
A LOW BUDGET PUPPET SHOW.
IT'S SUCH A SHAME
YOU CAN'T SEE WHAT FINGER I'M HOLDING UP.
ALL RIGHT.
WINE?
PLEASE.
WHOOP. SPILLED SOME.
I GOT IT.
I MUST TELL YOU.
YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL TONIGHT.
WHAT?
SORRY.
YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL.
OH.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THAT'S IT. THAT'S IT.
OH.
OH, YES.
OH. OH.
GOOD.
NO. YOU KNOW WHAT?
HEY, YOU GUYS. DID YOU...?
MONICA, WAKE UP.
MONICA.
WHAT'S UP?
I THOUGHT OF A THING.
YEAH?
YEAH.
I HAVE TO SLEEP-- HAVE TO-- ON THIS SIDE OF THE BED.
NO, HONEY.
YOU HAVE TO SLEEP ON THIS SIDE OF THE BED
BECAUSE I HAVE TO SLEEP ON THIS SIDE OF THE BED.
OR SO I WOULD HAVE YOU BELIEVE.
OH....
BIG DEAL.
SO YOU HAVE A SIDE OF THE BED.
EVERYBODY HAS A SIDE OF THE BED.
HEY, COME ON.
YOU HAVEN'T HEARD MY REASON YET.
ALL RIGHT, GO ON.
OKAY. I HAVE TO SLEEP ON THE WEST SIDE
BECAUSE I GREW UP IN CALIFORNIA
AND OTHERWISE THE OCEAN WOULD BE ON THE WRONG SIDE.
OH, MY GOD.
YOU'RE A FREAK.
YEAH.
HOW ABOUT THAT?
SO, RYAN, WHERE YOU SHIPPING OFF TO?
I REALLY CAN'T SAY.
DO YOU HAVE ANY NUCLEAR WEAPONS ON BOARD?
I CAN'T SAY.
DO YOU GET TO LOOK THROUGH ONE OF THOSE PERISCOPE THINGIES?
I'M SORRY, BUT I CAN'T SAY.
WOW. IT'S NEAT LEARNING ABOUT SUBMARINES.
I BETTER GET OUT OF HERE.
I'M GOING TO MISS MY FLIGHT.
I'LL WALK YOU OUT.
PLEASURE.
TAKE CARE.
SO, DO YOU, UH, THINK WE COULD GET YOU
ONE OF THOSE, UH, UNIFORM THINGS?
YOU LIKE THAT, DO YOU?
OH, YEAH.
I'LL MAKE SOME CALLS.
OKAY.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THIS IS HOW
WE SPENT OUR TWO WEEKS TOGETHER?
WE DIDN'T DO ANY OF THE ROMANTIC THINGS
I HAD PLANNED, LIKE HAVING A PICNIC IN CENTRAL PARK
AND COFFEE AT CENTRAL PERK.
OH, I JUST GOT THAT.
OH.
TAXI.
BYE, YOU.
OH, I'M SORRY. WE'RE CLO...
HEY, SAILOR.
IS THIS WHAT YOU HAD IN MIND?
I'LL SAY.
I'M SHIPPING OUT TOMORROW.
WELL, THEN, UH...
WE BETTER MAKE THIS NIGHT COUNT.
OH, WAIT.
I FORGOT TO TURN OFF THE CAPPUCCINO MACHINE.
SORRY.
OH.
ANCHORS AWAY.
OH, AND MY PURSE, MY PURSE.
MY PURSE, MY PURSE.
SORRY. OOH.
THANK YOU.
OH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I FORGOT TO TURN OFF THE BATHROOM LIGHT.
WHY DON'T I JUST MEET YOU UPSTAIRS?
HONEY...!