HUH? SO WHAT DO YOU THINK?
CASA DE JOEY.
I DECORATED IT MYSELF.
GET OUT. NO.
WOW, JOEY.
THIS IS, UH...
ART.
ART IT IS.
WOW. CHECK THIS OUT.
IS IT A COFFEE TABLE?
IS IT A PANTHER?
THERE'S NO NEED TO DECIDE.
HEY.
NICE PILLOW.
SO, NOW, TELL ME.
IS THIS GENUINE MUPPET SKIN?
HEY, EXCELLENT
EXCELLENT WATER TABLE THING.
THANKS. YEAH, I LOVE THIS
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
MAKES ME WANT TO PEE.
YEAH, WELL, ME, TOO.
I THINK THAT'S THE CHALLENGE.
HEY, HOW COME, UH...
CHANDLER DIDN'T COME?
WELL, UH, IT'S BECAUSE HE HAD A THING WITH...
WITH WITH THE THING.
RIGHT.
I GOT I GOT IT.
SO WHY DON'T YOU SHOW US THE REST OF YOUR CASA?
YEAH.
OH... OH, THE BEST PART!
COME ON!
EH?
HEY.
NICE TOILET.
NO, NO, NO. BEHIND IT.
OH, YOU HAVE A PHONE IN HERE?
THAT'S RIGHT.
I HAVE A PHONE... IN HERE.
JOEY, PROMISE ME SOMETHING.
YEAH.
NEVER CALL ME FROM THAT PHONE.
OH!
OKAY, HERE WE GO.
HONEY, I'M SORRY.
THEY WERE ALL OUT OF APPLE PIE.
SOMEONE JUST GOT THE LAST PIECE.
OH, MY GOD. OH, MY GOD. OH, MY GOD.
YOU ARE NOT GOING TO BELIEVE THIS.
I HAVE JUST BEEN DISCOVERED.
NOW, WAIT A MINUTE.
I CLAIMED YOU IN THE NAME OF FRANCE
FOUR YEARS AGO.
ANYWAY, NOW PROMISE YOU WON'T FREAK OUT
AND SAY HOW GREAT THIS IS UNTIL I'M DONE, OKAY?
OKAY.
I JUST MET THIS PRODUCER
OF THIS, LIKE, TEENY RECORD COMPANY
WHO SAID THAT I HAVE A VERY FRESH, OFFBEAT SOUND
AND SHE WANTS TO DO A DEMO OF "SMELLY CAT."
OKAY, I TOLD YOU NOT TO DO THAT YET.
OKAY...
AND SHE WANTS TO DO A VIDEO.
I'M NOT DONE YET, OKAY?
GOD.
OKAY, IF THAT GOES WELL
THEY MAY EVEN WANT TO MAKE AN ALBUM.
I'M DONE NOW.
OH, GOD, ROSS, IF YOU CARE ABOUT ME AT ALL
YOU'LL GET THE PIE OUT OF THE MAN'S HOOD.
GET THE WHAT?
THERE'S A PIE IN THE HOOD. PIE IN THE HOOD. GO.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'M SORRY.
MY PIE WAS IN YOUR HOOD.
NOW I JUST HAVE TO GET THE COFFEE
OUT OF THAT GUY'S PANTS
AND I'LL BE BACK IN THE HOSPITAL BY 7:00.
DAMN IT, ROSS, GET YOUR BUTT
OUT OF THE BATHROOM!
CALM DOWN.
I'M BLOW DRYING.
BLOW DRYING WHAT?
YOU HAVE NO HAIR.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
YOUR BOYFRIEND HAS BEEN IN THERE
FOR OVER AN HOUR.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
IT'S LIKE I'M LIVING WITH HIM AGAIN.
HE'S HERE WHEN I GO TO SLEEP
HE'S HERE WHEN I WAKE UP
HE'S HERE WHEN I WANT TO USE THE SHOWER.
UGH! I FEEL LIKE I'M 16 ALL OVER AGAIN.
WELL, YOU'RE NOT 16.
YOU'RE BOTH ADULTS NOW.
GET OUT, YOU DOOFUS!
OR, YOU KNOW
HE'S RUBBER AND YOU'RE GLUE.
ALL YOURS.
I HOPE YOU CLEANED YOUR HAIR OUT OF THE DRAIN.
SHUT UP.
CUT IT OUT!
I'VE NEVER WANTED YOU MORE.
MI MI MI MI MI MI MI.
Hello.
LOUIE? WHERE'S HOWARD?
He went home.
OH. HE SAID HE MIGHT STOP UP AFTER HIS SHIFT.
He said to tell you he wasn't feeling so good.
OH. HEY, WHAT TIME DO YOU GET OFF?
I'm not feeling too good either.
SO, WHAT DO YOU SAY, BOYS?
SHOULD I CALL HIM?
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY:
ASK YOUR SLIPPERS A QUESTION...
YOU'RE GOING CRAZY.
OW!
FREAKING ART!
HELLO.
Hey.
HEY!
LISTEN, I'M SORRY I DIDN'T MAKE IT OVER THERE TODAY.
OH, THAT'S OKAY.
YOU, UH... YOU HAD A THING.
YEAH, WELL, I HEAR THE PLACE LOOKS GREAT.
OH, FORGET ABOUT IT.
I'M HAVING A BALL.
HOW'S THE APARTMENT DOING?
OH, HEY, IT'S TERRIFIC.
I MEAN, IT'S A REGULAR SPACE...
FEST.
OH.
WELL, GREAT.
Yeah, I just...
YOU KNOW, WANTED TO CALL AND SAY "HEY."
WELL, OKAY THEN.
WAS THAT THE OVEN TIMER?
THAT'S RIGHT, MY FRIEND.
It's time for...
BAYWATCH!
Oh...
CAN YOU BELIEVE THEY GAVE STEPHANIE SKIN CANCER?
I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE THEY PROMOTED HER TO LIEUTENANT.
OH, YOU'RE JUST SAYING THAT
BECAUSE YOU'RE IN LOVE WITH YASMINE BLEETH.
WELL, HOW COULD ANYONE NOT BE IN LOVE WITH YASMINE BLEETH?
HEY!
HEY! THEY'RE RUNNING!
SEE, THIS IS THE BRILLIANCE OF THE SHOW.
I SAY ALWAYS KEEP THEM RUNNING.
ALL THE TIME, RUNNING.
Run!
RUN, YASMINE! RUN LIKE THE WIND!
BUT I THOUGHT YOU WANTED
TO LIVE BY YOURSELF.
I DID.
I THOUGHT IT'D BE GREAT.
I FIGURED I'D HAVE, LIKE, TIME ALONE WITH MY THOUGHTS
BUT, YOU KNOW, IT TURNS OUT
I DON'T HAVE AS MANY THOUGHTS AS YOU'D THINK.
JOEY, WHY DON'T YOU TALK TO CHANDLER ABOUT MOVING BACK?
YOU REALLY THINK HE'D TAKE ME?
I MEAN, WE HAD A PRETTY GOOD TALK LAST NIGHT
BUT, WHEN I MOVED OUT, I HURT HIM BAD.
I PROMISE YOU
HE WOULD DEFINITELY WANT YOU BACK.
I'M TELLING YOU, THERE'S NO WAY HE'S MOVING BACK.
BUT WE HAD ONE OF THE GREATEST TALKS
WE EVER HAD LAST NIGHT.
I MEAN, IT WAS...
IT WAS LIKE WHEN WE FIRST STARTED LIVING TOGETHER.
LOOK, I KNOW YOU DON'T WANT TO HEAR THIS RIGHT NOW, BUT...
WE'VE SEEN HIM IN HIS NEW PLACE, ALL RIGHT
AND HE'S HAPPY.
HE'S... HE'S DECORATED.
LOOK, CHANDLER, HE HAS MOVED ON, OKAY?
YOU HAVE TO, TOO.
BUT...
NO. YOU'RE JUST GOING TO HAVE TO ACCEPT THE FACT
THAT YOU'RE JUST FRIENDS NOW, OKAY?
YOU'RE NOT... ROOMMATES ANYMORE.
Okay, Phoebe.
Ready to try one?
OKAY.
? SMELLY CAT ?
? WHAT ARE THEY FEEDING YOU? ?
? SMELLY, SMELLY, SMELLY? ? SMELLY CAT, SMELLY CAT... ?
? REALLY BAD SMELLING SMELLY CAT...?
WHOA! OH, MY GOD!
I MEAN, LIKE, WHO WAS THAT?
They're your backup singers.
Behind you, hon.
OH!
OH, I THOUGHT THEY WERE JUST WATCHING ME.
YOU KNOW, LIKE...
LIKE AT AN AQUARIUM.
WOW, THEY'RE SO GOOD.
HI. YOU'RE SO GOOD.
All righty.
Okay. Now that everyone knows everyone
let's try it again.
OKAY.
From the top.
? SMELLY CAT ?
? WHAT ARE THEY FEEDING YOU? ?
? SMELLY, SMELLY, SMELLY? ? SMELLY CAT ?
? REALLY BAD SMELLING SMELLY CAT?
? IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT...?
OKAY. SORRY.
I'M JUST NOT GETTING
THAT EVERYONE, UM...
GETS HOW SMELLY THIS CAT ACTUALLY IS.
I JUST THINK IF WE COULD TALK ABOUT THIS
BECAUSE I NEED TO FEEL
THAT YOU REALLY CARE ABOUT THE CAT.
Honey, we can talk about this.
It's just that it's costing
about a hundred dollars a minute to be in here.
OH, OKAY.
SO THE CAT STINKS, BUT YOU LOVE IT.
LET'S GO.
NO. THERE IS NO WAY HE WAS A VELOCIRAPTOR.
NO, TONY.
LOOK AT THE CRANIAL RIDGE, OKAY?
IF DINO WAS A VELOCIRAPTOR
HE WOULD HAVE EATEN THE FLINTSTONES.
YEAH... YEAH.
OH, WERE YOU TAKING A NAP?
I WAS.
OH, WAIT.
TONY, CAN YOU HOLD ON? THAT'S THE OTHER LINE.
HELLO.
OH, YES, SHE'S HERE, BUT CAN SHE CALL YOU BACK?
OKAY, THANKS.
CALL JOANNA. HI.
DID SHE LEAVE A NUMBER?
DID YOU SEE ME
WRITE ONE DOWN?
I DON'T HAVE HER NUMBER, BUTTMUNCH.
WELL, SHE'LL CALL BACK.
DON'T BE SUCH A BABY.
I'M NOT A BABY. YOU'RE THE BABY.
YOU WANT TO GET OFF MY BACK?
YOU WANT TO GET OUT OF MY FACE?
WAIT. HOLD ON, TONY. HOLD ON.
HELLO.
HI.
YEAH. NO. SHE'S RIGHT HERE.
UM, HOLD ON.
HI. TONY, CAN I CALL YOU BACK?
THAT'S, UH... THAT'S MY SISTER'S BOYFRIEND.
GIVE ME THAT.
OKAY.
HI, SWEETIE.
LISTEN, BEFORE I FORGET--
DID I LEAVE MY DIAPHRAGM AT YOUR PLACE?
HI, MOM.
HEY!
SO, UH...
HOW'S THE PALACE?
YOU KNOW, IT'S FUNNY YOU SHOULD MENTION THAT
BECAUSE I WAS THINKING...
WHAT'S WITH THE BOXES?
OH, UH... ACTUALLY
I, UH, HAVE SOME NEWS.
HEY, CHAN, IS JOEY GOING TO PICK UP HIS MOOSE HAT
OR SHOULD I JUST TOSS IT OUT?
WELL, UH, WHY DON'T YOU ASK HIM YOURSELF.
JOEY, THIS IS MY NEW ROOMMATE, EDDIE.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
LIKEWISE.
HOW YOU DOING?
I'LL TAKE THAT.
OH.
IT'S, UH... WHAT I CAME FOR.
SO, THIS IS NEW.
WHERE'D YOU TWO MEET?
AT THE SUPERMARKET, IN THE ETHNIC FOOD SECTION.
I HELPED HIM PICK OUT A CHORIZO.
WOW.
YOU KNOW, WE GOT TO TALKING
AND HE SAID HE NEEDED A PLACE, AND I HAD A SPARE ROOM.
OH.
NOW IT'S A SPARE ROOM?
WELL, YEAH, IN THAT IT'S NOT BEING USED
AND I HAVE IT TO SPARE.
RIGHT.
WELL, I, UH, GOT WHAT I CAME FOR.
I'LL, UH, I'LL SEE YOU GUYS.
HEY, JOE?
WHEN DID YOU START USING MOOSE IN YOUR HAIR?
IS THIS GUY GREAT OR WHAT?
YEAH.
YEAH, HE IS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HE HAS A NEW ROOMMATE.
WHO IS THIS GUY?
EDDIE SOMETHING. HE JUST MET HIM.
IT'LL NEVER LAST.
HE'S JUST A REBOUND ROOMMATE.
HEY!
OOH, CHECK IT OUT.
CHECK IT OUT.
IT'S "SMELLY CAT"-- THE VIDEO.
HEY!
NOW, OKAY, I HAVEN'T SEEN IT YET
SO IF YOU DON'T LIKE IT, WELL, SO WHAT?
NONE OF YOU EVER MADE A VIDEO.
OKAY.
Get out of here, cat!
You stink!
WHOA.
SMOKING.
OH, LOOK AT ME!
? SMELLY CAT ?
? WHAT ARE THEY FEEDING YOU? ?
? IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT ?
? SMELLY, SMELLY, SMELLY ?
? REALLY BAD SMELLING SMELLY CAT?
? IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT?
? SMELLY CAT ?
OH, MY GOD.
I KNOW.
I SOUND AMAZING.
? IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT ?
? THEY WON'T TAKE YOU TO THE VET ?
? YOU'RE OBVIOUSLY NOT THEIR FAVORITE PET ?
? SMELLY CAT ?
? IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT ?
? OH, NO ?
I'VE NEVER HEARD MYSELF SING BEFORE.
I MEAN, EXCEPT IN MY OWN HEAD.
THIS IS SO COOL.
NOW I CAN HEAR WHAT YOU HEAR.
PRETTY DIFFERENT, HUH?
I AM SORRY, BUT I AM INCREDIBLY TALENTED.
? SMELLY CAT ?
? IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT. ?
HEY, JOEY. WHAT'S GOING ON, MAN?
EDDIE.
MORNING.
I JUST CAME BY TO PICK UP MY MAIL.
WHERE'S THE MAIL?
OH, IT'S OVER THERE ON THE TABLE.
YOU DON'T KEEP IT OVER HERE ON THIS TABLE ANYMORE?
NAH. EDDIE LIKES TO KEEP IT OVER THERE.
ALL RIGHT, HERE YOU GO, MY FRIEND.
EGGS A LA EDDIE.
OOH, OOH.
OH... OH...
THAT'S GREAT.
HUH.
WHAT?
NO, I JUST THOUGHT YOU LIKED YOUR EGGS
WITH THE BREAD WITH THE HOLE IN THE MIDDLE--
A LA ME.
I DO, BUT EDDIE MAKES THEM THIS WAY.
WELL, THEY'RE PRETTY DARN GOOD.
YOU LIKE SOME, MAN? THERE'S EXTRA.
NO, THANKS.
ALL RIGHT. WELL, YOU GUYS
I'M OUT OF HERE.
SEE YOU, PALS.
SEE YA.
SO, HOW YOU TWO GETTING ALONG?
OH, I COULDN'T BE HAPPIER.
GREAT.
WELL, I'M HAPPY FOR YOU.
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S IT.
HE JUST COMES IN HERE
MR. JOHNNY NEW EGGS
WITH HIS, HIS...
HIS MOVING THE MAIL AND HIS, HIS "SEE YA, PALS."
AND NOW THERE'S NO JUICE.
THERE'S NO JUICE FOR THE PEOPLE
WHO NEED THE JUICE AND WANT THE JUICE.
I NEED THE JUICE!
THERE'S ANOTHER CARTON RIGHT OVER THERE.
THIS ISN'T ABOUT JUICE ANYMORE, ALL RIGHT, MAN?
ALL RIGHT.
SO WHAT'S IT ABOUT?
EGGS.
WHOSE EGGS DO YOU LIKE BETTER?
HIS OR MINE?
WELL, I LIKE BOTH EGGS EQUALLY.
OH, COME ON.
NOBODY LIKES TWO DIFFERENT KINDS OF EGGS EQUALLY.
YOU LIKE ONE BETTER THAN THE OTHER
AND I WANT TO KNOW WHICH.
WHAT'S THE DIFFERENCE?
YOUR EGGS
AREN'T HERE ANYMORE, ARE THEY?
YOU TOOK YOUR EGGS AND YOU LEFT!
DID YOU REALLY EXPECT ME TO NEVER FIND NEW EGGS?
WELL, MAYBE THIS ISN'T ABOUT THE EGGS.
MAYBE THIS IS ABOUT THE CHICKEN THAT LAID THEM.
HUH?
WHAT CHICKEN?
THERE'S NO CHICKEN.
I CAN'T TALK TO YOU!
I WANT TO WATCH ENTERTAINMENT TONIGHT.
TOUGH NOOGIES. WE'RE WATCHING PREDATORS OF THE SERENGETI.
WOULD YOU GUYS STOP?
IT'S MY TV.
QUIT IT.
BITE ME.
OH, MY GOD.
MONICA KEEPS CHANGING THE CHANNEL.
THAT'S GREAT. WHY DON'T YOU TELL MOMMY ON ME?
NOW I'M MOMMY IN THIS LITTLE PLAY?
ALL RIGHT, LOOK.
I REFUSE TO GET SUCKED INTO THIS, LIKE, WEIRD
LITTLE GELLER DIMENSION THING.
SO I'M GOING TO GO
AND TAKE A NICE, LONG HOT BUBBLE BATH
BECAUSE YOU KIDS ARE DRIVING ME CRAZY!
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO ABOUT THIS?
I GUESS WE COULD TAPE ENTERTAINMENT TONIGHT.
NOT THAT.
THIS. US.
OH, MY GOD, ROSS, YOU... IT'S... YOU ARE...
OW. OW.
YOU'RE DRIVING ME... NIGHTMARE!
MON, MON, MON, YOU'VE GONE ULTRASONIC AGAIN.
I JUST CAN'T STAND YOU BEING HERE ALL THE TIME.
WHY? WHY? WHY CAN'T YOU STAND ME BEING HERE?
YOU KNOW, WE'RE JUST HAVING FUN.
FUN? YOU THINK THIS IS FUN?
YEAH.
I MEAN, I THOUGHT WE WERE JUST FOOLING AROUND
LIKE WHEN WE WERE KIDS.
ROSS, I HATED YOU WHEN WE WERE KIDS.
YOU HATED ME WHEN WE WERE KIDS?
YES. I HATED YOU.
I LOVED YOU IN A YOU'RE  MY BROTHER SO I HAVE TO KIND OF WAY
BUT, BASICALLY, YEAH, I HATED YOUR GUTS.
WHY DID YOU HATE ME?
BECAUSE YOU WERE MEAN TO ME, AND YOU... YOU TEASED ME
AND YOU ALWAYS, ALWAYS GOT YOUR WAY.
AND THAT WASN'T FUN FOR YOU?
TA HA!
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU HATED ME.
NOW I LOVE YOU.
AND NOT JUST BECAUSE I HAVE TO.
REALLY?
YEAH.
YOU'RE JUST GOING TO HAVE TO STOP PISSING ME OFF.
I CAN DO THAT.
THEN I WON'T HAVE TO KILL YOU.
SO YOU WANT TO WATCH ENTERTAINMENT TONIGHT?
AW, THANKS.
America's premier sports magazine...
YOU KNOW WHAT?
WHAT?
IF YOU REALLY WANT TO WATCH THAT SERENGETI THING
WE CAN.
OH... OKAY.
HEY, LISTEN, YOU ARE NOT GOING
TO BELIEVE THIS
BUT THAT IS NOT ME SINGING ON THE VIDEO.
NO! NO! NO!
YES.
WELL, HOW DID YOU FIND OUT?
OKAY, THE RECORD COMPANY SENT OVER
THIS PIECE OF PAPER FOR ME TO SIGN
SAYING THAT IT'S OKAY FOR SOMEONE ELSE TO SING FOR ME.
THAT WAS MY FIRST CLUE.
SO WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
WELL, I CAN'T WORK WITH PEOPLE WHO WOULD DO THIS.
SURE.
I MEAN, THIS POOR WOMAN.
WHAT WOMAN?
THE VOICE WOMAN.
SHE HAS A GREAT VOICE, BUT SHE DOESN'T HAVE A VIDEO.
OKAY, PHEEBS, BUT WHAT ABOUT YOU?
WELL, I HAVE A VIDEO.
YOU HAVE TO PAY ATTENTION.
NO, THIS VOICE WOMAN, SHE'S SO TALENTED.
BUT, ACCORDING TO THE PRODUCER PEOPLE
SHE DOESN'T HAVE, LIKE, THE RIGHT LOOK OR SOMETHING.
IT'S LIKE SHE'S, LIKE, ONE OF THOSE ANIMALS AT THE POUND
WHO, LIKE, NOBODY WANTS
BECAUSE THEY'RE NOT PRETTY ENOUGH
FOR IT, YOU KNOW.
LIKE SOME OLD DOG WHO'S JUST KIND OF, LIKE, STINKY AND...
OH, MY GOD. SHE'S SMELLY CAT.
OH, THAT SONG HAS SO MANY LEVELS.
HEY, EDDIE, YOU WANT TO PLAY SOME FOOSBALL?
NO, THANKS, MAN.
I'M NOT REALLY INTO SPORTS.
YEAH, OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
DOESN'T MATTER.
TIME FOR BAYWATCH.
WHAT?
YOU YOU LIKE THAT SHOW?
YOU DON'T LIKE THAT SHOW?
NO, MAN.
IT'S JUST A BUNCH OF PRETTY PEOPLE
RUNNING AROUND ON THE BEACH.
WELL, THAT'S THE BRILLIANCE OF IT.
THE PRETTY PEOPLE...
AND THE RUNNING.
I'M GOING TO GO READ
IN MY ROOM FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
OH, OKAY, MAN.
? ALL ALONE ?
? I THINK OF ALL THE FRIENDS I'VE KNOWN ?
? BUT WHEN I DIAL THE TELEPHONE ?
? NO ONE IS HOME ?
? ALL BY MYSELF ?
? DON'T WANT TO LIVE ALL BY MYSELF ?
? ANYMORE ?
? ALL BY MYSELF... ?
I'M GOING TO START OFF
WITH A LITTLE SONG CALLED "SMELLY CAT."
OH, fOR THOSE OF YOU WHO WERE WONDERING
THIS IS MY REAL VOICE.
? SMELLY CAT, SMELLY CAT ?
? WHAT ARE THEY FEEDING YOU? ?
EVERYBODY!
? SMELLY CAT ?
? IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT ?
MONICA!
? THEY WON'T TAKE YOU ?
? TO THE VET ?
CHANDLER!
? YOU'RE OBVIOUSLY NOT THEIR FAVORITE PET ?
JOEY!
? YOU MAY NOT BE A BED OF ROSES ?
RACHEL!
? YOU'RE NO FRIEND TO THOSE WITH NOSES... ?
ROSS, THOSE ARE THE ONLY LINES WE HAVE. SORRY.
OKAY.
BACK TO THE CHORUS, EVERYBODY.
? SMELLY CAT, SMELLY CAT ?
? WHAT ARE THEY FEEDING YOU? ?
? IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT ?
? SMELLY CAT, SMELLY CAT ?
? WHAT ARE THEY FEEDING YOU? ?
YEAH!
? SMELLY CAT, SMELLY CAT ?
? IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT. ?