CAN'T GET THE MONKEY OFF YOUR BACK?
THEN PUT IT IN YOUR MOUTH.
WITH MONKEYSHINE BEER.
? YAY, YAY, MONKEY ?
? MONKEY, MONKEY. ?
MONKEYSHINE BEER
BECAUSE IT'S A JUNGLE OUT THERE.
THAT COMMERCIAL ALWAYS MAKES ME SO SAD.
YEAH, BUT THEN, THE GUY OPENS HIS BEER
AND THOSE GIRLS RUN AT HIM
SO EVERYTHING SEEMS TO WORK OUT OKAY.
I MEANT BECAUSE THE MONKEY IN IT REMINDS ME OF MARCEL.
I CAN SEE THAT.
BECAUSE THEY BOTH HAVE THOSE BIG, BROWN EYES
AND, YOU KNOW, THE LITTLE, POUTY CHIN...
AND THE FACT THAT THEY'RE BOTH MONKEYS.
SOMETIMES I WONDER IF I DID THE RIGHT THING
YOU KNOW, GIVING HIM AWAY.
OH, ROSS, YOU HAD TO.
I MEAN, HE WAS HUMPING EVERYTHING IN SIGHT.
I MEAN, I HAVE A MALIBU BARBIE WHO WILL NO LONGER BE WEARING
WHITE TO HER WEDDING.
REMEMBER WHEN, SOMETIMES, HE'D BORROW YOUR HAT
AND WHEN YOU GOT IT BACK
THERE'D BE LITTLE MONKEY RAISINS IN IT?
GOD, HE LOVED THAT JOKE.
YEAH, SURE, WHEN HE DID IT, IT WAS FUNNY.
WHEN I DID IT
TO MY BOSS'S HAT?
ALL OF A SUDDEN, I HAVE
THIS BIG "ATTITUDE PROBLEM."
HEY, HEY. CHECK IT OUT.
GUESS WHAT I GOT.
RHYTHM?
NO. MY FIRST FAN MAIL.
ALL RIGHT. HEY.
"DEAR DR. RAMORAY: KNOW THAT I LOVE YOU
AND WOULD DO ANYTHING TO HAVE YOU."
GOSH!
"YOUR NOT SO SECRET ADMIRER, ERIKA FORD."
OH, WAIT.
"P.S.: ENCLOSED PLEASE FIND 14 OF MY EYELASHES."
YOU KNOW
IN CRAZY WORLD, THAT MEANS YOU'RE MARRIED.
THIS WASN'T ADDRESSED
TODAYS OF OUR LIVES.
THIS CAME TO YOUR APARTMENT.
THERE'S NO STAMP ON IT.
THIS WOMAN WAS IN OUR BUILDING.
OH, MY GOD.
I GOT MY VERY OWN STALKER.
HEY, YOU KNOW, YOU ARE SO LUCKY.
I HAVE TO SHARE MINE WITH A BUNCH OF GUYS
DOWN AT WORK.
OKAY, JOEY, REMEMBER WHEN WE TALKED
ABOUT GOOD THING, BAD THING?
THIS IS A BAD THING.
HEY, GUYS.
HEY.
WHERE ARE YOU OFF TO, TRAVELING JAKE?
WELL, THERE'S THIS PALEONTOLOGY CONFERENCE IN L.A.
SO, I FIGURED I'D GO, AND THEN DRIVE
DOWN TO THE ZOO AND SURPRISE MARCEL.
YOU KNOW, I THINK HE WILL BE SURPRISED, UNTIL HE REALIZES
HE'S A MONKEY
AND, UH, YOU KNOW, IS INCAPABLE OF THAT EMOTION.
OH! PHOEBE
THAT REALLY CUTE GUY IS HERE AGAIN.
OH? OH, OKAY. SO, EVERYONE PRETEND
LIKE I'M TELLING YOU A STORY, OKAY?
AND IT'S REALLY FUNNY, SO EVERYONE JUST LAUGH.
NOW.
I KNOW. I KNOW.
HELLO.
HI.
I'M ROB DONNAN.
HI, ROB DONNAN.
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT MUSIC
BUT I THINK YOU'RE REALLY, REALLY GREAT.
OH... WOW.
ANYWAY, I SCHEDULE PERFORMERS
FOR THE CHILDREN'S LIBRARIES AROUND THE CITY
AND I WAS JUST THINKING
HAVE YOU EVER THOUGHT ABOUT PLAYING YOUR SONGS FOR KIDS?
OH, I WOULD LOVE TO HAVE KIDS.
...HEAR... HEAR THE... HEAR ME PLAY THE SONGS
THAT I WILL WRITE FOR THEM.
HEY, WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO FOR DINNER?
WELL, WE COULD STAY IN AND COOK FOR OURSELVES.
HELLO.
It's Erika.
OH, MY GOD. THE STALKER.
Never mind.
It's open.
YES. HITTING HER WITH A FRYING PAN'S A GOOD IDEA.
WE MIGHT WANT A BACKUP PLAN, THOUGH, JUST IN CASE
SHE ISN'T A CARTOON.
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
THE ONE TIME THEY'RE NOT HOME.
OKAY. OKAY.
WE'LL JUST LEAVE
AND WHEN WE PASS HER ON THE STAIRS
SHE WON'T KNOW IT'S ME, BECAUSE WE NEVER MET.
THAT'S HOW RADIO STARS ESCAPE STALKERS.
SHE'S COMING.
IT'S ME.
UH, THIS IS IT.
THIS IS HOW WE'RE GOING TO DIE.
YOU READY?
WAIT, WAIT.
HI.
ERIKA...
MR. GELLER?
YES. HI.
HI. DEAN LIPSON, ZOO ADMINISTRATOR.
I WAS TOLD YOU HAD A QUESTION.
WELL, I CAN'T SEEM TO FIND THE MONKEY
I DONATED LAST YEAR.
HE'S A CAPUCHIN, ANSWERS TO THE NAME "MARCEL."
AH... I'M AFRAID I HAVE SOME BAD NEWS.
MARCEL HAS PASSED ON.
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT HAPPENED?
WELL, HE GOT SICK, AND THEN HE GOT SICKER
AND THEN HE GOT
A LITTLE BETTER
BUT THEN HE DIED.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
I'M SORRY, MR. GELLER
BUT, YOU KNOW, THERE'S AN OLD SAYING:
"SOMETIMES, MONKEYS DIE."
IT'S NOT A GREAT SAYING
BUT... IT CERTAINLY IS FITTING TODAY.
WELL, YOU KNOW, SOMEONE SHOULD HAVE CALLED ME.
I'M SORRY.
LOOK, I KNOW THIS CAN'T BRING HIM BACK, BUT, HERE.
IT'S JUST A GESTURE.
ZOO DOLLARS?
YES. AND COME SEE THE BIRD SHOW AT 4:00.
THE MACAWS
WEAR HATS.
WELL, IT'S A LOT CUTER
IF YOUR MONKEY HASN'T JUST DIED.
I KNOW.
I CAN'T BELIEVE JOEY'S HAVING LUNCH
WITH HIS STALKER.
WHAT IS SHE LIKE?
WELL, YOU REMEMBER KATHY BATES IN MISERY?
WELL, SHE LOOKS THE... EXACT OPPOSITE OF THAT.
AND SHE'S NOT CRAZY?
OH, NO, NO, NO.
SHE'S A TOTAL WHACK JOB.
YEAH. SHE THINKS THAT JOEY
IS ACTUALLY DR. DRAKE RAMORAY.
OH, MY GOD.
UGH. AND HE'S GOING OUT WITH HER?
HE CANNOT PURSUE THIS.
HEY, JUST BECAUSE THIS WOMAN THINKS SHE CAN ACTUALLY SEE JOEY
THROUGH THE MAGICAL BOX IN HER LIVING ROOM
DOESN'T MEAN SHE'S NOT A PERSON.
I MEAN, DOES SHE NOT DESERVE HAPPINESS?
DOES SHE NOT DESERVE LOVE?
WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING AT ME FOR?
HE'S THE ONE WHO WANTS TO BOFF THE MANIAC.
ARE YOU OKAY?
NO. UH UH.
I'M JUST... I'M NERVOUS.
MAYBE IF I PICTURE THEM ALL IN THEIR UNDERWEAR...
THAT'S NOT A GOOD IDEA.
THAT'S KIND OF THE REASON THE LAST GUY GOT FIRED.
I'M JUST... I'M... I'M USED TO PLAYING FOR GROWNUPS.
YOU KNOW, THEY JUST... GROWNUPS DRINK THEIR COFFEE
AND DO THEIR GROWNUP THING, AND KIDS... LISTEN.
IT'S JUST A HUGE RESPONSIBILITY.
WHAT?
ARE YOU GOING TO KISS ME?
I WAS THINKING ABOUT IT.
OKAY.
OKAY, ALL RIGHTY, LET'S PLAY SOME TUNES.
OKAY, LET'S GO FIND OUR SEATS.
CHANDLER, WE'RE GOING TO FIND OUR SEATS.
HOLD ON A SECOND.
"HE THINKS HE CAN.
HE THINKS HE CAN."
AW, WHAT THE HELL.
"HE CAN."
HI, EVERYBODY. I'M PHOEBE.
HI, PHOEBE.
OKAY.
UM, I'M GOING TO PLAY, UM, SOME SONGS ABOUT GRANDPARENTS.
OKAY?
? NOW, GRANDMA'S A PERSON WHO EVERYONE LIKES ?
? SHE BOUGHT YOU A TRAIN AND A BRIGHT, SHINY BIKE ?
? BUT LATELY, SHE HASN'T BEEN COMING TO DINNER ?
? AND LAST TIME YOU SAW HER, SHE LOOKED SO MUCH THINNER ?
? NOW, YOUR MOM AND YOUR DAD ?
? SAID SHE MOVED TO PERU ?
? BUT THE TRUTH IS, SHE DIED, AND SOMEDAY YOU WILL, TOO ?
? LA, LA, LA, LA, LA, LA, LA, LA, LA, LA ?
? LA, LA, LA, LA, LA, LA ?
? LA, LA, LA, LA ?
? LA, LA, LA, LA, LA, LA, LA, LA, LA, LA ?
? LA, LA, LA, LA, LA, LA, LA, LA, LA, LA. ?
I'LL HAVE THE GRILLED SALMON
AND THE DOCTOR
WILL HAVE THE RISOTTO.
THANK YOU.
OH, DRAKE, ISN'T IT AMAZING?
YEAH, IT IS.
WHAT?
WELL, I MEAN, HERE WE SIT, DEVIL MAY CARE
AND JUST A LITTLE WHILE AGO
YOU WERE REATTACHING SIMONE'S SPINAL CORD.
YEAH. THAT WAS A TRICKY ONE.
IN REALITY
THAT OPERATION TAKES, LIKE, OVER TEN HOURS
BUT THEY ONLY SHOWED IT FOR TWO MINUTES.
WHO'S THEY?
NO ONE.
OH, DRAKE, YOU ARE SO TALENTED.
LET ME SEE THOSE HANDS.
OH, THESE HANDS, THESE BEAUTIFUL HANDS.
OH, I COULD JUST EAT THEM... BUT I WON'T.
GOOD.
OTHERWISE, MY WATCH WOULD FALL OFF.
NO. SERIOUSLY.
THESE HANDS--
THESE MIRACLE, MAGICAL, LIFE GIVING HANDS--
OH, JUST TO BE NEAR THEM, TOUCH THEM--
MAYBE EVEN LICK ONE?
ALL RIGHT.
JUST ONE.
WOW...
YOU'RE GOOD AT THAT.
OH, MY GOD! SOMEONE! HE'S CHOKING!
IS ANYONE HERE A DOCTOR?
OH, YES.
YES. THE BEST DOCTOR IN ALL OF SALEM--
DR. DRAKE RAMORAY.
MEET ME IN THE NOCTURNAL HOUSE IN 15 MINUTES.
UH, HEY, LOOK.
I DON'T REALLY ENJOY BEING WITH OTHER MEN-- THAT WAY...
...BUT, UM, ZOO DOLLARS?
IT'S ABOUT YOUR MONKEY.
IT'S ALIVE.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHY DIDN'T YOU HELP THAT MAN?
UH... BECAUSE I'M A NEUROSURGEON.
AND THAT WAS CLEARLY A CASE OF...
FOODAL CHOKAGE.
YOU KNOW...
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, I'VE GOT TO TELL YOU SOMETHING...
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO TELL ME ANYTHING.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO EXPLAIN YOURSELF TO ME.
WHO AM I TO QUESTION THE GREAT DR. DRAKE RAMORAY?
BUT THAT'S...
I SHOULD JUST BE HAPPY TO BE NEAR YOU.
HEY WHAT?
THAT'S IT.
JUST HEY.
LIKE AT THE END OF A DANCE.
HEY!
HEY.
HEY. HEY. HEY.
? THERE'LL BE TIMES WHEN YOU GET OLDER ?
? WHEN YOU'LL WANT TO SLEEP WITH PEOPLE ?
? JUST TO MAKE THEM LIKE YOU ?
? BUT DON'T ?
? BECAUSE THAT'S ANOTHER THING THAT YOU DON'T WANT TO DO ?
EVERYBODY.
? THAT'S ANOTHER THING THAT ?
? YOU DON'T WANT TO DO.?
EXCELLENT.
VERY INFORMATIVE.
NOT AT ALL INAPPROPRIATE.
THANK YOU FOR COMING, EVERYBODY.
THERE ARE COOKIES IN THE BACK.
THAT WAS GREAT.
THE KIDS LOVED YOU.
YAY!
I ROCK.
AND YOU KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE YOU TOLD THE TRUTH.
AND NOBODY EVER TELLS KIDS THE TRUTH.
YOU WERE INCREDIBLE.
BUT?
HOW DID YOU KNOW THERE WAS A "BUT"?
I SENSE THESE THINGS.
IT WAS EITHER "BUT" OR "BUTTER."
THE THING IS, I THINK SOME OF THE PARENTS
THEY WERE KIND OF HOPING
THAT YOU WOULD PLAY MORE SONGS
ABOUT, LIKE, BARNYARD ANIMALS.
I CAN DO THAT.
REALLY? YEAH.
BECAUSE THAT WOULD BE FANTASTIC.
WHAT?
YOU WANT TO KISS ME?
I'M THINKING ABOUT IT.
OKAY, SO IF I GET A LIBRARY CARD
CAN I TAKE YOU OUT SOMETIME?
WHAT?
I'M UNEMPLOYED.
AH, THE BAT.
AMBASSADOR OF DARKNESS.
FLITTING OUT OF HIS CAVE LIKE A WINGED MESSENGER.
SIGHTLESS SPECTER OF THE MACABRE.
BUDDY, MY MONKEY?
OH, YEAH, RIGHT.
THERE WAS A BREAK IN
A FEW MONTHS BACK.
INSIDE JOB.
YOUR MONKEY WAS TAKEN
ALONG WITH A SNOWY EGRET
A TWO TOED SLOTH
AND THREE HOODED SWEATSHIRTS
FROM THE ZOO GIFT SHOP.
OH, MY GOD. BUT THE ZOO TOLD ME MY MONKEY WAS DEAD.
THE ZOO.
YOU BELIEVE EVERYTHING THE ZOO TELLS YOU?
THAT'S THE ONLY THING THE ZOO'S EVER TOLD ME.
OF COURSE, THEY'RE GOING TO SAY HE'S DEAD.
THEY DON'T WANT THE BAD PUBLICITY.
IT'S ALL A GREAT, BIG COVER UP.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA HOW HIGH UP THIS THING GOES?
THAT GUY LIPSON?
LIPSON KNOWS?
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA WHO ELSE KNOWS?
NO, I ONLY KNOW LIPSON.
HMM.
LIPSON KNOWS, HUH?
HELLO, MR. POSSUM.
ENIGMA OF THE TREES
UPSIDE DOWN DENIZEN OF THE NIGHT.
TAUNTING GRAVITY...
BUDDY, MY MONKEY? MY MONKEY?
WORD ON THE STREET...
WELL, WHEN I SAY STREET
I MEAN THOSE LITTLE PRETEND
STREETS THEY HAVE HERE AT THE ZOO.
OF COURSE.
YOUR MONKEY FOUND A NEW CAREER
IN THE ENTERTAINMENT FIELD.
THAT'S ALL I KNOW.
THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE.
SO... WHAT IS THIS INFORMATION WORTH TO YOU, MY FRIEND?
ARE YOU TRYING TO GET ME TO BRIBE YOU?
MAYBE.
BUT YOU ALREADY TOLD ME EVERYTHING.
CHECK IT OUT.
HE ACTUALLY IS THE MONKEYSHINE MONKEY.
WELL, SO WHAT
ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
I GUESS I'M GOING TO CALL THE BEER COMPANY
AND TRY TO FIND OUT WHERE HE IS.
THAT'S WHAT I DID WHEN I LOST
MY CLYDESDALES.
OKAY, HI AGAIN.
HI, PHOEBE!
TODAY, WE'RE GOING TO START WITH SOME SONGS
ABOUT BARNYARD ANIMALS.
? OH, THE COW IN THE MEADOW GOES MOO ?
? THEN THE FARMER HITS HIM ON THE HEAD AND GRINDS HIM UP ?
? AND THAT'S HOW WE GET HAMBURGERS ?
NOW, CHICKENS!
You're the only one who can save her, Drake.
Damn it, I'm a doctor!
I'm not God.
WELL, THERE GOES MY WHOLE BELIEF SYSTEM.
IT'S ERIKA.
OH, MY GOD! QUICK, TURN OFF THE TV.
NO, NO, NO.
WAIT, I WANT TO SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
I GET LESLIE OUT OF THE COMA, THEN WE MAKE OUT.
HOW CAN THAT BE?
YOU WERE JUST KISSING SABRINA.
RACHEL, IT'S A WORLD WHERE JOEY IS A NEUROSURGEON.
HEY, ERIKA. COME ON IN.
HOW DID YOU GET HERE SO FAST?
I JUST SAW YOU IN SALEM.
RIGHT.
THEY, UH... THEY CHOPPERED ME IN.
WHAT'S UP?
WELL, AND I SEE YOU'RE HAVING A LITTLE PARTY, TOO.
IS SHE HERE?
HUH? HUH? WHO?
SABRINA. I KNOW ABOUT YOU TWO.
I SAW YOU TODAY, KISSING IN THE DOCTORS' LOUNGE.
THAT'S NOT WHAT YOU THINK.
THAT WAS...
YOU TOLD ME
I WAS THE ONLY ONE.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, THAT'S IT.
I DON'T THINK WE SHOULD SEE EACH OTHER ANYMORE, ALL RIGHT?
LOOK, I KNOW I SHOULD HAVE TOLD YOU THIS A LONG TIME AGO
BUT I AM NOT DRAKE RAMORAY, OKAY?
I'M NOT EVEN A DOCTOR.
I'M AN ACTOR.
I JUST PRETEND TO BE A DOCTOR.
OH, MY GOD, DO THE PEOPLE
AT THE HOSPITAL KNOW ABOUT THIS?
SOMEBODY WANT TO HELP ME OUT HERE?
OH, I KNOW. I KNOW.
Where am I?
University Hospital.
The same place you've been for the last 18 years.
HOW CAN YOU BE HERE AND THERE?
BECAUSE IT'S A TELEVISION SHOW.
DRAKE, WHAT ARE YOU GETTING AT?
NICE GIRL.
NOT GREAT WITH CONCEPTS.
I'M NOT DRAKE.
THAT'S RIGHT.
HE'S NOT DRAKE.
HE'S...
HANS RAMORAY, DRAKE'S EVIL TWIN.
IS THIS TRUE?
YES, YES, IT IS TRUE.
AND I KNOW THIS BECAUSE...
BECAUSE HE PRETENDED TO BE DRAKE
TO SLEEP WITH ME.
AND THEN HE TOLD ME
HE WOULD RUN AWAY WITH ME.
AND HE DIDN'T.
AND YOU LEFT THE TOILET SEAT UP, YOU BASTARD!
IS ALL THIS TRUE?
YES.
I'M AFRAID IT IS.
YOU DESERVE MUCH BETTER THAN ME, ERIKA.
YOU DESERVE TO BE WITH THE REAL DRAKE.
HE'S THE ONE YOU FELL IN LOVE WITH.
GO TO SALEM.
FIND HIM.
HE'S THE GUY FOR YOU.
OH, HANS.
HANS?
YO, EVIL TWIN.
RIGHT.
GOOD BYE, ERIKA.
GOOD LUCK IN SALEM.
TAKE CARE.
I'LL NEVER FORGET YOU, HANS.
ALL RIGHT. THE PEOPLE WHO THREW THE WATER...
HEY, HEY, HELPING YOU OUT, HELPING YOU OUT.
FIRED?
WHY?
THE LIBRARY BOARD HAS HAD
A LOT OF COMPLAINTS FROM PARENTS
ABOUT SOME OF THE STUFF IN YOUR SONGS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
THIS IS THE LIBRARY, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, BOOKS, FREE SPEECH.
YOU KNOW, NEWSPAPERS ON STICKS.
I KNOW.
AND WHAT ABOUT THE KIDS, YOU KNOW?
DID YOU TELL YOUR "BOARD"
ABOUT HOW THE KIDS WANT TO HEAR THE TRUTH?
NO.
I SEE.
MAYBE IF YOU JUST PLAYED SOME REGULAR KIDDIE SONGS.
NO.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO BE?
LIKE SOME STUPID, BIG, LIKE, PURPLE DINOSAUR?
I'M NOT SAYING YOU HAVE TO BE BARNEY.
WHO'S BARNEY?
HEY, YOU'RE NEVER GOING TO BELIEVE THIS.
OOH, LET ME GUESS.
WHAT? WHAT? SOME WEEBLES ACTUALLY DO FALL DOWN? HUH?
A STITCH IN TIME
NOW ONLY SAVES SEVEN?
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT?
WELL...
NEVER MIND.
WHAT? WHAT?
WELL, I TRACKED DOWN MARCEL, AND GET THIS:
HE'S HEALTHY, HE'S HAPPY
AND HE'S RIGHT HERE IN NEW YORK
FILMING OUTBREAK II: THE VIRUS TAKES MANHATTAN.
YOU'RE KIDDING.
THIS IS AMAZING.
I KNOW.
I FINALLY GET A PART ON TV
AND THE MONKEY'S MAKING MOVIES.
OKAY, RACHEL, I'M READY.
OKAY.
EXCUSE ME.
IS THIS WHERE THE SINGING LADY IS
WHO TELLS THE TRUTH?
UM... YEAH, I GUESS THAT'S ME.
SHE'S HERE!
? SOMETIMES MEN LOVE WOMEN ?
? AND SOMETIMES MEN LOVE MEN ?
? AND THEN THERE ARE BISEXUALS ?
? THOUGH SOME JUST SAY THEY'RE KIDDING THEMSELVES ?
? LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA ?
? LA LA LA LA LA LA- LA LA LA LA. ?
THIS IS SO EXCITING.
I HAVEN'T SEEN MY MONKEY IN ALMOST A YEAR.
WHAT, YOU NEVER LOOK DOWN IN THE SHOWER?
OH, PLEASE.
I'M NOT ALLOWED TO MAKE ONE JOKE
IN THE MONKEY AS PENIS GENRE?
COME ON, PEOPLE, BACK UP, PLEASE.
BACK UP. COME ON, COME ON, COME ON.
EXCUSE ME. WHERE CAN WE FIND THE MONKEY?
I'M SORRY, GUYS, IT'S A CLOSED SET.
I'M SORRY.
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I'M I'M A FRIEND OF HIS.
WE, UH, WE USED TO LIVE TOGETHER.
YEAH, AND I HAVE A TIME SHARE IN THE POCONOS WITH FLIPPER.
ROSS, THERE HE IS.
HEY, BUDDY!
MARCEL!
? IN THE JUNGLE ?
? THE MIGHTY JUNGLE ?
? THE LION SLEEPS TONIGHT ?
? IN THE JUNGLE, THE MIGHTY JUNGLE ?
? A WEEM A WAY, A WEEM A WAY ?
? OOH, OOH, OOH, OOH ?
? A WEEM UM UM A WAY ?
? A WEEM A WAY ?
? OOH, OOH, OOH, OOH ?
? A WEEM A WAY. ?
UH, EXCUSE ME, FOLKS. THIS IS A...
CLOSED SET. WE KNOW.
BUT WE'RE FRIENDS WITH THE MONKEY.
GOOD MORNING.
HI, PAL. LOOK WHO I BROUGHT.
IT'S YOUR OLD FRIEND HARRY ELEPHANTAY.
WHOA, DUDE.
BURN.
I DON'T GET IT.
HE SEEMED SO HAPPY TO SEE ME YESTERDAY.
HEY, DON'T TAKE IT PERSONAL.
HE'S UNDER A LOT OF PRESSURE