HEY, JOEY. HOW'D THE AUDITION GO?
INCREDIBLE. I MET THE DIRECTOR THIS TIME.
YOU WILL NEVER BELIEVE WHO IT WAS.
WHO?
ALL RIGHT, I'LL GIVE YOU ONE HINT--
WARREN BEATTY.
WOW!
YEAH. THERE'S JUST ONE THING THAT MIGHT BE KIND OF A PROBLEM.
SEE, I, UH, I HAD TO KISS THIS GUY.
BECAUSE HE WAS JUST SO DARN CUTE?
NO. AS PART OF THE AUDITION.
SEE, I'M UP FOR THE PART OF THIS GUY WHO THE MAIN GUY KISSES.
WELL, HEY, YOU'RE AN ACTOR.
I SAY YOU JUST SUCK IT UP AND YOU DO IT.
OR YOU JUST DO IT.
I DID DO IT.
I'M A PROFESSIONAL.
BESIDES, MY FIRST GIRLFRIEND WAS LISA DeBATTISTA
SO I'M NO STRANGER TO THE MUSTACHE.
SO WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
SEE, AFTER THE SCENE, MR. BEATTY COMES UP TO ME
AND HE SAYS, "GOOD ACTOR. BAD KISSER."
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT?
ME, NOT A GOOD KISSER.
THAT'S LIKE, LIKE...
MOTHER TERESA-- NOT A GOOD MOTHER.
AW, COME ON. WHO CARES WHAT THAT GUY THINKS?
WHAT DOES WARREN BEATTY KNOW ABOUT KISSING?
OH.
?  ?
HEY, WHAT DID YOUR AGENT SAY?
YUP. THIS KISS THING IS DEFINITELY A PROBLEM.
MR. BEATTY WANTS TO SEE IT AGAIN ON MONDAY.
MAN, I GOT TO FIGURE OUT WHAT I'M DOING WRONG.
OH, OKAY, ONE OF YOU GIRLS COME OVER HERE AND KISS ME.
FORGET IT.
RIGHT.
HEY, COME ON. I NEED YOUR HELP HERE.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL DO IT.
I'VE KISSED HIM BEFORE.
I CAN DO IT AGAIN.
SEE THIS? HUH? THIS IS A FRIEND.
UH HUH. LET'S GO.
OH, WAIT. I HAVE GUM.
OH.
OKAY.
GOOD. VERY GOOD.
FIRM BUT TENDER.
I'D RECOMMEND YOU TO A FRIEND.
THEN I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS.
WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
JOEY, MAYBE YOU'RE JUST NOT USED TO KISSING MEN.
MAYBE YOU JUST TENSED UP A LITTLE BIT.
MAYBE THAT'S WHAT YOU NEED TO WORK ON.
YEAH. THAT MAKES SENSE.
OVER MY DEAD BODY.
AND I'LL BE USING HIS DEAD BODY AS A SHIELD.
COME ON OUT, HONEY.
I'M TELLING YOU, YOU LOOK GOOD.
TELL HER SHE LOOKS GOOD. TELL HER SHE LOOKS GOOD.
OH, MY GOD!
YOU LOOK SO GOOD.
I CANNOT BELIEVE I HAVE TO WALK DOWN THE AISLE
IN FRONT OF 200 PEOPLE
LOOKING LIKE SOMETHING YOU DRINK WHEN YOU'RE NAUSEOUS.
SO DON'T. I DON'T SEE WHY WE HAVE TO GO TO THIS THING ANYWAY.
IT'S YOUR EX FIANCE'S WEDDING.
BECAUSE I PROMISED MINDY I WOULD.
YEAH, WELL, YOU PROMISED BARRY
YOU'D MARRY HIM.
LOOK, YOU GUYS, I HAVE TO GO.
I'M THE MAID OF HONOR.
BESIDES, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I NEED TO BE IN A ROOM AGAIN WITH THESE PEOPLE
AND FEEL GOOD ABOUT MYSELF.
OOH... SOMEONE'S WEARING THE SAME CLOTHES
THEY HAD ON LAST NIGHT.
DID SOMEONE GET A LITTLE ACTION?
YEAH, I MAY HAVE.
WHOO HOO! STUD.
WHAT DID SHE LOOK LIKE?
WELL, WE HAVEN'T ACTUALLY MET.
WE JUST STAYED UP
ALL NIGHT TALKING ON THE INTERNET.
WHOO HOO! GEEK.
I LIKE THIS GIRL, OKAY?
I SERIOUSLY LIKE THIS GIRL.
YOU KNOW HOW SOMETIMES
I TEND TO GET A LITTLE DEFENDED AND QUIPPY?
GET OUT.
UH UH. PLEASE.
WELL, SHE TOTALLY CALLED ME ON IT, OKAY?
SHE SAID, "CUT IT OUT. GET REAL."
AND I DID.
WOW.
WHAT'S THAT LIKE?
IT'S LIKE THIS. ME.
NO JOKES.
ALL RIGHT, STOP IT.
YOU'RE FREAKING ME OUT.
OOH, YEAH. I DON'T LIKE YOU THIS WAY.
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL SEE YOU GUYS LATER.
BYE, RICHARD. BYE BYE.
BYE, SWEETIE.
I LOVE YOU.
I LOVE YOU, TOO.
"I THINK MY BOYFRIEND'S EVER SO DREAMY.
I WONDER WHAT OUR WEDDING'S GOING TO BE LIKE."
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
WHAT WEDDING?
COME ON. LIKE YOU NEVER TALK ABOUT THAT?
NO. NEVER.
WE'RE JUST LIVING IN THE MOMENT.
GOD, IT IS SO NICE, FOR ONCE
NOT TO GET ALL HUNG UP ON WHERE THIS IS GOING.
YOU AFRAID TO ASK HIM?
COULD NOT BE MORE TERRIFIED.
WELL, I THINK YOU SHOULD
SERIOUSLY CONSIDER THE MARRIAGE THING.
GIVE RACHEL ANOTHER CHANCE
TO DRESS UP LIKE PRINCESS BUBBLE YUM.
I WAS LAUGHING AT THIS QUIP
LENO MADE LAST NIGHT.
I WASN'T LAUGHING AT YOUR DRESS.
I LOVE YOU.
WHERE'S BENNY?
THERE HE IS.
AW... YOU KNOW, THAT'S PROBABLY WHY BABIES LEARN TO TALK--
SO THEY CAN TELL GROWN UPS
TO CUT IT OUT.
HEY, YOU KNOW, I GOT A QUESTION FOR YOU.
JUST A LITTLE THING, NO PRESSURE.
OKAY.
DO YOU EVER, UH, LIKE, THINK ABOUT THE FUTURE?
SURE I DO.
YEAH? AM I IN IT?
HONEY, YOU ARE IT.
OH, GOD.
YOU'RE ABOUT TO GET SO LUCKY.
YEAH?
YEAH.
KEEP TALKING.
WELL, UM, SOMETIMES I THINK ABOUT SELLING MY PRACTICE.
MM HMM.
WE COULD MOVE TO FRANCE.
MAKE FRENCH TOAST.
OOH. OKAY, SO, UM, WE'RE IN FRANCE...
MM HMM.
AND, UH, WE'RE MAKING THE TOAST...
DO YOU SEE A LITTLE BASSINET IN THE CORNER?
LIKE A HOUND?
NOT A BASSET.
A BASSINET.
YOU REALLY NEED THE BASSINET?
WELL, I JUST THINK
THE BABY WOULD KEEP FALLING OFF THE DOG.
DO YOU, UM, DO YOU NOT SEE KIDS IN OUR FUTURE?
OH... HEY, I LOVE CHILDREN.
I HAVE CHILDREN.
BUT I JUST DON'T WANT TO BE 70 WHEN OUR KIDS GO OFF TO COLLEGE
AND OUR LIFE CAN FINALLY START.
LOOK, I WANT YOU.
NOW.
WELL, THAT'S GREAT.
YOU KNOW, WE DON'T NEED TO TALK ABOUT THIS NOW.
REALLY. I MEAN, THIS IS SO, LIKE
WAY, WAY, WAY IN THE FUTURE.
I'M TALKING HOVERCRAFTS
AND APES TAKING OVER THE PLANET.
COME ON, CHANDLER.
I WANT THIS PART SO MUCH.
JUST ONE KISS.
I WON'T TELL ANYONE.
JOEY, "NO" MEANS NO.
HEY, HI.
HEY.
I'M SORRY. WE DON'T HAVE YOUR SHEEP.
OH, RACH, I THINK YOU LOOK CUTE.
AND YOU-- HUH! YOU...
YOU I COULD EAT WITH A SPOON.
GET AWAY FROM ME.
I SAID NO.
GUYS, RICHARD BUZZED-- HE'S WAITING DOWNSTAIRS.
OH, RICHARD'S HERE?
I SHOULD RUN DOWN
AND SAY GOOD BYE TO HIM.
BYE. BYE.
GOOD LUCK.
SO, HOW'S YOUR DATE WITH YOUR CYBER CHICK GOING?
OOH, HEY, WHAT IS ALL THAT?
OH, IT'S A WEB SITE.
IT'S THE GUGGENHEIM MUSEUM.
SEE, UH, SHE LIKES ART, AND... I LIKE FUNNY WORDS.
WHAT DOES SHE MEAN BY "HH"?
IT... MEANS WE'RE HOLDING HANDS.
ARE YOU THE CUTEST?
I'M AFRAID I MIGHT JUST BE.
YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK IS SO GREAT?
THAT YOU ARE TOTALLY INTO THIS PERSON
AND YET, FOR ALL YOU KNOW, SHE COULD BE, LIKE
90 YEARS OLD OR HAVE TWO HEADS, OR...
IT COULD BE A GUY.
OKAY, IT'S NOT A GUY, ALL RIGHT?
I KNOW HER.
IT COULD BE, LIKE, A BIG, GIANT GUY.
MAN, I GOT THIS CLOSE TO HIM
AND MONICA KNEED ME IN THE BACK.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WE WERE JUST WONDERING
IF CHANDLER'S GIRLFRIEND'S A GIRL.
JUST ASK HER HOW LONG SHE'S GOING TO LIVE.
WOMEN LIVE LONGER THAN MEN.
HOW DO YOU NOT FALL DOWN MORE?
OKAY, ASK HER
WHAT IS HER CURRENT METHOD OF BIRTH CONTROL.
ALL RIGHT.
"MY HUSBAND IS SLEEPING WITH HIS SECRETARY."
SHE'S MARRIED?
WELL, AT LEAST WE KNOW SHE'S A WOMAN.
I CAN'T BELIEVE SHE'S MARRIED.
OH, MAN, I'M SORRY.
THIS MUST BE REALLY TOUGH FOR YOU, HUH?
SO, I READ THIS ARTICLE THE OTHER DAY
AND IT SAYS YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO THROW RICE AT WEDDINGS
BECAUSE WHEN PIGEONS EAT RICE, IT KILLS THEM.
OH, SO THAT'S WHY YOU NEVER SEE PIGEONS IN SUSHI BARS.
SEE, WE'RE HAVING FUN.
OH, ABSOLUTELY. YEAH, YOU KNOW
I'M NOT EVEN THINKING ABOUT THAT THING
THAT WE'RE NOT GOING TO BE THINKING ABOUT.
NEITHER AM I.
HMM MM. YEAH.
HEY, THERE. ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH. WHEN I WAS IN THE BATHROOM
I SAW THE WINDOW THAT I CRAWLED OUT OF AT MY WEDDING
AND... GOD, I JUST START THINKING
I SHOULDN'T BE HERE, YOU KNOW? I SHOULDN'T.
PEOPLE ARE GOING TO BE LOOKING AT ME
AND JUDGING ME AND THINKING ABOUT THE LAST TIME.
SWEETIE, IT'S GOING TO BE OKAY, ALL RIGHT?
IT'S A WEDDING.
GENERALLY, PEOPLE FOCUS ON THE BRIDE.
GOD, I KNOW.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
ALL RIGHTY! EVERYBODY LOOK AT ME.
GOOD. ALL RIGHT.
IT'S TIME.
BRIDESMAIDS AND USHERS...
LET'S SEE TWO LINES. THANK YOU.
OKAY.
I'LL SEE YOU AFTER THE THING.
OKAY. GOOD LUCK.
THANK YOU. OKAY.
OKAY.
AH.
GOD! WHY THE HELL DIDN'T YOU TELL ME?
I'M SORRY. WHAT WAS I SUPPOSED TO DO?
STAND UP AND SHOUT, "HEY, RACHEL, YOUR BUTT IS SHOWING"?
YEAH. BETTER YOU THAN BARRY'S UNCLE.
OH, MY GOD, THIS IS SO HUMILIATING.
I THINK THE ONLY THING THAT TOPS THAT ONE
WAS WHEN I WAS IN EIGHTH GRADE
AND I HAD TO SING THE "COPACABANA"
IN FRONT OF THE ENTIRE SCHOOL.
I THINK I GOT TWO LINES INTO IT
BEFORE I RAN AND FREAKED OUT.
OH, MY GOD, MY ENTIRE LIFE'S FLASHING BEFORE MY EYES.
RACH, HEY, LOOK. I REMEMBER THAT.
IT WASN'T SO BAD.
OH, ROSS, WOULD YOU STOP?
YOU GOT ME. I'M DATING YOU.
RACHEL.
HI, MR. WEINBERG.
HI, MRS. WEINBERG.
IT'S SO WONDERFUL TO SEE YOU AGAIN, MY DEAR.
IN FACT, I HARDLY EXPECTED TO SEE SO MUCH.
YOU TOLD ME
YOU DIDN'T SEE ANYTHING.
I TELL YOU A LOT OF THINGS.
WELL, IT'S WONDERFUL
TO HAVE YOU UP AND ABOUT AGAIN, DEAR.
STAY WELL.
OKAY. NOW, THAT IS THE THIRD TIME
SOMEONE HAS SAID SOMETHING LIKE THAT TO ME TODAY.
RACH? RACH!
OH, HI.
OH, MY GOD!
I'M MARRIED!
I'M MRS. DR. BARRY HUNTER HYPHEN FARBER.
OH, HONEY. I'M SO PROUD OF YOU, MIN.
MIN?
OH, RACH. STILL HERE.
AT OUR WEDDING
THEY WERE PACKING UP THE CHOPPED LIVER
ABOUT NOW.
OH, YEAH, I LOVE THAT STORY.
UM, I HAVE A QUESTION FOR YOU GUYS.
WHY DO PEOPLE KEEP SAYING
IT'S GOOD TO SEE ME UP AND ABOUT?
WELL, UH, AFTER YOU RAN OUT ON YOUR WEDDING
BARRY'S PARENTS TOLD PEOPLE YOU WERE SORT OF... INSANE.
INSANE?
FROM THE SYPHILIS.
WHAT?!
WELL, WHAT WERE THEY GOING TO SAY?
YOU DIDN'T LOVE ME ANYMORE? COME ON.
YOUR CHOICES WERE THAT ORSYPHILIS?!
HEY, SWEETIE, AT LEAST THIS PUTS
YOUR WHOLE TUSHIE SHOW INTO PERSPECTIVE.
ANGELA?
JOEY TRIBBIANI.
LISTEN, UH, WHAT ARE YOU DOING TONIGHT?
I KNOW YOU'RE SEEING THAT GUY.
I WAS THINKING MAYBE YOU COULD BRING HIM...
HELLO? HELLO?
AH!
AREN'T YOU GOING TO ANSWER HER?
THAT'S, LIKE, THE TENTH "BING BONG" MESSAGE SHE SENT.
SHE WANTS TO KNOW WHAT'S WRONG.
WHAT'S WRONG? WHAT'S WRONG?
YOU'RE MARRIED.
THAT'S WHAT'S WRONG.
OH, MY.
WHAT?
SHE WANTS TO MEET YOU IN PERSON.
HEY, LOOK, PHOEBE, I WANTED TO MEET HER IN PERSON, TOO, OKAY?
BUT SHE'S MARRIED.
SHE HAS A HUSBAND.
WHAT IF THE HUSBAND PERSON IS THE WRONG GUY
AND YOU ARE THE RIGHT GUY?
YOU DON'T GET CHANCES LIKE THIS ALL THE TIME.
IF YOU DON'T MEET HER NOW
YOU'RE GOING TO BE KICKING YOURSELF
WHEN YOU'RE 80, WHICH IS HARD TO DO
AND THAT'S HOW YOU BREAK A HIP.
I DON'T KNOW.
LISTEN TO THAT.
THOSE ARE THE BING BONGS
OF A WOMAN IN LOVE WITH YOU.
OKAY. I'LL DO IT.
OH, YAY! OKAY, GREAT.
GO PUT ON YOUR SHOES
AND THEN MARCH OUT THERE AND MEET HER.
OH, MY GOD. NO! WAIT.
YOU HAVE TO TAKE A SHOWER, BECAUSE... EWW!
AND I'LL GET THE...
NO, YOU'VE TO... ANSWER HER.
ANSWER HER FIRST.
NO, NO. MAKE SOME COFFEE, BECAUSE IT'S TOO MUCH.
? TALL AND TAN ?
? AND YOUNG AND LOVELY... ?
OKAY. ONE MORE, PLEASE. COME ON.
I'M GOING TO GET IT IN THIS TIME. I WILL.
OKAY. LAST CHANCE.
? AND WHEN SHE PASSES, EACH ONE SHE PASSES GOES, "AH..." ?
AGAIN, I'M SORRY.
? WHEN SHE WALKS, IT'S LIKE A SAMBA ?
? SWINGS SO COOL, SWAYS SO GENTLY... ?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
MAYBE I DON'T NEED TO HAVE CHILDREN.
MAYBE I JUST THINK I DO, BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT SOCIETY--
AND BY THAT, I MEAN MY MOM--
HAS... HAS ALWAYS CONVINCED ME THAT I...
? OH, BUT I WANT HER SO BADLY... ?
I DO.
I HAVE TO HAVE CHILDREN.
I'M SORRY. I JUST DO.
YO!
CAN I HAVE YOUR ATTENTION, PLEASE?
BEST MAN MAKING A TOAST HERE.
THANK YOU.
I REMEMBER WHEN BARRY GOT HOME
FROM HIS FIRST DATE WITH RACHEL...
WHAT? YOU HIRED THE SAME BAND.
I CAN'T USE THE SAME SPEECH?
THANK YOU. THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
ANYWAY, I WISH YOU BOTH
A... A WONDERFUL LIFE TOGETHER.
AWW...
AND RACHEL...
WHAT?
NO, NO, NO-- IN ALL SERIOUSNESS
THERE'S NOT A LOT OF WOMEN
WHO WOULD HAVE HAD THE GUTS TO COME BACK HERE TONIGHT
AND EVEN FEWER WHO'D DO IT WITH THEIR ASSES
HANGING OUT!
CLASSIC!
UH, I'D LIKE TO ADD SOMETHING TO THAT.
WHAT ARE YOU ADDING? WHY ARE YOU ADDING?
IT'S OKAY. IT'S OKAY.
MOST OF YOU DON'T KNOW ME.
UH, I'M RACHEL'S BOYFRIEND...
OH, DEAR GOD.
...ROSS.
UH, AND, UH, I'D JUST LIKE TO SAY
THAT IT DID TAKE A LOT OF COURAGE
FOR RACHEL TO COME HERE TONIGHT.
AND, UH, JUST FOR THE RECORD
SHE DID NOT RUN OUT ON BARRY BECAUSE SHE HAD SYPHILIS.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'M SERIOUS.
UH, THE REASON
SHE WALKED OUT ON... ON BARRY
IS SIMPLY THAT... SHE DIDN'T LOVE HIM
WHICH, INCIDENTALLY
WORKED OUT PRETTY WELL FOR ME.
UH...
SO, TO REVIEW...
RACHEL... TOOK A LOT OF COURAGE...
DOESN'T HAVE THE SYPHILIS...
AND...
WOUND UP WITH ME.
CHEERS.
I'LL SEE YOU IN THE PARKING LOT.
NO, RACH...
AND ONCE AGAIN, SHE IS OUT OF HERE.
OKAY. WHO HAD 9:45? HMM?
HUH!
YOU KNOW WHAT, BAR?
I'M NOT GOING TO LEAVE.
I PROBABLY SHOULD, BUT I'M NOT.
SEE, BECAUSE I PROMISED MYSELF I WOULD MAKE IT THROUGH
AT LEAST ONE OF YOUR WEDDINGS.
SEE, NOW, TONIGHT, ALL I REALLY WANTED WAS TO MAKE IT
THROUGH THIS EVENING
WITH A LITTLE BIT OF GRACE AND DIGNITY.
WELL, I GUESS WE CAN ALL AGREE THAT'S NOT GOING TO HAPPEN.
I GUESS THERE'S NOTHING REALLY LEFT TO, UH, SAY...
EXCEPT, UM...
? HER NAME WAS LOLA ?
? SHE WAS A SHOW GIRL... ?
? WITH YELLOW FEA... ?
? ...FEATHERS IN HER HAIR ?
? AND A DRESS CUT DOWN TO THERE ?
? SH SHE... ?
? SHE WOULD... ?
? MERENGUE... ? ? MERENGUE... ?
THANK YOU, HONEY.
? AND DO THE CHA CHA ? ? CHA CHA ?
? AND WHILE SHE'D LIKE TO BE A STAR ?
? TONY ALWAYS TENDED BAR... ?
WAIT! WAIT!
EVERYBODY! EVERYBODY!
? AT THE COPA ?
? COPACABANA ?
? THE HOTTEST SPOT NORTH OF HAVANA ?
? AT THE COPA ?
? COPACABANA ?
? MUSIC AND PASSION WERE ALWAYS THE FASHION ?
? AT THE COPA... ?
? THERE'S A SOMEBODY I'M LONGING TO SEE... ?
OKAY.
I'LL DO IT.
YOU'LL DO WHAT?
IF KIDS IS WHAT IT TAKES TO BE WITH YOU
THEN KIDS IT IS.
OH, MY GOD.
IF I HAVE TO, I'LL I'LL DO IT ALL AGAIN.
I'LL DO THE 4:00 FEEDING THING.
I'LL GO TO THE P.T.A. MEETINGS.
I'LL COACH THE SOCCER TEAM.
REALLY?
YEAH, IF I HAVE TO.
MONICA...
I DON'T WANT TO LOSE YOU.
SO, IF I HAVE TO DO IT ALL AGAIN, THEN I WILL.
YOU ARE THE MOST WONDERFUL MAN.
AND IF YOU HADN'T HAVE SAID
"IF I HAVE TO," LIKE, 17 TIMES
THEN I'D BE SAYING, "OKAY. LET'S DO IT."
BUT YOU'RE NOT.
OH, MY GOD.
I CAN'T BELIEVE WHAT I'M GETTING READY TO SAY.
I WANT TO HAVE A BABY...
BUT I DON'T WANT TO HAVE ONE WITH SOMEONE
WHO DOESN'T REALLY WANT TO HAVE ONE.
I...
I LOVE YOU.
I KNOW YOU DO.
ME, TOO.
? WON'T YOU TELL HER, PLEASE... ?
SO, WHAT NOW?
I GUESS WE JUST...
KEEP DANCING.
? OH, HOW I NEED ?
? SOMEONE TO WATCH ?
? OVER ME. ?
WHERE IS SHE?
OH, HEY. I HAVE A QUESTION.
CHANDLER...
RELAX, CHANDLER. SHE'LL BE HERE.
OH. OH.
OH. THAT'S HER.
YEAH, BECAUSE LIFE'S JUST THAT KIND.
CHANDLER, YOU GOT
TO STOP STARING AT THE DOOR.
IT'S LIKE A WATCHED POT.
YOU KNOW, IF YOU KEEP LOOKING AT IT
THEN THE DOOR IS NEVER GOING TO BOIL.
I THINK WHAT YOU HAVE TO DO
IS TRY NOT TO...
OH, MY GOD.
OH...
MY...
GOD.
OH... MY... GOD.
ALL RIGHT, I'VE BEEN FEELING INCREDIBLY GUILTY ABOUT THIS
BECAUSE I WANT TO BE A GOOD FRIEND
AND DAMN IT, I AM A GOOD FRIEND.
SO JUST SHUT UP AND CLOSE YOUR EYES.
UH...
WOW.
YOU ARE A GOOD FRIEND.
OF COURSE
THE AUDITION WAS THIS MORNING
AND I DIDN'T GET IT.
BUT THAT WAS A HELL OF A KISS.
RACHEL IS A VERY LUCKY GIRL.