ALL RIGHT, NO PEEKING.
NO PEEKING.
NO PEEKING. NO PEEKING!
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT
BUT YOU'D BETTER BE WEARING CLOTHES WHEN I OPEN MY EYES.
ALL RIGHT. OPEN YOUR EYES.
SWEET MOTHER OF ALL THAT IS GOOD AND PURE.
DAYS OF OUR LIVES PICKED UP MY OPTION.
CONGRATULATIONS!
I KNOW.
NOW WE CAN FINALLY WATCH GREEN ACRES
THE WAY IT WAS MEANT TO BE SEEN.
SO, UH... WHICH ONE IS MINE?
WHICHEVER ONE YOU WANT, MAN.
WHICHEVER ONE YOU WANT.
NOT THAT ONE.
OH, YES.
OH, YEAH, THAT'S THE STUFF.
DO WE DARE?
WE DARE.
AH... AH...
AH... AH... AH... AH...
I CAN'T BELIEVE
TWO COWS MADE THE ULTIMATE SACRIFICE
SO YOU GUYS COULD WATCH TV WITH YOUR FEET UP.
THEY WERE CHAIR SHAPED COWS.
THEY NEVER WOULD HAVE SURVIVED IN THE WILD.
THAT SCREEN IS AMAZING.
DICK VAN DYKE IS PRACTICALLY LIFE SIZE.
ROSE MARIE REALLY BELONGS ON A SMALLER SCREEN, DOESN'T SHE?
HI, YOU GUYS.
HEY.
HEY, YOU.
HEY, YO. WHOA, HEY.
SO, UH, HOW WAS YOUR DAY?
OH, YOU KNOW, PRETTY MUCH THE USUAL.
SUN SHINING, BIRDS CHIRPING.
REALLY? MINE, TOO.
HEY, COOL, MINE, TOO.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
I GOT TO GET TO THE MUSEUM.
SO, UM... I'LL SEE YOU TONIGHT?
OKAY.
OH.
BYE, GUYS.
BYE.
TONIGHT?
HEY, YO, HEY, YO.
WHAT'S TONIGHT?
IT IS OUR FIRST OFFICIAL DATE.
OUR FIRST DATE.
HELLO?
HI.
TONIGHT YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO WAITRESS FOR ME.
MY CATERING THING?
ANY OF THOSE WORDS TRIGGER ANYTHING FOR YOU?
GOD, OH, GOD, MONICA, I FORGOT.
THIS IS OUR FIRST DATE.
YES, BUT MY MOM GOT ME THIS JOB.
I CAN BE A WAITRESS. I CAN BE A WAITRESS.
THANK YOU, THANK YOU, THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
SEE, PHOEBE, PHOEBE?
REALLY, PHEEBS?
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, YOU'D HAVE TO BE AN ACTUAL WAITRESS.
THIS CAN'T BE LIKE YOUR "I CAN BE A BEAR CUB" THING.
I CAN BE A WAITRESS.
OKAY, WATCH THIS.
GIVE ME TWO NUMBER ONES, 86 THE BACON
ONE ADAM AND EVE ON A RAFT AND WRECK THEM.
? LA LA LA LA LA, LA LA LA LA LA... ?
IT'S JAMES BOND.
SORRY WE'RE LATE.
THAT'S OKAY. COME ON IN.
I'M SORRY, IS MONICA GELLER COMING?
I WAS TOLD SHE WAS.
DR. BURKE, IT'S ME.
MONICA?
MY GOD!
YOU USED TO BE SO...
I MEAN, YOU... YOU MUST HAVE LOST, LIKE...
YOU LOOK GREAT.
THANK YOU.
THIS IS MY FRIEND PHOEBE.
SHE'S GOING TO BE HELPING ME TONIGHT.
HI, PHOEBE. NICE TO MEET YOU.
SO HOW'VE YOU BEEN?
I'VE BEEN GREAT. JUST GREAT.
HOW'VE YOU BEEN?
OH, WELL, OBVIOUSLY, BARBARA AND I SPLIT UP
OTHERWISE, YOU WOULDN'T HAVE DONE THE HEAD TILT.
THE HEAD TILT?
YEAH. SINCE THE DIVORCE, WHEN ANYBODY ASKS ME HOW I AM
IT'S ALWAYS WITH A SYMPATHETIC HEAD TILT.
"HOW YOU DOING? YOU OKAY?"
I'M SORRY.
NO, NO. IT'S FINE.
BELIEVE ME, I DO IT, TOO.
I ALWAYS ANSWER WITH THE "I'M OKAY" HEAD BOB.
"I'M OKAY."
"YOU SURE?"
"YEAH, I'M FINE."
HEY, LISTEN, I GOT TO SET UP THE MUSIC.
I GOT A NEW CD CHANGER.
OF COURSE THE DIVORCE ONLY LEFT ME WITH FOUR CDs TO CHANGE.
OH.
THAT'S TOO BAD.
I'LL SURVIVE.
...to the reverse.
UH, TWO LARGES.
EXTRA CHEESE ON BOTH.
BUT LISTEN, DON'T RING THE BUZZER FOR 19.
RING 20-- GELLER/GREEN.
THEY'LL LET YOU IN, OKAY?
IF YOU BUZZ OUR DOOR, THERE'S NO TIP FOR YOU.
OKAY, THANKS.
PIZZA'S ON THE WAY.
I TOLD YOU WE WOULDN'T HAVE TO GET UP.
WHAT IF WE HAVE TO PEE?
I'LL CANCEL THE SODAS.
YOU'VE GOT TO GET BACK OUT THERE.
IT'S YOUR PARTY.
BUT THEY'RE SO DULL.
THEY'RE ALL OPHTHALMOLOGISTS.
YOU'RE AN OPHTHALMOLOGIST.
ONLY BECAUSE MY PARENTS WANTED ME TO BE.
I WANTED TO BE A SHERIFF.
THAT'S FUNNY.
CADILLAC-- CATARACT.
I GET IT. NO, I GET IT.
YOU STAY OUT THERE!
YOU SEE?
ALL RIGHT, I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
I'LL COME GET YOU IN FIVE MINUTES
WITH SOME SORT OF, UM... KABOB EMERGENCY.
OKAY.
OH... YOU BETTER.
OH, GOD, HERE WE GO.
HEY, WANT TO SEE THEM GO NUTS?
WATCH THIS.
WHO NEEDS GLASSES?
YOU ARE SO SMITTEN.
I AM NOT.
OH, YOU ARE SO MUCH THE SMITTEN KITTEN.
YOU SHOULD ASK HIM OUT.
DR. BURKE? I DON'T THINK SO.
I MEAN, LIKE, HE'S A GROWNUP.
SO?
YOU TWO ARE TOTALLY INTO EACH OTHER.
PHOEBE, HE'S A FRIEND OF MY PARENTS'.
HE'S, LIKE, 20 YEARS OLDER THAN ME.
OKAY, SO WHAT, YOU'RE JUST NEVER GOING TO SEE HIM AGAIN?
NOT NEVER.
I MEAN, I'M GOING TO SEE HIM TOMORROW AT MY EYE APPOINTMENT.
DIDN'T YOU, LIKE, JUST GET YOUR EYES CHECKED?
WELL, YEAH, BUT, YOU KNOW, 27 IS A... DANGEROUS EYE AGE.
THEY'RE PICKING TEAMS TO PLAY "GUESS MY PRESCRIPTION."
HELP ME!
COME ON, I'M NOT SAYING IT WAS A BAD MOVIE.
I'M JUST SAYING, YOU KNOW, IT WAS A LITTLE...
HARD TO FOLLOW.
I TOLD YOU THERE WERE GOING TO BE SUBTITLES.
I KNOW.
I JUST DIDN'T WANT TO WEAR MY GLASSES ON OUR FIRST DATE.
OH.
MONICA?
IT WOULD REALLY HELP WHEN I'M KISSING YOU
IF YOU DIDN'T SHOUT OUT MY SISTER'S NAME.
HONEY, I'M JUST CHECKING.
OH. MONICA?
MON?
MONICA? MON?
MONICA?
WHAT?
I'M SORRY. OH, GOD, I'M SORRY.
IT'S JUST THAT WHEN YOU MOVED YOUR HANDS DOWN TO MY BUTT
IT WAS LIKE, "WHOA, ROSS'S HANDS ARE ON MY BUTT."
SORRY.
AND THAT'S, THAT'S FUNNY... WHY?
WELL, IT'S NOT.
I... I MEAN, I'M SORRY.
I GUESS I'M JUST NERVOUS.
I MEAN, IT'S YOU.
YOU KNOW, IT'S US.
I MEAN, WE'RE CROSSING THAT LINE.
IT'S SORT OF A BIG THING.
WELL, I KNOW IT'S BIG.
I JUST DIDN'T KNOW IT WAS... HA HA BIG.
OKAY.
OKAY, MY HANDS WERE NOWHERE NEAR YOUR BUTT.
I KNOW, I KNOW, I KNOW, I KNOW.
I WAS JUST THINKING ABOUT WHEN THEY WERE THERE
THE LAST TIME, I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY, I'M SORRY.
OKAY, LOOK, WHOA. I PROMISE
I'M GOOD, I'M NOT GOING TO LAUGH ANYMORE.
OKAY, PUT YOUR HANDS BACK ON.
NO. SEE, NOW, NOW I CAN'T BECAUSE, UH...
I'M FEELING TOO SELF CONSCIOUS.
COME ON, TOUCH MY BUTT.
NO.
JUST ONE CHEEK.
THE MOMENT'S GONE.
PUT YOUR HANDS OUT, AND I'LL BACK UP INTO THEM.
THAT'S ROMANTIC.
COME ON, TOUCH IT.   NO.
OH, COME ON, SQUEEZE IT. NO.
RUB IT? NO.
OH, COME ON, WOULD YOU JUST GRAB MY ASS?!
WOW, LOOK AT THAT.
THE CAR IS ON FIRE
YET SOMEHOW, ITS EXPENSIVE PAINT JOB
IS PROTECTED BY THE MIRACLE WAX.
YOU KNOW?
YOU GOT A CHEETO ON YOUR FACE, MAN.
THANKS.
HEY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
AREN'T YOU SUPPOSED TO BE OUT WITH RACHEL?
THAT WAS 14 HOURS AGO.
WHOA, WE GOT TO SET THE CLOCK ON THIS THING.
SO HOW'D IT GO?
OH... LISTEN, HAVE YOU EVER BEEN
YOU KNOW, FOOLING AROUND WITH A GIRL
AND, UH... SHE STARTED LAUGHING?
YEAH, BUT, UH, IT WAS 1982
AND MY FLOCK OF SEAGULLS HAIRCUT
WAS TICKLING HER CHIN.
SHE LAUGHED AT YOU?
YEAH. IT COULD HAVE BEEN WORSE.
I COULD HAVE BEEN NAKED.
I'VE JUST... I'VE WAITED...
I'VE BEEN WANTING THIS SINCE, LIKE, NINTH GRADE TYPING
AND I JUST WANT IT TO BE PERFECT AND... RIGHT AND...
WHY ISN'T THAT LASER BEAM CUTTING THROUGH THE PAINT?
IT'S THE MIRACLE WAX.
IT CERTAINLY IS A MIRACLE.
HI, YOU GUYS.
HEY. HEY.
HEY.
HI. LISTEN, I WAS, UM, THINKING ABOUT...
CAN YOU GUYS SPEAK UP?
IT'S HARDER FOR US TO HEAR YOU
WHEN YOU LOWER YOUR VOICE.
HALLWAY?
YEAH.
OKAY, LISTEN, I'M SORRY ABOUT LAST NIGHT
AND I REALLY WANT TO MAKE IT UP TO YOU.
NO. YOU... YOU KNOW, THERE'S NO NEED TO MAKE IT... HOW?
WELL, I WAS THINKING MAYBE A, UM...
...A ROMANTIC DINNER WITH, UM, CANDLES AND WINE
AND THEN, UM, MAYBE GOING BACK TO MY PLACE FOR, UM...
DESSERT.
HMM. THAT SOUNDS... I DON'T KNOW... PERFECT.
WHAT'S THIS?
CAN YOU GET US A COUPLE OF BEERS?
I'M GOING TO LOOK INTO YOUR EYES NOW.
REALLY?
YEAH. THAT'S MY JOB.
ALL RIGHT.
LOOK UP.
LOOK DOWN.
NOW OPEN YOUR EYES AND LOOK DOWN.
THAT'S RIGHT.
LOOK INTO THE LIGHT.
NOW LOOK AT ME.
OKAY.
YOUR EYES LOOK GOOD.
THOSE ARE GOOD EYES.
GOOD. THEY FEEL GOOD.
IN MY HEAD.
OH. UH...
SO...
IT'S GREAT TO SEE YOU.
YOU, TOO.
OKAY. UM...
GOOD BYE.
DROPS.
WHAT?
DROPS. HERE. THEY'RE FREE.
THANKS.
SO, I GUESS I'D BETTER BE GOING.
OH, OKAY. YEAH. I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
OH, THANKS AGAIN.
OH, UH...
WE HAVE GOT TO GET YOU LAZY BOYS OUT OF THESE CHAIRS.
HEY, WHOA, HEY, WHOA!
OH, OH, OH. YOU KNOW, YOU SHOULD GO OUTSIDE
AND BE WITH THE THREE DIMENSIONAL PEOPLE.
NO.
INSIDE GOOD.
OUTSIDE BAD.
YOU GUYS ARE SO PATHETIC.
OH! OH,XANADU!
OH! OH!
SHE'S ONE OF US NOW.
HI, YOU GUYS.
HEY.
HEY. HEY.
WELL, WE JUST WANTED TO STOP BY AND, UH, SAY GOOD NIGHT.
GOOD NIGHT.
LOOK AT THAT. THEY WON'T EVEN TURN THEIR HEADS.
ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS, I'M TAKING OFF MY SHIRT.
NAH, SHE'S LYING.
STOP SENDING FOOD TO OUR APARTMENT.
WHY ARE YOU ALL DRESSED UP?
YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE WHO HAS A DATE TONIGHT.
WELL, YOU HAVE A DATE? WHO WITH?
NO ONE.
COME ON, WHAT'S HIS NAME?
NOTHING.
COME ON, TELL ME.
ALL RIGHT, BUT I'M VERY EXCITED ABOUT THIS, OKAY?
SO YOU GOT TO PROMISE YOU WON'T GET
ALL BIG BROTHERY AND JUDGMENTAL.
I PROMISE. WHAT?
IT'S RICHARD BURKE.
WHO'S RICHARD BURKE?
DOC..? DR. BURKE?
YOU HAVE A DATE WITH DR. BURKE?
WHY? WHY? WHY... SHOULD THAT BOTHER ME?
I I LOVE THAT MAN.
HE'S LIKE A... A BROTHER TO DAD.
OH.
HERE WE GO.
WHAT? NO, I THINK IT'S GREAT THAT HE'S, LIKE, 50.
I MEAN, HE'LL BE AN INSPIRATION TO MEN WHO ARE ALMOST RETIRED
ALL OVER THE WORLD.
WELL, FOR YOUR INFORMATION
HE HAPPENS TO BE ONE OF THE BRIGHTEST
MOST SOPHISTICATED, SEXIEST MEN I'VE EVER BEEN WITH.
DR. BURKE IS SEXY?
OH, GOD. ABSOLUTELY.
DAMN.
IT'S THE MUSEUM AGAIN.
CAN I..? OH.
YOU KNOW, DR. BURKE KISSED ME ONCE.
WHEN?
WHEN I WAS SEVEN, I CRASHED MY BIKE
RIGHT OUT IN FRONT OF HIS HOUSE
AND TO STOP ME FROM CRYING, HE KISSED ME
RIGHT HERE.
OH, YOU ARE SO LUCKY.
I KNOW.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
AUSTRALOPITHECUS ISN'T SUPPOSED TO BE IN THAT DISPLAY. NO.
NO. NO. NO.
HOMO HABILIS WAS ERECT.
AUSTRALOPITHECUS WAS NEVER FULLY ERECT.
WELL, MAYBE HE WAS NERVOUS.
LOOK. I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS. LOOK...
HOMO HABILIS HASN'T EVEN LEARNED HOW TO USE TOOLS YET
AND THEY'VE GOT HIM HERE WITH CLAY POTS?
WHY DON'T THEY JUST GIVE HIM A MICROWAVE?
WELL, CLEARLY, HONEY
HE'D HAVE NO PLACE TO PLUG IT IN.
SORRY.
I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY THIS IS TAKING SO LONG.
YOU KNOW, I, I... IT'S LONGER THAN I EXPECTED.
WE WILL HAVE DINNER, OKAY?
IT'S OKAY. IT'S FINE.
CARL?
OH, WOW, IS THAT MICHELLE?
YEP.
I'VE NOT SEEN HER SINCE HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATION.
OH, MY GOD, THAT NIGHT SHE GOT SO DRUN...
...MOTIONAL.
YOU KNOW, SHE'S HAVING ANOTHER BABY.
I THOUGHT SHE JUST HAD ONE.
NO, NO. HENRY'S ALMOST TWO.
HE'S TALKING AND EVERYTHING.
HERE.
AW...
YOU KNOW, THE OTHER DAY HE TOLD ME HE LIKED ME BETTER
THAN HIS OTHER GRANDPA.
NOW, IN ALL FAIRNESS
HIS OTHER GRANDPA'S A DRUNK, BUT STILL...
OH. YOU'RE A GRANDPA?
YEAH.
ARE WE NUTS HERE?
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE.
I MEAN, I'M DATING A MAN WHOSE POOL I ONCE PEED IN.
I DIDN'T NEED TO KNOW THAT.
I GUESS 21 YEARS IS A LOT.
I MEAN, HELL, I'M A...
WHOLE PERSON WHO CAN DRINK OLDER THAN YOU.
YEAH.
SO...
SO, MAYBE WE SHOULD JUST...
YEAH.
YEAH, MAYBE.
WOW.
THIS REALLY SUCKS.
YEAH. IT SURE DOES.
AH...
WELL, WE DON'T REALLY HAVE TO DECIDE ANYTHING RIGHT NOW, DO WE?
NO. NO, THERE'S NO RUSH OR ANYTHING.
PIZZA DELIVERY!
OH, I'M GOING TO KILL THOSE GUYS.
RACH?
OH!
I'M DONE.
YEAH, WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT?
SO IS SORRENTINO'S.
OKAY. I'M SORRY.
LET'S... WHY DON'T WE FIND SOMEPLACE ELSE?
YOU KNOW WHAT, IT'S LATE. EVERYTHING'S GONNA CLOSED.
WHY DON'T WE DO IT ANOTHER NIGHT?
NO. NO, WE WON'T.
WE WON'T?
COME ON.
OKAY, THAT'S DEAD, RIGHT?
WHAT IS THIS?
WHAT ARE WE DOING?
SHH. DO YOU WANT CRAN APPLE OR CRAN GRAPE?
GRAPE.
OKAY, NOW... SIT.
OKAY.
OH, GOD.
Billions of years ago, the Earth was born...
SORRY.
OKAY.
UH... SO, WHAT ARE WE LOOKING AT?
WELL, YOU SEE THAT...
THAT LITTLE CLUSTER OF STARS NEXT TO THE BIG ONE?
THAT IS URSA MAJOR.
REALLY?
NO IDEA.
COULD BE, COULD BE.
LISTEN, I'M SORRY I HAD TO WORK TONIGHT.
OH, THAT'S OKAY.
YOU WERE WORTH THE WAIT.
AND I DON'T JUST MEAN TONIGHT.
OOH...
YOU'RE NOT LAUGHING.
? I NEVER DREAMED... ?
THIS TIME IT'S NOT SO FUNNY.
? ....THAT I'D MEET SOMEBODY LIKE YOU ?
? NO, I... WANNA FALL IN LOVE ?
? NO, I... ?
OKAY, LOOSEN THE KNOT.
LOOSEN THE KNOT.
SORRY, SORRY.
? WHAT A WICKED GAME WE PLAY... ?
OH, GOD!
OH...
HONEY?
OH, THAT'S OKAY.
WHAT?
OH, NO. YOU JUST ROLLED OVER THE JUICE BOX.
? NO, I WANNA FALL IN LOVE ?
OH, THANK GOD.
? NO, I... WANNA FALL IN LOVE... ?
UH...
HI.
HEY, YOU.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M WAKING UP NEXT TO YOU.
I KNOW, IT IS PRETTY UNBELIEVABLE...
WHAT?
WE'RE NOT ALONE.
Yeah.
IS THAT THE FIRE ALARM?
YEAH.
OH, IT'S NOT WARM YET.
WE STILL HAVE TIME.
COOL.