ROSS KISSED ME.
NO!
OH, MY GOD, OH, MY GOD, OH, MY GOD!
IT WAS UNBELIEVABLE.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
WE WANT TO HEAR EVERYTHING.
MONICA, GET THE WINE AND UNPLUG THE PHONE.
RACHEL, DOES THIS END WELL
OR DO WE NEED TO GET TISSUES?
OH, IT ENDED VERY WELL.
OH...
DO NOT START WITHOUT ME.
DO NOT START WITHOUT ME!
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
LET'S HEAR ABOUT THE KISS.
WAS IT LIKE, WAS IT LIKE A SOFT BRUSH AGAINST YOUR LIPS
OR WAS IT LIKE A, YOU KNOW
"I GOT TO HAVE YOU NOW" KIND OF THING?
WELL, AT FIRST, IT WAS REALLY INTENSE, YOU KNOW
AND THEN... OH, GOD.
AND THEN WE JUST SORT OF SUNK INTO IT.
SO, OKAY, WAS HE HOLDING YOU
OR WAS HIS HANDS, LIKE, ON YOUR BACK?
NO, ACTUALLY, FIRST
THEY STARTED ON MY WAIST
AND THEN, THEY SLID UP, AND THEN, THEY WERE IN MY HAIR.
OH.
AND, UH... AND THEN I KISSED HER.
TONGUE?
YEAH.
COOL.
ALL RIGHT, CHECK OUT THIS BAD BOY.
12 MEGABYTES OF RAM.
500 MEGABYTE HARD DRIVE.
BUILT IN SPREADSHEET CAPABILITIES
AND A MODEM THAT TRANSMITS AT OVER 28,000 B.P.S.
WOW. WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO USE IT FOR?
GAMES AND STUFF.
THERE ARE NO JOBS.
THERE ARE NO JOBS FOR ME.
WAIT, HERE'S ONE.
UH... WOULD YOU BE WILLING TO COOK NAKED?
THERE'S AN AD FOR A NAKED CHEF?
NO, BUT IF YOU'RE WILLING TO COOK NAKED
THEN YOU MIGHT BE WILLING TO DANCE NAKED
AND THEN...
HI.
HEY. OH, SO, UH...
HOW'D YOU MAKE OUT LAST NIGHT?
THAT THAT IS FUNNY.
THAT IS PAINFULLY FUNNY.
NO, WAIT. WAIT.
YEAH, THAT'S JUST PAINFUL.
WAIT A MINUTE.
I THOUGHT LAST NIGHT WAS GREAT.
YEAH, IT WAS, BUT...
I GET HOME, OKAY?
AND I SEE JULIE'S SALINE SOLUTION
ON MY NIGHT TABLE
AND I'M THINKING TO MYSELF
"OH, MY GOD, WHAT THE HELL AM I DOING?"
HERE I AM, I'M WITH JULIE, THIS INCREDIBLE, GREAT WOMAN
WHO I CARE ABOUT, AND WHO CARES ABOUT ME
AND I'M, LIKE, "WHAT, AM I JUST GOING
TO THROW ALL THAT AWAY?"
YOU GOT ALL THAT FROM SALINE SOLUTION?
I'M THE SAME WAY.
SHOW ME A BOTTLE OF VISINE
AND I AM, LIKE, WHOA, WHO AM I?
WAIT A MINUTE.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT RACHEL HERE.
YOU AND RACHEL.
BELIEVE ME, I'VE BEEN DREAMING ABOUT ME AND RACHEL
FOR, LIKE, TEN YEARS NOW, BUT NOW I'M WITH JULIE
SO IT'S, LIKE, ME AND JULIE, ME AND RACHEL, ME AND JULIE.
ME AND RACH...
RACHEL, RACHEL.
HEY, YOU.
HOW ARE YOU?
GOOD. HOW ARE YOU?
GOOD. I'M...
HI, HONEY.
HI, JULIE. HI... JULIE.
JULIE.
UM... HOW ARE YOU?
GOOD.
SO EVERYBODY'S HERE.
EVERYBODY'S GOOD.
GOOD, AND GREAT IN HERE.
SO, WERE YOU GOING TO PLAY SOMETHING, PHOEBE?
WELL, ACTUALLY...
PLAY IT.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
HEY, JULIE, I DIDN'T KNOW YOU WORE LENSES.
WHAT? SHH!
OKAY, UM... HI.
HELLO.
HI. OKAY.
SO, UM...
THIS IS A SONG, UM... ABOUT A LOVE TRIANGLE
BETWEEN THREE PEOPLE THAT I MADE UP.
UM... IT'S CALLED "TWO OF THEM KISSED LAST NIGHT."
? THERE WAS A GIRL ?
? WE'LL CALL HER BETTY ?
? AND A GUY, LET'S CALL HIM NEAL ?
? NOW... ?
? I CAN'T STRESS THIS POINT TOO STRONGLY ?
? THIS STORY ISN'T REAL... ?
? NOW OUR NEAL MUST DECIDE ?
? WHO WILL BE THE GIRL THAT HE CASTS ASIDE ?
? WILL BETTY BE THE ONE WHO HE LOVES TRULY ?
? OR WILL IT BE THE ONE WHO WE'LL CALL... LOOLIE? ?
? HE MUST DECIDE ?
? EVEN THOUGH I MADE HIM UP ?
? HE MUST DECIDE... ?
WELL, THIS IS A NICE RESUME.
NICE, NICE, NICE.
MUY IMPRESSIVO.
SHAME NONE OF IT'S TRUE.
I'M KIDDING. I'M KIDDING.
NO, IT'S ALL TRUE.
JUST A LITTLE NERVOUS, THAT'S ALL.
I'M FINE NOW.
SO, MR. RASTATTER, WHAT EXACTLY DOES THIS JOB ENTAIL?
THE AD WASN'T TOO CLEAR.
MOCKOLATE.
I'M SORRY?
IT'S A COMPLETELY SYNTHETIC CHOCOLATE SUBSTITUTE.
OOH!
WELL, GO AHEAD.
TRY A PIECE.
YEAH, WE THINK MOCKOLATE IS EVEN BETTER THAN CHOCOLATE.
ALL RIGHT.
MMM MMM.
YEAH?
I LOVE HOW IT CRUMBLES.
NOW, SEE, YOUR CHOCOLATE DOESN'T DO THAT.
NO, MA'AM.
WELL, ANYHOO
WE SHOULD BE GETTING OUR F.D.A. APPROVAL ANY DAY NOW.
HOPEFULLY, IN TIME FOR THANKSGIVING.
SEE, THE WAY WE LOOK AT IT, CHOCOLATE ALREADY DOMINATES
MOST OF YOUR MAJOR FOOD PREPARATION HOLIDAYS--
EASTER, CHRISTMAS, WHAT HAVE YOU.
MM HMM.
BUT... WE'RE THINKING, GIVEN THE RIGHT MARKETING
WE CAN MAKE THANKSGIVING THE MOCKOLATE HOLIDAY.
WOW.
AREN'T YOU GOING TO SWALLOW THAT?
JUST WAITING FOR IT TO STOP BUBBLING.
YEAH.
ISN'T THAT GREAT?
MMM.
WELL, ANYHOO, UH... WE'RE LOOKING FOR A COUPLE OF CHEFS
WHO CAN CREATE SOME THANKSGIVING THEMED RECIPES.
YOU THINK YOU MIGHT BE INTERESTED?
ABSO...
...LUTELY.
SEE, I LOVE CREATING NEW RECIPES.
I LOVE THANKSGIVING
AND, WELL, NOW...
I LOVE MOCKOLATE.
REALLY?
ESPECIALLY THAT AFTER TASTE.
I TELL YOU, THAT'LL LAST YOU TILL CHRISTMAS.
HOW ABOUT MOCKOLATE MOUSSE?
IT'S NOT...
IT'S NOT VERY THANKSGIVING Y.
OKAY. HOW ABOUT PILGRIM MOCKOLATE MOUSSE?
WHAT MAKES IT PILGRIM?
WE'LL PUT BUCKLES ON IT.
HEY.
HEY. HEY.
DID, UH... ROSS CALL?
NO. I'M SORRY.
WHY DIDN'T HE CALL?
HE'S GOING TO STAY WITH JULIE, ISN'T HE?
HE'S GOING TO STAY WITH HER AND SHE'S GOING TO BE ALL
"HI. I'M JULIE.
"ROSS PICKED ME
"AND WE'RE GOING TO GET MARRIED
AND HAVE LOTS OF KIDS, AND DIG UP STUFF TOGETHER."
NO OFFENSE, BUT THAT SOUNDS NOTHING LIKE HER.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M GOING TO DO
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?
I MEAN, THIS IS, LIKE, A COMPLETE NIGHTMARE.
OH, I KNOW, THIS MUST BE SO HARD.
"OH, NO. TWO WOMEN LOVE ME.
"THEY'RE BOTH GORGEOUS AND SEXY.
"MY WALLET'S TOO SMALL FOR MY 50s
AND MY DIAMOND SHOES ARE TOO TIGHT."
HEY, HERE'S A THOUGHT, ROSS.
DON'T TOUCH THE COMPUTER.
DON'T EVER TOUCH THE COMPUTER.
ROSS, LISTEN.
I GOT TWO WORDS FOR YOU.
THREESOME.
YOU STILL HAVE ANOTHER WORD
IF YOU WANT TO USE IT.
OH, HEY, I... I THINK I KNOW WHAT IT IS-- "HELP."
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
LOOK, LET'S GET LOGICAL ABOUT THIS. OKAY?
WE'LL MAKE A LIST--
RACHEL AND JULIE, PROS AND CONS.
OH!
OH.
WE'LL PUT THEIR NAMES IN BOLD
WITH DIFFERENT FONTS
AND I CAN USE DIFFERENT COLORS FOR EACH COLUMN.
CAN'T WE JUST USE A PEN?
NO, AMISH BOY.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S, UH...
LET'S START WITH THE CONS, BECAUSE THEY'RE MORE FUN.
RACHEL FIRST.
I DON'T KNOW.
I MEAN...
ALL RIGHT, I GUESS YOU CAN SAY SHE'S...
SHE'S A LITTLE SPOILED SOMETIMES.
YOU COULD SAY THAT.
I GUESS, YOU KNOW
SOMETIMES, SHE'S A LITTLE DITZY
AND I'VE SEEN HER BE A LITTLE TOO INTO HER LOOKS.
OH, AND LIKE, JULIE AND I, WE HAVE A LOT IN COMMON
BECAUSE WE'RE BOTH PALEONTOLOGISTS, RIGHT?
BUT RACHEL'S JUST A WAITRESS.
WAITRESS.
GOT IT. YOU GUYS WANT TO PLAY DOOM?
OR WE COULD KEEP DOING THIS.
WHAT ELSE?
I DON'T KNOW.
UH...
OH, HER ANKLES ARE A LITTLE CHUBBY.
OKAY.
LET'S DO JULIE.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH HER?
SHE'S NOT RACHEL.
OKAY, THIS IS PUMPKIN PIE
WITH A MOCKOLATE COOKIE CRUMB CRUST.
THIS IS MOCKOLATE CRANBERRY CAKE, AND THESE ARE
MOCKOLATE CHIP COOKIES, JUST LIKE
THE INDIANS SERVED.
OH, MY GOD!
"OH, MY GOD" GOOD?
OH, MY GOD, I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU LET ME PUT THIS
IN MY MOUTH.
OH! OH! SWEET LORD!
THIS IS WHAT EVIL MUST TASTE LIKE.
I'M TELLING YOU, THIS THING WON'T PRINT.
YES, I PRESSED THAT BUTTON, LIKE, A HUNDRED TIMES.
YOU KNOW, FOR A HOT LINE, YOU'RE NOT SO HOT.
WHAT...
WHAT IS THAT IN THE BACKGROUND?
ARE YOU WATCHING STAR TREK?!
HEY.
SO HOW'D IT GO WITH JULIE?
DID YOU-- DID YOU BREAK HER HEART?
YES.
IT WAS HORRIBLE.
SHE CRIED, I CRIED.
SHE THREW THINGS, THEY HIT ME.
HMM.
ANYWAY...
I DID THE RIGHT THING.
SO, SPOCK ACTUALLY HUGS HIS FATHER?
HEY, DO YOU GUYS HAVE...?
HI.
WHERE YOU GOING?
I, UH, I JUST GOT BACK
FROM, UH... FROM JULIE'S.
OH.
NO, NO, UH... IT'S NOT WHAT YOU THINK.
IT'S... UM, IT'S THE OTHER THING.
WELL... WHAT'S THE OTHER THING?
WHAT DO I THINK?
WELL, UH...
HE BROKE UP WITH JULIE.
WELL, GO HUG HER, FOR GOD SAKES.
REALLY?
REALLY.
IT'S ALWAYS BEEN YOU, RACH.
OH, GOD...
OH... OH...
OH...
OH, THIS IS GOOD, THIS IS REALLY GOOD.
I KNOW, I KNOW.
IT'S... IT'S ALMOST...
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE GO TAKE A WALK-- JUST US, NOT THEM?
OKAY. LET ME GET MY COAT.
NO-- HEY! I'LL GET YOUR COAT.
OKAY.
HE'S GOING TO GET MY COAT.
HE'S GOING TO GET MY COAT!
OH, MY GOD, YOU GUYS, I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS!
THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE!
WHAT'S THAT?
WHAT?! NOTHING!
WHAT IS THAT?
I SAW MY NAME. WHAT IS IT?
NO, NO. SEE? SEE?
HEY, IT'S PRINTING.
HEY, IT'S PRINTING!
WELL, WHAT IS IT?
LET ME SEE.
HEY, SOMEONE ORDER A COAT?
CHANDLER WROTE SOMETHING
ABOUT ME ON HIS COMPUTER
AND HE WON'T LET ME SEE.
HE WON'T... HE WON'T?
HE...
BECAUSE ISN'T THAT, ISN'T THAT THE... THE SHORT STORY
YOU WERE WRITING?
YES, YES, IT IS THE SHORT STORY...
THAT I WAS WRITING.
AND I'M IN IT? WELL, LET ME READ IT!
NO. NO. NO.
COME ON!
HEY, UH, WHY DON'T YOU READ IT TO HER?
ALL RIGHT.
"IT WAS SUMMER...
"AND IT WAS HOT.
RACHEL WAS THERE."
HUH?
"A LONELY GRAY COUCH.
"'OH, LOOK,' CRIED NED.
AND THEN THE KINGDOM WAS HIS FOREVER. THE END."
THAT'S IT? THAT'S ALL YOU WROTE?
YOU'RE THE WORST WRITER IN THE WHOLE WORLD!
ALL RIGHT, YOU KNOW WHAT?
THIS ISN'T FUNNY ANYMORE.
THERE'S SOMETHING ABOUT ME ON THAT PIECE OF PAPER
AND I WANT TO SEE IT.
NO, YOU DON'T.
ALL RIGHT, YOU KNOW WHAT? FINE.
IF YOU GUYS WANT TO BE CHILDREN
ABOUT THIS, THAT'S FINE.
I DO NOT NEED... TO SEE IT!
GO, GO, GO!
OOH!
WHAT IS THIS?
THAT IS...
THAT'S, THAT'S...
UH...
ROSS, WHAT IS THIS?
THANK YOU.
GOOD LUCK.
OKAY... JUST REMEMBER HOW CRAZY I AM ABOUT YOU, OKAY?
"KIND OF DITZY"?
"TOO INTO HER LOOKS"?
"SPOILED"?
NOW, THAT'S "A LITTLE SPOILED."
HE WAS SUPPOSED TO TYPE "LITTLE", THE IDIOT.
"JUST A WAITRESS"?
NOW, THAT... THAT WAS, UH...
I MEAN, AS OPPOSED TO, UH...
THE, UH...
OKAY, IS THIS OVER YET?
RACH?
OH! I DO NOT HAVE CHUBBY ANKLES.
NO, I...
NO, NO, RACH!
OKAY, LOOK AT THE OTHER SIDE.
LOOK AT JULIE'S COLUMN.
"SHE'S NOT RACHEM"?
NO...
WHAT THE HELL'S A RACHEM?
IS THAT SOME STUPID PALEONTOLOGY WORD THAT I WOULDN'T KNOW
BECAUSE I'M JUST A WAITRESS?
RACH, COME ON! RACH...
RACH! RACH! NO, NO, NO!
IT'S "SHE'S NOT RACHEL."
SHE'S... SHE'S NOT...
RA...
RACHEL?
MY DIARY... MY DIARY-- THAT'S BRILLIANT!
I SHOULD HAVE TOLD HER IT WAS MY DIARY!
SHE NEVER WOULD HAVE MADE ME READ HER MY DIARY!
NO, THAT'S TRUE.
YOU'D BE A GREAT PERSON TO HAVE AROUND
THE DAY AFTER AN EMERGENCY.
I CANNOT BELIEVE ROSS EVEN MADE THIS LIST.
I KNOW.
WHAT A DINKUS.
HEY, CUT HIM SOME SLACK.
IT WAS CHANDLER'S IDEA.
WHAT?! WHAT?!
OH, GOOD, I WAS HOPING THAT WOULD COME UP.
THIS WAS YOUR IDEA?
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING?
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET SOME PERSPECTIVE HERE, OKAY?
THESE THINGS, THEY HAPPEN FOR A REASON.
YEAH-- YOU!
ALL RIGHT, PHEEBS, BACK ME UP HERE, OKAY?
YOU BELIEVE IN THAT KARMA CRAP, DON'T YOU?
YEAH. LISTEN, BY THE WAY, GOOD LUCK IN YOUR NEXT LIFE
AS A DUNG BEETLE.
RACH-- WHOOPS!
HEY! OPEN UP! PLEASE?
WHEN SOMEBODY DOES NOT BUZZ YOU IN, ROSS, THAT MEANS "GO AWAY."
THAT DOESN'T MEAN "PLEASE CLIMB UP THE FIRE ESCAPE."
I JUST WANT TO READ YOU SOMETHING.
IT'S YOUR "PRO" LIST.
NOT INTERESTED.
OKAY. "NUMBER ONE:
"THE WAY YOU CRY AT GAME SHOWS.
"NUMBER TWO: HOW MUCH YOU LOVE YOUR FRIENDS.
"NUMBER THREE: THE WAY YOU PLAY WITH YOUR HAIR
"WHEN YOU'RE NERVOUS.
"NUMBER FOUR: HOW BRAVE YOU ARE
"FOR STARTING YOUR LIFE OVER.
"NUMBER FIVE" HOW GREAT YOU ARE WITH BEN.
"NUMBER SIX
THE WAY YOU SMELL."
HEY, ROSS.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
HEY, JOEY, YOU WANT TO OPEN THE WINDOW?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING OUT THERE?
I... I'M, UM...
OH, MY GOSH, YOU MUST BE FREEZING!
YOU KNOW WHAT YOU NEED?
HOW ABOUT A NICE, STEAMING CUP OF HOT MOCKOLATE?
RACH, COME ON, OPEN UP.
RACH, COME ON.
YOU GOT TO GIVE ME ANOTHER CHANCE.
NO.
NO?
THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
LOOK, MAYBE WE SHOULD GO.
NO, YOU GUYS REALLY DON'T HAVE TO GO.
WE'RE DONE TALKING.
RACH, COME ON. LOOK, I KNOW HOW YOU MUST...
NO, YOU DON'T, ROSS.
IMAGINE
THE WORST THINGS YOU'D THINK ABOUT YOURSELF.
NOW, HOW WOULD YOU FEEL
IF THE ONE PERSON THAT YOU TRUSTED THE MOST IN THE WORLD
NOT ONLY THINKS THEM, TOO
BUT ACTUALLY USES THEM AS REASONS NOT TO BE WITH YOU.
NO, BUT, BUT...
SEE, I WANT TO BE WITH YOU IN SPITE OF ALL THOSE THINGS.
OH! WELL, THAT'S...
THAT'S MIGHTY BIG OF YOU, ROSS.
I SAID, DON'T GO!
YOU KNOW WHAT? YOU KNOW WHAT?
IF THINGS WERE THE OTHER WAY AROUND
THERE WAS NOTHING YOU COULD PUT ON A LIST
THAT WOULD EVER MAKE ME NOT WANT TO BE WITH YOU.
WELL... THEN I GUESS THAT'S THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN US.
SEE, I'D NEVER MAKE A LIST.
I NEVER KNOW HOW LONG YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO WAIT
IN THIS TYPE OF SITUATION BEFORE YOU CAN TALK AGAIN
YOU KNOW?
MAYBE A LITTLE LONGER.
NOW, IN SOME OF THESE RECIPES
THE QUANTITIES MAY SEEM JUST A LITTLE UNUSUAL.
LIKE THESE COCONUT MOCKOLATE HOLIDAY NUT BARS?
I'VE INDICATED
FOUR CUPS OF COCONUT AND FOUR CUPS OF CRUSHED NUT
AND ONLY, UH, ONE TABLESPOON OF MOCKOLATE.
DOESN'T MATTER.
WHAT?
OUR F.D.A. APPROVAL DIDN'T COME THROUGH.
SOMETHING ABOUT LABORATORY RATS.
OH, GOSH, I'M SORRY.
YEAH...
HELL, ANYHOO, HERE'S YOUR CHECK
AND THANK YOU FOR ALL THE TROUBLE YOU WENT THROUGH.
UH, LISTEN, YOU DIDN'T EAT A LOT OF IT
WHILE YOU WERE COOKING, DID YOU?
WELL, UH, I ATE SOME.
SOME-- THAT'S FINE. SOME IS FINE.
SOME IS NOT "A LOT."
OKAY.
SO IT DOESN'T BURN WHEN YOU PEE, DOES IT?
HELLO.
HI.
IS THAT HIM AGAIN?
TELL HIM I'D COME TO THE PHONE
BUT MY ANKLES ARE WEIGHING ME DOWN.
LISTEN, I DON'T THINK THIS IS THE BEST TIME.
LOOK, CAN... CAN YOU DO SOMETHING FOR ME?
SURE. WHAT?
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
MUSIC?
SURE.
The next one is dedicated
to Rachel from Ross.
Rachel, he wants you to know
he's deeply sorry for what he did, and he hopes
you can find it in your heart to forgive him.
? See the stone set in your eyes ?
? See the thorn twist in your side ?
? I'll wait... for you ?
? Sleight of hand and twist of fate ?
? On a bed of nails she makes me wait ?
? And I'll wait without you... ?
Uh, we've just gotten a call from Rachel
and she told us what Ross did.
It's pretty appalling, and, Ross, if you're listening
I don't want to play your song anymore.
Why don't we devote our time
to a couple that stands a chance?
Avery, Michelle is sorry she hit you with her car
and she hopes you two will work it out.
? There's a room where I can go and ?
? Tell my secrets to ?
? In my room ?
? In my room. ?
HI. THANKS FOR COMING IN AGAIN.
OH, NOT AT ALL.
I HAVE NO MORALS, AND I NEED THE CASH.
IT'S LIKE I'M LOOKING IN A MIRROR.
ANYWAY
THEY'RE CALLED "FISHTACHIOS."
NOW, THEY TASTE EXACTLY LIKE PISTACHIOS, BUT THEY'RE
MADE PRIMARILY OF RECONSTITUTED FISH BITS.
HERE.
TRY ONE.
ALL RIGHT...
YOU'RE NOT ALLERGIC TO ANYTHING, ARE YOU?
CAT HAIR.
OH. SORRY.