WHO DA WENNY BENNY BOY?
OH, YOU DA WENNY WENNY BENNY BENNY BOY.
YES.
OH, DON'T CRY.
DON'T CRY.
WHY IS HE STILL CRYING?
DON'T WORRY.
IT'S NOTHING THAT CAN'T BE SOLVED BY HAPPY KEYS.
YEAH, I ALWAYS FEEL MUCH BETTER
WHEN SOMEONE SHAKES JAGGED METAL IN MY FACE.
ALL RIGHT. HERE.
LET ME HOLD HIM FOR A SEC.
THERE WE GO.
HUH? HUH? THERE WE ARE.
MAYBE IT'S ME.
DON'T BE SILLY. BEN LOVES YOU.
HE'S JUST BEING MR. CRANKY PANTS.
YOU KNOW, I ONCE DATED AMISS CRANKY PANTS.
LOVELY GIRL, KIND OF MOODY.
THERE WE GO, ALL BETTER.
THERE'S MY LITTLE BOY.
CAN I... UH... SEE SOMETHING?
COOL.
HE HATES ME.
MY NEPHEW HATES ME.
I'M UNEMPLOYED, AND MY NEPHEW HATES ME.
OH, STOP. DON'T DO THIS.
YOU'RE JUST UNEMPLOYED.
WHAT IF MY OWN BABY HATES ME? WHAT THEN?
MONICA, THIS IS NUTS.
DO YOU KNOW HOW LONG IT'S GOING TO BE
BEFORE YOU ACTUALLY HAVE TO DEAL
WITH THIS PROBLEM?
YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE A BOYFRIEND YET.
JOEY, SHE DOES NOT LOOK FAT.
HERE YOU GO.
OH, HEY, MON.
GOO! GOO! GOO!
THAT IS SO FUNNY.
LET ME SEE THAT A SEC.
UGH...
YOU OKAY, ROSS?
I DON'T KNOW. UGH...
WHAT'S IN THIS PIE?
I DON'T KNOW.
BUTTER AND EGGS AND FLOUR AND LIME AND KIWI...
KIWI? KIWI?
YOU SAID IT WAS A KEY LIME PIE.
NO, I DIDN'T. I SAID KIWILIME.
THAT'S WHAT MAKES IT SO SPECIAL.
THAT'S WHAT'S GOING TO KILL ME.
I'M ALLERGIC TO KIWI.
NO, YOU'RE NOT.
YOU'RE ALLERGIC TO LOBSTER AND PEANUTS AND...
OH, MY GOD.
IT'S DEFINITELY GETTING WORSE.
IS YOUR TONGUE SWELLING UP?
EITHER THAT OR MY MOUTH IS GETTING SMALLER.
GET YOUR COAT.
WE'RE GOING TO THE HOSPITAL.
WILL HE BE OKAY?
YEAH. HE NEEDS A SHOT.
YOU KNOW, ACTUALLY, IT'S GETTING BETTER.
IT IS. LET'S NOT GO.
ANYONE UP FOR SCRABBLE?
JACKET NOW!
BUT WHAT ABOUT BEN?
WE CAN'T BRING A BABY TO THE HOTHPITAL.
WE'LL WATCH HIM.
I DON'T THINK SO.
WHAT? I HAVE SEVEN CATHOLIC SISTERS.
I'VE TAKEN CARE OF HUNDREDS OF KIDS.
COME ON.
WE WANT TO DO IT, DON'T WE?
I WAS LOOKING FORWARD TO PLAYING BASKETBALL
BUT I GUESS THAT'S OUT THE WINDOW.
IF YOU TAKE HIM FOR HIS WALK, BWING HIS HAT.
THERE'S MILK IN THE FWIDGE AND DIAPERS IN THE BAG.
HAT, MILK, DI... GOT IT.
LET'S GO.
THRO UP A THRO THRO-- A THRO THRO.
CONSIDER IT DONE!
YOU UNDERSTOOD THAT?
YEAH. MY UNCLE SAL HAS A REALLY BIG TONGUE.
IS HE THE ONE WITH THE BEAUTIFUL WIFE?
RACH, WANT TO HEAR THE NEW SONG
I'M THINKING OF SINGING THIS AFTERNOON?
I WROTE IT IN THE SHOWER.
OKAY.
? I'M IN THE SHOWER ?
? AND I'M WRITING A SONG ?
? STOP ME IF YOU'VE HEARD IT ?
? MY SKIN IS SOAPY ?
? AND MY HAIR IS WET ?
? AND TEGRIN SPELLED BACKWARD ?
? IS NIRGET. ?
RACHEL, SWEETHEART
COULD I SEE YOU FOR A MINUTE?
WHAT'S UP?
F.Y.I., I'VE DECIDED
TO PAY A PROFESSIONAL MUSICIAN
TO PLAY HERE ON SUNDAY AFTERNOONS.
HER NAME IS STEPHANIE...
SOMETHING.
SHE'S SUPPOSED TO BE VERY GOOD.
BUT WHAT ABOUT PHOEBE?
RACHEL, IT'S NOT THAT YOUR FRIEND IS BAD.
IT'S... IT'S THAT SHE'S SO BAD
SHE MAKES ME WANT TO PUT MY FINGER
THROUGH MY EYE INTO MY BRAIN
AND SWIRL IT AROUND.
OKAY.
OKAY, SO YOU'RE NOT A FAN.
BUT, I MEAN, COME ON.
YOU CANNOT DO THIS TO HER.
UH...
OH, NO, NO, NO.
I HAVE TO DO THIS TO HER?
? LATHER, RINSE, REPEAT ?
? AND LATHER, RINSE, REPEAT ?
? AS NEEDED. ?
YOU KNOW, I DON'T THINK WE BROUGHT ENOUGH STUFF.
DID YOU FORGET TO PACK THE BABY'S ANVIL?
IT'S GOING TO BE WORTH IT.
IT'S A KNOWN FACT THAT WOMEN LOVE BABIES.
WOMEN LOVE GUYS WHO LOVE BABIES.
IT'S THE WHOLE SENSITIVE THING.
AIM HIM AT THAT PACK OF BABES.
MAYBE ONE OF THEM WILL BREAK AWAY.
NO, NO, WAIT. FORGET THEM.
WE GOT ONE HARD LEFT.
GIVE ME THE BABY.
NO, I'VE GOT HIM.
COME ON, SERIOUSLY.
OH, SERIOUSLY YOU WANT HIM?
HELLO.
HELLO. HELLO.
AND WHO IS THIS LITTLE CUTIE PIE?
WELL, DON'T THINK ME IMMODEST, BUT...
ME?
YOU WANT TO SMELL HIM?
I ASSUME WE'RE TALKING ABOUT THE BABY NOW.
OH, YEAH.
HE'S GOT THAT GREAT BABY SMELL.
GET A WHIFF OF HIS HEAD.
I THINK MY UTERUS JUST SKIPPED A BEAT.
WHAT DID I TELL YOU?
IT'S GREAT YOU'RE DOING THIS.
WELL, WE ARE GREAT GUYS.
MY BROTHER AND HIS BOYFRIEND HAVE BEEN TRYING TO ADOPT.
WHAT AGENCY DID YOU TWO GO THROUGH?
BUT THIS IS MY GIG.
THIS IS WHERE I PLAY.
MY NAME IS WRITTEN OUT THERE IN CHALK.
YOU KNOW, YOU CAN'T JUST ERASE CHALK.
HONEY, I'M SORRY.
AND HE'S GOING TO BE PAYING THIS WOMAN?
WHY DOESN'T HE GIVE HER A THRONE?
AND A CROWN, AND, LIKE, A...
YOU KNOW... GOLD STICK WITH A BALL ON TOP?
TERRY IS A JERK.
THAT'S WHY WE'RE ALWAYS SAYING, "TERRY'S A JERK."
THAT'S WHERE THAT CAME FROM.
YEAH, OKAY.
YOU PROBABLY DID EVERYTHING YOU COULD.
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
LET ME JUST SEE WHAT ELSE I CAN DO.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST LET HER GO ON AFTER
STEPHANIE WHATEVER HER NAME IS.
YOU WON'T BE HERE, YOU DON'T PAY HER.
I DON'T KNOW.
TERRY, I'LL EVEN CLEAN THE CAPPUCCINO MACHINE.
YOU DON'T CLEAN THE CAPPUCCINO MACHINE?
OF COURSE...
I CLEAN IT.
I MEAN, I WILL CLEAN IT.
I WILL CLEAN IT.
OH, ALL RIGHT.
FINE, FINE, FINE.
DONE.
REALLY?
YEAH. WHO'S WORKING FOR YOU, BABE?
OH, MY GOD!
THIS IS SO EXCITING.
HOW MUCH AM I GOING TO GET?
WHAT?
YOU SAID HE'S PAYING THE PEOPLE WHO PLAY.
OH, NO. NO, NO.
HE'S GOING TO BE PAYING THAT OTHER WOMAN
BECAUSE SHE'S A PROFESSIONAL.
I'M NOT GOING TO BE THE ONLY ONE WHO'S NOT GETTING PAID.
BUT, PHEEBS...
NO, UH UH, I'M SORRY.
NO, I'M NOT SOME, LIKE, SLOPPY SECOND
YOU KNOW, CHARITY BAND.
THERE ARE THOUSANDS OF PLACES IN THIS CITY
WHERE PEOPLE WOULD BE HAPPY TO PAY TO HEAR ME PLAY.
? WHEN I PLAY, I PLAY FOR ME ?
? I DON'T NEED YOUR CHARITY ?
THANK YOU.
? LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA ?
? LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA. ?
THERE'S NO WAY I'M GOING TO GET A SHOT.
MAYBE THEY CAN TAKE THE NEEDLE
AND THQUIRT IT INTO MY MOUTH LIKE A THQUIRT GUN.
HONEY, WHY DON'T WE JUST WAIT
AND SEE WHAT THE DOCTOR SAYS?
THEY'VE GOT TO BE ABLE TO DO SOMETHING.
THESE ARE THE '90s!
HELLO, THERE.
I'M DR. KARLEN.
I SEE SOMEONE'S HAVING A LITTLE ALLERGIC REACTION.
DOCTOR, CAN I SEE YOU FOR JUST A MOMENT, PLEASE?
MY BROTHER HAS
A SLIGHT PHOBIA ABOUT NEEDLES.
DID YOU TELL HIM ABOUT MY THQUIRT GUN IDEA?
MY BROTHER, THE Ph.D.
WOULD LIKE TO KNOW IF THERE'S ANY WAY TO TREAT THIS ORALLY.
NO. UNDER THESE CIRCUMSTANCES
IT HAS TO BE AN INJECTION AND IT HAS TO BE NOW.
THO?
OHHH!
THAT'S GOOD. HAVE A SEAT.
DOCTOR SAYS IT'S GOT TO BE A NEEDLE.
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO BE BRAVE, OKAY?
CAN YOU DO THAT FOR ME?
OKAY.
OKAY. OH, BOY!
YOU ARE DOING SO GOOD.
YOU WANT TO SQUEEZE MY HAND?
YEAH.
DON'T SQUEEZE IT SO HARD.
REALLY, DON'T SQUEEZE IT SO HARD.
OW! LET GO OF MY HAND!
THAT'S A GOOD PLAN.
NEXT TIME WE WANT TO PICK UP WOMEN
WE'LL JUST GO TO THE PARK AND MAKE OUT.
TAXI! TAXI!
LOOK AT THAT TALENT.
JUST PRACTICING.
YOU'RE GOOD. CARRY ON.
WAIT! WAIT! WAIT!
HEY, YOU.
HE'S JUST ADORABLE.
CAN YOU TELL HIM THAT?
BECAUSE HE THINKS HE LOOKS TOO PINK.
SO WHAT ARE YOU GUYS OUT DOING TODAY?
OH, WE'RE NOT OUT. NO, NO.
WE'RE JUST
TWO HETEROSEXUAL GUYS HANGING WITH THE SON
OF OUR OTHER HETEROSEXUAL FRIEND
DOING THE USUAL "STRAIGHT GUY" STUFF.
YOU DONE?
YEAH.
THERE'S OUR STOP.
GET OUT OF HERE.
THIS I SOUR STOP.
YOU GUYS LIVE AROUND HERE, TOO?
YEAH. WE LIVE IN THE BUILDING BY THE...
SIDEWALK.
YOU KNOW IT?
LOOK, SINCE WE'RE NEIGHBORS AND ALL
WHAT DO YOU SAY
WE GET TOGETHER FOR A DRINK?
SO, DO YOU WANT TO GO TO MARKEL'S?
OH, SURE. THEY LOVE US OVER THERE.
HEY, WHERE'S YOUR BABY?
BEN!
OH, THAT'S GOOD!
MAYBE HE'LL HEAR YOU AND PULL THE CORD!
STOP THE BUS!
WAIT, WAIT! WAIT!
ARE YOU SURE HE DIDN'T BREAK IT?
IT REALLY HURTS.
NO, IT'S JUST A GOOD BONE BRUISE
AND...
RIGHT HERE
IS THE PUNCTURE WOUND FROM YOUR RING.
OH, I'M SORRY. I'M REALLY SORRY.
THAT'S OKAY.
SORRY. SORRY!
HEY! HEY, I GOT MY S's BACK!
WHICH WE CAN CELEBRATE LATER.
CELEBRATE.
CELE...
? HE WAS A DOUBLE DOUBLE ?
? DOUBLE JOINTED BOY. ?
HEY. SO, UM...
ARE YOU THE PROFESSIONAL GUITAR PLAYER?
YEAH. I'M STEPHANIE.
OH. RIGHT, YEAH.
MY NAME WAS ON THERE
BUT NOW IT JUST SAYS "CARROT CAKE."
OKAY.
SO, UM, SO, UM, HOW MANY CHORDS DO YOU KNOW?
ALL OF THEM.
OH, YEAH? SO YOU KNOW "D"?
YEAH.
OKAY, DO YOU KNOW "A" MINOR?
OKAY. DO YOU KNOW HOW TO GO FROM "D"TO"A" MINOR?
YEAH.
OKAY.
UM, SO DOES YOUR GUITAR HAVE A STRAP?
NO.
OH. MINE DOES.
? STEPHANIE KNOWS ALL THE CHORDS... ?
COME ON, PICK UP! PICK UP!
PICK UP! PICK UP! HELLO...
TRANSIT AUTHORITY?
YES, HELLO.
I'M DOING RESEARCH FOR A BOOK
AND I WAS WONDERING WHAT SOMEBODY MIGHT DO
IF THEY LEFT A BABY ON A CITY BUS.
YES, I DO REALIZE THAT'D BE A VERY STUPID CHARACTER.
HI. HERE'S THE DEAL.
WE LOST A CAR SEAT ON A BUS TODAY.
IT'S WHITE WITH A HANDLE AND IT FITS ON A STROLLER.
OH, AND THERE WAS A BABY IN IT.
HE WANTS TO TALK TO YOU AGAIN.
OKAY, EVERYBODY, LET'S GIVE A WARM CENTRAL PERK WELCOME TO...
? TERRY'S A JERK ?
? AND HE WON'T LET ME WORK ?
? AND I HATE CENTRAL PERK... ?
UH, TO STEPHANIE SCHIFFER.
THANK YOU.
I'D LIKE TO START WITH A SONG
THAT I WROTE FOR THE FIRST MAN I EVER LOVED.
? ZACHARY ?
? YOU'RE ALL INVITED TO BITE ME! ?
HI! HI!
WE'RE THE GUYS THAT CALLED ABOUT THE BABY! WE LOST THE BABY!
IS HE HERE?
HE'S HERE.
I'M ASSUMING ONE OF YOU IS THE FATHER.
THAT'S ME. I'M HIM.
ACTUALLY, UH...
WE'RE BOTH THE FATHER.
OH, BEN! HEY, BEN!
HEY, BUDDY. HEY, BABY.
HI...
PLEASE TELL ME YOU KNOW WHICH ONE IS OUR BABY.
WELL, WELL, THAT ONE HAS DUCKS ON HIS T SHIRT
AND THIS ONE HAS CLOWNS
AND BEN WAS DEFINITELY WEARING DUCKS.
OKAY...
OR CLOWNS.
OH! OH, WAIT!
THAT ONE'S DEFINITELY BEN.
HE HAD THAT CUTE LITTLE MOLE BY HIS MOUTH.
YEAH?
YEAH.
HEY, BEN, REMEMBER US?
OKAY, THE MOLE CAME OFF.
AHH...
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
WE'LL FLIP FOR IT-- DUCKS OR CLOWNS.
WE'RE GOING TO FLIP FOR THE BABY?!
YOU GOT A BETTER IDEA?
CALL IT IN THE AIR.
ALL RIGHT.
HEADS.
HEADS IT IS.
YES!
PHEW!
WE HAVE TO ASSIGN HEADS TO SOMETHING!
OH! RIGHT!
OKAY. OKAY, UH...
DUCKS IS HEADS BECAUSE DUCKS HAVE HEADS.
WHAT KIND OF SCARY ASS CLOWNS CAME TO YOUR BIRTHDAY?
? THERE'LL BE NO STRINGS TO BIND YOUR HANDS ?
? NOT IF MY LOVE CAN'T BIND YOUR HEART ?
? AND THERE'S NO NEED TO TAKE A STAND ?
? FOR IT WAS I WHO CHOSE TO START ?
? I SEE NO REASON TO TAKE ME HOME ?
? I'M OLD ENOUGH TO FACE THE DAWN ?
? JUST CALL ME ANGEL OF THE MORNING ?
? ANGEL ?
? JUST TOUCH MY CHEEK ?
? BEFORE YOU LEAVE ME, BABY ?
? JUST CALL ME ANGEL ?
? OF THE MORNING ?
? ANGEL ?
? THEN SLOWLY TURN AWAY ?
? I WON'T BEG YOU TO STAY ?
? WITH ME ?
? MAYBE THE SUN'S LIGHT WILL BE DIM ?
? SO IT WON'T MATTER ANYHOW ?
? IF MORNING'S ECHO SAYS WE'VE SINNED ?
? WELL, IT WAS WHAT I WANTED NOW ?
? AND IF WE'RE VICTIMS OF THE NIGHT ?
? I WON'T BE BLINDED BY THE LIGHT ?
? JUST CALL ME ANGEL OF THE MORNING ?
? ANGEL ?
? JUST TOUCH MY CHEEK BEFORE YOU LEAVE ME, BABY ?
? JUST CALL ME ANGEL OF THE MORNING ?
? ANGEL ?
? THEN SLOWLY TURN AWAY ?
? I WON'T BEG YOU TO STAY ?
? WITH ME ?
? THROUGH THE TEARS ?
? OF THE PAIN ?
? OF THE YEARS ?
? BABY ?
? JUST CALL ME ANGEL OF THE MORNING ?
? ANGEL ?
? JUST TOUCH MY CHEEK BEFORE YOU LEAVE ME, BABY ?
? JUST CALL ME ANGEL OF THE MORNING ?
? ANGEL ?
? JUST TOUCH MY CHEEK BEFORE YOU LEAVE ME ?
? BABY, BABY, OH, BABY. ?
HEY.
OH, HI.
HERE. I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT BE COLD.
THANK YOU.
WHOA, LOOK AT YOU.
YOU DID PRETTY WELL.
$8.27 DOLLAR.
BUT NOT REALLY, BECAUSE I PUT IN THE FIRST TWO.
JUST TO, YOU KNOW, GET THE BALL ROLLING
AND TO MAKE MYSELF FEEL BETTER.
DO YOU?
NO.
YOU KNOW, THIS WHOLE, LIKE, PLAYING FOR MONEY THING
IS SO NOT GOOD FOR ME.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T KNOW.
WHEN I SANG "SU SU SUICIDE"
I GOT, LIKE... I GOT $1.75 DOLLAR.
BUT THEN "SMELLY CAT"?
I GOT 25 CENTS AND A CONDOM.
SO, YOU KNOW, NOW
I JUST FEEL REALLY BAD FOR "SMELLY CAT."
WELL, YOU KNOW, HONEY
I DON'T THINK EVERYBODY GETS "SMELLY CAT."
YOU KNOW, I MEAN, IF ALL YOU'VE EVER ACTUALLY HAD
ARE HEALTHY PETS, THEN WOOSH!
BUT IT'S NOT EVEN THAT, YOU KNOW?
I USED TO DO MY SONGS BECAUSE IT MADE ME HAPPY.
NOW IT'S, LIKE, IT'S JUST ALL ABOUT THE MONEY, YOU KNOW?
WELL, PEOPLE MISSED YOU IN THERE.
AND, IN FACT, THERE WAS ACTUALLY A REQUEST FOR "SMELLY CAT."
REALLY?! FROM WHO?
WELL, ME.
AND I KNOW IT'S NOT, YOU KNOW
YOUR BIG MONEY SONG, BUT IT'S MY FAVORITE.
OH...
OH!
HI. DID I ACCIDENTALLY DROP A CONDOM IN YOUR CASE?
IT'S KIND OF AN EMERGENCY.
YEAH. HERE YOU GO.
HEY, THANKS A LOT.
HEY, CHRISTINE, I GOT IT!
I WANT TO THANK YOU FOR BEING THERE FOR ME TODAY.
I'M SORRY I ALMOST BROKE YOUR HAND.
OH, THAT'S OKAY.
I'M SORRY I POISONED YOU.
HEY, REMEMBER THE TIME I JAMMED THAT PENCIL INTO YOUR HAND?
REMEMBER IT?
WHAT DO YOU THINK THIS IS-- A FRECKLE?
WHAT ABOUT THE TIME
I HIT YOU IN THE FACE WITH THE SYLVIANS' PUMPKIN?
REMEMBER WHEN I STUCK THAT BROOM
IN YOUR BIKE SPOKES AND YOU FLIPPED
AND HIT YOUR HEAD ON THE CURB?
NO.
BUT I REMEMBER PEOPLE TELLING ME ABOUT IT.
OH.
I HOPE BEN HAS A LITTLE SISTER.
YEAH.
I HOPE SHE CAN KICK HIS ASS.
I'M GOING TO GET A NEW BAND AID.
HOW ABOUT THE TIME I CUT THE LEGS OFF YOUR MALIBU KEN?
THAT WAS YOU?!
UH... THEY WERE INFECTED.
THEY WOULDN'T HAVE MADE IT.
AW, MY LITTLE NEPHEW.
COME HERE, LITTLE ONE.
AW, THERE'S MY LITTLE BABY.
HEY, MY LITTLE BOY.
OHH...
HEY! HE'S NOT CRYING.
HEY, HE'S NOT CRYING.
YES!
THERE'S STILL PIE!
OH, I'M HERE.
I'M HERE.
HOW'S MY LITTLE BOY, HUH? HUH?
YOU WANT DADDY TO CHANGE YOUR DIAPER?
HMM? I KNOW. I KNOW.
SO, DID YOU HAVE FUN
WITH UNCLE JOEY AND UNCLE CHANDLER TODAY?
OH, YEAH.
HE RODE THE BUS TODAY.
OH... WELL...
BIG BOY, RIDING THE BU...
HEY, I HAVE A QUESTION.
HOW COME IT SAYS "PROPERTY OF HUMAN SERVICES" ON HIS BUTT?
YOU...
YOU ARE GOING TO LOVE THIS!
CAN YOU HOLD BEN FOR A SEC?
ALL RIGHT.
COME HERE. COME HERE.
STAY BACK! I'VE GOT KIWI!
RUN, JOEY, RUN!
? SMELLY CAT, SMELLY CAT ?
? WHAT ARE THEY FEEDING YOU? ?
NO, NO, NO. I'M SORRY, IT'S
? SMELLY CAT, SMELLY CAT ?
BETTER. MUCH BETTER. GOOD.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
DON'T FEEL BAD, BECAUSE IT'S A HARD SONG.
YEAH.
DO YOU WANT TO TRY IT AGAIN?
YEAH. FROM THE TOP?
THERE IS NO TOP.
ALL RIGHT?
THAT'S THE BEAUTY OF "SMELLY CAT."
OH.
UM...
WHY DON'T YOU JUST FOLLOW ME?
OKAY.
? SMELLY CAT, SMELLY CAT ?
? WHAT ARE THEY FEEDING YOU? ?
? IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.... ?