Stocks and bonds are moving higher. Good day.
HEY, MONICA, WHY ARE WE WATCHING THE BUSINESS CHANNEL?
BECAUSE I WAS GOING BY IT THE OTHER DAY
AND I SAW THAT THERE WAS A STOCK WITH MY INITIALS, M.E.G., ON IT
AND SOMETIMES I HAVE TO WATCH FOR TWO OR THREE HOURS
BEFORE IT COMES UP AGAIN
BUT, WHEN IT DOES, IT'S PRETTY EXCITING.
HMM... OKAY, HONEY, YOU REALLY NEED A JOB.
MON, SPEAK ING OF WHICH
DAD SAYS HE KNOWS SOMEONE
REALLY? YOU CAN CALL FOR AN INTERVIEW.
OKAY, RIGHT THERE.
THAT'S THE THIRD SIGN TODAY, RIGHT THERE.
ON BEHALF OF EVERYONE, I'D JUST LIKE TO SAY, "MHEH?"
NO, BECAUSE YOU JUST SAID "DAD"
AND EVERYWHERE I GO TODAY, I KEEP GETTING SIGNS
TELLING ME TO GO SEE MY FATHER.
LIKE WHEN I WAS WALKING OVER HERE
AND I PASSED A BUFFET.
WHICH IS MY FATHER'S LAST NAME.
AH! OH! AH!
AND THEY WERE SERVING FRANKS
HIS FIRST NAME, MINUS THE "S" AT THE END.
AH! YES.
AND THERE WAS A ROTISSERIE WITH ASPINNING CHICKEN.
HIS INDIAN NAME?
NO, BECAUSE I CHICKENED OUT
THE LAST TIME...
WHEN I TRIED TO MEET HIM.
SO, I MEAN, COINCIDENCES?
I DON'T THINK SO.
FREAKY. WEIRD. EERIE.
OKAY, SO WHO WANTS THE, UH, LAST HAMBURGER?
OH, ALL RIGHT, NOW I HAVE TO GO SEE HIM.
WHY?
HAMBURGER.
McDONALD'S.
OLD McDONALD HAD A FARM.
MY DAD WAS A PHARMACIST.
OHH!
AND E I E I O IS WHAT YOUR MOM SAID WHEN YOUR DAD LEFT HER.
YES!
REALLY?
NO.
MAN, I AM SO BEAT.
OH, YEAH.
HEY, YOU WANT TO JUST FORGET ABOUT RACQUETBALL
AND HANG OUT HERE?
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
HEY, YOU'RE IN OUR SEATS.
OH, SORRY, WE DIDN'T KNOW.
HEY, WE WERE SITTING THERE.
OKAY, THERE IS ONE MORE WAY TO SAY IT.
WHO KNOWS IT?
IS THAT SUPPOSED TO BE FUNNY?
NO, ACTUALLY, I WAS JUST GOING FOR COLORFUL.
WHAT'S WITH THIS GUY?
WHAT'S WITH YOU?
UH... NOTHING.
NOTHING'S WITH HIM.
ENJOY YOUR COFFEE.
WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
I JUST TOOK YOUR HAT.
SEE, I CAN BE FUNNY, TOO.
MY MY JOKE IS THAT I I TOOK YOUR HAT.
THAT... THAT... THAT IS FUNNY.
CAN I HAVE IT BACK?
NO.
NO?
OKAY.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK YOU'VE VERY FUNNY.
KUDOS ON THAT HAT JOKE.
BUT COME ON, GUYS
JUST JUST GIVE HIM BACK THE HAT.
WHY SHOULD WE?
BECAUSE IT'S A SPECIAL HAT.
SEE, HE BOUGHT  IT
BECAUSE HE WAS FEELING REALLY DOWN ONE DAY.
SO HE GOT THE HAT TO CHEER HIMSELF UP, YOU KNOW?
NOW, CHANDLER, YOU WOULDN'T...
STOP TALKING.
STOP TALKING NOW.
LET ME JUST GET THIS STRAIGHT.
YOU'RE ACTUALLY STEALING MY HAT?
YOU GOT A PROBLEM WITH THAT?
NO. JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE WE'RE ON THE SAME PAGE.
I'M TELLING YOU, RACH
I'VE GONE DAD HUNTING WITH PHOEBE BEFORE.
THIS IS A VERY SCARY THING FOR HER.
SHE GETS REAL VULNERABLE AND ...
THAT'S WHY WE'RE THERE
TO, YOU KNOW, BE SUPPORTIVE AND CRAP.
OKAY. WELL, YOU JUST LET ME KNOW WHEN TO DO WHICH.
HEY, HOW'D
THE INTERVIEW GO?
IT BIT.
IT WAS A 50S
THEME RESTAURANT.
I'D HAVE TO COOK IN A COSTUME
AND DANCE ON THE COUNTER.
I MEAN, I WAS A SOUS CHEF AT CAFE DES ARTISTES.
I MEAN, HOW COULD I TAKE A JOB
WHERE I HAVE TO MAKE SOMETHING CALLED "LAVERNE & CURLY FRIES"?
SO DON'T DO IT.
HOW CAN I NOT DO IT?
I HAVE $127 DOLLARS IN THE BANK!
MONICA, RELAX.
GO GET A BEER.
I DON'T WANT A BEER!
WHO SAID IT WAS FOR YOU?
HI. HI.
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU?
THESE MEAN GUYS AT THE COFFEE HOUSE TOOK MY HAT.
NO! YOU'RE KIDDING.
IT WAS RIDICULOUS.
YOU KNOW, THESE GUYS, THEY WERE BULLIES.
ACTUAL BULLIES, YOU KNOW?
WE'RE GROWN UPS.
THIS KIND OF STUFF ISN'T SUPPOSED TO HAPPEN ANYMORE.
OHH!
HI. HI.
OH, NO, WAIT A MINUTE
I HAVE NO ONE.
HEY, WELL, LET'S GO DOWN THERE AND GET YOUR HAT BACK.
AW, FORGET IT.
IT'S PROBABLY STRIPPED AND SOLD FOR PARTS BY NOW.
HEY!
I WENT UP.
WHAT? MY STOCK.
M.E.G. IT WENT UP TWO POINTS.
DO YOU REALIZE THAT IF I HAD INVESTED MY $127
IN MYSELF YESTERDAY
THAT I'D, LIKE, HAVE...
A LOT MORE THAN THAT TODAY?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M GOING TO DO IT.
DO WHAT?
PUT ALL MY MONEY IN ME.
MONICA, WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
YOU DON'T KNOW THE FIRST THING ABOUT THE STOCK MARKET.
WHAT'S TO KNOW?
BUY! SELL! HIGH! LOW! BEARS! BULLS!
YES, MANHATTAN.
YEAH, TELEPHONE NUMBER OF THE STOCK...
SELLING...
STORE.
WELL... SEE? DIDN'T I TELL YOU
THESE PILLOWS WOULD BE A GOOD IDEA?
OH, GOD.
HERE WE GO.
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN MY LIFE
I'M GOING TO SAY, "HI, BIRTH FATHER."
WE LOVE YOU, AND WE'RE HERE FOR YOU.
YEAH, GOOD LUCK, GOOD LUCK.
THANKS.
HEY, RACH, YOU, UH, YOU WANT SOME SANDWICH?
OH! WHAT IS IN THAT?
OLIVE LOAF AND HAM SPREAD, NO MAYO.
NO, NO, BECAUSE MAY
THAT WOULD MAKE IT GROSS.
HEY! NO!
OH! OH!
RUN, PHOEBE!
NO, DOGGIE! NO, PLEASE!
I DO SO WANT TO LOVE ALL ANIMALS.
PLEASE, NO! GET OFF MY LEG!
GET HIM A BONE! YOU GOT A BONE?
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
LOOK! KIBBLES! BITS! OH...
ALL RIGHT, GET THE HELL OFF MY LEG
YOU YIPPITY PIECE OF CRAP!
OHH!
OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
WE HAVE A PROBLEM.
WELL, WHY DON'T YOU JUST REACH OUT AND TAKE HIS TRAMPOLINE?
OKAY, HERE
I KNOW WHAT WE CAN DO.
HEY, HEY! HEY, NO!
OKAY, DOGGIE!
GET THE... GET THE SANDWICH!
OKAY, GO GET THE SANDWICH.
GET THE SANDWICH, DOGGIE.
GOOD DOGGIE!
GET THE SANDWICH! GET THE...
OKAY, JOEY?
THE DOG WILL LICK HIMSELF
BUT HE WILL NOT TOUCH YOUR SANDWICH.
WHAT DOES THAT TELL YOU?
WELL, IF HE'S NOT GOING TO EAT IT, I WILL.
ARE YOU CRAZY?
PHEEBS, HE'S JUST A LITTLE DOG.
HEY.
WHAT?
DO YOU HAVE TO BE A CENTURY 21 REAL ESTATE AGENT
TO GET TO WEAR THOSE REALLY COOL JACKETS?
DO YOU SAY THIS STUFF TO GIRLS?
H H HEY, ISN'T THAT THE GUY WHO USED TO WEAR YOUR HAT?
AND LOOK WHERE THEY'RE SITTING.
YOU'RE JOKING, RIGHT?
YOU GUYS JUST WALKED THROUGH THE DOOR.
MAYBE WE DIDN'T MAKE IT CLEAR ENOUGH.
YEAH.
THIS COUCH BELONGS TO US.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
YOU CALL THE COUCH
AND THEN... AND THEN WE'LL CALL THE COUCH...
AND WE'LL  SEE
WHO IT COMES TO.
YOU KNOW WHAT I DON'T LIKE ABOUT YOU?
YOU ALWAYS GOT SOMETHING TO SAY.
WELL, THAT...
YOU KNOW WHAT I KEEP WONDERING?
WHY YOU TWO ARE STILL SITTING HERE.
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S IT!
I HAVE HAD ENOUGH OF THIS, ALL RIGHT?
GUNTHER!
THESE GUYS ARE TRY ING TO TAKE OUR SEATS.
FELLAS
THESE GUYS WERE HERE FIRST.
OH, I'M SORRY, DIDN'T REALIZE.
THERE YOU GO.
THANK YOU, GUNTHER.
WE DIDN'T WANT TO HAVE TO GO AND DO THAT.
HE TOLD ON US?
YOU TOLD ON US?
WELL, PAL, YOU DIDN'T GIVE ME
MUCH OF A CHOICE.
DON'T PLAY WITH HIS THING.
I KNOW.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S TAKE THIS OUTSIDE.
"LET'S LET'S TAKE THIS OUTSIDE"?
WHO TALKS LIKE THAT?
A GUY WHO'S ABOUT TO KICK YOUR ASS
TALKS LIKE THAT.
YOU HAD TO ASK.
YEAH.
OKAY, OKAY, LOOK.
SEE, THE THING IS
WE'RE... WE'RE NOT GOING TO FIGHT YOU GUYS.
WELL, THEN, HERE'S THE DEAL:
YOU WON'T HAVE TO
SO LONG AS YOU NEVER, EVER SHOW YOUR FACES
IN THIS COFFEE HOUSE EVER AGAIN.
I THINK YOU PLAYED
THE GUNTHER CARD TOO SOON.
HEY, PHEEBS, I I THINK YOU'RE GOOD TO GO.
YEAH, I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
I JUST THINK THAT THIS WAS A REALLY BAD SIGN, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, LIKE, "THE BEAST AT THE THRESHOLD," YOU KNOW.
IT'S JUST, I HAVE, LIKE, NO FAMILY LEFT.
I MEAN, WELL, EXCEPT FOR MY GRANDMOTHER.
YOU KNOW, BUT LET'S FACE IT
SHE'S NOT GOING TO BE AROUND FOREVER...
DESPITE WHAT SHE SAYS.
AND I HAVE A SISTER
WHO I'VE BARELY SPOKEN TO SINCE WE, LIKE, SHARED A WOMB.
YOU KNOW? I DON'T KNOW.
THIS IS MY REAL FATHER.
AND I JUST... I WANT THINGS TO BE, LIKE, JUST RIGHT.
YEAH, PHOEBE, I COMPLETELY UNDERSTAND.
YEAH, WHATEVER YOU NEED.
HEY, YOU WANT TO GO HOME?
OKAY, THANKS. SORRY AGAIN.
T? WHAT WAS THA
UH...
I'M GUESSING THE THRESHOLD'S CLEAR NOW.
I WANT TO BUY FIVE SHARES OF S.G.J.
AND I WANT TO BUY THEM NOW.
COME ON, TIME IS MONEY, MY FRIEND.
THANK YOU.
WHOO!
"TIME IS MONEY, MY FRIEND"?
YEAH. YOU MISSED "TAKES MONEY TO MAKE MONEY"
AND, UH, "DON'T MAKE ME COME DOWN THERE
AND KICK YOUR WALL STREET BUTT."
HEY, I MADE $17 DOLLARS BEFORE BREAKFAST.
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE?
WELL, UH, I HAD BREAKFAST HERE.
SO, TECHNICALLY, I SAVED $3.50 DOLLARS
HOW DID YOU MAKE $17 DOLLARS?
WELL, MY FINANCIALLY CHALLENGED FRIENDS, I SPLIT MY MONEY
AND I BOUGHT SOME SHARES OF C.H.P. AND Z.X.Y.
HOW COME THOSE?
WELL, C.H.P.
BECAUSE I USED TO HAVE A CRUSH ON ERIK ESTRADA.
AND Z.X.Y., BECAUSE I THINK IT SOUNDS ZEXY.
WHAT HAPPENED  TO, UH, M.E.G.?
M.E.G. WAS GOOD FOR ME, BUT I DUMPED HER.
YOU KNOW, MY MOTTO IS
"GET OUT BEFORE THEY GO DOWN."
THAT IS SO NOT MY MOTTO.
HEY.
HEY, PHEEBS.
OH, HEY, HOW'S THE DOG? YEAH.
OKAY, I TALKED TO THE VET.
PEOPLE ARE SO NICE UPSTATE. OH!
ANYWAY, HE SAID THAT THE LITTLE FELLA'S GOING TO BE OKAY
AND I CAN PICK HIM UP TOMORROW.
OH, GOOD.
OH, THANK GOD.
YEAH, BUT HE DID HAVE TO HAVE, LIKE, A BUNCH OF STITCHES
AND HE SAID THAT ONLY ONCE IN A BLUE MOON
DOES A DOG'S EAR GROW BACK, SO...
STILL HOPING.
OKAY, SO, PHOEBE
NOW ARE YOU GOING TO CALL YOUR DAD
TO LET HIM KNOW THAT HIS DOG IS OKAY?
I I DON'T WANT TO MEET MY FATHER OVER THE PHONE.
WHAT AM I GOING TO SAY?
LIKE, "HI. I'M PHOEBE, THE DAUGHTER YOU ABANDONED.
OH, BY THE WAY, I BROKE YOUR DOG."
WELL, HEY, PHEEBS, IF YOU WANT, I'LL DO IT.
OKAY.
LISTEN, JUST DON'T SAY ANYTHING
ABOUT ME, OKAY?
ALL RIGHT.
DON'T!
BE TOO LONG WITH THE PHONE.
OKAY, SHE'LL BE A MUCH BETTER FRIEND
ONCE THE MARKET CLOSES.
IT'S A WOMAN.
OKAY, SO, TALK TO HER.
UH... HELLO, MRS. BUFFAY?
I KNOW WHERE YOUR DOG IS.
I WANT YOU TO KNOW, HE'LL BE RETURNED TO YOU
ALMOST AS GOOD AS NEW WITHIN... WITHIN 24 HOURS.
UH, GOOD BYE.
WHY THE VOICE?
HARD TO SAY.
YOUR CAPPUCCINO, SIR.
THANK YOU.
YOU KNOW, I THINK THIS IS
MUCH BETTER THAN THE COFFEE HOUSE.
ABSOLUTELY.
HOW COME IT'S NOT MIXING WITH THE WATER?
WELL, THE PACKAGE SAYS
YOU HAVE TO, UH, CONSTANTLY KEEP IT MOVING.
STIR AND DRINK. STIR AND DRINK.
NEVER LET IT SETTLE.
HEY, THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT AFTER I GET BACK FROM MY NIECE'S CHRISTENING
I'LL GO DOWN TO THE COFFEE HOUSE WITH YOU
AND WE'LL ALL HAVE A NICE CUP OF COFFEE, ALL RIGHT?
NO PROBLEM.
JOEY'S THERE, HUH?
OKAY.
NO.
NO?
I DON'T WANT TO HAVE TO HAVE JOEY WITH ME
EVERY TIME I WANT A DECENT CUP OF COFFEE, YOU KNOW?
AND I DON'T WANT TO SP END THE REST OF MY LIFE
DRINKING CAPPUCCINO WITH A "K".
I SAY YOU AND I GO BACK DOWN THERE
AND STAND UP TO THOSE GUYS.
ALL RIGHT. HANG ON A SECOND THERE, CUSTER.
YEAH, REALLY.
ROSS, HAVE YOU EVER BEEN BEATEN UP BEFORE?
YEAH, SURE.
BY SOMEONE BESIDES MONICA?
NO.
SO WHAT? SO WHAT IF WE GET BEATEN UP?
MAYBE THAT'S JUST SOMETHING EVERY MAN HAS TO GO THROUGH
ONCE IN HIS LIFE, YOU KNOW?
LIKE A... LIKE A RITE OF PASSAGE OR SOMETHING.
WELL, COULDN'T WE JUST LOSE OUR VIRGINITIES AGAIN?
YOU KNOW, BECAUSE I THINK, ACTUALLY, MINE'S GROWING BACK.
ALL RIGHT, ARE YOU WITH ME OR NOT? COME ON.
ALL RIGHT, I'M WITH YOU.
JUST, UH...
LET ME PUT ON A CLEAN PAIR OF UNDERWEAR FOR THE HOSPITAL.
NEED TO BORROW A HUNDRED BUCKS.
WHAT?
HI. WELCOME HOME.
I NEED TO BORROW A HUNDRED BUCKS.
FOR WHAT?
I GOT TO GET BACK IN THE GAME.
WHY? WHEN DID YOU GET OUT OF THE GAME?
I DON'T KNOW. I LOST IT ALL, OKAY?
I LOST I OH, NO.
HEY, I'VE COME TO TERMS WITH IT.
YOU HAVE TO, TOO.
OKAY.
LOOK, UH...
MON, I'M I'M REALLY SORRY.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, WHERE ARE WE ON THE HUNDRED BUCKS?
I DON'T HAVE IT.
BUT I NEED IT!
OTHERWISE, I'M GOING TO HAVE TO TAKE
THAT HORRIBLE DINER JOB.
YOU KNOW, WITH THE DANCING AND THE COSTUMES.
I DON'T WANT TO HAVE TO WEAR FLAME RETARDANT BOOBS.
NOBODY DOES, HONEY.
HI.
SHNOODLE!
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED TO MY DOG?
UM, WELL, IT WAS AN ACCIDENT
AND, YOU KNOW, THE WOMAN WHO DID THIS
WOULD NEVER EVER HURT A DOG ON PURPOSE.
SHE'S A VEGETARIAN.
WHAT ARE THESE?
STITCHES?
YEAH, EIGHT OF THEM.
THAT'S 56 TO HIM.
YOU KNOW, ALSO, IF IT'S RAINING
YOU CAN'T LET  HIM LOOK UP TOO LONG
BECAUSE THAT CONE'LL FILL UP REALLY, REALLY FAST.
YEAH. WELL, THANKS
FOR BRINGING BACK WHAT'S LEFT OF HIM.
IS FRANK HOME?
HOW DO YOU KNOW FRANK?
JUST FROM A LONG TIME AGO.
IS HE HERE?
YEAH.
FRANK?
YEAH?
WHAT?
OH, OKAY.
UM, I MEAN FRANK, SR.
HE WENT OUT FOR GROCERIES.
OKAY, SO WILL HE BE BACK SOON?
WELL, HE LEFT FOUR YEARS AGO
SO WE'RE EXPECTING HIM BACK ANY MINUTE NOW.
ALL RIGHT.
I'M I'M GOING TO GO.
I'M SORRY... ABOUT THE DOG, EVERYTHING.
I'M SORRY.
HEY, LADY.
HEY, WAIT UP.
HOW DO YOU KNOW MY DAD?
UM, WELL, I DON'T REALLY.
JUST GENETICALLY.
HE'S KIND OF MY DAD, TOO.
HEAVY.
YEAH.
SO, UM...
DID HE EVER TALK ABOUT ME PHOEBE?
NAH, BUT HE DIDN'T REALLY TALK ABOUT ANYTHING.
OH.
EXCEPT STILTS.
STILTS?
YEAH. HE LOVED STILTS.
THIS ONE TIME, I WAS UPSTAIRS.
I WAS STEALING CIGARETTES OUT OF MY MOM'S PURSE
AND, UH, ALL OF A SUDDEN, I LOOK OVER
AND THERE'S MY DAD'S HEAD BOBBING PAST THE WINDOW.
HE JUST HAD THIS BIG SMILE ON HIS FACE
AND HE WAS WAVING, BECAUSE HE WAS ALWAYS HAPPIEST
WHEN HE WAS ON HIS STILTS.
WOW.
YEAH.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO WITH THAT.
ME NEITHER.
SO, YOU'RE, LIKE, MY BIG SISTER?
YEAH.
THIS IS HUGE.
YOU CAN BUY ME BEER.
I'M NOT GONNA.
OH.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT'S COOL, THOUGH?
IF YOU HAD A FRIEND NAMED PETE
THEN I COULD SAY, "YEAH, I KNOW PETE.
HE'S FRIENDS WITH MY BROTHER."
I GOT A FRIEND NAMED MARK.
THAT'LL WORK, TOO.
COOL. ALL RIGHT.
SO... MAYBE, YOU KNOW
I COULD GIVE YOU A CALL SOMETIME.
WE COULD TALK OR SOMETHING, YOU KNOW.
YEAH. THAT'D BE OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
I'M IN THE BOOK.
OKAY, YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
SO, UM, STILTS, HUH?
YEAH. HEY, YOU KNOW, IF YOU WANT, I CAN TAKE YOU AROUND BACK
AND SHOW YOU WHERE HE HIT HIS HEAD ON THE RAIN GUTTER.
OKAY.
WELL, WE DID IT. WE'RE HERE.
WE ARE STANDING OUR GROUND.
HOW LONG DOES A CUP OF COFFEE TAKE?
WOULD YOU COME ON?!
COME ON!
THANK YOU.
WELL, THERE WE GO.
I THINK WE PROVED OUR POINT.
YOU BURN YOUR MOUTH?
CANNOT FEEL MY TONGUE.
BULLIES. BIG BULLIES.
OH, LOOK WHO'S HERE.
IT'S THE WEENIES.
DID WE NOT MAKE OURSELVES CLEAR THE OTHER DAY?
YES, AND THAT'S WHY WE'RE HERE.
YES. WE'RE STANDING OUR GROUND.
APPARENTLY.
LET'S DO THIS.
WHOA, WHAT DO YOU GOT THERE, A WEAPON?
IT'S A NICE WATCH.
I DON'T WANT TO BREAK IT ON YOUR RIBS.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S DO THIS.
QUESTION.
IF I DON'T CARE ABOUT MY WATCH
CAN I USE IT AS A WEAPON?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WELL, IT'S SHARP. IT'S METAL.
I THINK I CAN DO SOME
YOU KNOW, SERIOUS DAMAGE WITH IT.
NO, YOU CAN'T USE YOUR WATCH.
OKAY.
OR YOUR KEYS.
LOOK, HERE'S WHAT WE'LL DO.
WE'LL PUT ALL KEYS AND WATCHES
IN THE HAT OVER THERE.
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, COME ON, MAN!
LET'S DO THIS ALREADY!
BEFORE I FORGET, ARE WE HITTING FACES?
OF COURSE YOU'RE HITTING FACES!
WHY WOULDN'T YOU HIT FACES?
BECAUSE I HAVE TO WORK ON MONDAY.
I HAVE A BIG PRESENTATION.
ACTUALLY, YOU KNOW, I GOT TO SHOW THIS APARTMENT TOMORROW
AND, YOU KNOW, THIS NO FACES THING
MIGHT NOT BE A BAD IDEA.
OKAY. NOTHING FROM THE NECK UP.
ALL RIGHT.
OR THE WAIST DOWN.
DANA'S OVULATING.
OH, REALLY? YOU GUYS TRYING AGAIN?
YEAH.
SO LET ME JUST GET THIS STRAIGHT.
SO, WE'RE STRICTLY TALKING ABOUT THE MIDDLE?
COME ON!
YOU WANT SOME OF THIS, HUH?!
YOU WANT A PIECE OF THIS, HUH?
I'M STANDING HERE!
HEY, HEY! THOSE GUYS
ARE TAKING OUR STUFF!
WHERE?!
GET OUT OF THE WAY!
LOOK OUT!
GOD! THAT WAS AMAZING.
THAT WAS INCREDIBLE.
YOU GUYS KICKED BUTT.
US? WHAT ABOUT YOU GUYS?
MAN, YOU REALLY GAVE IT TO OL' MR. CLEAN BACK THERE.
HE WAS A BIG GUY.
YEAH, HE WAS, WASN'T HE?
I WOULDN'T KNOW, HAVING MISSED EVERYTHING.
OH, DON'T DO THAT TO YOURSELF.
ANY ONE OF US COULD HAVE TRIPPED OVER
THAT LITTLE GIRL'S JUMP ROPE.
SO, LISTEN, GUYS, ARE WE, UH...
ARE WE OKAY HERE?
WE'RE OKAY.
OKAY. SO, CAN I HAVE MY HAT BACK?
NO.
HUH.
OH, MY GOD-- LOOK AT HER.
HI, MONICA.
HOW'S IT GOING?
HEY, NICE BOOBS.
GUYS, GUYS
CHECK THIS OUT.
?? Young man ??
?? There's no need to feel down  ??
?? I said, young man, pick yourself off the ground ? ?
?? I said, young man... ??
EXCELLENT.
?? There's no need to be unhappy ??
?? It's fun to stay at the Y.M.C.A. ??