ONE OF MY SPECIAL HOMEMADE BROWNIES?
I WILL HAVE ONE.
OH! OH!
YEAH, I'M NOT GOING TO HAVE ONE. THAT'S OKAY.
NO, NO, IT'S JUST MY TOOTH.
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL HAVE ONE.
SO WHAT'S THE MATTER, YOU NEED A DENTIST?
I'VE GOT A GOOD ONE.
THANKS. I HAVE A GOOD ONE, TOO.
I JUST... I CAN'T SEE HIM.
SEE, THAT IS THE PROBLEM
WITH INVISIBLE DENTISTS.
IT'S VERY UNSETTLING
TO SEE ALL THOSE METAL TOOLS
JUST, YOU KNOW, FLYING AROUND.
WHY? WHY CAN'T YOU GO TO HIM?
BECAUSE... EVERY TIME I GO TO THE DENTIST
SOMEBODY DIES.
THAT IS SO WEIRD
BECAUSE EVERY TIME I GO TO THE DENTIST
I LOOK DOWN THE HYGIENIST'S BLOUSE.
PHOEBE...
WHAT, UM... WHAT?
YEAH, YEAH. FIRST THERE WAS MY AUNT MARY
AND THEN THERE WAS JOHN, MY MAILMAN
AND THEN MY COWBOY FRIEND, ALBINO BOB.
AND ALL OF THESE PEOPLE ACTUALLY DIED?
YES. WHILE I WAS IN THE CHAIR.
THAT'S WHY I TAKE SUCH GOOD CARE OF MY TEETH NOW.
YOU KNOW, IT'S NOT ABOUT ORAL HYGIENE.
I FLOSS TO SAVE LIVES.
PHEEBS, COME ON.
YOU DIDN'T KILL ANYBODY.
THESE PEOPLE JUST HAPPENED TO DIE
WHEN YOU WENT TO THE DENTIST.
IT'S JUST A COINCIDENCE.
WELL, TELL THAT TO THEM.
OH, YOU CAN'T! THEY'RE DEAD!
THANKS, GUNTHER.
HI. HI.
UM, COULD I GET A NAPKIN, TOO?
OH, LIKE YOU DON'T ALREADY HAVE EVERYTHING.
OW! OW!
PHOEBE, YOU'RE IN PAIN.
WOULD YOU JUST GO TO THE DENTIST?
JUST GO.
ALL RIGHT, FINE, FINE.
BUT IF YOU'RE MY NEXT VICTIM, DON'T COME BACK AS A POLTERGEIST
WHO, LIKE, SUCKS ME INTO THE TV SET.
I PROMISE.
ALTHOUGH DON'T FEEL LIKE YOU CAN'T VISIT.
HEY, IS CHANDLER HERE?
NO. NO, HE'S NOT.
YOU GUYS, JOEY JUST SAW JANICE
KISSING HER EX HUSBAND.
OH! WHAT?
SO, WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
I MEAN, HOW HOW ARE YOU GOING TO TELL CHANDLER?
WELL, I WAS THINKING ABOUT THAT
AND I THINK THE BEST WAY WOULD BE... TO NOT.
JOEY, YOU CAN'T KEEP THIS TO YOURSELF.
IF YOU KNOW ABOUT THIS, YOU HAVE TO TELL HIM.
IT'LL KILL HIM. I MEAN, IT'LL JUST KILL HIM.
WELL, YOU COULD WAIT TILL I GO TO THE DENTIST.
MAYBE I'LL KILL HIM.
OOH! UGLY NAKED GUY
IS USING HIS NEW HAMMOCK.
IT'S LIKE A PLAY DOH FAT FACTORY.
WELL, I'M GOING TO THE DENTIST
SO LISTEN, OKAY?
JUST BE ON THE LOOKOUT
FOR ANYTHING THAT THAT THAT YOU COULD FALL INTO
OR THAT CAN FALL ON YOU
OR...
OR JUST LOOK OUT!
OKAY, AND, UM...
I ALSO JUST WANT TO...
I JUST WANT TO TELL YOU ALL THAT, UM...
OKAY, I HAVE A PROBLEM.
I HAVE TO GO IN TO WORK FOR A FEW HOURS.
SOME KIDS MESSED UP THE HOMO SAPIEN DISPLAY.
WHAT DID THEY DO?
WELL, THEY PAINTED OVER THE WORD "SAPIEN"
FOR ONE THING.
THEN THEY...
REARRANGED THE FIGURES.
LET'S JUST LEAVE IT AT THAT.
DO YOU WANT ME TO WATCH BEN FOR YOU?
YES. THAT'S WHAT I WAS GOING TO ASK. THANK YOU.
WHOA, WAIT-- HELLO? WHAT ABOUT ME?
YOU... YOU WANT TO WATCH BEN.
YES... THAT WOULD BE GREAT.
NO, I JUST ASKED MONICA
BECAUSE I KNOW HOW EMPTY HER LIFE IS.
HEY, ROSS, I GOT A SCIENCE QUESTION.
IF THE HOMO SAPIENS WERE, IN FACT, HOMO SAPIENS...
ALL RIGHT?
IS THAT WHY THEY'RE EXTINCT?
JOEY, HOMO SAPIENS ARE PEOPLE.
HEY, I'M NOT JUDGING.
I'M JUST ASKING.
LOOK, BENNY. SPOON.
SPOON.
COME ON.
ALL RIGHT, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK HE'S BORED.
HERE. BEN, YOU WANT TO PLAY THE AIRPLANE GAME?
YOU WANT TO SHOW RACHEL?
COME HERE. YOU WANT TO DO SOMETHING FUN?
OKAY... WHEE!
OH!
WHEE!
OH... WHEE!
YOU'RE SO BRAVE.
YOU'RE SO BRAVE. YES, YOU ARE.
OKAY.
HONEY, HE'S FINE.
LET'S JUST PUT HIM DOWN.
COME HERE, BABE. YES, YOU'RE SUCH A GOOD BOY.
HOW COULD YOU DO THAT TO HIM?!
ROSS TRUSTED ME. WHAT IS HE GOING TO SAY?!
HE WON'T SAY ANYTHING BECAWE'RE NOT GOING TO TELL HIM.
WE'RE NOT? NO, WE'RE NOT.
ALL RIGHT, I LIKE THAT.
OKAY.
OKAY, SO WE'RE OKAY.
WE'RE OKAY, WE'RE OKAY, AREN'T WE?
NO, WE'RE NOT OKAY. WE'RE NOT OKAY.
THERE'S A BUMP. THERE'S A BUMP.
LOOK, THERE'S A BUMP.
OH, MY GOD. WELL, PU SH IT IN! PUSH IT IN!
I CANNOT PUSH IT IN!
OKAY, WE'RE GOING TO NEED A DISTRACTION.
OKAY.
THAT'S IT.
I GOT IT! OKAY.
THE SECOND THAT ROSS WALKS IN THAT DOOR
I WANT YOU TO TAKE HIM BACK TO YOUR BEDROOM
AND YOU DO WHATEVER IT IS THAT YOU DO
THAT MAKES HIM GO, "REEE"!
OR...
WE COULD PUT A HAT ON HIS HEAD.
A HAT! YES!
WE NEED A HAT.
WHERE ARE WE GOING TO FIND A TINY, LITTLE HAT?
OH, OH, OH!
I'LL GET RAINY DAY BEAR!
BECAUSE HE'LL KNOW WHAT TO DO?
OH, MY GOD, YOU'RE A GENIUS!
OH, GOD. IT'S KIND OF SEWN ON, THOUGH.
GIVE IT, GIVE IT!
OH! OH!
OH, IT'S JUST LIKE A BLOODBATH IN HERE TODAY.
HEY, HOLD ON A SECOND.
HOLD ON A SECOND.
DO YOU THINK THESE PEARLS ARE NICE?
I'D REALLY PREFER A MOUNTAIN BIKE.
JANICE'S BIRTHDAY IS COMING UP.
I WANT TO GET HER SOMETHING SPECIAL.
COME IN HERE WITH ME.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WAIT. WHOA.
YOU, UH... YOU WANT TO GET HER SOMETHING SPECIAL
GET HER FLOWERS, GET HER CANDY.
GET HER GUM. GIRLS LOVE GUM.
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
"DEAR JANICE, HAVE A HUBBA BUBBA BIRTHDAY."
I WOULD LIKE TO GET HER SOMETHING SERIOUS.
OH, YOU WANT SOMETHING SERIOUS.
YOU KNOW WHAT YOU SHOULD DO
YOU SHOULD GET HER ONE OF THOSE, UM...
BARIUM ENEMAS.
THOSE ARE DEAD SERIOUS.
AND YOU KNOW SHE'LL NEVER GET ONE FOR HERSELF.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, I'M GOING TO GO IN HERE
AND YOU DON'T BUY ME ANYTHING EVER.
NO, NO, YOU CAN'T! YOU CAN'T, OKAY? YOU CAN'T.
YOU CAN'T BUY HER PEARLS. YOU JUST CAN'T.
YOU CAN'T, YOU CAN'T, YOU CAN'T.
WHY NOT?
OH, GOD. UH... OKAY.
HERE'S THE THING...
THIS IS THE THING...
OKAY, THE THING IS...
WHAT IS THE THING? OKAY.
I WENT DOWN TO THE MATTRESS KING SHOWROOM AND...
AND I SAW JANICE KISSING HER EX HUSBAND.
WHAT?
THEY WERE IN HIS OFFICE.
WELL, SHE... SHE WOULDN'T DO THAT.
SHE'S SHE'S WITH ME.
I'M TELLING YOU, MAN, I SAW IT.
WELL, YOU'RE WRONG, OKAY? YOU'RE WRONG.
I'M NOT WRONG.
I WISH I WAS.
I'M SORRY.
I BET THAT BARIUM ENEMA
DOESN'T SOUND SO BAD NOW, HUH?
IT JUST MAKES MORE SENSE AS AN ENSEMBLE.
BESIDES, IT TAKES
THE FOCUS OFF THE HAT.
NO... OH!
YOU'RE ALIVE! YOU'RE ALIVE!
SEE, PHEEBS?
I PROMISED YOU NO ONE WOULD DIE, DIDN'T I?
YEAH, WELL, WE'LL SEE ABOUT THAT. CAN I USE YOUR PHONE?
I WANT TO CALL EVERYONE I KNOW.
SURE. WE HAVE NO MONEY.
GO AHEAD.
HEY, YOU'RE NOT DEAD!
OKAY, SEE YOU.
MONKA.
OH, MY GOD.
HE JUST SAID MY NAME.
DID YOU HEAR?
YEAH.
MONKA BANG.
OKAY, I HEARD THAT.
DID HE JUST SAY, "MONICA BANG"?
UH HUH.
OH, MY GOD!
HE'S GOING TO RAT ME OUT!
MONKA BANG.
OH!
SWEETIE! SWEETIE, YOU NEED TO STOP SAYING THAT, NOW.
THAT'S NO BIG DEAL.
IT'S NOT EVEN WORTH MENTIONING.
YOU SEE, WE ALL DO IT ALL THE TIME.
SEE? WATCH THIS.
BEN! BEN! BEN!
OW! MONICA BANG.
EVERYBODY BANG.
BEN BANG.
RACHEL BANG.
BANG, RACHEL. BANG!
OKAY.
OH, ISN'T IT FUN?
LOOK AT THAT.
WE ALL DO IT.
OKAY, I'M STOPPING NOW.
YOU OKAY?
OH, YEAH.
YOU KNOW, IF IT'S NOT A HEADBOARD
IT'S JUST NOT WORTH IT.
HOW'S MY BING A LING?
UH... I DON'T KNOW.
Y YOU TELL ME.
ANYTHING YOU, UH...
WANT TO TELL ME?
BECAUSE IF YOU... YOU SHOULD...
IF YOU'D... TELL ME.
WHY ARE YOUR EYES SO WIDE?
YOU TELL ME.
MAYBE IT'S BECAUSE I WAS JUST FOOLING AROUND WITH MY EX.
OH, NO, NO! NO, NO, NO, NO!
THAT WAS YOU!
OH, MY GOD!
ALL RIGHT.
HOW DID YOU KNOW? JOEY TOLD ME.
HE SAW YOU TWO KISSING.
IN THE PARK?
NO. IN HIS OFFICE.
HOW MANY KISSES WERE THERE?
JUST THOSE TWO!
WH WH WHY?!
W WHY? WHY WHY WAS THERE KISSING?
THERE SHOULD BE NO KISSING.
OH, I'M SORRY, HONEY.
I'M SO, SO... HAH!
I'M SO, SO SORRY.
I JUST... HAH!
WHEN I...
OH, WHAT HAPPENED WAS THAT I...
I CAN'T BREATHE!
CAN YOU GET ME A BAG OR SOMETHING?
YEAH.
HERE, HERE.
THERE.
IT'S THE RECEIPT.
I'LL TAKE IT.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK.
I'VE GOT TO KNOW--
ARE YOU FINISHED WITH ME?
ARE YOU FINISHED WITH HIM?
DO YOU STILL LOVE HIM?
DO YOU STILL LOVE ME?
ALL RIGHT, LOOK.
I'M GOING TO NEED AN ACTUAL ANSWER HERE, OKAY?
SO, WHICH IS IT--
HIM OR ME?
I DON'T KNOW.
OKAY, IF YOU'RE ALIVE
YOU ANSWER YOUR PHONE!
OKAY, BEN, I WON'T TELL YOUR DADDY
THAT YOU HAD ICE CREAM BEFORE DINNER
IF YOU WON'T TELL HIM
ABOUT OUR LITTLE BONKING INCIDENT.
MONICA, NUMBER ONE, I DON'T THINK BEN
UNDERSTANDS THE CONCEPT OF BRIBERY.
AND NUMBER TWO...
WHAT?
YOU SAID "NUMBER TWO."
I ALSO SAID "NUMBER ONE."
I KNOW.
HEY, EVERYONE.
HI.
HOW'S MY LITTLE BOY?
HE'S PERFECT, AREN'T YOU, BEN?
HE'S NEVER BEEN BETTER.
WHAT DID YOU DO, TAKE HIM WHALING?
MONKA.
OH, MY GOD.
HE JUST SAID YOUR NAME.
THAT'S GREAT.
GOOD JOB, BEN.
MONKA BANG.
OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
THAT'S WHAT I'D SOUND LIKE IF I EXPLODED.
WHOO HOO! THE CURSE IS BROKEN.
I CALLED EVERYBODY I KNOW, AND EVERYONE IS ALIVE.
HUH.
WHAT?
UGLY NAKED GUY LOOKS AWFULLY STILL.
OH, MY GOD.
I KILLED HIM. I KILLED ANOTHER ONE.
AND THIS CURSE IS GETTING STRONGER, TOO--
TO BRING DOWN SOMETHING THAT BIG?
WELL, MAYBE HE'S JUST TAKING A NAP.
I'M TELLING YOU
HE HASN'T MOVED SINCE THIS MORNING.
WE SHOULD CALL SOMEBODY.
AND TELL THEM WHAT?
THAT THE NAKED GUY WE STARE AT ALL THE TIME ISN'T MOVING?
BUT WE'VE GOT TO FIND OUT IF HE IS ALIVE.
YEAH, BUT HOW ARE WE GOING TO DO THAT?
THERE'S NO WAY.
WELL, THERE IS ONE WAY.
HIS WINDOW'S OPEN.
I SAY... WE POKE HIM.
HEY.
YOU KNOW HOW WE SAVE
ALL THOSE CHOPSTICKS FOR NO REASON
WHEN WE GET CHINESE FOOD?
YEAH.
WELL, NOW WE GOT A REASON.
WHAT?
WE'RE FASHIONING A VERY LONG POKING DEVICE.
ALL RIGHT.
HEY, UH... WHAT'S THE MATTER?
I TALKED TO JANICE.
OH, MY GOD.
IS SHE GOING BACK TO HIM?
SHE DOESN'T KNOW.
SAYS SHE LOVES US BOTH.
YOU KNOW, I WOKE UP
THIS MORNING, I WAS IN LOVE.
I WAS HAPPY.
YOU KNOW, IT SERVES ME RIGHT
FOR BUYING THAT 12 PACK OF CONDOMS.
AND NOW, I CAN'T EVEN RETURN THEM
BECAUSE SHE CHOKED ON THE RECEIPT.
WHAT ARE YOU, UH...
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU KNOW? WHAT, WHAT WOULD YOU DO?
UH, IT DOESN'T MATTER WHAT I'D DO.
COME ON.
COME ON. TELL ME.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE, UH...
PROBABLY NOT GOING TO WANT TO HEAR THIS
BUT, UH...
IF IT WAS ME--
AND THIS IS JUST ME--
I WOULD, UH...
I WOULD BOW OUT.
WHAT?!
WHAT ARE YOU...
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
THEY HAVE A KID TOGETHER.
YOU KNOW?
THEY'RE LIKE...
THEY'RE LIKE A FAMILY....
AND IF, I DON'T KNOW
IF THERE'S A CHANCE THEY CAN MAKE THAT WORK
I KNOW I WOULDN'T WANT TO BE THE GUY
WHO STOOD IN THE WAY OF THAT.
YOU OKAY?
YOU, UH...
YOU WANT TO COME POKE A NUDE GUY?
WELL, HE'S FINALLY ASLEEP.
ABOUT THAT, UH, BUMP ON HIS HEAD...
ARE, UH, ARE YOU SURE IT'S A NEW BUMP?
I MEAN, NO OFFENSE
BUT I'VE ALWAYS THOUGHT OF BEN
AS A FAIRLY BUMPY HEADED CHILD.
IT'S OKAY IF HE BUMPS HIS HEAD.
KIDS BUMP THEIR HEADS ALL THE TIME.
IT WAS YOUR FIRST TIME BABY SITTING.
I'M SURE YOU DID THE BEST YOU COULD.
I DID.
I KNOW. I'M JUST SAYING
YOU HAVE TO WATCH THEM ALL THE TIME.
I DID!
I WATCHED. I WATCHED.
I WATCHED MONICA BANG HIS HEAD
AGAINST THAT THING!
MONICA DID IT?
MONICA?
YEAH?
DID YOU NOTICE ANYTHING WEIRD
ABOUT BEN TODAY?
NO. WHY?
WELL, I WAS JUST PLAYING WITH HIM
AND, YOU KNOW, WE WERE DOING THE ALPHABET SONG
WHICH HE USED TO BE REALLY GOOD AT
BUT SUDDENLY HE'S JUST LEAVING OUT "E" AND "F."
IT'S LIKE THEY JUST, UH, I DON'T KNOW
FELL OUT OF HIS HEAD.
REALLY?
OH, AND ALSO, HE'S, HE'S WALKING...
KIND OF FUNNY.
YEAH, I MEAN
IT'S LIKE HIS LEFT LEG
IS MOVING A LOT FASTER
THAN HIS RIGHT LEG.
YEAH, HE'S IN THERE
JUST SORT OF, YOU KNOW...
OH, MY GOD, I WRECKED YOUR BABY!
I HOPE IT'S STILL FUNNY WHEN YOU'RE IN HELL.
YOU JERK.
YOU KNOW HOW MUCH I LOVE THAT KID.
MONKA BANG! MONKA BANG!
OW.
I'LL GET THE HAT.
JANICE, I HAVE SOMETHING I NEED TO TELL YOU
AND I WANT YOU TO LET ME GET THROUGH IT
BECAUSE IT'S...
IT'S, IT'S NOT GOING TO BE EASY.
OKAY.
I THINK YOU SHOULD GO BACK WITH GARY.
I DON'T WANT TO BE THE GUY THAT BREAKS UP A FAMILY.
YOU KNOW, WHEN MY PARENTS SPLIT UP
IT WAS BECAUSE OF THAT GUY
AND WHENEVER I WOULD SEE HIM
I WOULD ALWAYS THINK, "YOU'RE THE REASON.
YOU ARE WHY THEY'RE NOT TOGETHER."
AND I HATED THAT GUY.
AND IT DIDN'T MATTER HOW NICE HE WAS
OR, YOU KNOW, HOW HAPPY HE MADE MY DAD.
WOW.
YEAH, WELL...
IT'S THE RIGHT THING TO DO.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
OH, GOD.
BUT BEFORE I CAN SAY... GOOD BYE...
THERE'S SOMETHING I REALLY NEED YOU TO KNOW, CHANDLER.
THE WAY I FEEL ABOUT YOU...
IT'S LIKE I FINALLY UNDERSTAND
WHAT LIONEL RICHIE'S BEEN SINGING ABOUT.
YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, WHAT WE HAVE--
IT'S LIKE MOVIE LOVE.
YOU'RE MY SOUL MATE.
AND I CAN'T BELIEVE
WE'RE NOT GOING TO BE SPENDING
THE REST OF OUR LIVES TOGETHER.
THEN DON'T LEAVE ME.
WHAT?
FORGET WHAT I SAID.
I WAS BABBLING.
PICK ME.
NO, YOU WERE RIGHT. YOU WERE RIGHT.
I'VE GOT TO GIVE MY MARRIAGE ANOTHER CHANCE.
NO, YOU DON'T.
NO, NO, NO.
I SAY YOU HAVE TO GIVE YOUR DIVORCE ANOTHER CHANCE.
SWEETIE, YOU SHOULD NOT HAVE TO SETTLE
FOR JUST HALF MY HEART.
I'LL SETTLE FOR HALF YOUR HEART.
I'LL SETTLE FOR A QUARTER OF YOUR HEART.
I'LL SETTLE FOR A LITTLE... A TINY... A VENTRICLE.
I'M SORRY.
OH, DON'T GO.
NO, I I GOT TO GO.
NO.
NO, NO.
HONEY, HONEY...
PEOPLE ARE LOOKING.
I DON'T CARE.
I DON'T CARE!
YEAH, UM... OKAY.
I'M, I'M LEAVING NOW.
YOU CAN'T LEAVE!
I HAVE YOUR SHOE!
GOOD BYE, CHANDLER BING.
RACHEL HAS THOSE IN BURGUNDY.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, REMEMBER: SOMETHING THIS BIG AND LONG
IS GOING TO BE VERY DIFFICULT TO MANEUVER.
FORTUNATELY, I HAVE A LOT OF EXPERIENCE
IN THAT AREA.
WHAT ARE YOU, 12 TODAY?
CAN WE PLEASE FOCUS HERE?
A NAKED MAN'S LIFE HANGS IN THE BALANCE.
I'M TELLING YOU, HE'S DEAD.
WHAT WE'RE ABOUT TO HAVE HERE
IS A DEAD FAT GUY ON A STICK.
ALL RIGHT. LADIES AND GENTLEMEN, LET'S POKE.
STEADY, STEADY...
OKAY, A LITTLE HIGHER.
CAREFUL OF THE ANGLE.
OKAY, OKAY.
WE'RE APPROACHING THE WINDOW.
THREAD THE NEEDLE.
HE'S ALIVE!
HE'S ALIVE!!!
AND YET WE'RE STILL POKING HIM.
OKAY, RETRACT THE DEVICE.
RETRACT THE DEVICE!
HE DOES NOT LOOK HAPPY.
HEY, NOW HE'S SHOWING US HIS POKING DEVICE.
HEY, THAT'S NEVER GOING TO MAKE IT
ALL THE WAY OVER HERE, BUDDY.
HA!
?? I'LL HOLD YOU CLOSE IN MY ARMS ??
?? I CAN'T RESIST YOUR CHARM ??
?? AND LOVE... ??
?? LOVE... ??
?? I'LL BE A FOOL ??
?? FOR YOU, I'M SURE ??
?? YOU KNOW I DON'T MIND ? ?
?? OH, YOU KNOW I DON'T MIND... ??
?? YES! ?? ?? AND YES! ??
?? YOU MEAN THE WORLD TO ME, OH... ??
?? I KNOW ??
?? I'VE FOUND IN YOU ??
?? MY ENDLESS LO... ??
?? MY ENDLESS... ??
?? LOVE ??
?? LOVE... LO... LOVE. ??