Welcome, everybody.
Welcome to Amazing Discoveries!
OH!
OH, IT'S ON AGAIN!
YOU GUYS, CAN WE PLEASE NOT WATCH THIS?
SHH! SHH! SHH!
Folks, this ever happen to you?
You go in the refrigerator to get a nice glass of milk
but these darn cartons
are so flingin'-flangin' hard to open?
You said it, Mike.
Oh! Oh! There's got to be
a better way.
And there is, Kevin.
CAN WE PLEASE TURN THIS OFF?
NO WAY, KEVIN.
What if I told you
that there's a revolutionary new product that guarantees
you'll never have to open up milk cartons again?
Meet the Milkmaster 2000!
ARE YOU INTRIGUED?
YOU'RE FLINGIN'-FLANGIN' RIGHT I AM.
This is his first time.
He's never used this product before.
You're going to see how easy this is to do.
Go ahead. This works in any milk carton.
Wow, it is easy.
Now I can have milk every day.
I CAN'T WATCH THIS ANYMORE, YOU GUYS.
ALL RIGHT, YOU'VE SUFFERED ENOUGH.
WE'LL CHANGE IT.
How many times has this happened to you?
THERE ARE NO GOOD MOVIES.
SO YOU CAN BUNNY BUMP AGAINST MY BACK.
HEY.
HEY, MAN. WHAT'S UP?
MAYBE YOU CAN TELL ME.
MY AGENT WOULD LIKE TO KNOW WHY I DIDN'T SHOW UP
AT THE AUDITION I DIDN'T KNOW I HAD TODAY--
THE FIRST GOOD THING SHE GETS ME IN WEEKS.
HOW COULD YOU NOT GIVE ME THE MESSAGE?
WELL, I TELL YOU, I DO ENJOY GUILT...
BUT, UH, IT WASN'T ME.
YES, IT WAS.
IT WAS HIM. UH HUH.
OKAY, IT WAS ME.
HOW WAS IT YOU?
WELL, IT WAS ALL SO CRAZY, YOU KNOW.
I MEAN, CHANDLER WAS IN THE CLOSET COUNTING TO TEN
AND HE WAS UP TO SEVEN AND I HADN'T FOUND A PLACE
TO HIDE YET.
I... I MEANT TO TELL YOU
AND I WROTE IT ALL DOWN ON MY HAND.
SEE? ALL OF IT.
YEP, THAT'S MY AUDITION.
SEE? NOW THIS IS WHY I KEEP NOTEPADS EVERYWHERE.
YEP, AND THAT'S WHY
WE DON'T INVITE YOU TO PLAY.
WHAT IS THE GREAT TRAGEDY HERE?
YOU GO GET YOURSELF ANOTHER APPOINTMENT.
WELL, ESTELLE TRIED, YOU KNOW.
THE CASTING DIRECTOR TOLD HER I MISSED MY CHANCE.
WELL, THAT IS UNFAIR.
I'LL CALL HER.
I'LL TELL HER IT WAS TOTALLY MY FAULT.
PHEEBS, YOU CAN'T DO THAT.
THE CASTING DIRECTOR DOESN'T TALK TO FRIENDS.
SHE ONLY TALKS TO AGENTS.
WHAT A SAD LITTLE LIFE SHE MUST LEAD.
OKAY. OOH.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING? WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
NO, NO, NO, I KNOW, I KNOW.
OOH.
HI, THIS IS CAITLIN
FROM PHOEBE BUFFAY'S OFFICE.
UM... IS ANNE THERE FOR PHOEBE?
SHE'LL KNOW WHAT IT'S ABOUT.
HANG UP. HANG UP RIGHT...
ANNIE?
HI. LISTEN
WE'VE GOT A PROBLEM WITH JOEY TRIBBIANI.
APPARENTLY HE MISSED HIS AUDITION.
WHO DID YOU SPEAK TO IN MY OFFICE?
ESTELLE?
NO. I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M GOING TO DO WITH HER.
ALL RIGHT, SO YOUR HUSBAND LEAVES YOU
AND THEN BURNS DOWN THE APARTMENT.
THE WORLD DOES NOT STOP.
IS ANYBODY ELSE SCARED?
RIGHT, WELL, LOOK, IF JOEY LOSES THIS AUDITION
THEN THAT IS IT FOR ESTELLE.
I DON'T CARE.
ANNIE, YOU ARE A DOLL.
WHAT TIME CAN YOU SEE HIM?
I NEED A PEN.
GET THE WOMAN A PAD! GET THE WOMAN A PAD!
A PAD! A PAD!
OH, NOW YOU WANT A PAD.
HUH.
WELL, THAT'S FUNNY.
UGLY, NAKED GUY IS STILL NAKED
BUT HIS DOG'S WEARING A SWEATER.
HEY!
HERE'S MY BOY.
AND HERE'S HIS... BARBIE.
WHAT'S, UH...?
WHAT'S MY BOY DOING WITH A BARBIE?
HE PICKED IT OUT OF THE TOY STORE HIMSELF.
HE LOVES IT.
HE CARRIES IT EVERYWHERE.
IT'S LIKE A SECURITY BLANKET--
BUT WITH SKI BOOTS AND A KICKY BERET.
YEAH, IT'S-- IT'S CUTE.
WHY-- WHY DOES HE HAVE IT AGAIN?
SO HE'S GOT A DOLL. SO WHAT?
UNLESS YOU'RE AFRAID
HE'S GOING TO GROW UP TO BE... IN SHOW BUSINESS.
THIS WOULDN'T HAVE ANYTHING
TO DO WITH THE FACT THAT HE'S BEING RAISED
BY TWO WOMEN, WOULD IT?
YOU KNOW WHAT? IT'S FINE.
IF YOU'RE OKAY WITH THE BARBIE THING
SO AM I.
GIVE DADDY THE BARBIE.
DON'T YOU WANT TO PLAY
WITH A MONSTER TRUCK?
NO?
OKAY, OOH, OOH, HOW ABOUT
A DINO SOLDIER.
ROSS, YOU ARE SO PATHETIC.
WHY CAN'T YOUR SON JUST PLAY WITH HIS DOLL?
I GOT TO GO TO WORK.
HAS ANYBODY SEEN MY LEFT BOOB?
I LOVED THAT MOVIE.
THERE IT IS.
JOEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'M SORRY.
IT JUST FELT NICE.
JOE, JOE, ANSWER THE PHONE.
HEY, I ONLY GOT ONE GOOD ARM.
YOU SHOULD BE DOING STUFF FOR ME.
GO GET ME A SWEATER.
JUST DO IT, OKAY? IT'S JANICE
AND IF I GET IT, I'M GOING TO HAVE TO SEE HER TONIGHT.
OH, THAT'S GREAT.
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO SEE HER TONIGHT.
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
WHY DON'T YOU WANT TO SEE JANICE?
OKAY, LAST NIGHT AT DINNER WHEN THE MEALS CAME
SHE PUT HALF HER CHICKEN PICCATA ON MY PLATE
AND THEN SHE TOOK ALL MY TOMATOES.
AND THAT'S BAD BECAUSE...
YOU HATE CHICKEN PICCATA?
NO.
YOU DIDN'T WANT TO SHARE YOUR TOMATOES.
TOMATOES ARE VERY IMPORTANT TO YOU.
NO. IT'S LIKE ALL OF A SUDDEN, WE WERE THIS COUPLE, OKAY?
AND THIS ALARM STARTED GOING OFF IN MY HEAD--
"RUN FOR YOUR LIFE! GET OUT OF THE BUILDING!"
OH, MEN ARE UNBELIEVABLE.
JANICE JUST THOUGHT SHE WAS GIVING YOU CHICKEN.
SHE DIDN'T THINK SHE WAS GIVING YOU SCARY CHICKEN.
WHAT IS IT WITH YOU PEOPLE?
I MEAN, THE MINUTE YOU START TO FEEL SOMETHING
YOU HAVE TO RUN AWAY?
I KNOW, THAT...
THAT'S WHY I DON'T WANT TO GO TONIGHT.
I'M AFRAID I'M GOING TO SAY SOMETHING STUPID.
OH, YOU MEAN LIKE THAT GUY THING
WHERE YOU ACT ALL MEAN AND DISTANT
UNTIL YOU GET US TO BREAK UP WITH YOU.
HEY, YOU KNOW ABOUT THAT?
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, WHAT DO I DO?
I WANT TO GET PAST THIS.
I DON'T WANT TO BE AFRAID OF THE COMMITMENT THING.
I WANT TO GO THROUGH THE TUNNEL
TO THE OTHER SIDE.
WHERE THERE'S NO FEAR OF COMMITMENT.
SO DO WE HAVE ANY...?
DO WE HAVE ANY THOUGHTS HERE?
WELL, I'VE NEVER BEEN THROUGH THE TUNNEL MYSELF
BECAUSE, AS I UNDERSTAND IT, YOU'RE NOT ALLOWED
TO GO THROUGH WITH MORE THAN ONE GIRL
IN THE CAR, RIGHT?
BUT IT SEEMS TO ME
IT'S PRETTY MUCH LIKE ANYTHING ELSE, YOU KNOW?
FACE YOUR FEAR.
YOU HAVE A FEAR OF HEIGHTS
YOU GO TO THE TOP OF THE BUILDING.
YOU'RE AFRAID OF BUGS...
GET A BUG.
RIGHT?
IN THIS CASE
YOU HAVE A FEAR OF COMMITMENT.
SO I SAY YOU GO IN THERE AND YOU BE
THE MOST COMMITTED GUY THERE EVER WAS.
AMAZINGLY, THAT MAKES SENSE.
DO YOU THINK?
OH, YEAH. GO FOR IT, MAN.
JUMP OFF THE HIGH DIVE.
STARE DOWN THE BARREL OF THE GUN.
PEE INTO THE WIND.
JOE, I ASSURE YOU, IF I'M STARING DOWN
THE BARREL OF A GUN, I'M GOING TO BE PRETTY MUCH
PEEING EVERY WHICH WAY.
YOU GUYS, LISTEN TO THIS
AND TELL ME WHAT YOU THINK, OKAY?
OKAY.
THAT'S INTERESTING.
HONEY...
OH, BECAUSE IT'S THE BEEPER.
OH, IT'S YOUR AUDITION FROM THIS MORNING!
CAN I USE THE PHONE AGAIN?
SURE, PHEEBS. YOU KNOW, THAT'S WHAT IT'S THERE FOR--
EMERGENCIES AND PRETEND AGENTS.
COME ON, BABY, COME ON.
HI. I HAVE PHOEBE BUFFAY
RETURNING A PAGE.
WELL, SHE'S IN HER CAR.
I'LL HAVE TO PATCH YOU THROUGH.
VERY NICE TOUCH.
OKAY, GO AHEAD.
TALK TO HER.
HI, ANNIE?
FANTASTIC.
YOU GOT IT!
OH, OKAY.
WILL HE WORK FOR SCALE, YOU ASK ME?
WELL, I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT.
EXCEPT THAT I DO, AND HE WILL.
GREAT. YOU ARE SUCH A SWEETHEART.
I WOULD LOVE TO HAVE LUNCH WITH YOU.
HOW ABOUT WE HAVE LUNCH NEXT...
OOP. WENT THROUGH A TUNNEL.
UNBELIEVABLE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
HEY, IT WAS REALLY FUN.
I'VE NEVER TALKED ON A CAR PHONE BEFORE.
YOU WERE SO AMAZING.
COULD YOU DO ME THIS HUGE FAVOR?
SEE, THERE'S THIS ONE OTHER AUDITION THAT I REALLY, REALLY WANT
AND ESTELLE COULDN'T GET ME IN.
OH, I DON'T KNOW. I MEAN, IT WAS FUN ONE TIME, BUT...
COME ON, PLEASE?
IT WOULD JUST BE THIS ONE MORE.
WELL, ACTUALLY IT'S TWO.
TWO?
YEAH... WELL, REALLY IT'S THREE.
PLEASE? YOU'RE SO GOOD AT IT.
I LOVE YOU.
OKAY, I'LL DO IT.
BUT JUST THESE THREE, RIGHT?
NO, IT'S FOUR.
SO HOW COME YOU WANTED TO EAT IN TONIGHT?
BECAUSE I WANTED TO, UH...
GIVE-- GIVE YOU THIS.
OH, ARE YOU A PUPPY.
CONTACT PAPER.
YOU NEVER REALLY KNOW
WHAT TO SAY WHEN SOMEONE YOU'RE SLEEPING WITH
GIVES YOU CONTACT PAPER.
WELL, WAIT, THERE'S MORE.
SEE, THE CONTACT PAPER IS TO GO IN...
YOUR BRAND NEW DRAWER.
SEE, THE DRAWER ACTUALLY GOES IN MY DRESSER.
OH, YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO DO THIS.
YES, I DID.
BECAUSE YOU'RE MY GIRLFRIEND.
AND THAT'S WHAT GIRLFRIENDS SHOULD GET.
OH, WELL, I GOT TO BUY A VOWEL...
BECAUSE "O" MY GOD!
WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT
THAT SOMEDAY CHANDLER BING WOULD BUY ME A DRAWER?
WELL, NOT ME.
BUT THAT'S WHAT'S HAPPENED.
AND... AND THERE'S MORE.
WE SHOULD TAKE A TRIP.
WE SHOULD?
YEP. WE'RE A COUPLE, AND THAT'S WHAT COUPLES DO.
AND I WANT TO MEET YOUR PARENTS.
WE SHOULD TAKE A TRIP WITH YOUR PARENTS.
I DON'T THINK WE NEED TO
BECAUSE YOU'RE TRIPPING ME OUT RIGHT NOW.
ARE YOU OKAY?
I AM.
I ACTUALLY AM.
I MEAN, THIS IS AMAZING.
MY ENTIRE LIFE, I HAVE FEARED THIS PLACE.
AND NOW THAT I'M HERE
IT'S LIKE, WHAT WAS THE BIG DEAL?
I MEAN, I COULD PROBABLY SAY, "LET'S MOVE IN TOGETHER"
AND I'D BE OKAY.
YOU PROBABLY WANT US TO MOVE IN TOGETHER?
IT DOESN'T SCARE ME.
YEAH, WELL, IT SCARES ME.
I MEAN, I'M NOT EVEN DIVORCED YET, CHANDLER.
YOU KNOW, YOU JUST INVITED ME OVER HERE FOR PASTA
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT MOVING IN TOGETHER.
I WASN'T EVEN THAT HUNGRY.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT'S GETTING REALLY LATE, AND I SHOULD JUST, UM...
OH, NO. DON'T GO.
I'VE SCARED YOU.
I'VE SAID TOO MUCH.
I'M HOPELESS AND AWKWARD
AND DESPERATE FOR LOVE.
HEY, JANICE, IT'S ME.
UM... YEAH, I JUST WANTED TO APOLOGIZE IN ADVANCE
FOR HAVING CHASED YOU DOWN THE STREET.
BYE BYE.
HERE YOU GO, HONEY.
THIS WILL HELP.
SO I FINALLY CATCH UP TO HER
AND SHE SAYS THIS RELATIONSHIP'S GOING TOO FAST
AND WE HAVE TO SLOW DOWN.
EWW, THAT IS NEVER GOOD.
THEN I GOT ALL... NEEDY AND CLINGY.
YOU DIDN'T BEG , DID YOU?
I SAID "PLEASE."
WELL, WAS IT "PLEASE"
WITH ONE "E" IN THE MIDDLE OF IT
OR LOTS OF "E's"?
OH, DEAR LORD, I BEGGED.
OKAY, NOW WAIT A MINUTE.
MAYBE IT'S NOT SO BAD.
HOW DID YOU LEAVE IT?
SHE SAID SHE'D CALL ME.
OH! OH!
OH, GOD.
WELCOME TO OUR SIDE
OF THE TUNNEL.
THIS ICE CREAM TASTES LIKE CRAP, BY THE WAY.
YEAH. WELL, THAT'S THAT LOW CAL, NON DAIRY SOY MILK JUNK.
WE SAVE THE REAL STUFF FOR THE TRULY TERMINAL CASES.
WHEN YOU START GETTING SCREWED OVER ALL THE TIME
YOU GOTTA SWITCH TO LOW FAT.
YEAH, YOU DO.
SO, YOU... YOU DON'T THINK I'M TERMINAL?
NO. NOT AT ALL.
YOU'RE NOT TERMINAL.
YOU JUST NEED SOME DAMAGE CONTROL.
OKAY. OKAY. SO, SHOULD I CALL HER?
NO! NO!
IT'S A VERY CRITICAL TIME RIGHT NOW.
IF YOU FEEL YOURSELF REACHING FOR THAT PHONE
YOU GO SHOE SHOPPING.
YOU GET YOUR BUTT IN A BUBBLE BATH.
IF YOU WANT HER BACK
YOU HAVE GOT TO START ACTING ALOOF.
ALOOF?
SHE NEEDS TO KNOW THAT YOU'RE NOT NEEDY.
RIGHT. SO WHAT YOU HAVE TO DO IS
YOU HAVE TO ACCIDENTALLY RUN INTO HER ON PURPOSE
AND THEN ACT ALOOF.
AND THEN I'LL BE OKAY?
YEAH. I THINK SO.
SO I'M NOT GOING TO LOSE HER?
OH, HONEY, YOU'RE NOT A TOTAL LOSER.
I SAID, "SO I'M NOT GOING TO LOSE HER?"
OH.
GUESS WHO'S HERE.
IT'S THE TOUGHEST GUY IN TOYLAND, BEN.
?? REAL AMERICAN HERO ??
?? I'M G.I. JOE... ??
DROP THE BARBIE.
G.I. JOE?
YOU REALLY THINK HE'S GOING TO FALL
FOR THAT?
G.I. JOE?
COOL. CAN I PLAY?
LOOK, BEN.
IT'S A TOY THAT PROTECTS U.S. OIL INTERESTS OVERSEAS.
GO, JOE! GO, JOE!
HELLO... OH.
PHOEBE, THERE YOU ARE.
NO. IT'S NOT. SORRY.
BUT, PHOEBE, WAIT. WAIT.
PHOEBE. PHOEBE.
OH, JOEY.
OH, OKAY.
SEE, I DIDN'T RECOGNIZE YOU IN THOSE... PANTS.
LISTEN, THAT TV MOVIE I WENT IN FOR--
DID YOU HEAR ANYTHING?
I THINK I GOT A SHOT AT IT.
YES. THEY CALLED.
YOU DIDN'T GET IT.
OKAY? I MEAN, YOU DIDN'T GET IT.
I'M SORRY.
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S OKAY.
THESE THINGS HAPPEN.
BUT THEY SHOULDN'T HAPPEN.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU'RE IN A TERRIBLE, TERRIBLE BUSINESS.
OH, GOD, I DON'T WANT TO BE
THE PERSON WHO MAKES YOUR FACE LOOK LIKE THAT.
I'M... I'M OKAY. SEE?
NOW YOU'RE SAD AND CREEPY.
YOU KNOW WHAT? I'M SORRY.
I QUIT. OKAY?
NO, NO. YOU CAN'T QUIT.
YOU'RE THE BEST AGENT I EVER HAD.
LOOK, PHEEBS
REJECTION IS PART OF BEING AN ACTOR.
YOU CAN'T TAKE IT PERSONAL.
NOT PERSONAL? REALLY?
WELL, THEY SAID THEY'D NEVER MET AN ITALIAN ACTOR
WITH A WORSE ITALIAN ACCENT.
THEY ACTUALLY SAID THAT?
YEAH. OH, GOD, THERE'S THAT FACE AGAIN.
SEE? I CAN'T DO THIS JOB. I CAN'T.
NO, NO, SEE, THIS IS WHY YOU HAVE TO DO THIS JOB.
AGENTS ALWAYS LIE.
YOU KNOW, ESTELLE JUST SAYS STUFF LIKE
"THEY WENT ANOTHER WAY," BUT THIS-- I CAN USE THIS.
I CAN A WORK ON A YOU ACACENTAY.
YEAH. OKAY.
NO, IF IT HELPS YOU, OKAY, YEAH.
YOU'LL NEVER GET ME, JOE.
NO, THANK YOU.
CHANDLER.
HELLO... JANICE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
OH, JUST A BIT OF SHOPPING.
HOW'VE YOU BEEN?
ARE YOU BEING BRITISH?
NO. NOT ANYMORE.
WHY ARE YOU SHOPPING HERE?
YOU DON'T LIVE IN THIS NEIGHBORHOOD.
WERE YOU HERE WAITING FOR ME?
YA HUH.
I'M JUST, UH, YOU KNOW
PICKING UP SOME THINGS FOR A PARTY.
BARLEY?
WHAT KIND OF A PARTY SERVES BARLEY?
WELL, I'M SORRY IF MY FRIENDS
AREN'T AS SOPHISTICATED AS YOURS.
WHERE IS THIS PARTY?
HERE IN CHELSEA.
WHOSE PARTY IS IT?
A WOMAN'S.
WHAT WOMAN?
CHELSEA.
OKAY. YOU KNOW ONE OF TWO THINGS
IS HAPPENING HERE.
EITHER YOU'RE SEEING SOMEBODY BEHIND MY BACK
WHICH WOULD MAKE YOU
THE BIGGEST JERK ON THE PLANET
OR ELSE YOU'RE PRETENDING YOU'RE SEEING SOMEBODY
WHICH JUST MAKES YOU SO PATHETIC
I COULD JUST START CRYING HERE IN THE CEREAL AISLE.
SO, LIKE, WHICH OF THESE TWO GUYS
DO YOU WANT TO BE?
COULD I BE THAT GUY?
OKAY, SO WE GOT TWO MORE GOOD REJECTIONS--
LOTS OF STUFF TO WORK ON.
OH. OKAY, SHOOT.
OKAY. UM, OH, THE ZOO COMMERCIAL.
I DIDN'T GET IT?
NO. THEY SAID THAT YOU
"WEREN'T BELIEVABLE AS A HUMAN BEING."
SO, YOU CAN WORK ON THAT.
OKAY.
UH, WHAT ELSE?
UM, THE OFF BROADWAY PLAY PEOPLE SAID
THAT YOU WERE PRETTY BUT DUMB.
OH. OH, NO. WAIT. I'M SORRY.
THAT'S "PRETTY DUMB."
LOOK, THAT'S OKAY.
NO, NO, NO. REALLY.
LOOK, UM, I REALLY APPRECIATE THIS, PHEEBS
BUT... I THINK I'M GOING
TO HAVE TO GO BACK TO ESTELLE.
OH. DON'T GET ME WRONG.
YOU'RE A BETTER AGENT THAN SHE IS, BUT AT LEAST WITH HER
I DON'T WANT TO BLOW MY PRETTY DUMB BRAINS OUT.
YEAH. I KNOW.
I UNDERSTAND.
YOU DO? THANKS.
YEAH.
OKAY.
SORRY.
WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT?
DID YOU JUST MAKE ALL THAT STUFF UP
TO GET OUT OF BEING MY AGENT?
OOH, YOU CAUGHT ME.
HUH.
I AM SO BUSTED.
THAT'S A WHAT I SUSPECTED A.
HUH?
AND THEN I JUST, YOU KNOW...
THREW THE BAG OF BARLEY AT HER
AND RAN OUT OF THE STORE.
OH, MY GOD, CHANDLER.
WE SAID, "BE ALOOF," NOT "A DOOF."
I'VE ACTUALLY RUINED THIS, HAVEN'T I?
IT'S TIME FOR THE GOOD ICE CREAM NOW, RIGHT?
IT'S TIME.
YEAH, IT IS.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
EVERYTHING'S GOING TO BE OKAY.
YOU KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE YOU'VE GOT 65 GRAMS OF FAT
COMING YOUR WAY.
HELLO.
HI, JANICE.
CAN YOU HOLD ON FOR A SECOND?
OKAY.
OKAY, WHAT DO I DO?
SHOOT, I DON'T KNOW.
THIS IS TOTALLY UNPRECEDENTED.
IF WE EVER DID WHAT YOU DID
A MAN WOULD NEVER CALL.
NO, NO... OKAY, I GOT IT.
PRETEND THAT YOU JUST WOKE UP.
THAT'LL THROW HER OFF. BE SLEEPY.
YES, AND GRUMPY.
STOP NAMING DWARFS.
HELLO, JANICE.
HI.
I'M SO GLAD THAT YOU CALLED.
I KNOW I'VE BEEN ACTING REALLY WEIRD... LATELY, AND...
IT'S JUST BECAUSE I'M CRAZY ABOUT YOU, AND...
I JUST GOT...
STUPID AND SCARED AND...
AND STUPID A COUPLE MORE TIMES.
AND I'M SORRY.
REALLY?
HE'S SO LUCKY.
IF JANICE WERE A GUY
SHE'D BE SLEEPING WITH SOMEBODY ELSE BY NOW.
MM HMM.
I LOVE YOU, TOO.
OH, IT'S SO UNFAIR.
G.I. JOE? G.I. JOE?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO TELL YOU GUYS.
THAT'S THE DOLL HE CHOSE.
WHAT'D YOU DO?
DIP IT IN SUGAR?
LOOK, G.I. JOE'S IN, BARBIE'S OUT.
AND IF YOU GUYS CAN'T DEAL WITH IT
THAT'S JUST YOUR TOO BAD.
WHAT ARE YOU BEING SUCH A WEENIE FOR?
SO HE HAS A BARBIE-- BIG DEAL.
YOU USED TO DRESS UP LIKE A WOMAN.
WHAT?
THE WAY YOU USED TO DRESS UP IN MOM'S CLOTHES ALL THE TIME?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
THE BIG HAT, THE PEARLS
THE LITTLE PINK HANDBAG?
OKAY. YOU ARE TOTALLY MAKING THIS UP.
HOW CAN YOU NOT REMEMBER?
YOU MADE US CALL YOU "BEA."
OH, GOD.
I HAVE LITERALLY NEVER BEEN THIS HAPPY.
WASN'T THERE A LITTLE SONG?
OH, PLEASE, GOD, LET THERE BE A SONG.
THERE WAS NO SONG.
?? I AM BEA ??
OKAY. ?? I DRINK TEA ??
OKAY, THAT'S ENOUGH.
?? WON'T YOU...? ??
.? ??
?? WON'T YOU..
"WON'T YOU DANCE AROUND WITH ME?"
?? I AM BEA ??
?? I DRINK TEA ??
?? WON'T YOU DANCE AROUND WITH...? ??
OH...
Ross!