SO I TOLD CARL
NOBODY-- NO MATTER HOW FAMOUS
THEIR PARENTS ARE--
NOBODY'S ALLOWED TO CLIMB ON THE DINOSAUR.
BUT, OF COURSE...
I LOVE HOW HE CARES SO MUCH ABOUT STUFF.
IF I SQUINT, I CAN PRETEND HE'S ALAN ALDA.
OH, GOOD. ANOTHER DINOSAUR STORY.
WHEN ARE THOSE GOING TO BECOME EXTINCT?
IF I WAS A SUPERHERO WHO COULD FLYANDBE INVISIBLE
THAT WOULD BE THE BEST.
WHAT DOES RACHEL SEE IN THIS GUY?
I LOVE RACHEL.
I WISH SHE WAS MY WIFE.
AND YOU PLAYED HAPPY DAYS, WHO WERE YOU?
I WAS ALWAYS RICHIE.
I WAS ALWAYS JOANIE.
QUESTION.
WAS "EGG THE GELLERS!"
THE WAR CRY OF YOUR NEIGHBORHOOD?
EW! EW!
IT'S THE MATTRESS KING.
DON'T LOOK, HONEY. CHANGE THE CHANNEL.
WAIT. I WANT TO SEE THIS.
AFTER I DIVORCE HIM, HALF OF THAT KINGDOM
IS GOING TO BE MINE.
Despair fills the mattress showroom.
My kingdom is suddenly without a queen.
I'm so depressed, I'm going to slash...
my prices!
Check it out!
599 DOLLARS for a Comfort King!
499 DOLLARS for a pillow top queen set!
I'm going medieval on prices!
WHAT A WANK.
OH, I CANNOT BELIEVE HE'S USING OUR DIVORCE
TO SELL MATTRESSES.
I KNOW. AT $499 FOR A PILLOW TOP QUEEN SET
WHO CARES ABOUT THE DIVORCE?
THOSE BABIES WILL SELL THEMSELVES.
AND I'M APPALLED FOR YOU, BY THE WAY.
You'll be glad you did.
I'm close. I'm cheap.
I'm the king.
HE STUFFS THAT COD PIECE, RIGHT?
OH, YEAH.
HERE YOU GO.
OH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I ASKED FOR NO CINNAMON ON TOP.
OH.
YEAH. OKAY. ALL RIGHT, DADDY.
WE'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW NIGHT.
OKAY. BYE.
"WE"?
...ARE, UH, HAVING DINNER WITH MY DAD TOMORROW NIGHT.
I HOPE THAT'S OKAY.
OH, SHOOT.
TOMORROW'S NOT SO GOOD.
I'M SUPPOSED TO FALL OFF THE EMPIRE STATE BUILDING
AND LAND ON A BICYCLE WITH NO SEAT, SO...
ROSS, MY FATHER DOESN'T HATE YOU.
PLEASE.
HE REFERS TO ME AS "WET HEAD."
BUT, HONEY, HE CALLS EVERYBODY BY A NICKNAME.
OKAY, LOOK, JUST ONE DINNER.
PLEASE, ONE NIGHT FOR ME?
PLEASE? I JUST WANT HIM TO LOVE YOU LIKE I DO.
ALL RIGHT. WELL, NOT EXACTLY LIKE I DO.
BUT, IF YOU DO COME TO DINNER
I'LL LOVE YOU LIKE I DO
IN THAT BLACK THING THAT YOU LIKE.
I'LL GO.
FINE.
THANK YOU.
HI, GUNTHER.
YEAH. WE'LL SEE.
HEY, YOU GUYS.
HEY.
GUESS WHAT.
I GOT A GIG.
THAT'S WHY I COULD NEVER BE AN ACTOR--
BECAUSE I CAN'T SAY "GIG."
I CAN'T SAY "CROISSANT."
OH, MY GOD!
WHAT'S THE PART?
IT'S NOT A PART.
NO. I'M TEACHING ACTING FOR SOAP OPERAS
DOWN AT THE LEARNING EXTENSION.
COME ON, THAT'S GREAT.
YEAH, YEAH, IT'S LIKE MY CHANCE
TO GIVE SOMETHING BACK TO THE ACTING COMMUNITY.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE PROBABLY NOT ALLOWED TO SLEEP
WITH ANY OF YOUR STUDENTS.
I KNOW.
I DON'T KNOW, MONICA.
IT FEELS FUNNY JUST BEING HERE.
I MEAN, IF YOU BUY A BED FROM JANICE'S EX HUSBAND
THAT'S LIKE BETRAYING CHANDLER.
NOT AT THESE PRICES.
HI.
YOU KNOW, IN ENGLAND
THIS CAR WOULD BE ON THE OTHER SIDE OF THE STORE.
WHOOSH!
OHH... OHH...
PHOEBE, COME HERE.
OHH. THIS IS MY NEW BED.
YOU GOT TO FEEL THIS BAD BOY.
MONICA, IT STILL FEELS SO WEIRD, YOU KNOW.
CHANDLER'S YOUR FRIEND.
OH, MY GOD!
OHH.
ALL RIGHT, TAKE THIS BED.
YOU CAN MAKE OTHER FRIENDS.
GOOD EVENING.
I AM MR. TRIBBIANI...
AND I'LL BE TEACHING ACTING FOR SOAP OPERAS.
UNFORTUNATELY, TONIGHT WILL BE MY ONLY CLASS
BECAUSE, DUE TO A RARE BLOOD DISEASE
I ONLY HAVE TWO WEEKS TO LIVE.
SO DO WE GET OUR DEPOSIT BACK?
THAT WAS SUPPOSED TO BE AN EXAMPLE
OF ACTING FOR SOAP OPERAS.
THEN WHY ARE YOU ONLY TEACHING TONIGHT?
I'M NOT.
LOOK, WHY DON'T WE GET STRAIGHT TO THE LESSON.
OKAY? ALL RIGHT.
NOW, UM...
ON MY FIRST DAY AS DR. DRAKE RAMORAY
ON DAYS OF OUR LIVES...
UH, I LEARNED THAT ONE OF THE MOST IMPORTANT THINGS
IN SOAP OPERA ACTING ISREACTING.
THIS DOES NOT MEAN ACTING AGAIN.
IT MEANS YOU DON'T
HAVE A LINE, BUT SOMEONE ELSE JUST DID
AND IT GOES SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
THANKS. THANKS.
THANKS A LOT.
OH, BY THE WAY, BEFORE I FORGET
TO WORK IN SOAP OPERAS
SOME OF YOU ARE GOING TO HAVE TO BECOME MUCH MORE ATTRACTIVE.
ALL RIGHT.
MOVING RIGHT ALONG...
HI.
HEY.
OOH! HOW WAS TEACHING LAST NIGHT?
OH, IT WAS GREAT! YEAH, YOU GET TO SAY STUFF LIKE
"HEY, THE BELL DOESN'T DISMISS YOU.
I DIS MISS YOU."
OHH. NICE.
YEAH. OH, AND GUESS WHAT.
I GOT AN AUDITION FOR ALL MY CHILDREN.
OH, YAY!
YEAH, IT'S THIS GREAT PART.
THIS BOXER NAMED NICK, AND I'M SO, SO RIGHT FOR IT, YOU KNOW?
HE'S JUST LIKE ME, EXCEPT THAT HE'S A BOXER
AND HAS AN EVIL TWIN.
OH!
DUM TA DA DUM.
HEAR YE, HEAR YE.
DELIVERY FROM THE MATTRESS KING.
YOU MISS GELLER?
OKAY.
SIGN HERE.
OOH. DO I HAVE A MIDDLE NAME?
ALL RIGHT. MONICA FALOOLA...
GELLER.
IT'S THAT BEDROOM THERE.
HEY, MONICA BOUGHT A BED FROM THE MATTRESS KING?
YEAH. SO, PLEASE, PLEASE
PLEASE DON'T SAY ANYTHING TO CHANDLER.
YOU WANT ME TO LIE TO CHANDLER?
IS THAT A PROBLEM?
NO.
OH, HEY, HEY, NICK THE BOXER
LET'S SEE WHAT YOU GOT.
PUT THEM UP. COME ON.
HEY...
YOU'RE PRETTY GOOD AT THIS.
YEAH, WELL, I HAD TO LEARN.
I WAS STAYING AT THE "Y"
AND SOME OF THE YOUNG MEN WEREN'T
ACTING CHRISTIAN ENOUGH.
HEY, NOW. HEY!
OW!
AND I'M BLEEDING.
OKAY, GREAT.
WOW! AND I'M A VEGETARIAN.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, I'M SORRY.
WE'LL PUT SOME ICE ON IT.
PUT YOUR HEAD BACK.
ALL RIGHT.
I CAN'T SEE.
I HAVE YOU.
OH, GOD.
WHICH BEDROOM DO YOU WANT IT IN, MISS GELLER?
IT'S THE COMPULSIVELY NEAT ONE
BY THE WINDOW, OKAY?
GOTCHA.
HI, DADDY.
THIS IS WHERE THEY PUT US?
WHAT? THERE WAS NO TABLE AVAILABLE IN THE KITCHEN?
OH. HI, DADDY.
HELLO, BABY.
YOU REMEMBER ROSS.
NICE TO SEE YOU AGAIN, DR. GREEN.
SO!
HOW'S THE LIBRARY?
UH, MUSEUM.
WHAT HAPPENED TO THE LIBRARY?
THERE NEVER WAS A LIBRARY.
I MEAN, THERE ARE LIBRARIES.
IT'S JUST THAT I, UM.. . I'VE NEVER WORKED AT ONE.
YOU KNOW WHAT'S REALLY GOOD HERE? THE LOBSTER.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
SHALL I JUST ORDER THREE?
YEAH, IF YOU'RE REALLY HUNGRY.
IT WAS A JO... I MADE A JOKE.
YEAH. ACTUALLY, DADDY
ROSS IS ALLERGIC TO LOBSTER.
WHAT KIND OF PERSON IS ALLERGIC TO LOBSTER?
I GUESS THE KIND OF PERSON THAT WORKS IN A LIBRARY.
IT'S NOT A LI...
I KNOW. IT'S A MUSEUM. WHAT, YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
AROUND HERE WHO CAN MAKE A JOKE? AT LEAST MINE WAS FUNNY.
UHH... WAITER.
WE WILL HAVE TWO LOBSTERS AND A MENU.
SO, DR. GREEN, HOW'S THE OLD BOAT?
THEY FOUND RUST.
YOU KNOW WHAT RUST DOES TO A BOAT?
GIVES IT A NICE, ANTIQUE Y LOOK?
RUST IS BOAT CANCER, ROSS.
WOW. I'M SORRY.
WHEN I WAS A KID, I LOST A BIKE TO THAT.
EXCUSE ME FOR A MOMENT, WILL YOU, PLEASE?
I WANT TO SAY GOOD NIGHT TO THE LEVINES BEFORE WE GO.
OKAY.
HONEY, STOP.
IT'S NOT THAT BAD.
YEAH.
UH OH.
I THINK YOUR DAD MUST HAVE ADDED WRONG.
HE ONLY TIPPED, LIKE, FOUR PERCENT.
YEAH. THAT'S DADDY.
THAT'S DADDY?
DOESN'T IT BOTHER YOU?
YOU'RE A WAITRESS.
YES, IT BOTHERS ME, ROSS
BUT, YOU KNOW, IF HE WAS A REGULAR
AT THE COFFEE HOUSE, I'D BE SERVING HIM "SNEEZERS."
SO?
SO, ROSS
I'VE BUGGED HIM ABOUT THIS A MILLION TIMES.
HE'S NOT GOING TO CHANGE.
DO YOU REALLY SERVE PEOPLE "SNEEZERS"?
WELL, UM, I DON'T.
ALL RIGHT, KIDS
READY?
THANKS AGAIN, DR. GREEN.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
I THINK I FORGOT MY RECEIPT...
YOU DON'T NEED THAT.
WHY NOT?
THE CARBON-- IT'S MESSY.
I MEAN, GETS ON YOUR FINGERS
AND CAUSES THE, THE... NIGHT BLINDNESS.
WHAT IS THIS?
WHO PUT A 20 DOWN HERE?
HUH?
OH, YEAH, THAT WOULD BE ME.
UM, I HAVE... I HAVE A PROBLEM.
I I TIP WAY TOO MUCH. WAY, WAY TOO MU...
IT'S A SICKNESS, REALLY.
YEAH. IT IS.
WE REALLY, REALLY HAVE TO DO SOMETHI...
I KNOW. EXCUSE ME.
YOU THINK I'M CHEAP?
OH, DADDY, HE DIDN'T MEAN...
HUH?
HE REALLY DIDN'T.
NOTHING I DO MEANS ANYTHING, REALLY.
THIS IS NICE.
I PAY 200 DOLLARS FOR DINNER, YOU PUT DOWN 20
AND YOU COME OUT LOOKING LIKE MR. BIG SHOT.
YOU REALLY WANT TO BE MR. BIG SHOT? HERE.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
YOU PAY THE WHOLE BILL, MR. BIG SHOT, ALL RIGHT?
WELL, "MR. BIG SHOT" IS BETTER THAN "WET HEAD."
OKAY. SOME TRICKS OF THE TRADE.
NOW, I'VE NEVER BEEN ABLE TO CRY AS AN ACTOR.
SO, IF I'M IN A SCENE WHERE I HAVE TO CRY
I CUT A HOLE IN MY POCKET, TAKE A PAIR OF TWEEZERS...
AND JUST START PULLING.
OKAY?
OR, UH, LET'S SAY I WANT TO CONVEY
THAT I'VE JUST DONE SOMETHING EVIL.
WELL, THAT WOULD BE YOUR BASIC
"I'VE GOT A FISHHOOK IN MY EYEBROW"
AND I, LIKE...
HMM? OKAY.
LET'S SAY I'VE JUST GOTTEN BAD NEWS.
WELL, ALL I DO THERE
IS TRY AND DIVIDE 232 BY 13.
AND THAT'S HOW IT'S DONE.
GREAT SOAP OPERA ACTING TONIGHT, EVERYBODY.
CLASS DISMISSED.
HEY, MR. TRIB, GUESS WHAT.
I GOT AN AUDITION!
OH. ONE OF MY STUDENTS GOT AN AUDITION.
I'M SO PROUD.
I WAS WONDERING IF YOU WOULD CONSIDER
COACHING ME FOR IT?
YOU BET.
WHAT'S THE PART?
OH, IT'S GREAT.
IT'S A ROLE IN ALL MY CHILDREN.
NICK THE BOXER.
YOU HAD TO DO  IT, DIDN'T YOU?
YOU COULDN'T JUST LEAVE IT ALONE.
FOUR PERCENT, OKAY?
I TIP MORE THAN THAT
WHEN THERE'S A BUG IN MY FOOD.
ROSS, TONIGHT WAS ABOUT THE TWO OF YOU GETTING ALONG.
WOULD YOU JUST SEE MY CHIROPRACTOR ALREADY?
YEAH, I'M GOING TO GO TO A DOCTOR
WHO WENT TO MEDICAL SCHOOL
IN A MINI MALL.
HEY, PHEEBS.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I... I'M FREAKING OUT!
MONICA KIND OF TRUSTED ME WITH SOMETHING
AND SHE SHOULDN'T HAVE.
I HAVEN'T LIVED HERE IN A WHILE, SO I HAVE TO ASK YOU SOMETHING.
DOES MONICA STILL TURN THE LIGHTS ON IN HER BEDROOM?
YEAH.
I AM SO DEAD.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, HERE'S THE BOTTOM LINE, ROSS.
THIS IS FIXABLE IF WE ACT FAST, OKAY?
I'LL INVITE HIM TO BRUNCH TOMORROW
AND YOU CAN MAKE NICE.
HONEY, I HAVE TRIED TO MAKE NICE.
IT DOESN'T WORK.
LOOK, ROSS, I REALIZE THAT MY FATHER IS DIFFICULT
BUT THAT'S WHY YOU HAVE GOT
TO BE THE BIGGER MAN HERE.
LOOK, SWEETIE, I COULD BE THE BIGGER MAN.
I COULD BE THE BIGGEST MAN.
I COULD BE A BIG, HUGE, GIANT MAN
AND IT STILL WOULDN'T MAKE ANY DIFFERENCE
EXCEPT THAT I COULD PICK YOUR FATHER UP
AND SAY, "LIKE ME. LIKE ME, TINY DOCTOR."
OKAY, WELL, CAN'T YOU JUST TRY IT
ONE MORE TIME, ROSS? FOR ME. FOR ME.
RACHEL, ONE BRUNCH IS NOT GOING TO SOLVE ANYTHING.
YOU'VE GOT TO FACE IT, OKAY?
WE'RE NEVER GOING TO GET ALONG.
OKAY, WELL, YOU ARE JUST GOING TO HAVE TO, OKAY?
BECAUSE I'VE ALREADY GOT A MOTHER AND A FATHER
WHO CANNOT STAY IN THE SAME ROOM TOGETHER, OKAY?
I DON'T WANT A SEPARATE ROOM FOR YOU, TOO!
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
I'LL GET THE BAGELS.
WHAT'S THIS?
ISN'T IT COOL? VROOM! VROOM!
THIS IS NOT THE BED I ORDERED.
WON I KNOW. YOU MUST HAVE
LIKE, A CONTEST OR SOMETHING.
PHOEBE.
WHY IS THIS CAR IN MY BEDROOM?
I'M SORRY, OKAY? I WASN'T LOOKING
AND THE STORE SAID THAT THEY WON'T TAKE IT BACK
BECAUSE YOU SIGNED FOR IT.
WHEN DID I SIGN FOR IT?
WHEN I WAS YOU.
YOU KNOW WHAT? IT'S ALL JOEY'S FAULT
BECAUSE HE LEFT HIS NOSE OPEN.
DID YOU MAKE BROWNIES TODAY?
KNOCK, KNOCK.
QUICK, TAKE OFF YOUR DRESS.
HE WON'T NOTICE THE BED.
HEY, I'M GOING FOR SUSHI.
DOES ANYBODY WANT, UH...
WHOA, SOMEBODY MISSED THE OFF RAMP.
IT'S MONICA'S BED.
WHAT?
OKAY.
IT'S A RACE CAR.
SO, THIS HAS ALWAYS BEEN MONICA'S BED.
YOU'RE JUST NOTICING NOW?
HOW SELF INVOLVED ARE YOU?
OKAY, WELL, IF THIS BED ISN'T NEW
THEN HOW COME THERE'S PLASTIC ON THE MATTRESS?
SOMETIMES I HAVE BAD DREAMS.
LOOK...
I JUST SAW MY BEST FRIEND'S BRAINS
SMEARED ACROSS THE CANVAS.
IT'S NOT GOING TO BE ME.
NOT ME.
WOW.
THAT... THAT... THAT WAS GOOD. THAT WAS...
TWEEZERS?
NO.
OH, WOW.
THAT WAS REALLY GOOD.
THANKS.
ANY SUGGESTIONS?
HMM. I...
YOU TOLD HIM TO PLAY THE BOXER GAY?!
WELL, I I MIGHT HAVE SAID "SUPER GAY."
JOEY, THE LAST TIME
AN ACTOR DID SOMETHING THIS BAD
A PRESIDENT DIED.
LINCOLN. BOOTH.
SOMETHING HAPPEN ED AT THE TUNNEL?
JOEY, YOU'RE THIS GUY'S TEACHER.
I MEAN, HOW COULD YOU DO THIS?
BECAUSE, MONICA, THE GUY'S SO GOOD
AND I REALLY, REALLY WANT THIS PART.
WELL, IF YOU REALLY, REALLY WANT IT, THEN IT'S OKAY.
HI, DADDY.
BABY.
ROSS.
DR. GREEN, HOW ARE YOU?
THANKS FOR DINNER LAST NIGHT.
THANK YOU FOR TEACHING ME A VALUABLE LESSON.
NICE HAIR.
WHAT DID YOU DO, SWIM HERE?
OKAY, THAT'S IT.
I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE.
WHAT? HE'S INTERESTED IN YOU.
HE LIKES YOUR HAIR
AND HE JUST WANTS TO KNOW HOW YOU GOT HERE.
OH, PLEASE. SWEETIE, IT'S HOPELESS, OKAY?
I'M JUST GOING TO GO. WHAT? ROSS...
LOOK, I'M SORRY. IT'S JUST...
ROSS, WHAT'S WITH THE NECK?
HE'S GOT THIS THING.
I KEEP TELLING HIM TO GO TO MY CHIROPRACTOR.
YOU'RE STILL GOING TO THAT CHIROPRACTOR?
THAT MAN COULDN'T GET INTO MED SCHOOL IN IXTAPA.
YEAH, THANK YOU.
THAT'S WHAT I KEEP SAYING.
EXCUSE ME. DR. BOBBY HAPPENS TO BE AN EXCELLENT DOCTOR.
WAIT A MINUTE.
HIS NAME IS DR. BOBBY?
WELL, THAT'S HIS LAST NAME.
AND HIS FIRST NAME.
HE'S BOBBY BOBBY?
IT'S ROBERT BOBBY.
OH HO.
AND, UM... EXCUSE ME. HE HELPS ME.
OH, PLEASE. ASK HER HOW.
WHAT DO YOU NEED HELP FOR?
WITH MY ALIGNMENT. I'VE GOT ONE LEG SHORTER THAN THE OTHER.
OH, MY GOD.
ARGUE WITH THAT.
WHAT? IT'S TRUE. MY RIGHT LEG IS TWO INCHES SHORTER.
COME ON. YOU'RE JUST TILTING.
HER LEGS ARE FINE.
I KNOW THAT.
SO WHAT DO YOU LET HER GO TO A CHIROPRACTOR FOR?
I'M SORRY. "LET HER"?
WHAT CAN I DO? SHE DOESN'T LISTEN TO ME
ABOUT RENTER'S INSURANCE EITHER.
WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU DON'T HAVE RENTER'S INSURANCE?
NO.
WELL, WHAT IF SOMEBODY STEALS SOMETHING?
HOW YOU GOING TO RUN AFTER THEM WITH
ONE LEG SHORTER THAN THE OTHER?
HEY, WOULD YOU, UH, WOULD YOU LIKE SOME JUICE?
I'D LOVE SOME JUICE. THANK YOU.
OKAY.
WOW. THIS IS GOING SO WELL.
DID YOU SEE US ? DID YOU SEE?
YEAH, HONEY, I WAS STANDING RIGHT THERE.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST TELL HIM ABOUT THE MOLE
I HAVEN'T GOTTEN CHECKED YET?
EXCELLENT.
THERE WILL COME A TIME IN EACH OF YOUR CAREERS
WHEN YOU'LL HAVE A CHANCE
TO SCREW OVER ANOTHER SOAP OPERA ACTOR.
I HAD SUCH AN OPPORTUNITY IN THE RECENT PRESENT...
AND I'M ASHAMED TO SAY THAT I TOOK IT.
I ADVISED A FELLOW ACTOR TO PLAY A ROLE...
HOMOSEXUALLY.
YEAH.
WE BOTH AUDITIONED FOR THE PART
AND, UH... AS IT TURNED OUT...
THEY, UH...
THEY LIKED THE STUPID GAY THING AND CAST HIM.
AND NOW...
HE'S GOT A TWO YEAR CONTRACT OPPOSITE...
SUSAN LUCCI, THE FIRST LADY OF DAYTIME TELEVISION.
AND ME...
ME, I'M STUCK HERE TEACHING A BUNCH OF PEOPLE
MOST OF WHOM ARE TOO UGLY TO EVEN BE ON TV.
I'M SORRY. I'M SORRY. I'M SORRY.
THANK YOU.
MAY I HELP YOU?
WE SPOKE ON THE PHONE.
I'M THE LADY WHO GOT STUCK WITH THE RACE CAR BED.
LOOK, IT'S LIKE I TOLD YOU.
THERE'S NOTHING I CAN DO.
YOU SIGNED FOR IT.
"MONICA FALOOLA GELLER."
ALL RIGHT, JESTER MAN, WE WANT TO SEE THE KING.
NOBODY SEES THE KING.
OKAY, I'M TALKING TO THE KING.
HEY, YOU CAN'T GO BACK THERE.
OHH... MY... GOD.
HEY! WATCH IT, LADY!
HEY, HEY, GOOD LOOKIN'.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL LEAVE.
MY BED'S SO BORING.