HEY.
HEY, HEY, HEY.
SO WHAT HAPPENED?
DID A FOREST TICK YOU OFF?
NO.
YOU KNOW HOW WE'RE ALWAYS SAYING
WE NEED A PLACE FOR THE MAIL.
YEAH?
WELL, I STARTED BUILDING ONE.
BUT THEN I DECIDED TO TAKE IT TO THE NEXT STEP.
YOU'RE BUILDING A POST OFFICE?
NO, AN ENTERTAINMENT UNIT
WITH A MAIL CUBBY BUILT RIGHT IN.
IT'S A ONE DAY JOB, MAX.
OKAY.
MY WORD, THOSE ARE SNUG.
OH, YEAH.
THESE ARE MY OLD WORK PANTS.
SERGIO VALENTE.
POWER SAW KIND OF GOT AWAY FROM ME THERE.
HEY, PHEEBS.
HEY.
ANY SIGN OF YOUR BROTHER?
NO, BUT HE'S ALWAYS LATE.
I THOUGHT YOU ONLY MET HIM ONCE.
YEAH, I DID.
I THINK IT SOUNDS, LIKE, BIG SISTER Y.
YOU KNOW, "FRANK'S ALWAYS LATE."
WELL, RELAX, HE'LL BE HERE.
YEAH. OH, I KNOW. I'M JUST NERVOUS.
YOU KNOW, IT'S JUST...
MOM'S DEAD, DON'T TALK TO MY SISTER...
GRANDMA'S BEEN SLEEPING A LOT LATELY.
IT'S JUST, LIKE, THE LAST DESPERATE CHANCE
TO HAVE A FAMILY KIND OF THING.
YOU'RE SO SWEET TO WAIT WITH ME.
WELL, ACTUALLY, GUNTHER SENT ME.
YOU'RE NOT ALLOWED
TO HAVE CUPS OUT HERE.
MMM.
DOES ANYONE ELSE THINK
DAVID COPPERFIELD'S CUTE?
NO...
BUT HE TOLD ME HE THINKS YOU'RE A FOX.
ALL RIGHT, JANICE LIKES HIM.
IN FACT, SHE LIKES HIM SO MUCH SHE PUT HIM ON HER, UH...
FREEBIE LIST.
HER WHAT?
WELL, WE HAVE A DEAL WHERE WE EACH GET
TO PICK FIVE DIFFERENT CELEBRITIES
THAT WE CAN SLEEP WITH...
AND THE OTHER ONE CAN'T GET MAD.
AH, THE HEART OF EVERY HEALTHY RELATIONSHIP...
HONESTY, RESPECT AND SEX WITH CELEBRITIES.
SO, CHANDLER, WHO'S ON YOUR LIST?
AH, KIM BASINGER...
UH, CINDY CRAWFORD, HALLE BERRY...
YASMINE BLEETH.
OH, BOY.
AND, UH, JESSICA RABBIT.
NOW, YOU DO REALIZE THAT SHE'S A CARTOON
AND WAY OUT OF YOUR LEAGUE?
YEAH, I KNOW. I KNOW.
I JUST ALWAYS WONDERED IF I COULD GET HER EYES
TO POP OUT OF HER HEAD.
MAN, THIS IS SUCH A GREAT THING.
ANNIE ESPOSITO WOULD NEVER HAVE DUMPED ME
HAD WE HAD A LIST LIKE THAT.
US. AND ALSO, OF COURSE, IF HER SISTER WAS FAMO
HEY, MONICA, WHO WOULD YOURS BE?
FIRST, I NEED A BOYFRIEND, THEN I CAN HAVE A LIST.
JUST A GAME, MON.
RACH, HOW ABOUT YOU?
OH, I DON'T KNOW.
I GUESS...
CHRIS O'DONNELL, JOHN F. KENNEDY JR.
DANIEL DAY LEWIS, STING AND PARKER STEVENSON.
SPIDER MAN?
HARDY BOY.
PETER PARKER.
THANK YOU.
WHAT ABOUT YOU, HONEY? WHO'D BE ON YOUR LIST?
I... I DON'T KNOW.
THAT KIND OF THING
REQUIRES SOME SERIOUS THOUGHT.
FIRST, I'LL DIVIDE MY PROSPECTIVE CANDIDATES INTO CATEGORIES.
WHAT A GEEK.
EVERYBODY, THIS IS FRANK.
THIS IS MY HALF BROTHER FRANK.
THIS IS EVERYBODY. THIS IS ROSS.
HI. HOW ARE YOU?
HEY.
CHANDLER.
HI, HI. HI.
JOEY.
HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY...
THIS IS MONICA.
WHOA.
AND THIS IS RACHEL.
HEY.
W WHOA...
I'M GOING TO GET COFFEE.
HEY, HOW DO YOU GUYS GET ANYTHING DONE?
WE DON'T REALLY.
WELL, SO, NOW, DO YOU GUYS HAVE A LOT OF BIG PLANS?
OH, YEAH. WE'RE GOING TO, LIKE, CONNECT
AND BOND AND EVERYTHING.
YEAH, I WAS THINKING MAYBE WE COULD GO DOWN
TO TIMES SQUARE AND PICK UP SOME NINJA STARS.
OH, AND MY FRIEND, LARRY
HE WANTS ME TO TAKE A PICTURE OF A HOOKER.
YOU KNOW, WE REALLY DON'T TAKE ADVANTAGE
OF LIVING IN THE CITY.
OH, SORRY. DID I GET YOU?
NO, YOU DIDN'T "GET ME".
IT'S AN ELECTRIC DRILL.
YOU "GET ME," YOU KILL ME!
CALM DOWN.
DO YOU WANT THIS UNIT OR NOT?
I DO NOT WANT THIS UNIT.
WELL, YOU SHOULD HAVE
TOLD ME THAT BEFORE.
I'M NOT A MIND READER.
OOH... AND WE'RE OUT OF BEER.
OKAY, I'M GOING TO MONICA'S.
FINE!
HEY.
WHERE YOU HEADING IN THOSE PANTS, 1982?
OH, MONICA, LISTEN.
I SAW DOWN AT THE HARDWARE STORE
THEY GOT THOSE DESIGNER TILES ON SALE
IF YOU EVER WANT TO REDO YOUR BATHROOM FLOOR.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH MY BATHROOM FLOOR?
NOTHING. IT'S JUST...
OLD AND DINGY, THAT'S ALL.
I HIGHLY DOUBT THAT.
OH, YEAH?
IF YOU, UH...
MOVE YOUR HAMPER
YOU CAN SEE THE COLOR THE TILE USED TO BE.
YEAH.
I CAN'T LIVE LIKE THIS.
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO? WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
RELAX, RELAX. HERE, HOLD THIS.
THIS OLD STUFF COMES RIGHT UP.
I'LL SHOW YOU.
A LITTLE MORE THAN I WANTED TO SEE.
OH.
LOOK AT THAT.
EVERY INCH OF THIS IS GLUED DOWN.
IT'D TAKE FOREVER TO PRY THIS UP.
YOU SHOULD, UH... YOU SHOULD JUST LEAVE IT.
I CAN'T LEAVE IT.
YOU GOUGED A HOLE IN MY DINGY FLOOR.
UH...
YEAH, THERE YOU GO.
AW...
YEAH, THAT'S NICE.
WE CAN PUT IT BACK THERE
AFTER THE SURGEONS REMOVE IT FROM YOUR COLON.
GIVE ME A NEW FLOOR.
I CAN'T, MONICA.
CHANDLER WILL KILL ME
IF I DON'T FINISH THE UNIT.
I'LL PAY YOU DOUBLE WHAT HE'S PAYING YOU.
HE'S NOT PAYING ME ANYTHING.
TRIPLE.
WHAT? OOH! OOH!
YEAH, I KNOW WHAT I WANTED TO ASK YOU.
UM, CAN YOU ROLL YOUR TONGUE?
BECAUSE...
BECAUSE I CAN, AND MY MOM COULDN'T
AND I THOUGHT, YOU KNOW
I FIGURED THAT WAS SOMETHING I GOT FROM OUR DAD.
WELL, WAIT, YOU MEAN LIKE THIS?
YEAH.
YEAH, YOU CAN DO IT, TOO. YEAH.
YOU'RE NOT DOING IT.
OH, RIGHT. OKAY, YEAH.
MY MOM COULD AND I CAN'T.
WE DON'T HAVE THAT.
WHEN'S YOUR BIRTHDAY?
FEBRUARY 16.
I KNOW A GUY WHO'S THE 18th.
THAT'S CLOSE.
WHEN'S YOURS?
OCTOBER 25.
THAT'S THE SAME MONTH AS HALLOWEEN.
YEAH.
SO, UM, WHAT KIND OF THINGS DO YOU LIKE TO DO AT HOME?
MELT STUFF.
OKAY, I'VE GOT THREE OF MY FIVE.
THREE OF YOUR FIVE WHAT?
CELEBRITIES I'M ALLOWED TO SLEEP WITH.
OH, MY GOD,YOU ARE GIVING THIS A LOT OF THOUGHT.
HEY, IT'S HARD, OKAY?
I ONLY HAVE TWO SPOTS LEFT.
ALL RIGHT, WHO YOU GOT IT NARROWED DOWN TO?
OKAY... ELIZABETH HURLEY.
OOH, VERY ATTRACTIVE.
YEAH.
FORGIVING.
SUSAN SARANDON.
YOU KNOW WHAT? SHE'S TOO POLITICAL.
SHE PROBABLY WOULDN'T LET YOU DO IT
UNLESS YOU DONATED FOUR CANS OF FOOD FIRST.
AND ISABELLA ROSSELLINI.
OOH... VERY HOT, VERY SEXY.
BUT, UH... YOU KNOW, SHE'S TOO INTERNATIONAL.
YOU KNOW, SHE'S NEVER GOING TO BE AROUND.
SO?
YOU GOT TO PLAY THE ODDS.
PICK SOMEBODY WHO'S GOING
TO BE IN THE COUNTRY, LIKE, ALL THE TIME.
YEAH, BECAUSE THAT'S WHY YOU WON'T GET ISABELLA ROSSELLINI--
GEOGRAPHY.
OKAY, SO, BY "MELTING" YOU MEANT MELTING.
YEAH.
SO, IS IT, LIKE, ART?
YEAH, YOU CAN MELT ART.
HEY, CAN I USE YOUR PHONE?
MMM. YEAH, SURE.
WHY, YOU WANT TO CALL YOUR MOM?
NO, I WANT TO MELT IT.
OH, JUST THE NUMBERS.
IT'LL STILL WORK.
OH, WELL, UM, NOT RIGHT NOW.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK I'M JUST GOING TO GO TO BED.
I THINK THE FUMES ARE GIVING ME A HEADACHE.
YEAH, YEAH...
NIGHT... BRO.
NIGHT.
HERE.
JUST IN CASE.
OH, EXCELLENT.
WHAT KIND OF KARATE IS THAT?
NO KIND.
HE JUST MAKES IT UP.
OH.
SO, HOW'S IT GOING WITH YOU GUYS?
SO FAR, IT KIND OF BLOWS.
I JUST THOUGHT, YOU KNOW, THAT...
HE'D FEEL MORE LIKE A BROTHER.
YOU KNOW, LIKE YOU AND ROSS.
JUST, LIKE, CLOSE AND CONNECTED AND...
HONEY, WE'RE CLOSE NOW
BUT YOU WOULDN'T BELIEVE THE YEARS OF NOOGIES AND WEDGIES
AND FLYING WEDGIES AND ATOMIC WEDGIES AND...
THAT'S WHEN THE WAISTBAND
ACTUALLY GOES OVER YOUR HEAD.
AH.
WE USED TO DRIVE
EACH OTHER CRAZY PLAYING THE SHADOW GAME.
OH, HOW DO YOU PLAY THE SHADOW GAME?
I JUST ASKED YOU.
I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR THIS.
THAT IS WHAT THE GAME IS.
YOU JUST GAVE UP REALLY QUICKLY.
YOU SEEN JOEY?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
OH, JUST...
THIS!
YOU KNOW WHAT? IT'S MY FAULT, REALLY
BECAUSE THE COUCH IS WHERE WE USUALLY KEEP THE VARNISH.
HEY, SOMEBODY WANT TO HAND ME
ONE OF THOSE TILES?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
HE'S RETILING MY FLOOR.
YO!
SPACKLE BOY.
GET UP.
AH AH! YOU STARTED THIS
YOU WILL FINISH IT.
HE STARTED MINE FIRST.
BUILD THE UNIT, CINDERELLY. LAY THE TILES, CINDERELLY.
HE WAS HELPING ME FIRST.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
YOU GUYS FIGURE IT OUT.
I'M GOING TO TAKE A LITTLE BREAK.
OH, THAT'S GOOD.
TAKE A BREAK?
YEAH, I THINK EVEN GOD RESTED
ON THE SEVENTH DAY.
JOEY, IF THIS TAKES SEVEN DAYS
YOU'LL BE ABLE TO MEET GOD
AND ASK HIM ABOUT IT YOURSELF.
WHOA.
BIG OCTOPUS.
YEAH.
HELLO.
OH, MY GOD, I TOTALLY FORGOT.
WELL, CAN'T SOMEONE ELSE DO IT?
BUT I HAVE COMPANY.
YEAH, NO, THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'LL COME IN.
OKAY.
FRANK, I'M REALLY SORRY, BUT I HAVE TO GO IN TO WORK.
IT'S ONE OF MY REGULARS
AND HE'S INSISTING THAT I DO HIM, SO...
HEY, WHAT KIND OF WORK DO YOU DO?
OH! I'M A MASSEUSE.
I GIVE PEOPLE MASSAGES AND STUFF.
YOU... YOU WORK AT ONE OF THOSE MASSAGE PARLORS?
WELL, WE DON'T CALL IT THAT, BUT YEAH.
THAT'S WILD.
NO, I HAD NO IDEA.
ALL RIGHTY.
I'LL BE BACK IN A LITTLE BIT.
UNLESS YOU WANT TO COME WITH ME.
YOU MEAN, LIKE, WATCH?
NO, NO. YOU CAN GET ONE YOURSELF.
IT'LL BE ON THE HOUSE, YOU KNOW...
WHAT ARE BIG SISTERS FOR?
I DON'T THINK THIS... YOU KNOW.
NO, NO, NO.
I WOULDN'T DO YOU MYSELF.
I MEAN, THAT WOULD BE WEIRD.
YEAH...
NO, I'LL GET ONE OF THE OTHER GIRLS TO DO IT.
OH! THIS IS SO MUCH FUN!
YAY!
ARE YOU EXCITED?!
YEAH.
HEY, DO MONICA AND RACHEL WORK THERE?
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
IT'S LIKE THE FIRST BATHROOM FLOOR THERE EVER WAS.
WHOA!
WHAT ARE YOU GOING IN THERE FOR?
YOU WANT, LIKE, A NUMBER?
HEY.
OKAY--
I'M DONE WITH MY CHOICES.
THESE ARE FINAL.
WELL, IT'S ABOUT TIME.
YEAH, VERY OFFICIAL.
OH, YEAH.
WELL, CHANDLER PRINTED IT UP ON HIS COMPUTER.
AND WHO LAMINATED IT?
THAT WAS ME.
ALL RIGHT, LET ME SEE.
HUH... "UMA THURMAN, WINONA RYDER, ELIZABETH HURLEY
"MICHELLE PFEIFFER...
AND DOROTHY HAMILL"?
HEY, IT'S MY LIST.
OKAY, HONEY
YOU DO REALIZE SHE ONLY SPINS LIKE THAT ON ICE.
OW, OW, OW!
OW, OW, OW, OW!
OW, OW.
OW, YOU KNOW, OW...
HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
SHE BROKE MY ARM.
HE TOUCHED MY FANNY.
NO. SHE TOUCHED MINE FIRST.
THAT'S MY JOB.
SO WAIT. WHAT'S THE DEAL HERE?
I CAN HAVE SEX WITH YOU, BUT I CAN'T TOUCH YOU?
EWW! EWW!
YOU CAN'T HAVE SEX WITH HER.
WHAT DID YOU THINK I WAS, A HOOKER?
NO, OKAY, I KNOW-- YOU'RE A "MASSEUSE."
IT'S COOL. I'M NOT A COP.
HEY, JASMINE, CAN YOU ASK MR. WIFFLER
IF HE CAN WAIT FOR, LIKE, FIVE MINUTES?
FINE.
I DON'T LIKE YOU.
SO... THAT'S WHAT YOU THOUGHT I DID?!
GOD!
THAT'S NOT WHAT I DO!
WELL, THAT... THAT...
WELL, THAT'S NOT WHAT YOU DO?
NO!
WHY WOULD YOU THINK THAT?
I DON'T KNOW. I MEAN, YOU KNOW...
THIS IS THE CITY, YOU KNOW?
I JUST... I MEAN, I...
I DON'T KNOW.
WHATEVER.
IT'S THE PERFECT END
TO THE PERFECT WEEKEND ANYWAY.
OH... WAIT.
NO, YOU'RE RIGHT.
NO, IT WAS PERFECT, UH...
I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT I SCREWED IT UP SO BAD.
YOU REALLY THOUGHT IT WAS PERFECT?
WELL, NO, MAYBE IT WASN'T PERFECT
BUT, YOU KNOW, IT WAS PRETTY COOL, YOU KNOW.
BECAUSE WE HAD ALL THOSE GREAT TALKS, YOU KNOW?
YEAH. UM...
WHICH ONES IN PARTICULAR WERE GREAT FOR YOU?
WELL, YOU KNOW
ABOUT THE TONGUE THING, YOU KNOW...
AND HOW I TOLD YOU ABOUT MY LIKES AND MY DISLIKES.
I DON'T...
HOW I LIKE TO MELT STUFF
AND HOW I DISLIKE STUFF THAT DOESN'T MELT?
RIGHT. OKAY.
MM HMM.
YEAH, YOU KNOW...
BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE I CAN REALLY TALK TO YOU
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, YOU'RE MY SISTER. YOU KNOW?
YEAH.
I GUESS I DO. YEAH.
AND THEN I GO FEEL YOUR FRIEND UP
AND MAKE YOU MAD AT ME.
WELL, I WASN'T HOPPING MAD...
YOU KNOW...
YOU HOPPED A LITTLE BIT.
YEAH, I'M REALLY SORRY... REALLY.
WELL, OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, WELL
THIS IS MY FAVORITE PART OF THE WEEKEND.
RIGHT NOW. THIS.
THIS? UH HUH.
OH, COME ON. WE WENT TO TIMES SQUARE.
WE... WE FOUND NINJA STARS.
I ALMOST GET MY ARM BROKEN BY A HOOKER...
SHE'S NOT A HOOKER.
WHEN I TELL MY FRIENDS ABOUT HER, SHE WILL BE.
PHOEBE, WHAT'S THAT?
OH!
OH, FRANK JR. GAVE ME THIS BEFORE HE LEFT.
IT'S A PRESENT.
IT USED TO BELONG TO OUR DAD.
IT WAS HIS GARAGE DOOR OPENER
TILL FRANK MELTED IT.
COOL!
SOUND THE BELL.
GATHER UP ALL THE MEN YOU CAN FIND.
WE GOT OURSELVES AN ENTERTAINMENT UNIT RAISING.
NO, SERIOUSLY, CAN YOU HELP US?
OKAY. ON THREE.
ONE, TWO...
WHY DON'T WE JUST GO ON TWO?
WHY TWO?
BECAUSE IT'S FASTER.
I COULD HAVE COUNTED TO THREE, LIKE, FOUR TIMES
WITHOUT ALL THIS "TWO" TALK.
ALL RIGHT, BUT IN THE FUTURE...
OKAY, OKAY.
HEAVY THING, NOT GETTING LIGHTER.
OKAY. ONE, TWO...
SO WE ARE GOING WITH TWO?
OH!
A GOOD JOB, JOE.
WOW.
IT'S BIG.
YEAH. YEAH.
SO BIG, THAT IT ACTUALLY MAKES OUR DOORS LOOK SMALLER.
MAYBE MY RULER'S WRONG.
MAYBE ALL THE RULERS ARE WRONG.
IT'S NOT THAT BAD.
SO WHAT?
IT BLOCKS A LITTLE OF YOUR DOOR
A LITTLE OF MY DOOR.
I GOT A BETTER IDEA.
HOW ABOUT IT BLOCKS NONE OF MY DOOR AND A LOT
OF YOUR DOOR?
OKAY. LISTEN, BEFORE I FORGET
THAT SIDE IS STILL WET.
ARM HAIR STUCK. ARM HAIR STUCK!
OKAY, SIR
LET ME JUST SEE IF I'VE GOT THIS RIGHT.
SO THIS IS A HALF CAF, DOUBLE TALL
EASY HAZELNUT
NONFAT, NO FOAM, WITH WHIP, EXTRA HOT LATTE, RIGHT?
OKAY. GREAT.
YOU FREAK.
THANK YOU.
COFFEE TO GO, PLEASE.
ISABELLA ROSSELLINI!
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
OH, MY GOD.
DAMN, I CANNOT BELIEVE I TOOK HER OFF MY LIST.
WHY? BECAUSE OTHERWISE, YOU'D "GO FOR IT"?
YEAH. MAYBE.
OH HO! YOU LIE.
WHAT, YOU DON'T THINK I'D GO UP TO HER?
ROSS, IT TOOK YOU TEN YEARS TO FINALLY ADMIT YOU LIKED ME.
YEAH?
WELL, MISSY, YOU BETTER BE GLAD THAT LIST IS LAMINATED.
YOU KNOW WHAT, HONEY?
YOU GO AHEAD.
WE'LL CALL HER AN ALTERNATE.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
HOLD MY CRULLER.
OKAY.
RACH, ARE YOU REALLY GOING TO LET HIM DO THIS?
HONEY, HE'S ABOUT TO GO HIT ON ISABELLA ROSSELLINI.
I'M JUST SORRY WE DON'T GOT POPCORN.
HI...
HI.
I'M ROSS.
UM, YOU DON'T KNOW ME
BUT I'M A BIG, BIG FAN OF YOURS.
I MEAN, UM, BLUE VELVET... WHOO!
I WAS WONDERING IF I COULD MAYBE BUY YOU
A, UM, CUP OF COFFEE.
OR... REIMBURSE YOU FOR THAT ONE.
AREN'T YOU WITH THAT GIRL OVER THERE?
WELL, YEAH. KIND OF.
UM, BUT THAT'S OKAY.
SEE, WE HAVE AN UNDERSTANDING.
UM, SEE, WE EACH HAVE THIS LIST
OF FIVE FAMOUS PEOPLE, AND YOU WERE ONE OF MINE.
SO I'M ALLOWED TO SLEEP WITH YOU.
NO, NO, NO.
IT'S FLATTERING.
WHOA!
I DON'T KNOW... W WAIT...
WAIT. ISABELLA...
DON'T DON'T JUST DISMISS THIS SO FAST.
I MEAN, THIS IS
A ONCE IN A LIFETIME OPPORTUNITY.
YEAH, FOR YOU.
IS THAT THE LIST?
UM, YES.
CAN I SEE IT?
UM, NO.
COME ON.
BUT, OKAY...
I'M NOT ON THE LIST.
UM, SEE, BUT THAT'S NOT THE FINAL DRAFT.
IT'S LAMINATED.
YEAH...
UM, OKAY, SO YOU WERE-- YOU WERE ON MY LIST
BUT THEN
MY FRIEND CHANDLER...
BROUGHT UP THE VERY GOOD POINT
THAT YOU ARE INTERNATIONAL.
SO I BUMPED YOU FOR WINONA RYDER.
LOCAL.
YOU KNOW, IT'S IRONIC.
BECAUSE I HAVE A LIST OF FIVE GOOFY COFFEEHOUSE GUYS
AND YESTERDAY I JUST BUMPED YOU FOR...
THAT GUY OVER THERE.
WE'RE JUST GOING TO BE FRIENDS.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
MM?
BET YOU I COULD FIT
IN THERE.
I GOT FIVE BUCKS SAYS YOU CAN'T.
GET OUT YOUR CHECKBOOK, MISTER.
OH, I THINK I HAVE THE CASH.
YOU ARE DOGGED, MAN.
I TOTALLY FIT.
YEAH. YOU GOT ME.
I'M OUT FIVE BIG ONES.
THERE YOU GO.
THANK YOU.
CHA CHING!
OH, HELLO, MR. LINCOLN!
BETTER LUCK NEXT TIME, BUDDY.
AND THE DRINKS ARE ON ME.