HEY, HOW MUCH YOU GIVE ME TO EAT THIS WHOLE JAR
OF OLIVES?
I WON'T GIVE YOU ANYTHING
BUT YOU'LL OWE ME $2.95.
DONE.
HEY. I NEED AN ATLAS.
I NEED AN ATLAS.
WHY?
DO YOU HAVE A REPORT DUE?
I HAVE A DATE WITH THIS DIPLOMAT I MET
WHILE I WAS GIVING FREE MASSAGES OUTSIDE THE U.N.
AND I DON'T KNOW WHERE HIS COUNTRY IS.
OKAY, LET'S START WITH THE FREE MASSAGES AT THE U.N.
OH, IT'S MY NEW THING.
I FIGURE, "BODIES AT PEACE MAKE PEACE."
WOW. YOU MIGHT JUST GET
THE FIRST NOBEL PRIZE IN RUBBING.
SO WHAT COUNTRY IS THIS GUY FROM?
UM, ICHNECH... TRAIAN... ISTAN.
THERE'S A "G" IN THERE.
WHERE'S THAT?
IN YOUR ATLAS.
I DON'T HAVE AN ATLAS.
OH, WELL, WAIT.
I DO HAVE A GLOBE.
SO, PHEEBS, WHAT'S THIS GUY LIKE?
UM, WELL, HE'S VERY DASHING, YOU KNOW?
AND, UM, VERY, VERY SOPHISTICATED.
AND HE DOESN'T SPEAK ANY ENGLISH
BUT, ACCORDING TO HIS TRANSLATOR, HE TOTALLY GETS ME.
OKAY, HERE YOU GO.
WHAT IS THIS?
IT'S A GLOBE...
AND A PENCIL SHARPENER.
PEOPLE OF EARTH, SURRENDER.
GIANT ALIENS...
FIVE TINY HEADS.
HEY, ANYBODY NEED ANYTHING COPIED?
I'M GOING DOWN TO THE XEROX PLACE.
OH, NO, THANKS.
OKAY, LISTEN, JUST GIVE ME ANYTHING I CAN MAKE TWO OF.
IF YOU DON'T HAVE ANYTHING TO COPY
WHY ARE YOU GOING DOWN THERE?
ARE YOU JUST GOING DOWN THERE
TO GAWK AT THAT HOT GIRL
WITH THE BELLY BUTTON RING AGAIN?
YEAH. DO YOU WANT TO COME?
YEAH.
COME ON, CHLOE.
FINISH UP WITH YOUR CUSTOMER FIRST.
CAN I HELP YOU?
UH OH.
UH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
WE'RE HAVING SECOND THOUGHTS ABOUT OUR, UH, COPYING NEEDS
AND WE'LL NEED A LITTLE MORE TIME TO THINK ABOUT IT.
CHLOE, SWITCH WITH ME.
THERE ARE SOME GUYS HERE WHO GOT A CRUSH ON YOU.
OKAY, THAT HURT US.
HI, GUYS. I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU SINCE THIS MORNING.
WELL, UH...
YOU KNOW.
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING
TOMORROW NIGHT?
BOTH OF US?
MAYBE. DOES THAT SCARE YOU?
RELAX. JUST ISAAC'S DEEJAYING AT THE PHILLY.
YOU SHOULD COME.
OH, WE'LL BE THERE.
GREAT. I'LL, UH, SEE YOU THEN.
ALL RIGHT. ROCK ON.
HE SAYS THAT WALKING WITH YOU
MAKES THIS STRANGE CITY FEEL LIKE HOME.
OH. ME, TOO...
ALTHOUGH THIS CITY IS MY HOME, SO...
SO THAT'S DUMB, WHAT I SAID.
DON'T TELL HIM I SAID THAT.
JUST... YOU MAKE SOMETHING UP.
NICE. THANK YOU.
THIS IS ME, HERE.
UH...
"YOUR EYES ARE VERY PRETTY."
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
OH, THANK YOU.
HE WOULD LIKE TO KISS YOU.
OKAY, YOU KNOW, YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO THAT NOW.
OH, NO, NO, NO.
NOT HIM. NO, YOU DON'T.
OH.
OKAY, WELL, THE MOMENT'S OVER.
"OY."
SEE, THERE IT IS, RIGHT THERE.
WOW. IT'S SMALL.
YEAH, BUT SERGEI SAID
IT TOOK THE GERMANS SIX WEEKS
TO GET ALL THE WAY ACROSS IT.
SO YOU HAD FUN, HUH?
YEAH. EXCEPT FOR...
YOU KNOW WHEN YOU'RE ON A DATE
AND YOU'RE GETTING ALONG REALLY GREAT
BUT THE GUY'S TRANSLATOR KEEPS GETTING IN THE WAY?
NO.
HEY.
IS RACH IN HER ROOM?
OH, NO, SHE'S STILL AT WORK
BUT SHE TOLD ME TO TELL YOU TO CALL HER.
OH, WHAT?
IS SHE GOING TO CANCEL ON ME AGAIN?
HOW COULD SHE DO THIS?
DOESN'T SHE KNOW IT'S OUR ANNIVERSARY?
ALL RIGHT, ROSS.
THIS IS THE EXTENT OF MY KNOWLEDGE ON THE SUBJECT.
"CALL RACHEL."
WHAT'S THAT ON THE BOTTOM?
OH, THAT'S MY DOODLE OF A LADYBUG WITH A TOP HAT.
SHE'S FANCY.
HELLO.
Hey, honey.
OH, HI.
HEY, WHAT'S...? HOW'S IT GOING?
WELL, KIND OF HAVING AN UNDERWEAR EMERGENCY.
OH, YEAH? WHAT HAPPENED?
SOMEONE SCARE YOU AND MAKE YOU LAUGH TOO HARD?
THERE WAS A DISASTER IN SHIPPING
AND NOW I'VE GOT TO GET THIS ORDER IN.
HONEY, I'M SO SORRY
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE I'M GOING TO BE HERE ALL NIGHT.
WHAT, DO YOU...? WELL, UM...
OH, HOW ABOUT I COME UP THERE?
NO, NO, NO, NO. HONEY, PLEASE.
I'VE GOT... I JUST HAVE TOO MUCH TO DEAL WITH.
ANYWAY, I'M GOING OUT WITH SERGEI AGAIN TONIGHT.
COULD YOU COME AND BE THE TRANSLATOR'S DATE
SO THAT WHEN WE--
YOU KNOW, IT'S TIME FOR OUR ALONE TIME--
YOU TWO CAN SPLIT OFF?
YOU KNOW, HE'S RE... HE'S KIND OF CUTE.
"KIND OF CUTE" LIKE REALLY" KIND OF CUTE"
OR "KIND OF CUTE" LIKE YOUR FRIEND "SPACKLE BACK" LARRY?
HEY, DON'T CALL HIM THAT.
HIS NAME IS SPACKLE BACKHARRY.
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT? MAYBE WE SHOULD GET GOING.
WHAT TIME DID CHLOE SAY WE SHOULD GET THERE?
UH, 10:30.
WHAT TIME IS IT NOW?
4:30.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT, SO WE'LL HANG OUT.
YEAH.
HEY, REMEMBER WHEN SHE BROUGHT UP THAT THING ABOUT--
YOU KNOW, THE THREE OF US?
YES. VIVIDLY.
SHE WAS KIDDING ABOUT THAT, RIGHT?
YEAH, I THINK SO.
GOD, IT WOULD BE WEIRD IF THAT SITUATION
PRESENTED ITSELF TONIGHT, HUH?
OH, YEAH.
YEAH, I MEAN, UH...
WHAT WHAT WOULD WE DO?
DUDE, I DON'T KNOW.
SHE WAS KIDDING.
YEAH.
SHE WAS...
JUST IN CASE
MAYBE WE SHOULD COME UP
WITH A SET OF GROUND RULES.
YEAH, FOR SURE.
OKAY. PROBABLY WANT THE FIRST ONE TO BE:
"NEVER OPEN YOUR EYES."
YOU KNOW?
BECAUSE YOU DON'T WANT TO BE DOING SOMETHING
AND THEN LOOK UP, RIGHT?
AND SEE SOMETHING THAT YOU DON'T WANT TO BE SEEING, YOU KNOW?
YEAH. GOOD CALL.
NICE...
HOLD IT. HOLD IT.
WHAT IF MY EYES ARE CLOSED, AND...
AND MY HAND IS OUT THERE...
AH! OKAY. EYES OPEN AT ALL TIMES.
OH, HEY, HOW DO WE DECIDE
WHERE WE, YOU KNOW, EACH WOULD
YOU KNOW...
BE?
RIGHT. RIGHT.
WELL, I, UH, WE COULD FLIP FOR IT.
YEAH, I GUESS, BUT, LIKE, WHAT'S HEADS AND WHAT'S TAILS?
WELL, IF YOU DON'T KNOW THAT
THEN I DON'T WANT TO DO THIS WITH YOU.
NO, NO, NO.
I AM LOOKING AT A PURCHASE ORDER RIGHT HERE
AND IT CLEARLY STATES
THAT WE ORDERED THE RIVIERA BIKINI
IN A VARIETY OF SIZES AND COLORS, AND...
WHAT DOES IT MATTER WHAT I'M WEARING?
COULD I PLEASE SPEAK TO YOUR SUPERVISOR?
THANK YOU. WE'RE HOLDING.
HI.
OH! OH, MY GOD.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
WELL, YOU SAID YOU COULDN'T GO OUT SO...
YOU BROUGHT A PICNIC.
OH, WHAT A BOYFRIEND.
THAT'S IT. ON MONDAY, I START WEARING MAKEUP.
ROSS, HONEY, THIS IS VERY NICE
BUT I I'VE GOT A CRISIS.
YEAH, BUT I'VE GOT COUSCOUS.
HONEY...
HONEY, I'M SORRY.
I KNOW IT'S OUR ANNIVERSARY
BUT I TOLD YOU ON THE PHONE
I DON'T HAVE TIME TO STOP.
OKAY, YOU DON'T HAVE TO STOP.
I'M INVISIBLE.
I'M NOT HERE.
YEAH, BUT, I DON'T...
WHO APPROVED THAT ORDER?
WELL, THERE IS NO MARK ROBINSON IN THIS OFFICE.
GET ME MARK ON THE PHONE.
OH, I LOVE MARK.
DO YOU KNOW MARK?
YEAH.
LET ME JUST CHECK THAT WITH WHAT I'VE GOT HERE.
038 IS NOT THE NUMBER FOR THIS STORE.
038 IS ATLANTA, AND I...
PEPPER?
NONE FOR ME.
OKAY, SORRY POUR VOUS.
I'M SORRY. AS I WAS SAYING
THE STORE NUMBER IS WRONG
AND I'M SORRY, BUT THAT IS...
OH, MY GOD! ROSS!
GEEZ. OH, MY...
GOD.
OKAY, IT'S FINE, IT'S FINE.
WHOA, YEAH. OH, YEAH.
EXCUSE ME. I'M SORRY.
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO CALL YOU BACK.
I'VE GOT SHEMP
IN MY OFFICE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'M SORRY, BUT, UM...
HEY, WHOA, SOMEBODY'S OFF THE PHONE.
HOW ABOUT A GLASS OF WINE BY THE FIRE?
I CAN GET IT GOING AGAIN IF YOU...
ROSS, YOU'RE NOT LISTENING TO ME.
I DON'T HAVE TIME TO STOP.
COME ON, RACH.
YOU DON'T HAVE, WHAT, TEN MINUTES?
SOPHIE, DOES SHE HAVE TEN MINUTES?
HEY, ROSS, I TOLD YOU, I DON'T.
DON'T YELL AT ME.
THIS IS THE MOST I'VE SEEN YOU ALL WEEK.
LOOK, I CANNOT DO THIS RIGHT NOW, OKAY?
I HAVE GOT A DEADLINE.
WOULD YOU JUST GO HOME?
I'LL TALK TO YOU LATER.
YEAH, BUT WHY...
GOOD BYE.
UH, ACTUALLY
THAT'S OUR THREE HOLE PUNCH.
HEY.
HI.
LOOK, UM, ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED EARLIER...
UH, WELL, I...
I COMPLETELY UNDERSTAND.
YOU WERE... YOU WERE STRESSED.
I WAS GOING TO GIVE YOU A CHANCE TO APOLOGIZE TOME.
FOR WHAT? FOR LETTING YOU THROW ME OUT OF YOUR OFFICE?
YOU HAD NO RIGHT COMING DOWN TO MY OFFICE, ROSS.
YOU DO NOT BRING A PICNIC BASKET TO SOMEBODY'S WORK
UNLESS MAYBE THEY WERE A PARK RANGER.
YEAH, WELL, EXCUSE ME FOR WANTING
TO BE WITH MY GIRLFRIEND ON OUR ANNIVERSARY.
BOY, WHAT AN ASS AM I.
BUT I TOLD YOU I DIDN'T HAVE THE TIME.
YOU NEVER HAVE THE TIME.
I DON'T FEEL LIKE
I EVEN HAVE A GIRLFRIEND ANYMORE, RACHEL.
ROSS, WHAT DO YOU WANT FROM ME?
YOU WANT ME TO QUIT MY JOB
SO YOU CAN FEEL LIKE YOU HAVE A GIRLFRIEND?
NO, BUT IT WOULD BE NICE
IF YOU'D REALIZE THAT IT'S JUST A JOB.
JUST... A JOB?
YES.
ROSS, DO YOU REALIZE THIS IS THE FIRST TIME IN MY LIFE
I'M DOING SOMETHING I ACTUALLY CARE ABOUT?
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME IN MY LIFE
I'M DOING SOMETHING THAT I'M ACTUALLY GOOD AT.
I MEAN, IF YOU DON'T GET THAT...
NO, HEY, I GET THAT. I GET THAT BIG TIME
AND I'M HAPPY FOR YOU, BUT I'M TIRED OF HAVING
A RELATIONSHIP WITH YOUR ANSWERING MACHINE, OKAY?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO ANYMORE.
WELL, NEITHER DO I!
IS THIS ABOUT MARK?
HUH... OH, MY GOD.
OKAY, IT'S NOT.
OH, MY GOD.
I CANNOT KEEP HAVING
THIS SAME FIGHT OVER AND OVER AGAIN, ROSS.
NO. YOU'RE MAKING THIS TOO HARD.
OH, I'M. I'M MAKING THIS TOO HARD.
OKAY, WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO?
I DON'T KNOW. I DON'T KNOW.
LOOK, MAYBE WE SHOULD JUST TAKE A BREAK.
OKAY, OKAY, FINE. YOU'RE RIGHT.
LET'S, UH, LET'S TAKE A BREAK.
LET'S COOL OFF, OKAY?
LET'S GET SOME FROZEN YOGURT OR SOMETHING.
NO.
A BREAK FROM US.
...AND THE ADVANCES IN COLLATING IN THE PAST FIVE YEARS-- PHEW.!
I MEAN, WE JUST GOT IN AN X-5000, YOU KNOW?
THE X-5000 MAKES AN X-50 LOOK LIKE A T-71.
OH!
HEY, IT'S THE DINOSAUR GUY!
HI, ROSS.
OH, HI, CHLOE.
I WANT YOU TO MEET SOME FRIENDS OF MINE.
THIS GUY'S MY HERO.
HE COMES IN WITH SOME STUFF, HE WANTS IT BLOWN UP 400% PERCENT.
WE SAY, "WE DON'T DO THAT."
HE SAYS, "YOU GOT TO," AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
WE DID IT- - AND NOW
ANYTIME ANYBODY WANTS 400, WE JUST SAY, "LET'S ROSS IT."
AND THAT'S THE ONLY COLOR THAT COMES IN.
YO, CHLOE, DO YOU HAVE A QUARTER
FOR THE CONDOM MACHINE?
SO WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I THOUGHT TONIGHT WAS
YOUR BIG ANNIVERSARY DINNER.
YEAH, A LITTLE CHANGE OF PLANS.
UH, WE'RE GOING TO BREAK UP INSTEAD.
OH, AND I CAN ALSO SPEAK A LITTLE FRENCH.
VOULEZ VOUS COUCHEZ AVEC MOI, CE SOIR?
WHY? WHAT DID I SAY?
WELL, YOU JUST ASKED
IF I WANTED TO GO TO BED WITH YOU TONIGHT.
OH, MY GOD.
NO WONDER I GET SUCH GREAT SERVICE
AT CAFE MAURICE.
KNOCK, KNOCK, KNOCK, KNOCK, KNOCK. HI.
UM, COULD YOU PLEASE TELL SERGEI THAT, UM...
I WAS FASCINATED BY WHAT BOUTROS BOUTROS GHALI SAID
IN THENEW YORK TIMES?
YOU DIDN'T SAY "BOUTROS BOUTROS GHALI."
BOUTROS BOUTROS GHALI.
HE SAYS HE WAS, TOO.
INTERESTING.
UH, SO, I WAS WONDERING...
OKAY, HEY, BEFORE YOU GET
ALL TALKY AGAIN
COULD YOU ALSO PLEASE TELL SERGEI THAT...
I REALLY LIKE HIS SUIT.
UH, HE SAID, "THANK YOU VERY MUCH."
HE THINKS YOU LOOK VERY PRETTY TONIGHT.
YOUR HAIR GOLDEN LIKE THE SUN.
SO, YOU'RE A CHEF?
MM HMM.
I'M ALSO THINKING
OF OPENING UP MY OWN RESTAURANT.
OH, REALLY?
MONICA, CAN I TALK TO YOU
BEHIND MY MENU, PLEASE?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WELL, I WAS HAVING A CONVERSATION.
BUT MISCHA IS SO INTERESTED IN YOU
THAT SERGEI AND I HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE
TO SAY TWO WORDS TO EACH OTHER.
WHAT, DO YOU WANT ME TO SIT HERE SILENTLY
WHILE THE THREE OF YOU HAVE A CONVERSATION?
THAT WOULD BE GREAT. THANK YOU.
HELLO.
OH, HI.
IT'S MARK.
OH.
What?
IS IT MY BREATH?
NO. SORRY. I JUST THOUGHT YOU WERE SOMEBODY ELSE. HI.
HI. LOOK, I WAS JUST GOING TO LEAVE A MESSAGE.
ISN'T TONIGHT YOUR BIG ANNIVERSARY DINNER?
WELL...
WELL, UM...
RACH, ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH. I'M FINE.
You want to talk?
I can come over.
NO. REALLY, NO.
PLEASE.
THAT'S THAT'S OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT, I'M COMING OVER
AND I'M BRINGING CHINESE FOOD.
OH, YEAH, I'M NOT... I'M NOT HUNGRY.
It's for me.
OH.
Okay.
OKAY. BYE.
WELL, SO WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
WHAT CAN I DO?
ONE PERSON WANTS TO BREAK UP, YOU BREAK UP.
HEY, NO WAY.
THIS IS YOU GUYS.
CALL HER AND WORK IT OUT.
COME ON.
WE JUST HAD THIS HUGE FIGHT.
DON'T I HAVE TO WAIT A WHILE?
HEY, THIS ISN'T LIKE SWIMMING AFTER YOU EAT.
PICK UP THE PHONE!
THAT WHOLE SWIMMING THING IS A MYTH.
YEAH, TELL THAT TO MY UNCLE LENNY.
WHY, WHAT HAPPENED TO HIM?
NOTHING. HE JUST REALLY BELIEVES IN THAT.
OH, AND THEN WE GOT INTO
THIS BIG, STUPID FIGHT
AND I JUST...
IT WAS AWFUL.
I TOLD HIM HE TREATS ME
LIKE A PARK RANGER OR SOMETHING...
OH...
AND THEN...
I TOLD HIM I WANTED TO TAKE A BREAK.
I DON'T WANT TO TAKE A BREAK.
OH, I'M SORRY.
EGG ROLL?
NO.
AND THEN I CALLED HIM AND HE WASN'T THERE.
WELL, HE'S PROBABLY JUST OUT.
OH, THANK YOU.
THAT'S VERY HELPFUL.
I'M GLAD YOU CAME OVER.
HELLO.
HI, IT'S ME.
HI.
OH, I'M SO GLAD YOU CALLED.
Really?
I'VE BEEN THINKING THIS IS CRAZY.
DON'T YOU THINK WE CAN WORK ON THIS?
HEY, WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DRINK?
WHO'S THAT?
NOBODY.
IS IT OKAY IF I FINISH
THE APPLE JUICE?
IS THAT MARK?
OH, HONEY, LOOK, HE JUST CAME OVER...
YEAH, GOT IT.
HEY, DINOSAUR GUY...
LOOK AT YOU SO SAD.
COME DANCE.
OH, THAT'S OKAY, THANKS.
HEY...
YOU DON'T HAVE TO SMILE.
YOU JUST HAVE TO DANCE.
I DON'T FEEL LIKE DANCING.
I FEEL LIKE HAVING A DRINK.
OH, OKAY.
HEY, TWO BEERS.
OKAY, NOW WE'RE JUST DANCING WITH EACH OTHER.
AND THE VET SAID IT WAS TIME
AND SO, FROM HALF A WORLD A WAY
WHILE MY MOTHER HELD THE PHONE TO HIS EAR
I SAID GOOD BYE TO MY DOG...
IN SEVEN LANGUAGES.
COULD I HAVE A TISSUE?
OH, YEAH, SURE.
I JUST HOPE
YOU DON'T ACCIDENTALY
SUCK IT UP THROUGH YOUR NOSE
AND CHOKE ON IT.
SERGEI WOULD LIKE TO APOLOGIZE
FOR MY BEHAVIOR TONIGHT.
WELL, TELL HIM APOLOGY ACCEPTED.
OH, HE'S UNBELIEVABLE
I MEAN, FOR THE FIRST TIME IN THREE YEARS
SOMEONE ACTUALLY WANTS TO TALK TO ME
BUT DO YOU THINK HE WOULD LET ME ENJOY THAT? NO!
YOU SILLY DIPLOMAT.
WHY DON'T YOU LEARN SOME ENGLISH, SERGEI?
EXCUSE ME, BUT, UM...
ISN'T HE PAYING FOR YOUR DINNER?
HEY, THE MAN'S DOG JUST DIED.
I HAVE JUST RESIGNED MY POST.
WOULD YOU CARE TO ACCOMPANY ME TO THE RAINBOW ROOM?
I HAVE DIPLOMATIC COUPONS.
WELL, IT WILL BE MY PLEASURE.
MY GUY HAS COUPONS.
YOUR GUY CAN'T EVEN SAY "COUPONS."
UH...
PLATE.
PLATE, YES!
PLATE! PLATE!
PLATE.
SEE? WE DON'T NEED THEM.
PLATE?
YEAH.
?? SLEIGHT OF HAND AND TWIST OF FATE ??
?? ON A BED OF NAILS, SHE MAKES ME WAIT ??
I LIKE THIS SONG.
WELL, YOU'RE PRACTICALLY DANCING ALREADY.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST DO IT OVER HERE?
OH, NO.
WHAT, ARE YOU MARRIED?
BECAUSE THAT'S OKAY.
?? THROUGH THE STORM WE REACH THE SHORE ??
?? YOU GAVE IT ALL, BUT I WANT MORE ??
?
?? AND I'M WAITING FOR YOU ?
OH, BE HOME, BE HOME, BE HOME, BE HOME, BE HOME, BE HOME.
BE HOME, BE HOME, BE HOME. ?? WITH OR WITHOUT YOU ??
?
YOU'RE NOT HOME. ?? WITH OR WITHOUT YOU, OH ?
?? I CAN'T LIVE ??
?? WITH OR WITHOUT YOU ??
STILL NO SMILE?
??
?? AND YOU GIVE YOURSELF AWAY
?? AND YOU GIVE YOURSELF AWAY  ??
?? AND YOU GIVE ??
?? AND YOU GIVE YOURSELF AWAY... ??
?? MISS AMERICAN PIE... ??
UH... AMERI GHEN.
AMERI CANE.
AMERI GHEN.
YEAH, IT'S A VERY HARD LANGUAGE.
SLOWER...
LET'S DO IT AGAIN.
?? TUCHI, TUCHI, MISS AMERI GHEN PIE... ??