I DON'T EVEN FEEL LIKE I HAVE A GIRLFRIEND ANYMORE.
YOU WANT ME TO JUST QUIT MY JOB
SO YOU CAN FEEL LIKE YOU'VE GOT A GIRLFRIEND?
IS THIS ABOUT MARK?
OH, MY GOD!
OKAY, IT'S NOT.
OH, MY GOD. I CANNOT KEEP HAVING
THIS SAME FIGHT WITH YOU, ROSS.
LOOK, MAYBE WE SHOULD JUST TAKE A BREAK!
FINE, YOU'RE RIGHT.
LET'S, UH... LET'S TAKE A BREAK.
LET'S GET SOME FROZEN YOGURT.
NO...
A BREAK FROM US.
THEN WE HAD THIS
BIG, STUPID FIGHT
AND I SAID I WANTED TO TAKE A BREAK.
I DON'T WANT TO TAKE A BREAK.
I'VE BEEN THINKING THIS IS CRAZY.
Don't you think we can work on this?
HEY, WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DRINK?
WHO'S THAT?
NOBODY?
IS THAT MARK?
HONEY, LOOK, HE JUST CAME OVER...
YEAH. GOT IT.
HEY! COME DANCE.
WHAT, ARE YOU MARRIED?
BECAUSE THAT'S OKAY.
HEY.
HOW WAS THE BIG ANNIVERSARY DINNER?
WELL...
WE NEVER ACTUALLY GOT TO DINNER.
WHOA... NICE.
NO, WE KIND OF BROKE UP INSTEAD.
WHAT?!
OH, MY GOD!
MONICA, IT'S ON THE CEILING!
THAT'S OKAY.
THIS IS MORE IMPORTANT THAN FRUIT...
ON MY CEILING.
YOU BROKE UP?
YEAH, BUT IT'S OKAY
BECAUSE WHEN ROSS LEFT, MARK CAME OVER.
OH, NO!
RACHEL, YOU AND MARK?
NO, NO, IT'S OKAY.
CALM DOWN.
MARK AND I TALKED
AND I REALIZED HOW MUCH I LOVE YOUR STUPID BROTHER
AND...
YEAH, WE GOT OUR PROBLEMS
BUT I REALLY WANT TO MAKE IT WORK.
MORNING.
?  ?
Hi. It's me.
I've been trying to reach you all night.
I feel awful.
Please, Ross, you've got to know
there's nothing between me and Mark.
This whole breakup thing is just stupid.
YEAH!
I'm just so sorry I put you through it.
And I I, you know, I don't want to get back together
over a machine...
UH UH.
I love you.
I LOVE YOU.
And you know what?
I'm going to go to bed now
but on my way to work tomorrow morning
I'm going to stop by around 8:30.
Bye.
CHLOE! CHLOE, HOW'S IT COMING?
HEY, WHAT KIND OF PUPPY DO YOU THINK I SHOULD GET?
UM, HEY, YOU KNOW, I DON'T KNOW.
HOW ABOUT A BIG ONE?
MY APARTMENT'S...
THEN A SMALL ONE.
LISTEN, LET'S...
WE KIND OF HAVE TO GET GOING.
WAIT! WHERE'S MY SHOES?
YOUR... YOU NEED SHOES?
OKAY.
DO I KNOW WHY WE'RE RUSHING?
YEAH. YOU KNOW THE GIRLFRIEND
I TOLD YOU ABOUT LAST NIGHT?
WELL, IT TURNS OUT THAT SHE...
SHE WANTS TO GET BACK TOGETHER WITH ME.
OH, I FOUND IT!
THAT'S SO GREAT FOR YOU GUYS!
YEAH.
YOU MUST BE SO HAPPY.
YES. YES, I AM--
ONE OF THE MANY THINGS I'M FEELING.
WELL...
GOOD LUCK WITH YOUR GIRLFRIEND.
OH, THANK YOU.
AY! HEY...
RACHEL...!
OH, YOU GOT MY MESSAGE?
OH, AND YOU ARE RIGHT ON TIME.
SO WHAT DO YOU SAY?
CAN I BE YOUR GIRLFRIEND AGAIN?
YES, YOU CAN. VERY MUCH.
AH AH AH...
HEY.
HEY, WHY ARE YOU MOPPING YOUR CEILING?
OH, THERE'S BANANA ON IT.
WOW. I HAVE THE SPIRIT OF AN OLD INDIAN WOMAN
LIVING IN MINE.
SO THEN YOU KNOW.
THE MAILMAN WAS DOWNSTAIRS, SO I BROUGHT UP YOUR MAIL.
OH, GOOD. THANKS.
NOW, WHAT IS "FABUTEK"?
OKAY...
ALL RIGHT, DON'T JUDGE ME TOO MUCH, OKAY?
BUT I SAW THIS INFOMERCIAL, AND I SWEAR TO YOU
I'VE NEVER, EVER BOUGHT ANYTHING ON TV BEFORE...
EXCEPT FOR THIS MOP.
BUT THERE WAS THIS STUFF
ON LEG WAXING.
IT LOOKED SO AMAZING...
WAXINE!
YES! HAVE YOU SEEN IT?
OH! IT'S INCREDIBLE!
I SO WANT TO BE A WAXINE GIRL!
I KNOW!
GOD... DO YOU THINK IT REALLY DOESN'T HURT?
BECAUSE HOW CAN THEY DO THAT?
HELLO? "ORGANIC SUBSTANCES RECENTLY DISCOVERED
IN THE DEPTHS OF THE RAIN FOREST"?
THEY HAVE THE BEST STUFF IN THERE.
OH, MY GOD.
YEAH, WE FIGURED WHEN WE COULDN'T FIND YOU
YOU'D GONE HOME TO MAKE UP WITH RACHEL
WHICH IS PROBABLY WHAT YOU SHOULD HAVE DONE
HUH?
YOU THINK?!
GOD, I...
I'M IN HELL.
I MEAN, WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?
RACHEL'S ALL, LIKE, "I LOVE YOU" AND "LET'S WORK ON THIS."
ALL I CAN THINK ABOUT IS, WHAT IS SHE GOING TO DO?
WHAT IS SHE GOING TO SAY WHEN I TELL HER WHAT I DID?
WELL, BEFORE WE ANSWER THAT
I THINK WE SHOULD ADDRESS THE MORE IMPORTANT QUESTION--
HOW DUMB ARE YOU?
WHAT?
LOOK, WE'RE TRYING TO REBUILD A RELATIONSHIP HERE.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO DO THAT
WITHOUT BEING TOTALLY HONEST WITH EACH OTHER?
ROSS, LOOK
I'M ON BOARD ABOUT THE "TOTAL HONESTY" THING-- I AM.
JUST NOT ABOUT STUFF THAT'S GOING TO GET YOU IN TROUBLE.
HE'S RIGHT-- NOBODY'S GOING TO BENEFIT
AND YOU'RE JUST GOING TO HURT HER.
AND THERE WON'T BE A RELATIONSHIP LEFT TO REBUILD.
YEAH, BUT DON'T YOU...?
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, IF YOU ABSOLUTELY HAVE TO TELL HER
AT LEAST WAIT TILL THE TIMING'S RIGHT.
AND THAT'S WHAT DEATH BEDS ARE FOR.
YEAH, OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, NOW, WE JUST HAVE TO MAKE SURE
SHE DOESN'T FIND OUT SOME OTHER WAY.
DID YOU THINK ABOUT THE TRAIL?
WHAT TRAIL?
THE TRAIL
FROM THE WOMAN YOU DID IT WITH
TO THE WOMAN YOU HOPE NEVER FINDS OUT
YOU DID IT.
YOU ALWAYS HAVE TO THINK ABOUT THE TRAIL!
NO, I DON'T THINK
THERE'S ANY TRAIL.
OKAY. OKAY, OKAY.
UH, CHLOE WORKS WITH THAT GUY ISAAC
ISAAC'S SISTER IS JASMINE
AND JASMINE WORKS AT THE MASSAGE PLACE WITH PHOEBE
AND PHOEBE'S FRIENDS WITH RACHEL, AND THAT'S THE TRAIL!
I DID IT!
"AFTER APPLYING THE WAXINE AND LINEN STRIPS
TO LEG NUMBER ONE..."
DID THAT. OKAY.
"...GRASP ONE OF THE LINEN STRIPS BY ITS EASY GRAB TAB
AND PULL IT OFF IN ONE QUICK PAIN FREE MOTION."
OKAY...
OWW!
IS IT NOT PAIN FREE?
NO! IT WAS PAINFUL!
OH, MY GOD, THEY SHOULD CALL IT
"PAINZEEN, NOW WITH A LITTLE WAX."
HUH. WELL, THE GIRLS IN THE SATIN NIGHTIES
ON THE COMMERCIAL
DON'T SEEM TO THINK IT'S THAT BAD.
THAT'S BECAUSE THEIR NERVES ARE PROBABLY DEADENED
FROM BEING SO STUPID.
BUT, HEY, YOU KNOW, IF YOU DON'T BELIEVE ME
PLEASE, BE MY GUEST.
OW! OW! OW! OW! OH, MY GOD!
NOW AREN'T YOU GLAD WE DIDN'T START
WITH THE BIKINI STRIPS?
CHLOE, HI.
IS THIS ABOUT ME TAKING YOUR WATCH?
YOU TOOK MY WATCH?
I'M SORRY. I DO THAT.
JUST... YOU KEEP IT.
LISTEN, DID YOU TELL ANYONE ABOUT US?
OH, NO.
I FEEL LIKE IT REALLY ISN'T
ANYBODY'S BUSINESS, YOU KNOW?
SO YOU DIDN'T MENTION ANYTHING TO ISAAC, RIGHT?
OH, WELL, I TELL ISAAC EVERYTHING.
OF COURSE YOU DO.
ISAAC...
HI, ISAAC.
ISAAC, HI.
WE HAVEN'T ACTUALLY MET.
YOU DOG!
YES, I SUPPOSE I AM A DOG
BUT, ISAAC, SEE, I I HAPPEN TO HAVE A GIRLFRIEND.
OH, RIGHT. THAT RACHEL CHICK FROM THE COFFEE PLACE.
YEAH, THAT'S THE ONE.
LISTEN, I DON'T WANT TO HURT HER.
OH, HEY, MAN, I KNOW.
DOESN'T MATTER HOW MUCH WE LOVE THEM.
MONOGAMY IS TOO CRUEL A RULE.
YEAH.
LISTEN, CAN YOU KEEP THIS INFORMATION TO YOURSELF?
OH, NO PROBLEM, DUDE.
WE GOT TO LOOK OUT FOR EACH OTHER.
WE'RE THE SAME, YOU AND ME.
ACTUALLY... NO, WE'RE NOT.
YEAH, WE ARE.
NO... WE'RE NOT.
NO, WE'RE NOT.
OKAY, WE'RE NOT. ALL RIGHT.
BUT WE ARE.
FINE. I JUST NEED TO KNOW
THAT YOU'RE NOT GOING TO TELL YOUR SISTER.
I CAN PROMISE NOT TO TELL HERA GAIN.
JASMINE?
UH HUH.
WE MET AT PHOEBE'S BIRTHDAY PARTY.
I'M ROSS GELLER.
YOU DID A BAD THING!
YES, I DID.
VERY BAD. VERY BAD.
VERY, VERY BAD.
I'M AGREEING WITH YOU.
DID YOU... LISTEN, DID YOU HAPPEN TO TELL PHOEBE YET?
NO.
OKAY, JASMINE
PLEASE... PLEASE DON'T.
I LOVE MY GIRLFRIEND VERY MUCH
AND I WANT MORE THAN ANYTHING
TO JUST WORK IT OUT WITH HER, OKAY?
ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU. THANK YOU.
BUT YOU SHOULD PROBABLY TALK TO MY ROOMMATE
BECAUSE I TOLD HIM, AND HE KNOWS PHOEBE, TOO.
WHO'S YOUR ROOMMATE?
GUNTHER...
GUNTHER, PLEASE TELL ME
YOU DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING TO RACHEL
ABOUT ME AND THE GIRL FROM THE COPY PLACE.
I'M SORRY.
WAS I NOT SUPPOSED TO?
OKAY, I GOT AN IDEA.
WHY DON'T YOU PULL OFF MINE
AND I PULL OFF YOURS?
OR YOU PULL OFF YOURS, AND I WILL LEAVE MINE ON
BECAUSE I THINK I CAN MAKE THIS LOOK WORK.
COME ON, PHOEBE, WE CAN DO THIS.
OH?
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY...
OW! OW!
WE'RE ALL RIGHT.
IT'S OKAY, IT'S OKAY.
WE WERE JUST WAXING OUR LEGS.
OFF?!
FOR YOUR INFORMATION, THIS HAPPENS TO BE A PAIN
LIKE NO MAN WILL EVER EXPERIENCE.
YEAH, WELL, I DON'T THINK YOU CAN MAKE THAT STATEMENT
UNLESS YOU'VE BEEN KICKED IN AN AREA
THAT GOD ONLY MEANT TO BE TREATED NICELY.
I THINK WOMEN JUST HAVE A LOWER THRESHOLD FOR PAIN
THAN MEN, THAT'S ALL.
COME ON, IT'S JUST A LITTLE WAX.
OH, YEAH?
COME HERE.
OH, THAT'S MATURE.
OKAY, FINE.
SO, NOW WHAT?
I JUST PULL IT OFF?
THAT'S RIGHT. UH HUH.
OKAY, TIN MAN.
COME ON, RACHEL.
COME ON. TALK TO ME,PLEASE.
I CAN'T EVEN LOOK
AT YOU RIGHT NOW.
WHAT?
NOTHING. NOTHING.
RACHEL SAID EVERYTHING WAS OKAY.
WHAT ARE THEY TALKING ABOUT?
RACHEL, I MADE...
JUST GET AWAY FROM ME!
I MADE A MISTAKE, OKAY?
"A MISTAKE"?!
WHAT WERE YOU TRYING TO PUT IT IN-- HER PURSE?!
WHERE... WHERE DID HE PUT IT?
ROSS, YOU HAD SEX WITH ANOTHER WOMAN!
OH, MY GOD.
OH.
I KNEW SOMETHING HAD TO BE WRONG
BECAUSE MY FINGERNAILS
DID NOT GROW AT ALL YESTERDAY.
YEAH, WELL, I GUESS THEY HAD A FIGHT
AND HE GOT DRUNK...
YOU GUYS KNEW ABOUT THIS
AND YOU DIDN'T TELL US?!
HE HAD SEX
AND WE GET HIT ON OUR HEADS.
I WANT YOU TO LEAVE.
NO! NO! JUST GET OUT. NOW!
I WANT TO STAY.
I WANT TO TALK ABOUT THIS.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
HOW WAS SHE?
UH OH.
WHAT?
WAS SHE GOOD?
DON'T ANSWER THAT.
COME ON, ROSS.
YOU SAID YOU WANTED TO TALK ABOUT IT.
LET'S TALK ABOUT IT!
HOW WAS SHE?
SHE WAS...
AWFUL.
HORRIBLE. SHE WAS NOT GOOD.
NOTHING COMPARED TO YOU.
SHE... SHE WAS DIFFERENT.
OH... UH OH.
GOOD. DIFFERENT?
NOBODY LIKES CHANGE... I...
YOU JUST STOP...
WHAT? OKAY, OKAY, OKAY-- OKAY.
SH SHOULD WE DO SOMETHING?
YEAH.
NEVER CHEAT ON RACHEL.
I'M SORRY, OKAY? I'M SORRY.
I WAS... I WAS DISGUSTED WITH MYSELF
AND THIS MORNING, I WAS SO... SO UPSET
AND THEN I GOT YOUR MESSAGE AND I WAS SO HAPPY
AND ALL I WANTED WAS TO GET HER
OUT OF MY APARTMENT AS FAST AS POSS...
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT TIME DID YOUR LITTLE FRIEND LEAVE?
UH...
OH, MY GOSH.
SHE WAS THERE... SHE WAS STILL THERE?
SHE WAS IN THERE WHEN I WAS IN THERE?!
OH! JUST... GET... OUT!
LISTEN-- OH, HEY, HEY, THE IMPORTANT THING IS
SHE MEANT NOTHING TO ME.
AND YET SHE WAS WORTH JEOPARDIZING
OUR RELATIONSHIP!
LOOK, I DIDN'T THINK
THERE WAS A RELATIONSHIP
TO JEOPARDIZE.
I THOUGHT WE WERE BROKEN UP.
WE WERE ON A BREAK.
THAT, FOR ALL I KNEW, COULD LAST FOREVER.
THAT, TO ME, IS A BREAKUP.
YOU THINK YOU'RE GOING TO GET OUT OF THIS ON A TECHNICALITY?
LOOK, I'M NOT TRYING TO GET OUT OF ANYTHING, OKAY?
I THOUGHT OUR RELATIONSHIP WAS DEAD.
WELL, YOU SURE HAD
A HELL OF A TIME AT THE WAKE.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I DON'T THINK WE SHOULD LISTEN TO THIS ANYMORE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WE CAN'T GO OUT THERE.
WHY NOT?
I'M HUNGRY.
BECAUSE THEY'LL KNOW WE'VE BEEN LISTENING.
GOD! AND TO HAVE TO HEAR ABOUT IT FROM GUNTHER!
COME ON, LIKE I WANTED HIM TO TELL YOU?
I RAN ALL OVER THE PLACE TRYING TO MAKE SURE
THAT DIDN'T HAPPEN.
OH, THAT IS SO SWEET.
I THINK I'M FALLING IN LOVE WITH YOU ALL OVER AGAIN.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK WE CAN GO OUT THERE.
THEY HAVE MORE IMPORTANT THINGS TO WORRY ABOUT.
YEAH, WE'LL BE FINE.
LOOK, RACHEL, I WANTED TO TELL YOU.
I THOUGHT I SHOULD, I DID
AND THEN CHANDLER AND JOEY CONVINCED ME NOT TO.
WAX THE DOOR SHUT.
WE'RE NEVER LEAVING, EVER.
HI. IT'S PHOEBE.
LISTEN, SOMEONE'S GOING TO HAVE TO TAKE MY 9:00 WITH MR. REHAK
BECAUSE IT'S, LIKE, 9:15 NOW, AND I'M NOT THERE.
NO, I'M IN THE MIDDLE OF A HUGE RELATIONSHIP FIGHT.
OH, THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
IT'S NOT MINE.
DON'T YOU REALIZE
NONE OF THIS WOULD EVER HAVE HAPPENED
IF I DIDN'T THINK, AT THAT SAME MOMENT
YOU WERE HAVING SEX WITH MARK?
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S SAY I HAD SLEPT WITH MARK.
WOULD YOU HAVE BEEN ABLE TO FORGIVE ME?
YES, I WOULD.
YOU'D BE OKAY IF YOU KNEW THAT MARK HAD KISSED ME
AND BEEN NAKED WITH ME AND MADE LOVE TO ME?
YES.
IF YOU KNEW THAT OUR HOT, SWEATY, WRITHING BODIES...
LA LA LA LA
LA LA LA LA LA!
OKAY, OKAY, YEAH, IT...
I WOULD HAVE BEEN DEVASTATED
BUT...
I WOULD STILL WANT TO BE WITH YOU...
BECAUSE IT'S... I MEAN, IT'S YOU.
AWW...
WHAT?
COME ON, RACH, TELL ME WHAT YOU'RE THINKING.
I'M THINKING...
I'M GOING TO ORDER A PIZZA.
ORDER A PIZZA, LIKE...
"I FORGIVE YOU"?
OH, MAN... PIZZA?
I LIKE PIZZA.
PUT OLIVES ON THE PIZZA.
WE COULD EAT THE WAX.
IT'S ORGANIC.
OH, GREAT-- FOOD WITH HAIR ON IT.
NO, NOT THE USED WAX.
BECAUSE THAT WOULD BE CRAZY?
HEY, COULD I... COULD I GET IN ON THAT
BECAUSE I'M KIND OF HUNGRY MYSELF.
FINE.
HI. YES, I'D LIKE TO ORDER A LARGE PIZZA.
NO ANCHOVIES.
WITH EXTRA ANCHOVIES.
IT'S OKAY, I'LL JUST PICK THEM OFF.
AND COULD YOU PLEASE CHOP SOME UP
AND JUST PUT IT RIGHT THERE IN THE SAUCE?
YOU CAN HAVE THE LAST PIECE IF YOU WANT.
WELL, I SHOULD THINK SO.
YOU SLEPT WITH SOMEONE.
THEY'RE GOING TO GET THROUGH THIS, AREN'T THEY?
YEAH. COME ON, IT'S ROSS AND RACHEL.
THEY'VE GOT TO.
WHAT IF THEY DON'T?
YOU THINK I NEED A NEW WALK?
WHAT?
WELL, YOU KNOW, I'VE BEEN WALKING THE SAME WAY
SINCE HIGH SCHOOL.
YOU KNOW HOW SOME GUYS-- THEY WALK INTO A ROOM
AND EVERYBODY TAKES NOTICE?
I THINK I NEED A TAKE NOTICE WALK.
ARE YOU ACTUALLY SAYING THESE WORDS?
WHAT, NOW YOU'RE NOT EVEN TALKING TO ME?
LOOK, RACHEL, I'M SORRY. OKAY?
I'M SORRY. I WAS OUT OF MY MIND.
I THOUGHT I'D LOST YOU.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
COME ON, COME ON. HOW INSANE MUST I HAVE BEEN
TO DO SOMETHING LIKE THIS? HUH?
I DON'T CHEAT. RIGHT?
THAT'S NOT ME. I'M NOT JOEY.
WHOA!
YEAH, OKAY.
HEY, IT'S 3:00 IN THE MORNING.
THEY DON'T KNOW THAT I'VE COME HOME YET.
YOU NOTICE HOW NEITHER ONE OF THEM ARE WONDERING WHERE I AM.
YEAH. YOU KNOW, PEOPLE CAN BE SO SELF INVOLVED.
YOU KNOW WHAT? YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M NOT... I'M NOT THE ONE THAT WANTED THAT...
THAT "BREAK," OKAY?
YOU'RE THE ONE THAT BAILED ON US.
YOU'RE THE ONE
THAT RAN THE MOMENT THINGS GOT JUST A LITTLE ROUGH.
THAT'S WHAT? THAT'S...
THAT IS NEITHER HERE NOR THERE.
OKAY, WELL, HERE WE ARE.
NOW WE'RE IN A TOUGH SPOT AGAIN, RACH.
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
HOW DO YOU WANT TO HANDLE IT?
DO YOU WANT TO FIGHT FOR US
OR DO YOU WANT TO BAIL?
LOOK, I...
I DID A TERRIBLE, STUPID, STUPID THING--
OKAY, AND I'M SORRY.
I WISH I COULD TAKE IT BACK, BUT I CAN'T.
I JUST CAN'T SEE US THROWING AWAY SOMETHING
WE KNOW IS SO DAMN GOOD.
RACHEL, I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
NO, ROSS!
DON'T!
YOU CAN'T JUST KISS ME
AND THINK YOU'RE GOING TO MAKE IT ALL GO AWAY.
IT DOESN'T WORK THAT WAY.
IT DOESN'T JUST
MAKE IT BETTER, OKAY?
OKAY, OKAY.
I THINK YOU SHOULD GO.
WHAT?
I REALLY THINK YOU NEED TO GO NOW.
OKAY, OKAY--
THIS MORNING, YOU SAID
THERE WAS NOTHING SO BIG THAT WE COULDN'T WORK
PAST IT TOGETHER.
WHAT THE HELL DID I KNOW?
LOOK, THERE'S GOT TO BE A WAY WE CAN WORK PAST THIS, OKAY?
I CAN'T IMAGINE... I CAN'T IMAGINE MY LIFE WITHOUT YOU
YOU KNOW, WITHOUT...
WITHOUT THESE ARMS...
AND YOUR FACE AND YOUR HEART--
YOUR GOOD HEART, RACH, AND...
NO.
I CAN'T. YOU'RE A TOTALLY DIFFERENT PERSON TO ME NOW.
I USED TO THINK OF YOU AS SOMEBODY THAT WOULD NEVER
EVER, HURT ME. EVER.
GOD, AND NOW I JUST CAN'T STOP PICTURING YOU WITH HER.
I CAN'T. IT DOESN'T MATTER WHAT YOU SAY OR WHAT
YOU DO, ROSS.
IT'S JUST CHANGED EVERYTHING.
FOREVER.
THIS...
THIS CAN'T BE IT.
I MEAN...
THEN HOW COME IT IS?
THEY'VE BEEN QUIET FOR A LONG TIME.
MAYBE SHE KILLED HIM.
LET'S GO.
IS THAT YOUR NEW WALK?
NO. I REALLY HAVE TO PEE.