WOW. THIS GIRL'S GOOD.
OH, YEAH, A SONG WITH RHYMING WORDS--
OOH, I NEVER THOUGHT OF THAT BEFORE.
? SAY YOU'LL STAY BESIDE ME... ?
I LIKE HER.
WHY, BECAUSE SHE CAN SING AND PLAY GUITAR
AND DO BOTH AT THE SAME TIME?
WELL, THAT'S PRETTY MUCH ALL I'M LOOKING FOR
FROM THESE PEOPLE.
LOOK AT YOU, ALL JEALOUS.
YEAH, PHEEBS, COME ON.
YOU TWO HAVE COMPLETELY DIFFERENT STYLES.
YOU KNOW, SHE'S MORE...
YOU KNOW, AND...
YOU'RE MORE...
? SAY YOU'LL STAY ?
? BESIDE ME. ?
YEAH!
SEE? SEE? EVERYBODY ELSE IS HAPPY SHE'S DONE.
OKAY, MY NEXT SONG IS CALLED
"PHOEBE BUFFAY, WHAT CAN I SAY?
"I REALLY LOVED
"WHEN WE WERE SINGING PARTNERS
"AND I SHOULDN'T HAVE LEFT YOU
THAT WAY."
OH, NO.
ONE OF THOSE "LOOK FOR THE HIDDEN MEANING" SONGS.
?  ?
HEY, PHOEBE.
HEY, LESLIE.
HOW DID YOU KNOW I'D BE HERE?
I RAN INTO VLAD AT THE PLACE WHERE THEY SELL THE BIG FISH.
HE SAID YOU PLAYED HERE A LOT, SO, UM...
ALL RIGHT, LISTEN, I HAVE TO GO TO THE BATHROOM
BUT IF "THE PLACE WITH THE BIG FISH" COMES UP AGAIN
I'D LIKE TO KNOW WHETHER THAT'S SEVERAL BIG FISH
OR JUST ONE BIG FISH.
SO PHOEBE TELLS US YOU WRITE JINGLES.
ACTUALLY, I SAID SHE ABANDONED ME
TO WRITE JINGLES.
UH, ANYTHING
WE MIGHT HAVE HEARD OF?
UH, YEAH, UM...
? HOME IS NEVER FAR AWAY ?
All except  ? HOME IS HOMESTAR STEW. ?
YEAH, BUT I DON'T DO THAT ANYMORE.
I GOT KIND OF SICK OF IT
AND THEN I COULDN'T COME UP WITH ANYTHING GOOD
SO THEY FIRED ME.
BUMMER.
WELL, UH, YOU KNOW, I WAS JUST...
UM, I WAS JUST THINKING
AND JUST HOPING THAT...
MAYBE YOU'D WANT TO GET BACK TOGETHER.
NO, BUT THANKS.
COME ON, PHOEBE, WOULD YOU JUST THINK ABOUT IT?
OKAY.
NO, BUT THANKS.
UH...
SEE YOU, PHEEBS.
WOW. THAT WAS KIND OF BRUTAL.
WELL, OKAY, LET THIS BE A LESSON TO ALL OF YOU.
ONCE YOU... ONCE YOU BETRAY ME
I BECOME LIKE THE ICEWOMAN.
YOU KNOW, I'M JUST... VERY COLD, HARD...
UNYIELDING.
YOU KNOW, NOTHING...
NOTHING CAN PENETRATE THIS ICY EXTERIOR.
CAN I HAVE A TISSUE, PLEASE?
SOMEONE IN THERE?
NO, THIS IS JUST PART
OF A DAREDEVIL GAME THAT I PLAY
CALL "WAIT UNTIL THE LAST MOMENT
BEFORE I BURST AND DIE."
GEEZ, MAN, DID YOU FALL...?
HI.
SO, UH, DID YOU?
DID YOU FALL HI?
SOMEONE WAS IN THE LADIES' ROOM; I COULDN'T WAIT.
I LEFT THE LID UP FOR YOU, THOUGH.
YOU KNOW WHAT, GUNTHER?
GO, UH, GO AHEAD.
I'M TALKING TO, UH...
THIS IS THE PART WHERE YOU SAY YOUR NAME.
GINGER.
I'M TALKING TO GINGER. SO...
DON'T YOU HAVE TO USE THE BATHROOM?
NO. NO.
I JUST, UH...
I'D RATHER, UH, TALK TO YOU.
YES, I DO.
YES, I DO HAVE TO GO TO THE BATHROOM.
SOMEONE IN HERE.
WHERE'S CHANDLER?
HE CAN'T MAKE IT.
HE SAID HE HAD TO GO BACK TO HIS JOB
AND DO, UH...
WHOA OH.
JOEY?
JOEY TRIBBIANI.
JOEY, I CAN SEE YOU, OKAY?
YOU'RE HIDING BEHIND THE COATS.
OH...
CLOSE ONE.
HI.
HI, SWEETIE.
HELLO.
HEY, ROSS.
YUH HUH.
I'VE GOT SOME BAD NEWS. WHAT?
I CAN GET A QUICK BITE TO EAT
BUT THEN I'M GOING TO HAVE TO COME BACK UP HERE.
COME ON, SWEETIE, YOU'VE HAD TO WORK LATE EVERY NIGHT
FOR THE PAST TWO WEEKS.
WHAT IS IT THIS TIME?
ACTUALLY, IT'S KIND OF MY FAULT.
I QUIT TODAY.
BUT WORK COMES FIRST.
OH, HEY, BUT THAT'S SAD ABOUT YOU, THOUGH.
WHAT HAPPENED?
WHAT HAPPENED? BURN OUT?
BURN ALL OUT, DID YOU?
NO, HE'S LEAVING
FOR A BETTER JOB.
OH, WELL, THAT'S GREAT.
SO I GUESS THIS IS GOOD BYE THEN.
GOOD BYE.
OKAY THEN.
OKAY.
WELL, WE'RE GOING TO MISS YOU AROUND HERE.
YEAH. ME, TOO.
SO, SEE YOU ON SATURDAY.
YEAH. YOU BET.
UCCH!
YOU KNOW, THOSE ARE A DELICACY IN INDIA.
YEAH, THAT WAS LESLIE CALLING AGAIN
TO SEE IF WE CAN GET BACK TOGETHER.
IT'S, LIKE, THE 20th TIME TODAY.
GOOD LUCK, LESLIE.
WOW. SHE MUST HAVE HURT YOU PRETTY BAD, HUH?
WELL, YEAH.
YOU KNOW, WE WERE BEST FRIENDS.
EVER SINCE WE WERE LITTLE
OUR MOMS WORKED ON THE BARGE TOGETHER.
OH.
YOU TWO MUST HAVE BEEN SO CUTE
RUNNING AROUND ON A BARGE.
YOU NEVER RUN ON A BARGE.
HEY.
HEY. HEY.
IS, UH, IS CHANDLER AROUND?
NO. HE MET SOME GIRL AT THE COFFEEHOUSE.
OOH.
YEAH. GINGER SOMETHING.
NO.
NO, NO.
ARE YOU SURE IT WASN'T SOMETHING THAT SOUNDED LIKE GINGER?
LIKE, UH, GINGEER?
NO, IT WAS GINGER.
I REMEMBER BECAUSE WHEN HE TOLD ME, I SAID...
? THE MOVIE STAR... ?
AW, MAN.
THAT'S THE GIRL I WAS HIDING FROM.
WHEN SHE FINDS OUT HE'S MY ROOMMATE
SHE'S GOING TO TELL HIM WHAT I DID.
WHAT DID YOU DO?
OH, OH, NO, NO, I CAN'T...
I CAN'T TELL YOU THAT.
IT'S, LIKE, THE MOST AWFUL, HORRIBLE THING
I'VE EVER DONE IN MY WHOLE LIFE.
WOW! YOU'RE REALLY NOT MAKING US
WANT TO HEAR IT LESS.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
DON'T TELL US.
WE'LL JUST WAIT TILL CHANDLER GETS HOME
BECAUSE IT'LL BE MORE FUN THAT WAY.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, IT WAS, LIKE, FOUR YEARS AGO.
OKAY, GINGER AND I HAD GONE OUT A FEW TIMES.
AND THEN, THIS ONE WEEKEND
WE WENT UP TO HER DAD'S CABIN--
JUST ME, HER, AND HER ANNOYING LITTLE DOG, PEPPER.
WELL, THAT NIGHT, I COOKED THIS REALLY ROMANTIC DINNER...
YOU GAVE HER FOOD POISONING!
I WISH.
AFTER DINNER, ME, HER, AND PEPPER ALL FELL ASLEEP
IN FRONT OF THE FIRE.
WELL, I WOKE UP IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT
AND I SAW THAT THE FIRE WAS DYING OUT
SO I PICKED UP A LOG AND THREW IT ON.
OR AT LEAST WHAT I THOUGHT WAS A LOG.
OH, MY GOD, YOU THREW PEPPER ON THE FIRE!
I WISH.
SEE, I GUESS ANOTHER THING
I PROBABLY SHOULD'VE TOLD YOU ABOUT GINGER
IS THAT SHE KIND OF HAS A, UH...
ARTIFICIAL LEG.
OH, MY GOD!
YOU THREW IT ON THE FIRE?
WHAT... SHE MUST HAVE FREAKED OUT!
YEAH, SHE MUST HAVE.
YOU DON'T KNOW?
WELL, I...
JOEY, WHAT DID YOU DO
AFTER YOU THREW HER LEG ON THE FIRE?
I RAN!
YOU RAN?
YEAH. THROUGH THE WOODS, WITH NO SOCKS ON.
WELL, THAT'S THE BEST KISS I'VE HAD
WITH ANYBODY I MET IN THE MEN'S ROOM.
ACTUALLY, ME, TOO.
OH. FOOT IN THE PUDDLE.
FOOT ALL IN THE PUDDLE.
OH, DAMN. I HATE THAT.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO GET YOU OUT
OF THOSE SHOES.
OH, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
NO, REALLY, YOU'RE GOING TO FREEZE.
NO, I'M NOT. I'M...
YOU'RE NOT?
WHAT DO YOU...?
WHAT DO YOU GOT, A BIONIC FOOT?
SOMEDAY MAYBE.
FUNNY BOOK?
HMM?
OH, NO, NO.
I'M JUST THINKING ABOUT SOMETHING FUNNY I HEARD TODAY--
UM, MARK... MARK SAYING, "I'LL SEE YOU SATURDAY."
YEAH, AT THE LECTURE.
I TOLD YOU THAT LAST WEEK.
YOU SAID YOU DIDN'T MIND.
OH, NO, NO, IT'S NOT THE LECTURE I MIND.
UM...
PLEASE TELL ME IT'S NOT BECAUSE I'M GOING WITH MARK.
WELL...
OH, MY GOD! ROSS!
WELL, I'M SORRY, BUT...
LOOK, IF YOU'RE NOT WORKING WITH HIM ANYMORE
WHY DO YOU STILL HAVE TO DO STUFF WITH HIM?
BECAUSE HE'S MY FRIEND.
OKAY, BUT DO YOU REALLY NEED ANOTHER FRIEND?
OKAY, WELL
IF I STOP PLAYING WITH JOEY AND CHANDLER
CAN I PLAY WITH MARK?
IS THAT FUNNY?
AM I SUPPOSED TO BE LAUGHING?
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU THOUGHT
"SEE YOU SATURDAY" WAS FUNNY.
LOOK, HONEY, MARK IS IN FASHION, OKAY?
I LIKE HAVING A FRIEND
THAT I CAN SHARE THIS STUFF WITH.
YOU GUYS WOULD NEVER WANT
TO GO TO A LECTURE WITH ME.
PAAH!
I WOULD LOVE
TO GO WITH YOU.
REALLY?
YEAH. HEY, I HAVE CLOTHES.
I EVEN PICK THEM OUT.
I MEAN, FOR ALL YOU KNOW, I COULD BE A FASHION...
MONGER.
OKAY, HONEY, I WOULD LOVE
FOR YOU TO GO WITH ME.
WHAT?
WHAT SHOULD I WEAR?
NOW I'M A LITTLE NERVOUS.
YOU KNOW, THEY SAY A WATCHED POT NEVER BEEPS.
IT'S... YOU KNOW, IT'S BEEN A COUPLE OF HOURS, AND...
SHE HASN'T CALLED.
NOT THAT I EVEN CARE.
I DON'T.
PHOEBE, WHY DON'T YOU JUST CALL HER?
YOU OBVIOUSLY WANT TO.
YOU THINK YOU KNOW ME SO WELL.
WELL, DON'T YOU WANT TO?
YEAH.
OKAY, SO I DO KNOW YOU.
THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
WELL, SO?
I CAN'T.
SHE DUMPED ME.
I TOTALLY TRUSTED HER
AND THEN ONE DAY, IT WAS, LIKE, "BYE, PHEEBS." GONE.
YOU KNOW WHAT THE SADDEST PART IS?
WHEN WE WERE PLAYING TOGETHER
THAT WAS, LIKE, THE MOST FUN I'VE EVER HAD
IN, LIKE, ALL MY LIVES.
? MY FAVORITE SHOES, SO GOOD TO ME ?
? I WEAR THEM EVERY DAY ?
? DOWN AT THE HEEL, HOLES IN THE TOES ?
? DON'T CARE WHAT PEOPLE SAY ?
? MY FEET'S BEST FRIEND, PALS TO THE END ?
? WITH THEM I'M ONE HOT CHICKY ?
? THOUGH LATE ONE NIGHT ?
? NOT MUCH LIGHT ?
? I STEPPED IN SOMETHING ICKY ?
? STICKY SHOES ?
? ALWAYS MAKE ME SMILE ?
? NEXT TIME I'LL ?
? AVOID THE ?
? PILE. ?
WE'RE BEGINNING TO SEE
A LOT OF LAYERING OF SHEER FABRICS AND COLORS.
FOR INSTANCE, A SHEER NAVY BLOUSE
OVER A PINK BODYSUIT...
I'M REALLY GLAD WE CAME.
...THE WISPY CHIFFONS AND DELICATE MESHES
WE'RE SEEING ON THE RUNWAYS ARE TOTALLY SHEER...
YOU'RE SO PRETTY.
...AND THE DESIGNERS ARE USING HEAVIER JERSEYS
OR PROVIDING SLIPS...
I LOVE YOU.
OH.
WE'RE ALSO TAKING THESE GARMENTS...
? SMELLY CAT, SMELLY CAT ?
? WHAT ARE THEY FEEDING YOU? ?
? IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT. ?
WOW, THAT'S GREAT!
OH, YEAH?
YOU KNOW, YOU COULD TOTALLY SELL THIS!
IT WOULD BE PERFECT FOR, LIKE, UM....
A KITTY LITTER CAMPAIGN.
A JINGLE? NO.
NO, NO, NO. NO.
WHY NOT? YOU'D MAKE A TON OF MONEY.
WELL, IF I WAS IN THIS FOR THE MONEY
I WOULD BE A MILLIONAIRE BY NOW, YOU KNOW?
YOU JUST GOT TO GET OUT
OF THAT JINGLE HEAD, SWEETIE.
AH! YOU'RE RIGHT. YOU'RE RIGHT! I'M SORRY.
THAT'S OKAY.
ALL RIGHT. I'M GOING TO PLAY A SONG NOW
THAT'S REALLY, REALLY SAD, OKAY?
IT'S CALLED
"MAGICIAN BOX MIX UP."
...OVERSIZED BRACELETS, OVERSIZED EARRINGS
OVERSIZING OF ACCESSORIES IN GENERAL
IS VERY POPULAR NOW.
...GARMENTS WITH A FAR EASTERN INFLUENCE
ARE REALLY BREAKING OUT THIS YEAR.
HI. HEY.
CAN I BORROW THIS?
MY MILK'S GONE BAD.
OH. I HATE THAT.
I ONCE HAD A THING OF HALF AND HALF--
IT STOLE MY CAR.
SO, UM... HOW WAS YOUR DATE WITH GINGER?
GREAT. IT WAS GREAT.
SHE'S, UH...
SHE'S GREAT-- GREAT LOOKING, GREAT PERSONALITY.
SHE'S GREATNESS.
HMM.
SOUNDS LIKE SHE'S GOT THE, UH...
WHOLE PACKAGE.
OH, YEAH.
SO SHE'S GOT IT ALL, HUH?
SHE'S THE REAL DEAL.
JOEY TOLD YOU ABOUT THE LEG, HUH?
UH HUH.
OH, GOD.
IT FREAKED ME OUT, OKAY?
I KNOW IT SHOULDN'T HAVE, BUT IT DID.
I MEAN, I LIKE HER.
I DON'T WANT TO STOP SEEING HER
BUT, EVERY SO OFTEN, IT'S, LIKE
"HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT? WHERE'S YOUR LEG?"
I MEAN, I'M THE SMALLEST PERSON
IN THE WORLD, AREN'T I?
I'M THE SMALLEST PERSON IN THE WORLD.
MORNING.
ACTUALLY,HE'S THE SMALLEST PERSON
IN THE WORLD.
HEARD ABOUT THE LEG BURNING, HUH?
IT CAME UP.
LISTEN, I, UH... I KNOW IT'S A LONG SHOT BUT...
BY ANY CHANCE, DID SHE FIND THAT FUNNY?
SO I NODDED OFF A LITTLE.
NODDED OFF?!
ROSS, YOU WERE SNORING!
MY FATHER'S BOAT
DIDN'T MAKE THAT MUCH NOISE WHEN IT HIT ROCKS!
COME ON.
45 MINUTES!
45 MINUTES THE MAN TALKED ABOUT STRAPPY BACKED DRESSES.
WELL, OKAY, HOW ABOUT FOUR HOURS
IN A FREEZING MUSEUM AUDITORIUM
LISTENING TO PROFESSOR PIT STAINS
AND HIS, "HEY, EVERYBODY!
"REMEMBER THAT THING THAT'S BEEN DEAD FOR A GAZILLION YEARS?
WELL, HERE'S A LITTLE BONE WE DIDN'T KNOW IT HAD!"
FIRST OF ALL, IT'S PROFESSORPITAIN.
AND, SECOND OF ALL, THAT LITTLE BONE PROVED
THAT THAT PARTICULAR DINOSAUR HAD WINGS BUT DIDN'T FLY.
OKAY, SEE, NOW, WHAT I JUST HEARD:
BLAH BLAH BLAH, BLAH BLAH BLAH BLAH
BLAH BLAH, BLAH BLAH.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
A HUNDRED MILLION PEOPLE WENT TO SEE A MOVIE
ABOUT WHAT I DO.
I WONDER HOW MANY PEOPLE
WOULD GO SEE A MOVIE CALLED JURASSIC PARKA.
OH...
THAT IS SO...!
NO, NO, NO-- A BUNCH OF OUT OF CONTROL JACKETS
TAKE OVER AN ISLAND!
YOU KNOW, IF WHAT I DO IS SO LAME
THEN WHY DID YOU INSIST ON COMING WITH ME THIS MORNING?
HUH? WAS IT SO I JUST WOULDN'T GO WITH MARK?
NO.
I... I WANTED TO BE WITH YOU.
I DON'T KNOW.
I FEEL LIKE... LATELY...
I FEEL LIKE YOU'RE SLIPPING AWAY FROM ME
YOU KNOW, WITH THIS NEW JOB
AND ALL THESE NEW PEOPLE
AND YOU'VE  GOT THIS WHOLE LIFE GOING ON.
I KNOW IT'S DUMB
BUT I... I JUST HATE
THAT I'M NOT A PART OF IT.
IT'S NOT DUMB.
BUT MAYBE IT'S OKAY THAT YOU'RE NOT A PART OF IT.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
I MEAN, IT'S LIKE
I LIKE THAT YOU'RE NOT INVOLVED
IN THAT PART OF MY LIFE.
THAT'S A LITTLE CLEARER.
NO, BUT HONEY, SEE
IT DOESN'T MEAN THAT I DON'T LOVE YOU
BECAUSE I DO.
I LOVE YOU.
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH
BUT MY WORK, IT'S FOR ME, YOU KNOW?
I'M OUT THERE ON MY OWN AND I'M DOING IT
AND IT'S SCARY
BUT I LOVE IT BECAUSE IT'S MINE.
BUT, I MEAN, IS THAT OKAY?
SURE, UH...
YOU'RE THINKING ABOUT MY LEG, AREN'T YOU?
NO.
NO. ACTUALLY, I FORGET.
WHAT IS THE DEAL WITH THAT AGAIN?
LOOK, IT'S OKAY IF IT BOTHERS YOU.
REALLY. I MEAN, THE ONLY THING I NEED TO KNOW
I SHOW MUCH IT BOTHERS YOU
BECAUSE I DON'T LIKE WASTING MY TIME.
AM I WASTING MY TIME?
NO.
NO, I DON'T THINK SO.
OKAY.
I MEAN, IT'S JUST LIKE ANYTHING ELSE:
YOU JUST HAVE TO GET USED TO IT.
MMM.
WHAT'S THAT?
THAT'S... THAT'S MY NUBBIN.
WHAT'S A NUBBIN?
IT'S KIND OF A, UH...
A THIRD NIPPLE KIND OF THING.
DO YOU HAVE THREE NIPPLES?
WELL, YOU KNOW, TWO REGULARS
AND ONE THAT BARELY QUALIFIES AS A...
UH, WHAT?
NOTHING.
I... I JUST REMEMBERED I HAVE TO LEAVE.
YOU, UH...
YOU HAVE TO LEAVE NOW?
HOW COME?
UH, WELL, IT'S NUBBIN... NOTHING!
UM...
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'LL SEE YOU LATER, OKAY?
EEW!
OH, I THOUGHT YOU WEREN'T COMING.
WHERE WERE YOU?
COME HERE, COME HERE.
OKAY.
DON'T GET MAD, OKAY?
DON'T GIVE ME A REASON TO GET MAD, OKAY?
I PLAYED "SMELLY CAT"
FOR THE PEOPLE AT MY OLD AD AGENCY.
THEY WENT NUTS.
NO... LOOK, I TOLD YOU
THAT I DIDN'T WANT YOU TO TRY AND SELL IT
AND YOU JUST...
YOU BIG, FAT DID IT ANYWAY.
UH...
GOD, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK, FIVE YEARS AGO
I PROBABLY WOULD HAVE DONE ANYTHING TO PLAY WITH YOU
BUT I CAN DO IT BY MYSELF
AND IF I CAN'T TRUST YOU, THEN JUST FORGET IT.
NO, NO. I DON'T WANT TO FORGET IT.
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU HAVE TO CHOOSE.
IF THE MOST IMPORTANT THING ON THE PLANET TO YOU
IS THIS CAT POOPY THING
THEN, OKAY, YOU CAN HAVE "SMELLY CAT"
BUT WE WON'T BE PARTNERS.
OH.
SO WHAT'S IT GOING TO BE?
? Smelly cat, smelly cat ?
Problem odor in the litter box?
Don't change your kitty.
Change your kitty litter.
? ...smelly cat, it's not your fault. ?
SORRY, PHEEBS.
YEAH. YOU OKAY?
YEAH. I ACTUALLY AM, YEAH.
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, LIFE'S...
LIFE'S GOING TO HAND YOU ALL KINDS OF STUFF
AND, YOU KNOW, YOU LEARN YOUR LITTLE LESSONS
AND, HOPEFULLY, YOU GROW.
YEAH.
YOU WANT TO HEAR A NEW SONG?
YEAH. I'D LOVE TO.
OKAY.
? JINGLE BITCH SCREWED ME OVER ?
? GO TO HELL, JINGLE WHORE ?
? GO TO HELL, GO TO HELL ?
? GO TO HE EH ELL. ?
THAT'S ALL I HAVE SO FAR.
WOO! WOO! WOO!
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
THE DOCTOR.
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
OH, YES.
JUST HAD ME A LITTLE NUBBINECTOMY.
YUP.
TWO NIPPLES, NO WAITING.
WOW. JUST LIKE RACHEL IN HIGH SCHOOL.
WHAT?!
COME ON! I WAS KIDDING.
IT WAS SUCH AN OBVIOUS JOKE.
THAT WAS AN OBVIOUS JOKE
AND I DIDN'T THINK OF IT.
WHY DIDN'T I THINK OF IT?
THE SOURCE OF ALL MY POWERS.
OH, DEAR GOD, WHAT HAVE I DONE?