HERE YOU GO.
THANK YOU.
SAY, RACHEL, I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU'D LIKE TO GO TO A MOVIE WITH ME SOMETIME...
AS MY LOVER.
HMM, TOO OUT THERE.
MAYBE YOU'D JUST LIKE
TO GET SOMETHING TO EAT WITH ME SOMETIME...
AS MY LOVER.
HI.
ALL RIGHT. LET'S GO SHOPPING.
GOT A POSITIVE BALANCE ON MY CREDIT CARD.
I WANT TO USE IT UP BEFORE CITIBANK GOES UNDER.
GOOD IDEA. GOOD IDEA.
UM... BEFORE WE GO, YOU KNOW
THERE'S.... THERE'S SOMETHING I NEED TO SAY.
OH, OKAY.
I'VE KIND OF HAD THIS, UH...
THIS CRUSH ON YOU
BUT SINCE YOU WERE WITH ROSS
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING ABOUT IT
BUT NOW THAT YOU'RE NOT
I'D REALLY LIKE TO ASK YOU OUT SOMETIME
SO, THAT'S THAT'S WHAT I'M DOING...
NOW.
WOW. UM...
I DROPPED A CUP.
?  ?
THAT'S WHY, WITHIN A FEW YEARS
THAT VOICE RECOGNITION IS GOING
TO BE PRETTY MUCH STANDARD
ON ANY COMPUTER YOU BUY.
SO YOU CAN BE, LIKE, "WASH MY CAR," "CLEAN MY ROOM."
IT'S NOT GOING TO BE ABLE TO DO ANY OF THOSE THINGS
BUT IT WILL UNDERSTAND WHAT YOU'RE SAYING.
WOW. WILL IT BE ABLE TO RECOGNIZE MY VOICE
IF I TALK LIKE THIS?
IT'LL UNDERSTAND YOU, BUT IT'S GOING
TO MAKE FUN OF YOU.
OH, THIS IS SO GREAT.
YEAH, IT WAS.
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
BYE.
HELLO, PEOPLE WHO DO NOT LIVE HERE.
HI. HELLO.
I GAVE YOU A KEY FOR EMERGENCIES.
WE WERE OUT OF DORITOS.
HEY, HOW'D THE DATE GO
WITH MR. MILLIONAIRE?
"MR. MILLIONAIRE, NEW FROM SNOOTY PLAYTHINGS.
THIRD WIFE SOLD SEPARATELY."
HE'S GREAT.
I MEAN, WE HAD SUCH A GOOD TIME TOGETHER.
HE'S SO FUNNY AND SO SWEET
AND I'M NOT ATTRACTED TO HIM AT ALL.
STILL?
NO!
IT'S DRIVING ME CRAZY.
IN EVERY OTHER WAY, HE'S LIKE THE PERFECT GUY.
HE HAS EVERYTHING.
PLUS, HE ACTUALLY HAS EVERYTHING.
LIFE SIZED IMPERIAL STORM TROOPERS FROM SHARPER IMAGE?
TWO.
WOW. CAN JOEY AND I PUT THEM ON AND FIGHT?
OH, MOMMY!
OH, DADDY!
I AM A BIG OLD BADDY!
OH, MOMMY!
OH, DADDY!
I AM A BIG OLD BADDY!
I GUESS HE MUST HAVE GOTTEN THE PART IN THAT PLAY.
EITHER THAT OR GLORIA ESTEFAN WAS RIGHT.
EVENTUALLY, THE RHYTHM IS GOING TO GET YOU.
JOE, HOW'S IT GOING?
GOOD.
HEY.
HI.
OH, SO YOU'RE PLAYING ADRIENNE, HUH?
YES. ARE YOU ONE OF THE RETARDED COUSINS?
NO, NO. I'M PLAYING YOUR HUSBAND, VICTOR.
I'M JOEY TRIBBIANI.
HI. NICE TO MEET YOU.
KATE MILLER.
SO, THE PLAY'S PRETTY GREAT, HUH?
OH, YEAH. I LOVE JENNIFER BANBERRY'S WORK.
SHE'S SO BRILLIANTLY INCISIVE
WHEN IT COMES TO DECONSTRUCTING
THE PSYCHE OF THE AMERICAN MIDDLE CLASS.
OH, FORGET ABOUT IT.
SHE ROCKS!
WHERE DO I KNOW YOU FROM?
DR. DRAKE RAMORAY?
DAYS OF OUR LIVES?
VOTED MOST DATEABLE NEUROSURGEON BY TEEN BEAT?
NO, THAT'S NOT IT.
SO, YOU'RE A SOAP ACTOR.
WELL, THIS MUST BE PRETTY EXCITING FOR YOU
BEING IN A REAL PLAY, HMM?
HEY, I'VE DONE PLAYS BEFORE.
I'M A SERIOUS ACTOR.
THAT INFOMERCIAL...
FOR THE MILK CARTON SPOUT THING.
YOU'RE THE GUY WHO DOESN'T KNOW HOW TO POUR MILK.
SEE, I ACTUALLY CANPOUR MILK
BUT I GOT YOU BELIEVING THAT I COULDN'T.
NOW, SEE, THAT'S ACTING.
RIGHT. AT THE END, YOU CHOKED ON A COOKIE.
YEAH. THAT WAS REAL.
WOW. I CANNOT BELIEVE MARK ASKED YOU OUT.
I KNOW.
SO WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO TELL HIM?
WELL, I TOLD HIM I WOULD THINK ABOUT IT
BUT I'M GOING TO TELL HIM NO.
HUH.
I THINK I'D SAY NO TO ANYBODY RIGHT NOW.
OH, BUT IT WAS SO STRANGE.
I MEAN, I'M STANDING THERE
WITH THIS CHARMING, CUTE GUY
WHO'S ASKING ME TO GO OUT WITH HIM--
WHICH I AM ALLOWED TO DO--
AND I FELT GUILTY, YOU KNOW
LIKE I'D BE CHEATING ON ROSS OR SOMETHING.
WOW. SO, OKAY
MAYBE THAT MEANS THAT YOU'RE NOT OVER ROSS YET
AND YOU HAVE ISSUES WITH YOUR FATHER.
I DON'T HAVE ANY ISSUES WITH MY FATHER.
OKAY, SO IT'S PROBABLY JUST THE ROSS THING THEN.
I HATE THIS WOMAN. I HATE HER!
SHE TOLD EVERYONE IN THE COMPANY
ABOUT THAT INFOMERCIAL
AND NOW THEY ALL KEEP ASKING ME
TO OPEN THEIR DRINKS, OKAY
AND WHENEVER I CAN'T DO IT
THEY'RE ALL, LIKE... LIKE, LAUGHING AT ME.
HELLO.
HEY!
SO RACHEL CALLED.
WANTS TO SEE ME.
GOING OVER IN A MINUTE.
WOW. WHAT DO YOU THINK SHE WANTS?
WELL, MAYBE THE CRAZY FOG HAS LIFTED
AND SHE REALIZES THAT LIFE WITHOUT ME SUCKS.
IT'S POSSIBLE.
YOU ARE VERY LOVABLE.
I'D MISS YOU IF I BROKE UP WITH YOU.
I'M JUST TRYING TO BE SUPPORTIVE.
WELL, BE SUPPORTIVE LIKE A GUY.
IF I BROKE UP WITH YOU, I'D MISS YOU.
HI.
YOU, UH... WANTED TO SEE ME?
YEAH.
UH, HERE'S A BOX OF YOUR STUFF.
WHAT?
YOU KNOW, IT'S JUST, LIKE, HATS AND SHIRT AND CDs.
JUST SORT OF STUFF THAT YOU'VE LEFT HERE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
ARE YOU TRYING TO HURT ME
OR SOMETHING?
NO.
ROSS, IT...
IT JUST SEEMS THAT, YOU KNOW
IT'S TIME WE, YOU KNOW, MOVE ON.
I MEAN, DON'T YOU THINK?
YES.
YEAH.
YES, I DO.
GOOD.
YEAH, I I REALLY DO.
HEY!
THIS... THIS WAS A GIFT.
ROSS
YOU GOT THAT FOR FREE FROM THE MUSEUM GIFT SHOP.
IT'S STILL A GIFT.
I GOT IF FROM THE GIFT SHOP.
OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
GIVE ME THE MUG.
I'LL KEEP THE MUG.
NO! YOU KNOW, DON'T DO ME ANY FAVORS.
IN FACT, WHERE...
WHERE'S THE REST OF MY STUFF?
LIKE, LIKE...
MY, UM... HEY!
THIS BOOK IS MINE!
AND AND AND
AND THAT T SHIRT YOU SLEEP IN, I'D LIKE THAT BACK, TOO.
YES, I DO.
YOU KNOW HOW MUCH I LOVE THAT T SHIRT.
YOU NEVER EVEN WEAR THAT T SHIRT.
I'M JUST TRYING TO HELP YOU MOVE ON.
OH, YOU ARE A PETTY MAN.
YOU ARE A PETTY, PETTY...
PETTY, PETTY...
PETTY, SMALL...
SMALL...
YOU ARE SO JUST DOING THIS OUT OF SPITE.
UH UH. NO, NO, NO.
I'M GOING TO WEAR THIS ALL THE TIME.
I LOVE THIS SHIRT.
YOU HAVE NOT WORN THAT T SHIRT SINCE YOU WERE 15.
IT DOESN'T EVEN FIT YOU ANYMORE.
OH, YEAH, YEAH.
YEAH, YEAH.
OH, OKAY, OKAY.
NOW, IF YOU DON'T MIND
I'M GOING TO TAKE THE REST OF MY STUFF
AND RELAX
IN MY FAVORITE SHIRT.
YOU HAVE A PLEASANT EVENING.
SO YOU'RE, LIKE, A ZILLIONAIRE.
AND YOU'RE OUR AGE.
YOU'RE OURAGE.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU SHOULD, LIKE, YOU SHOULD BUY A STATE
AND THEN JUST NAME IT AFTER YOURSELF.
LIKE PETE DAKOTA.
OR MISSISSIPETE.
OH, OH, I GOT IT.
PETE CHICAGO.
THAT'S NOT A STATE, JOE.
OH, AND MISSISSIPETE IS?
I GOT TO GO.
SO, I'LL SEE YOU GUYS LATER.
OKAY.
YOU'RE OURAGE.
SO, WE ON FOR TOMORROW?
ABSOLUTELY.
NOW GET OUT OF HERE, YOU.
OKAY, I'M RUNNING OUT OF PLACES I CAN TOUCH HIM.
IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG WITH ME?
WHY AM I ONLY ATTRACTED TO GUYS WHERE THERE'S NO FUTURE?
EITHER THEY'RE TOO OLD OR THEY'RE TOO YOUNG
OR THEY'RE A BIG, MISOGYNIST, JERK POET LIKE JULIO--
WHO, BY THE WAY, I'M STILL ATTRACTED TO--
AND THEN THERE'S PETE
WHO'S CRAZY ABOUT ME, AND HE'S ABSOLUTELY PERFECT
AND THERE'S, LIKE, ZIP GOING ON.
SERIOUSLY, DOES IT SOUND LIKE THERE'S SOMETHING WRONG WITH ME?
YEAH. KIND OF.
HAPPY? IS THAT WHAT I'M SUPPOSED TO BE, VIC?
HAPPY?
WHY DON'T YOU TELL ME WHAT YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE, HUH?
BECAUSE I SURE AS HELL CAN'T FIGURE IT OUT.
I TALK TO YOU AND NOTHING.
YOU LOOK AT ME AND IT'S NOTHING.
NOTHING.
MMM, TASTY.
I'M REALLY STARTING TO FEEL LIKE YOU GUYS HAVE A HISTORY.
IT'S NICE.
I HAVE A QUESTION ABOUT THIS SCENE.
YES.
WELL, I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY ADRIENNE'S ATTRACTED TO VICTOR.
PEEL THE ONION.
FIRST OF ALL, HE'S GOOD LOOKING.
YEAH.
I THINK MY CHARACTER'S GOING TO NEED
A LITTLE BIT MORE OF A REASON THAN THAT.
HEY, HOW ABOUT THIS ONE--
UH, IT SAYS SO IN THE SCRIPT!
YOU KNOW, I DON'T KNOW
WHY MY CHARACTER LIKES YOU EITHER.
I MEAN, IT SAYS IN THE SCRIPT HERE
THAT YOU'RE A BITCH.
IT DOESN'T SAY THAT IN THE SCRIPT.
IT DOES IN MINE.
I CAN BLOW DRY IT.
I CAN PUT GEL ON IT.
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
I STILL WIND UP WITH THIS LITTLE COWLICKY THING
ON THE MIDDLE PART OF MY HEAD.
IT'S SO ANNOYING.
DOES IT BUG YOU?
YOU BUG ME.
IS THERE ANY CHANCE YOU DIDN'T SEE THAT?
ROSS, YOU GOT TO STOP, OKAY?
YOU CAN'T JUST STARE THROUGH THE PEEPHOLE
FOR THREE HOURS.
YOU'RE GOING TO GET PEEP EYE.
I KNEW IT. I KNEW IT.
I ALWAYS KNEW SHE LIKED HIM.
SHE'D SAY NO, BUT HERE WE ARE, RIGHT?
WE JUST BROKE UP, FIRST THING SHE DOES...
YOU DIDN'T JUST BREAK UP.
HEY, IT'S BEEN, LIKE, THREE WEEKS.
YOU SLEPT WITH SOMEBODY
THREE HOURS AFTER YOU THOUGHT YOU BROKE UP.
I MEAN, BULLETS HAVE LEFT GUNS SLOWER.
HERE THEY COME. HERE THEY...
OH, IF SHE KISSES HIM GOOD NIGHT
I'M GOING TO KILL MYSELF, I SWEAR.
I CAN'T... I CAN'T WATCH...
COME ON. DATE OVER.
DATE OVER.
OH, OH. HERE WE GO.
SHE'S GOING IN.
OKAY.
HE'S GOING IN.
THE DOOR'S CLOSED.
I CAN'T SEE ANYTHING WITH THE DOOR CLOSED.
AND THE INVENTOR OF THE DOOR RESTS HAPPILY IN HIS GRAVE.
OKAY. I HAVE TO DO SOMETHING.
I MEAN, I HAVE TO STOP IT.
STOP WHAT? I DON'T KNOW.
BUT I HAVE A FEELING THAT MY BEING THERE WILL DO IT.
LOOK, THIS GUY
IS BAD NEWS, CHANDLER.
HE'S... I CAN SEE HE'S AN OPERATOR.
RACHEL WOULDN'T DATE AN OPERATOR.
THEY ONLY MAKE 20 GRAND A YEAR
AND THEY HAVE TO WORK NIGHTS.
I'LL GO OVER, AND I WILL BORROW SOMETHING.
JUICE. I NEED JUICE.
NO, YOU CAN'T!
LOOK, THEY MUST BE STOPPED!
I AM YOUR FRIEND
AND I AM NOT GOING TO LET YOU DO THIS!
YOU ARE SURPRISINGLY STRONG!
I NEED JUICE.
PEOPLE NEED JUICE!
LOOK, MAN...
LISTEN TO ME.
JUICE! THEY NEED JUICE!
SHE'S MOVING ON, OKAY?
IF IT'S NOT THIS GUY, IT'S GOING TO BE SOMEBODY ELSE.
UNLESS YOU'RE THINKING ABOUT SUBLETTING MY PEEPHOLE
YOU ARE GOING TO HAVE TO GET USED TO THE FACT
THAT THE RELATIONSHIP IS OVER.
OKAY, MAN?
IT'S OVER.
YEAH. OKAY.
OKAY.
IT'S JUST I MISS HER SO MUCH.
I KNOW.
IS IT JUST ME, OR DID "SUBLETTING MY PEEPHOLE"
SOUND KIND OF DIRTY?
WHY DO ALL YOUR COFFEE MUGS HAVE NUMBERS ON THE BOTTOM?
OH, THAT'S SO MONICA CAN KEEP TRACK.
THAT WAY, IF ONE OF THEM'S MISSING
SHE CAN BE, LIKE, "WHERE'S NUMBER 27?"
YOU KNOW WHAT?
NO, AND I DON'T THINK I'M GOING TO WANT TO.
I CAN'T DO THIS.
YEP, YEP. THAT'S WHAT I DIDN'T WANT TO KNOW.
YEAH. OH, MARK, I'M JUST DOING THIS
FOR THE WRONG REASONS, YOU KNOW?
I'M JUST DOING IT TO GET BACK AT ROSS.
I'M SORRY.
IT'S NOT VERY FAIR TO YOU.
AH, FAIR SHMAIR, YOU KNOW?
LOOK, YOU WANT TO GET BACK AT ROSS
I AM HERE FOR YOU.
REALLY.
NO, NO.
I SAY WE GET BACK AT HIM RIGHT HERE ON THIS COUCH.
RIGHT HERE.
OH, GOD.
I'M SORRY ABOUT THIS.
THAT'S OKAY.
YOU SURE?
YEAH.
I CAN JUST GO HOME
AND GET BACK AT HIM BY MYSELF.
...POISED TO BECOME THE PENICILLIN OF THE 21st CENTURY.
AND SO, TODAY, THIS HOSPITAL IS ABOUT TO TAKE MAJOR STEPS
TOWARD LEADING THAT REVOLUTION.
IT IS TRULY IRONIC...
HEY.
COULD I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
...ON THE ONE HAND, TO CONSIDER THE SIZE
OF THE HUMAN GENE...
WHERE ARE WE?
WELL, WITH ALL THESE DOCTORS AND NURSES
I'M GOING TO SAY MIDGET RODEO.
JUST TELL ME THE TRUTH.
OKAY.
UM...
YOU KNOW, I I DON'T THINK I TOLD YOU THIS
BUT I JUST RECENTLY GOT OUT
OF A REALLY SERIOUS RELATIONSHIP.
WASN'T THAT, LIKE, A YEAR AGO?
SO I DID TELL YOU.
OKAY. WELL, YOU KNOW, THAT'S NOT REALLY THE THING.
THE THING IS, IS THAT RIGHT NOW
I'M JUST IN A PLACE IN MY LIFE
WHERE I JUST NEED TO FOCUS ON ME.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
OH, YEAH. I KNOW.
I SO WANT TO BE ATTRACTED TO YOU...
BUT YOU'RE NOT.
OKAY. GOOD.
I'M SORRY.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
DON'T BE.
THIS IS NOT...
DON'T BE, BECAUSE IT'S NOT SO BAD.
IT'S NOT?
I KNOW I'M NO JON BON JOVI...
OR SOMEONE YOU FIND ATTRACTIVE.
I'M JUST... I JUST THINK, YOU KNOW
THAT YOU MIGHT END UP FEELING DIFFERENTLY.
HOW CAN ANY OF US FORGET JEFFREY ASTROFT?
WELL, LOOK, I DON'T WANT THIS TO COME OUT WRONG
BUT, UH, YOU SEEM AWFULLY CONFIDENT
FOR A GUY I JUST TOLD I WASN'T ATTRACTED TO.
YEAH. STUPIDLY CHARMING, ISN'T IT?
AH, LISTEN, LET'S...
YOU WANT TO GET SOMETHING TO EAT?
BECAUSE THIS PLACE IS KIND OF DEE PRESSING.
AND NOW THE MAN WHO MADE ALL THIS POSSIBLE...
MR. PETER BECKER.
ONE SEC.
I DON'T THINK THIS TOWN IS BIG ENOUGH
FOR THE BOTH OF US TO RELAX IN.
DRAW!
I WASN'T DOING ANYTHING.
UH OH. WHAT DID SHE DO NOW?
JUST BECAUSE SHE WENT TO YALE DRAMA
SHE THINKS SHE'S, LIKE, THE GREATEST ACTRESS SINCE...
SINCE SLICED BREAD.
AH, SLICED BREAD-- A WONDERFUL LADY MACBETH.
GOD, I JUST... I HATE HER.
I HATE HER WITH HER, "OH, I'M SO TALENTED"
AND, "OOH, I'M SO PRETTY" AND, "OOH, I SMELL SO GOOD."
I THINK SOMEBODY HAS A CRUSH ON SOMEBODY.
CHANDLER, CAN WE PLEASE TRY AND STAY FOCUSED
ON MY PROBLEM HERE, YOU KNOW?
I'M TALKING ABOUT YOU, YOU BIG, BIG FREAK.
OH.
OH. OH. YOU'RE OUT OF YOUR MIND.
YOU HAVE DONE NOTHING BUT TALK ABOUT HER.
FOR THE LAST 48 HOURS.
IF YOU WERE IN A SCHOOLYARD, YOU'D BE PULLING HER PIGTAILS
AND PUSHING HER DOWN NOW.
OH, YEAH?
THEN HOW COME I KEEP THINKING ABOUT HER
IN ALL THESE SEXUAL SCENARIOS AND STUFF, HUH?
HAPPY?
IS THAT WHAT I'M SUPPOSED TO BE, VIC? HAPPY?
WELL, WHY DON'T YOU TELL ME
WHAT YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE, HUH?
BECAUSE I SURE AS HELL CAN'T FIGURE IT OUT.
I TALK TO YOU, AND IT'S NOTHING.
YOU LOOK AT ME, AND NOTHING.
NOTHING.
YOU GUYS MAKE ME FLY...
HIGH.
OKAY.
WE'RE GOING TO PICK IT UP HERE TOMORROW.
WELL, THAT WAS, UH...
BETTER?
YEAH, YEAH.
IT WAS DEFINITELY AN IMPROVEMENT, UH...
GOOD NIGHT.
UH, KATE.
YEAH.
YOU, UH... YOU FORGOT YOUR SHOES.
I'M PROBABLY GOING TO NEED THOSE, HUH?
HEY, LISTEN. YOU, UH...
FEEL LIKE GETTING A CUP OF COFFEE?
KATE.
YEAH.
YOU READY TO GO?
VERY NICE. VERY NICE.
SO, UH...
SEE YOU TOMORROW, HUH?
YEAH, YEAH. SURE.
RIGHT. GOOD NIGHT.
HEY.
WHY ISN'T IT SPIDERMAN?
YOU KNOW, LIKE GOLDMAN, SILVERMAN?
BECAUSE IT'S... IT'S NOT HIS LAST NAME.
IT ISN'T?
NO. IT'S NOT, LIKE... LIKE, PHIL SPIDERMAN.
HE'S A SPIDER...MAN.
YOU KNOW, LIKE, UH, LIKE GOLDMAN IS A LAST NAME
BUT THERE'S NO GOLD MAN.
OH. OH, OKAY.
THERE SHOULD BE A GOLD MAN.
HEY.
HEY, RACH.
HOW WAS WORK?
GREAT, ALTHOUGH I DID SIT DOWN WHERE THERE WASN'T A CHAIR.
BY THE WAY, ROSS DROPPED BY A BOX OF YOUR STUFF.
OH. WELL, I GUESS I HAD THAT ONE COMING.
I'M JUST GOING TO THROW IT OUT.
IT'S PROBABLY JUST A BUNCH OF SHAMPOO AND...
SOMETHING WRONG?
NO, NOTHING.
SO WHAT KIND OF POWERS WOULD GOLD MAN HAVE?
OKAY. WELL, HE WOULD TURN THINGS TO GOLD.
WHAT ABOUT THINGS THAT ARE ALREADY GOLD?
AH, HIS WORK IS DONE.
OKAY, I HAVE A FRIEND--
JIMMY TUPPERMAN-- WHAT WOULD HIS POWERS BE?
TUPPER MAN.
HE WOULD KEEP CRIMINALS FRESH UNTIL THE POLICE CAME.
COOL.
OKAY, LET'S PLAY MY GAME NOW.
OKAY.
OH, YOU YELLOW BELLIED, LILY LIVERED...
DRAW!