WHAT'S SO FUNNY?
OH, NOTHING.
NO, IT'S AN ACTING EXERCISE
I'M PRACTICING MY FAKE LAUGH.
OH.
WHAT? WHAT'S SO FUNNY?
OH, NO, NO.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
THERE'S NONE OF THAT IN HERE.
OH, COME ON, MAN.
AT LEAST LET ME FINISH THIS LAST ONE.
OKAY. BUT ONLY IF YOU GIVE ME A DRAG.
OKAY.
OH...
OH, DARK MOTHER.
ONCE AGAIN I SUCKLE AT YOUR SMOKY TEAT.
NO, NO.
WHY DON'T YOU HOLD ON TO THAT ONE?
OKAY, THAT'S, LIKE, THE LEAST FUN GAME EVER.
WELL, I'M REALLY SICK OF YOUR SMOKING
SO I BROUGHT SOMETHING
THAT IS GOING TO HELP YOU QUIT.
OH.
NOPE. THAT PATCH IS NO GOOD.
COME ON, IT'S A HYPNOSIS TAPE.
THIS WOMAN AT WORK USED IT FOR TWO WEEKS STRAIGHT
AND SHE HASN'T SMOKED SINCE.
HUH!
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
NOTHING. IT'S JUST THAT HYPNOSIS IS BEYOND CRAP.
ROSS, I WATCHED YOU GET HYPNOTIZED
IN ATLANTIC CITY.
HEY, THAT GUY DID NOT HYPNOTIZE ME, OKAY?
OH, RIGHT. BECAUSE YOU ALWAYS PULL YOUR PANTS DOWN
ON THE COUNT OF THREE AND PLAY "WIPE OUT"
ON YOUR BUTT CHEEKS.
LOOK, I WAS JUST TRYING TO DISTRACT ATTENTION
FROM THAT POOR, OLD WOMAN WHO WAS TRYING
TO STUFF HER BREASTS INTO TUBE SOCKS.
ALL RIGHT, FORGET HYPNOSIS.
THE WAY TO QUIT SMOKING
IS YOU HAVE TO DANCE NAKED IN A FIELD OF HEATHER
AND THEN BATHE IN THE SWEAT OF SIX HEALTHY YOUNG MEN.
OR WHAT MY FATHER CALLS "THURSDAY NIGHT."
?  ?
HERE YOU GO.
OH, THANKS. OH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I DIDN'T WANT CINNAMON ON THIS.
SORRY.
HI.
OH, MY GOD!
HI!
FRANK! HI!
HOW ARE YOU?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
WELL, YOU KNOW
I WOULD HAVE CALLED
BUT I LOST YOUR PHONE NUMBER
AND THEN MY MOM LOCKED ME OUT OF THE HOUSE
SO I COULDN'T FIND IT
AND THEN I TRIED TO FIND A PAY PHONE
AND THE RECEIVER WAS CUT OFF, SO...
WELL, WHAT HAPPENED?
UH... OH.
UH... VANDALISM.
BUT ALSO... WHAT HAPPENED BETWEEN YOU AND YOUR MOM?
WELL, WE GOT IN A FIGHT
UH, BECAUSE SHE SAID THAT I WAS TOO IMMATURE TO GET MARRIED.
YOU'RE GETTING MARRIED?!
OH, YEAH, YEAH.
OH, MY GOD!
MY LITTLE BROTHER'S GETTING MARRIED!
YEAH.
I KNEW YOU'D BE SO COOL ABOUT THIS.
ALL RIGHT, HEY, DO YOU WANT TO MEET HER?
DO I?!
DO YOU?
YEAH, I DO! YEAH!
OKAY, COOL! ALL RIGHT!
SHE'S JUST, UH, PARKING THE TRUCK.
I'M GOING TO... I'M GOING TO GO GET MY, UH...
MY FIANCEE, MAN!
YOU KNOW, I WOULD HAVE BET GOOD MONEY
THAT HE'D BE THE FIRST ONE OF US TO GET MARRIED.
YEAH, ISN'T IT FANTASTIC?
YEAH, BUT, PHEEBS, DON'T YOU THINK
HE'S A LITTLE YOUNG TO GET MARRIED?
WELL, HE'S 18.
EXACTLY. IT WILL BE ILLEGAL
FOR HIM TO DRINK AT HIS OWN BACHELOR PARTY.
YEAH, OR TO GET A HOOKER.
ALWAYS ILLEGAL, JOE.
HEY... THIS IS, UH...
MY FIANCEE, MRS. KNIGHT.
YOU KNOW, IT'S FUNNY.
FRANK'S TOLD ME SO MUCH ABOUT YOU
BUT YOU'RE NOT HOW I PICTURED YOU AT ALL.
YEAH.I'M A BIG SURPRISE.
HERE YOU GO.
OH, THANK YOU.
OH, YEAH. GRAB A SEAT.
SO, UH, HOW DID YOU GUYS MEET?
WELL, UM...
I WAS IN MRS. KNIGHTS'...
I MEAN ALICE. SORRY.
ALICE. I ALWAYS DO THAT.
YOU KNOW...
I WAS IN HER HOME EC CLASS.
AND HE WAS MY BEST STUDENT.
YEAH. SHE WAS MY BEST TEACHER.
OH!
IF THAT DOESN'T KEEP KIDS IN SCHOOL, WHAT WILL?
AND SO NOW YOU GUYS ARE GOING TO BE MARRIED.
YEAH. YOU KNOW
WE TALKED ABOUT JUST LIVING TOGETHER
BUT, UM...
WE WANT TO HAVE KIDS RIGHT AWAY!
OH, MY GOD.
GREAT!
WOW. KIDS. FRANK, ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE READY FOR THAT?
HOW HARD CAN IT BE?
YOU KNOW, I MEAN, YOU KNOW... BABIES.
WHO DOESN'T WANT BABIES, RIGHT?
AND BESIDES, YOU KNOW
I NEVER HAD A DAD AROUND, AND NOW I ALWAYS WILL
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, IT WILL BE ME, RIGHT?
YOU KNOW, I MEAN, REALLY, WE DO REALIZE
THAT THERE'S AN AGE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN US.
OH, GOOD. OKAY. BECAUSE YOU WERE ACTING LIKE YOU DIDN'T.
OH, NO, BUT WHEN IT COMES TO LOVE
WHAT DOES AGE MATTER?
MM... MM...
You are falling fast asleep.
Deeper... deeper... deeper...
You are now completely asleep.
You don't need to smoke.
Cigarettes don't control you.
You are a strong, confident woman
who does not need to smoke.
A strong, confident woman...
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
I JUST REALIZED, IN THE LAST YEAR
I'VE ONLY GONE OUT WITH TWO GUYS: RICHARD AND JULIO.
YOU GOT TO HELP ME OUT HERE.
YOU GOT TO SET ME UP, YOU GOT TO GET ME BACK IN THE GAME.
WELL, THAT SHOULDN'T BE A PROBLEM.
I MEAN, I WORK IN FASHION, AND ALL I MEET
ARE ELIGIBLE STRAIGHT MEN.
PETE, CAN I GET YOU SOMETHING ELSE?
I'LL HAVE A SLICE OF CHEESECAKE
AND A DATE, IF YOU'RE GIVING THEM OUT.
HAVEN'T YOU AND I COVERED THAT TOPIC?
COME ON. YOU JUST SAID TO HER...
YOU ONLY WANT TO GO OUT WITH ME
BECAUSE OF MY BLOND WIG AND THE BIG BOOBS
AND THE FACT THAT I SERVE YOU FOOD.
WELL, IF THAT WERE TRUE, I'D BE DATING
MY AUNT RUTH.
AND THE TWO TIMES WE WENT OUT
IT WAS JUST PLAIN AWKWARD.
COME ON, YOU THINK SHE SHOULD GO OUT WITH ME, DON'T YOU?
WELL, I MEAN, ARE YOU SURE YOU WANT TO GO OUT WITH HER?
I MEAN, THAT AIN'T A PRETTY PICTURE IN THE MORNING.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
THAT WIG
ALL IN DISARRAY AND...
BOOBS FLUNG OVER THE NIGHTSTAND.
OH, YEAH.
I MEAN, REALLY, THINK ABOUT IT.
OH HO, I WILL.
NO, I KNOW, I KNOW
THAT THIS IS FRANK'S LIFE, YOU KNOW?
YOU KNOW, I DON'T WANT TO BE ALL JUDGMENTAL, YOU KNOW
BUT THIS IS SICK.
IT'S SICK AND WRONG!
PHEEBS, WHAT? IS IT THE AGE THING?
NO, NO. OH, I'M FINE WITH THE AGE THING
UNTIL IT STARTS STICKING ITS TONGUE
DOWN MY LITTLE BROTHER'S THROAT.
PHEEBS, HE SEEMS TO ENJOY IT.
BUT, I MEAN, DO YOU THINK HE'S GOING TO ENJOY IT
WHEN HE'S UP TO HIS ELBOWS IN THE DIAPERS
OF ALL THE BABIES
THEY HAVE TO HAVE RIGHT AWAY?
THIS IS NOT FAIR TO FRANK
AND IT'S NOT FAIR TO THE BABIES.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT'S NOT GOOD HOME ECONOMICS.
WELL, HAVE YOU TOLD HIM HOW YOU FEEL?
YES.
NOT OUT LOUD.
PHEEBS, HE'S NOT A MIND READER.
WE DON'T KNOW THAT.
PHEEBS, IF YOU DON'T TELL HIM
SOON HE'S GOING TO BE MARRIED
AND THEN YOU'RE GOING TO HATE YOURSELF.
YEAH, BUT IF I DO TELL HIM, THEN HE'S GOING TO HATE MYSELF.
I MEAN, LOOK AT HIM AND HIS MOM.
I CAN'T.
BUT YOU GUYS CAN.
PLEASE, YOU GOT TO TALK HIM OUT OF IT.
NO, NO, NO, NO...
COME ON, YOU GUYS!
YOU HAVE... YOU...
YOU HAVE NOTHING TO LOSE.
I HAVE EVERYTHING TO LOSE.
DO YOU WANT ME TO LOSE EVERYTHING?
EVERYTHING?
NO.
OKAY. I'M GOING TO GO GET FRANK.
SO, WE'RE WALKING DOWN THE STREET
AND I TURN TO YOU AND I SAY
"HEY! LET'S GO HANG OUT AT TOTALLY NUDE NUDES."
REMEMBER? AND THEN...
AND THEN YOU TURN TO ME AND YOU SAY
"NAH. LET'S JUST HANG OUT AT YOUR PLACE."
WELL, THAT WAS A NICE MOVE, DUMB ASS.
I THINK YOU SHOULD DEFINITELY GO OUT WITH THIS GUY.
NAH. HE JUST DOESN'T DO ANYTHING FOR ME.
MONICA, LAST SATURDAY NIGHT
WHAT HAPPENED ON WALKER, TEXAS RANGER?
WELL, WALKER WAS LOOKING FOR THIS BIG BUSLOAD OF KIDS...
HE WAS...
ALL RIGHT. I GET YOUR POINT.
ALL RIGHT.
HI.
HEY.
YOU KNOW, I FORGOT THE COMBINATION TO THIS
ABOUT A YEAR AGO.
I JUST CARRY IT AROUND.
YOU GOT ANY CHAP STICK?
UH, YEAH.
HEY, HOW ARE THOSE TAPES WORKING OUT FOR YOU?
YOU KNOW WHAT? PRETTY GOOD. GOOD!
I HAVEN'T SMOKED YET TODAY.
I FEEL GREAT AND CONFIDENT...
THAT IS A STUNNING BLOUSE.
THANK YOU.
HERE YOU GO.
HEY, MON, LET'S GIVE PETE A CHANCE.
COME ON. HE WAS FUNNY, HE SEEMS REALLY NICE
AND THAT CHECK THING WAS ADORABLE.
WHAT CHECK THING?
AS A JOKE, THIS CUSTOMER AT WORK
WHO HAS A CRUSH ON ME GAVE ME A $20,000 DOLLARS TIP.
HIS NUMBER'S ON THE CHECK.
HE JUST DID IT SO I'D CALL.
PETE BECKER.
PETE...
IS THIS HIM?
THAT'S BILL CLINTON.
WHO IS HE HUGGING?
OH, MY GOD.
THAT'S PETE!
WHY IS BILL HUGGING PETE?
THIS GUY INVENTED MOSS 865.
EVERY OFFICE IN THE WORLD USES THAT PROGRAM.
WE USE IT!
THERE YOU GO!
OH, MY GOD. MONICA'S GOING TO GO OUT
WITH A MILLIONAIRE.
NO. I'M NOT GOING TO GO OUT WITH HIM.
WHY NOT? HE'S A MILLIONAIRE.
SO?
OH, MY GOD! I CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS IS A REAL $20,000 DOLLARS CHECK.
OH, THIS IS JUST SO EXCITING.
OR INCREDIBLY OFFENSIVE.
WELL, YEAH. SURE, THAT, TOO.
WHAT?
ALL WE'RE SAYING IS DON'T RUSH INTO ANYTHING.
YEAH. COME ON, THINK ABOUT IT.
YOU'RE 18, OKAY?
SHE'S 44.
WHEN YOU'RE 36, SHE'S GOING TO BE 88.
WHAT, YOU DON'T THINK I KNOW THAT?
ALL RIGHT, I'M GOING TO GO PLAY BASKETBALL.
OR AT LEAST LET THE REALLY GOOD GUYS USE MY BALL
WHILE I SAY, "CAN I PLAY? CAN I PLAY?"
OH, UH, JOE, YOU LEFT YOUR KEYS IN THE DOOR.
OH.
HERE YOU GO.
ANYWAY...
THE POINT IS
THERE'S A LOT OF WOMEN OUT THERE
YOU HAVEN'T EVEN HAD SEX WITH YET.
YEAH. HE'S... HE'S RIGHT. HE'S RIGHT.
THIS IS YOUR TIME, YOU KNOW?
YOU'RE YOUNG, YOU'RE WEIRD...
CHICKS DIG THAT.
OKAY, BUT ISN'T SEX BETTER
WHEN IT'S WITH ONE PERSON THAT YOU REALLY, REALLY CARE ABOUT?
YEAH, IN A POEM, MAYBE.
NO, THE MAN'S RIGHT.
THAT'S WHAT I HAD WITH RACHEL.
YOU DON'T HAVE IT ANYMORE?
NO, I, UH...
I SLEPT WITH SOMEONE ELSE.
OKAY, SO WAIT. ALL RIGHT.
SO HOW DID THAT MAKE THINGS BETTER?
IT DIDN'T.
OKAY, SO WHAT YOU USED TO HAVE WITH RACHEL
IS WHAT I GOT WITH ALICE.
WHAT IS THAT LIKE?
IT'S SO COOL, MAN.
IT'S JUST BECAUSE BEING WITH HER
IS SO MUCH BETTER THAN, LIKE... NOT BEING WITH HER.
YEAH, YEAH.
WHY CAN'T I FIND THAT?
DON'T ASK ME.
I HAD IT AND I BLEW IT.
WELL, I WANT IT!
YOU CAN HAVE IT!
I DON'T KNOW, MAYBE I CAN'T.
MAYBE THERE'S SOMETHING WRONG WITH ME.
NO, IT'S OUT THERE, MAN.
I'VE SEEN IT.
I GOT IT.
THEN YOU HOLD ON TO IT!
ALL RIGHT, MAN!
ALL RIGHT, CONGRATULATIONS!
YOU LUCKY BASTARD!
YOU'RE FRANK'S BEST MAN?!
I COULDN'T HELP IT.
THEIR LOVE IS SO PURE.
WELL, WHAT ABOUT YOU, HUH?
I'M THE RING BEARER.
OH, ALICE, HI.
I'M SO GLAD YOU COULD COME
BECAUSE I GOT A REAL HOME EC EMERGENCY.
OH, MY GOD. WHO DIED ON THIS?
YEAH, YEAH, I KNOW.
IT'S A REAL MUSTARD TASTROPHE.
CAN YOU HELP ME?
ABSOLUTELY.
FIRST WE'LL START WITH A LITTLE CLUB SODA AND SALT.
IF THAT DOESN'T WORK, THEN WE CAN GO BACK TO...
YOU KNOW WHAT? FORGET IT. IT'S RUINED.
OH, NO, NEVER SAY THAT.
IF YOU CAN'T GET IT OUT, THEN YOU CAN CUT AROUND THE STAIN
ADD A LITTLER LACE, YOU MAKE A STYLISH THROW.
OR, INSTEAD, MAYBE YOU COULD
JUST NOT MARRY MY BROTHER FRANK.
OKAY, THAT'S GREAT, BUT COULD WE MAKE IT SMALLER?
CAN WE MAKE IT FIT ON THE HEAD OF A PIN?
I LOVE WHEN WE MAKE THINGS FIT ON THE HEAD OF A PIN.
You have a Ms. Monica Geller here.
UH, ABSOLUTELY. YEAH, SEND HER IN.
HI.
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
HANG ON FOR A SEC.
I'LL TALK TO YOU IN THE MORNING?
You got it.
I'M SORRY. WHAT?
SERIOUSLY
WHAT IS THIS SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
WELL, YOU KNOW-- I NEVER KNOW HOW MUCH TO TIP.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO DOUBLE THE TAX...
NOT DOUBLE THE TAX OF ROMANIA.
WHAT'S THE DEAL?
ARE YOU TRYING TO BUY ME?
IS THIS THE WAY YOU GET GIRLS TO GO OUT WITH YOU?
Uh... I'm still here.
YOU'RE TAKING THIS ALL WRONG, BECAUSE IF
I DIDN'T LEAVE YOU THAT TIP, YOU WOULDN'T HAVE COME DOWN HERE
WE WOULDN'T BE HAVING THIS ARGUMENT
AND THERE WOULDN'T BE THIS HEAT BETWEEN US.
WHAT?
COME ON, YOU GOT TO, UH, ADMIT
THAT OUR RELATIONSHIP IS HITTING A NEW LEVEL NOW
BECAUSE YOU USED TO BE, LIKE, THE CHEF
AND I WAS THE CUSTOMER
BUT NOW WE'RE LIKE THIS COUPLE THAT FIGHTS.
OKAY, UM, YOU'RE A LOON, YOU KNOW?
LOOK, FORGET THE CHECK, OKAY?
I LIKE YOU.
I THINK YOU'RE GREAT.
COME ON, WHAT DO YOU SAY?
I DON'T KNOW.
WHY NOT?
I DON'T WANT TO ENCOURAGE THIS KIND OF BEHAVIOR.
ONE MEAL.
THAT'S ALL I'M ASKING FOR. PLEASE.
WE GO OUT, WE EAT
AND, IF YOU DON'T HAVE A GOOD TIME
I GIVE YOU TEN GRAND, WE CALL IT EVEN.
HI.
GOD! NO!
WAIT. JUST PUT THE MAIL DOWN. IT'S ME.
OKAY. SORRY.
WHY WERE YOU JUST, LIKE, ALL IN THE DARK?
OH, WELL, UM, YOUR YOUR LAUNDRY SMELLED SO GOOD
THAT I THOUGHT I'D CURL UP IN IT.
IS THAT ALL RIGHT?
OH, YEAH. SURE.
SO, HOW WAS YOUR DAY?
WELL, JUST PROBABLY THE WORST ONE
SINCE I'VE BEEN ALIVE.
WHAT, UM, WHAT HAPPENED?
UM...
ALICE, UH...
SHE, UH...
CALLED IT OFF.
OH, NO.
DID, UM, DID SHE SAY WHY?
UH, NO, NOT REALLY.
JUST THAT I WAS TOO YOUNG.
BUT I DON'T SEE HOW I COULD ALL OF A SUDDEN BE TOO YOUNG
BECAUSE I'M OLDER THAN I WAS WHEN WE FIRST GOT TOGETHER.
YEAH, YEAH.
NO, I DON'T...
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
MAYBE IT'S JUST ALL FOR THE BEST.
YEAH, IF... THE BEST IS, LIKE, UNBELIEVABLE PAIN.
OH, SWEETIE...
OH...
YOU KNOW, I WAS JUST FINALLY HAPPY, YOU KNOW?
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN MY LIFE...
AFTER MY DAD LEFT ME...
AND THEN... AND THEN...
GETTING ARRESTED FOR STEALING THOSE BIRDS...
AND THEN THE...
AND THEN THE... WHOLE PUNCTURED LUNG THING...
I CAN ST... IT'S STILL REALLY HARD
TO TAKE DEEP BREATHS IN COLD WEATHER
BUT WITH ALICE, ALL THAT STUFF KIND OF WENT AWAY.
AND NOW IT'S...
NOW IT'S GONE, AND I DON'T KNOW WHY!
UH, WELL, I CAN TELL YOU WHY.
IT'S IT'S BECAUSE OF ME.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
I ONLY DID IT BECAUSE I LOVE YOU, OKAY?
WHAT?
UM... WELL, I...
I KIND OF HAD A LITTLE CHAT WITH ALICE
AND I SORT OF MADE HER SEE WHY YOU TWO SHOULDN'T BE TOGETHER.
YOU'RE GOING TO SEE IT, TOO, ONE DAY.
YOU REALLY, REALLY WILL.
WAIT A MINUTE. WAIT.
THIS IS BECAUSE OF YOU?
OKAY...
WAIT, NO.
MY MOTHER DIDN'T WANT US TO BE TOGETHER
BUT THE WORST THING SHE EVER DID
WAS TIE ME TO THE PORCH.
OKAY, BUT...
WAIT. YOU KNOW WHAT?
I I CAME TO YOU
BECAUSE I THOUGHT YOU'D UNDERSTAND!
OH, NO, I...
YOU KNOW? OH...
I WOULD STORM OUT OF HERE RIGHT NOW
IF I HAD SOME MONEY OR A PLACE TO GO.
ROSS, IF YOU HAD A MILLION DOLLARS
WHAT'S THE FIRST THING YOU'D BUY?
I'D PROBABLY GET SOME MUNICIPAL BONDS
THEN PUT THE REST OF THE MONEY IN THE BANK
AND LIVE OFF THE INTEREST.
WELL, WE'VE HEARD FROM DR. FUN.
OH, MY GOD. THE MILLIONAIRE'S HERE.
OH, MY GOD!
YOU GUYS, PLEASE?
I'M JUST GOING TO HAVE DINNER WITH HIM, OKAY?
OKAY, OKAY, JUST BECAUSE HE BUYS YOU DINNER
DOES NOT MEAN YOU OWE HIM ANYTHING.
I KNOW.
OKAY, THEN GET THE LOBSTER.
HEY. HI.
HI. HI.
HEY, HOW MUCH CASH YOU GOT
IN YOUR POCKET RIGHT NOW?
AND THAT'S WHY I'M NOT INVITING YOU IN FOR A DRINK.
BYE!
WHY NOT? WAIT!
WHY NOT A DRINK?
WHERE DO YOU WANT TO GO?
DO YOU LIKE PIZZA?
OH... THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
I KNOW A GREAT LITTLE PLACE.
? WHEN THE MOON HITS YOUR EYE ?
? LIKE A BIG PIZZA PIE ?
? THAT'S AMORE ?
HEY, YOU'RE NOT PAYING FOR THE PIZZA.
OH, COME ON, IT'S ONLY FAIR.
YOU PAID FOR THE FLIGHT.
NOW, IS THAT ENOUGH LIRA?
UH, I'D THROW ANOTHER THOUSAND ON THERE.
WELL, HOW MUCH IS THAT?
THAT'S ABOUT 60 CENTS.
? THAT'S AMORE. ?
OH!
OOH...
EVERY NIGHT...!
You don't need to smoke.
Cigarettes don't control you.
You're a strong, confident woman
who does not need to smoke.
A strong, confident woman who does not need to smoke.
OW!
So can I.
HEY, FRANK.
LOOK, OKAY, I KNOW THAT YOU THINK
I DID THIS, LIKE, TOTALLY EVIL THING, BUT I SO DIDN'T.
THERE'S SOMEONE HERE WHO I THINK
CAN EXPLAIN THIS BETTER THAN I CAN.
HI, FRANK.
HI...
MRS. KNIGHT.
PHOEBE'S RIGHT, FRANK.
I KNOW IT'S HARD TO HEAR
BUT IT WOULD HAVE BEEN WRONG TO GO THROUGH WITH IT.
I... I WAS BEING SELFISH.
EVEN THOUGH WE WANT
THE SAME THINGS RIGHT NOW
IN THE FUTURE...
WE MAY NOT.
IS THAT IT? IS THAT WHAT IT IS?
YES, BUT NOT JUST THAT.
RIGHT. NOT JUST THAT...
UM...
EVEN THOUGH...
WE LOVE EACH OTHER AS MUCH AS WE DO
NONETHELESS...
UM...
YOU'RE TOO YOUNG TO...
TO REALLY KNOW WHAT
YOU WANT...
ALL RIGHT, EXACTLY.
ALL RIGHT, IT'S A GOOD BYE KISS.
THAT'S GOOD.
BYE BYE.
OKAY, NO, THE IMPORTANT THING IS IS THAT YOU SEE WHAT I'M SAYING.
YOU KNOW, JUST, YOU KNOW...
THIS IS CLEARLY WRONG.
OKAY, I'VE DECIDED I'M GOING TO LET THIS HAPPEN.
OKAY, CAN I JUST GET MY PURSE?
MMM...
OKAY. ALL RIGHT. GOOD.
Cigarettes don't control you.
You're a strong, confident woman
who does not need to smoke.
Joey's your best friend.
You want to make him a cheese sandwich every day.
And you also want to buy him
hundreds of dollars worth of pants.