HI.
SIX DOLLARS, PLEASE.
SIX? I JUST HAD IT FOR ONE NIGHT.
IT'S THREE.
8 OCLOCK is THE CUTOFF
AND... OH, IT'S 8 0 2.
YOU KNOW, IN A WEIRD WAY, YOU HAVE TOO MUCH POWER.
LOOK, YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO HELP ME OUT HERE
BECAUSE I ONLY HAVE THREE.
I CAN HELP WITH THAT.
OH, MY GOD.
RICHARD?
HI.
WOW, YOUR LIP WENT BALD.
HEY, THANKS.
SO... YOU LOOK GREAT.
YEAH, RIGHT.
NO, YOU DO.
YOU... YOU JUST...
WHAT?
YOU GOT PANTIES STUCK TO YOUR LEG.
THAT'S BECAUSE I WAS JUST GRABBING SOME THINGS
OUT OF THE DRYER, AND STATIC CLING.
OR MAYBE IT'S JUST BECAUSE GOD KNEW
I'D BE RUNNING INTO YOU AND SAW AN OPPORTUNITY.
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU.
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU, TOO.
?  ?
THAT GUY'S IN CLASSICS NOW
BUT YOU KNOW, AS SOON AS WE LEAVE
HE'S GOING STRAIGHT TO THE PORN.
HE'S GOING TO GO UP TO THE COUNTER
WITH CITIZEN KANE, VERTIGO AND CLOCKWORK ORGY.
THIS IS NICE.
I MISS THIS.
YEAH.
EXCUSE ME.
WE'RE GOING BE HERE FOR A WHILE
SO WHY DON'T YOU JUST GO BACK THERE.
YEAH. WE'RE NOT JUDGING.
SO YOU WANT TO GET A HAMBURGER OR SOMETHING?
OH, UM... I DON'T KNOW IF THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
LOOK, JUST FRIENDS.
I WON'T GROPE YOU, I PROMISE.
NO, I THINK IT'S TOO SOON.
NO, IT'S NOT TOO SOON.
I HAD LUNCH AT 11:00.
YEAH, BABY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
MAKING CHOCOLATE MILK.
YOU WANT SOME?
NO, THANKS. I'M 29.
OH, MY GOD, I GOT TO GO TO WORK.
OH, SWEETIE, WHAT TIME DO YOU THINK YOU'RE GOING TO GET OFF TONIGHT?
OH, I DON'T KNOW, HONEY, IT COULD BE REALLY LATE.
OH, COME ON, NOT AGAIN.
I KNOW. I'M SORRY.
I'LL MAKE A DEAL WITH YOU, OKAY?
FOR EVERY NIGHT THAT YOU'RE ASLEEP
BEFORE I GET HOME FROM WORK
I WILL WAKE YOU UP IN A WAY
THAT HAS PROVED VERY POPULAR IN THE PAST.
WELL, NOW, IF YOU NEED TO STAY LATE
I WANT TO BE SUPPORTIVE OF THAT.
HI.
HEY.
LOOK AT YOU.
SINCE WHEN DO YOU ROLLERBLADE?
OH, SINCE TOMORROW.
I MET THIS REALLY CUTE GUY IN THE PARK.
AND HE, LIKE, YOU KNOW, JOGS AND BLADES AND SWIMS
AND SO WE MADE A DEAL.
HE'S GOING TO TEACH ME HOW TO DO ALL SORTS OF JOCK STUFF.
AND WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO FOR HIM?
I'M GOING TO LET HIM.
OKAY.
MORNING.
HEY, SOMEBODY GOT IN LATE LAST NIGHT.
WELL, I RAN INTO RICHARD.
WHEN DID THIS HAPPEN?
OH, AROUND 8:02.
WE, UH, TALKED FOR A LITTLE WHILE
AND THEN WE WENT OUT FOR AN INNOCENT BURGER.
OH, THERE'S NO SUCH THING AS AN INNOCENT BURGER.
ARE YOU GOING TO SEE HIM AGAIN?
TOMORROW NIGHT.
MONICA, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WELL, SHE SPENT THE LAST SIX MONTHS
GETTING OVER HIM
AND NOW SHE'S CELEBRATING THAT
BY GOING ON A DATE WITH HIM.
IT'S NOT A DATE, OKAY?
I'M JUST GOING TO TEACH HIM HOW TO MAKE A LASAGNA
FOR SOME POTLUCK DINNER HE HAS.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO MAKE A LITTLE EXTRA
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, YOU'LL PROBABLY BE HUNGRY
AFTER THE SEX.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO HAVE SEX.
OKAY, NOTHING'S CHANGED HERE.
HE STILL DOESN'T WANT CHILDREN
AND I STILL DO.
SO THAT'S WHY WE'RE GOING TO JUST BE FRIENDS.
NAKED FRIENDS.
HEY. HEY.
DO YOU HAVE ANY ICE?
CHECK THE FREEZER.
IF THERE'S NONE IN THERE, WE'RE PROBABLY OUT.
ARE YOU JUST GETTING HOME FROM WORK?
IT'S LATE.
YEAH, I KNOW.
I HAD THE GREATEST DAY THOUGH.
I GOT TO SIT IN ON A MEETING
WITH THE REPS FROM CALVIN KLEIN.
I TOLD MY BOSS I LIKED THIS LINE OF LINGERIE.
SHE ORDERED A TON OF IT.
HOW WAS YOUR DAY?
I DISCOVERED I'M ABLE TO COUNT ALL MY TEETH
USING JUST MY TONGUE.
HMM.
UM, WHY DO YOU HAVE A COPY OF THE SHINING IN YOUR FREEZER?
OH, I WAS READING IT LAST NIGHT
AND I GOT SCARED, SO...
BUT YOU'RE SAFE FROM IT IF IT'S IN THE FREEZER?
WELL, SAFER.
YOU KNOW, I NEVER START READING THE SHINING
WITHOUT MAKING SURE
WE GOT PLENTY OF ROOM IN THE FREEZER, YOU KNOW?
HOW OFTEN DO YOU READ IT?
HAVEN'T YOU EVER READ THE SAME BOOK
OVER AND OVER AGAIN?
WELL, UM, I GUESS I READ
LITTLE WOMEN MORE THAN ONCE.
BUT IT'S A CLASSIC.
WHAT'S SO GREAT ABOUT THE SHINING?
THE QUESTION SHOULD BE, RACH
WHAT IS NOT SO GREAT ABOUT THE SHINING?
OKAY?
AND THE ANSWER WOULD BE "NOTHING."
ALL RIGHT?
THIS IS, LIKE, THE SCARIEST BOOK EVER.
I BET IT'S WAY BETTER THAN THAT "CLASSIC" OF YOURS.
OKAY.
WELL, WE'LL JUST SEE ABOUT THAT, OKAY?
I WILL READ THE SHINING
AND YOU WILL READ LITTLE WOMEN.
ALL RIGHT, YOU GOT IT.
ALL RIGHT?
OKAY.
NOW, RACH, THESE LITTLE WOMEN...
YEAH?
HOW LITTLE ARE THEY?
I MEAN, ARE THEY, LIKE, SCARY LITTLE?
YOU KNOW, I LOVE THIS FABRIC.
I THINK I'M GOING TO HAVE A SUIT MADE OUT OF THIS.
CHANDLER, ROSS, THIS IS ROBERT.
OH, HEY. HEY.
YOU HAVE LIPSTICK RIGHT HERE.
THAT'S OKAY. IT'S MINE.
WE JUST KISSED.
OH.
SO ISN'T IT
A BIT COLD OUT FOR SHORTS?
WELL, I'M FROM CALIFORNIA.
RIGHT, RIGHT, SOMETIMES YOU GUYS JUST BURST INTO FLAME.
I'M UP...
I'M UP.
I'VE GOTTEN UP NOW.
ANYBODY WANT ANYTHING?
I'LL HAVE COFFEE.
YEAH, ME, TOO.
MAKE THAT THREE.
OKAY. ROSS, WHY DON'T YOU COME WITH ME?
OKAY.
WHAT IS THE MATTER WITH YOU?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
ROBERT'S COMING OUT.
WHAT... WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WHAT, IS HE GAY?
NO, HE...
HE'S COMING OUT OF HIS SHORTS.
WHAT?
THE MAN IS SHOWING BRAIN.
ARE YOU SURE?
HOLD ON.
I'M SORRY, YOU GUYS, THAT WAS A COFFEE AND A...?
COFFEE.
WE COULD WRITE IT DOWN FOR YOU.
NO, THAT WON'T BE, UH... WON'T BE NECESSARY.
WELL?
YEP, YEP, YEP.
WHAT DO WE DO? WHAT DO WE DO?
WELL, I SUPPOSE
WE JUST TRY TO NOT LOOK DIRECTLY AT IT.
LIKE AN ECLIPSE.
SO WHEN PEOPLE COMPLIMENT ME ON MY COOKING TONIGHT
WHAT DO I SAY?
YOU SAY, "THANK YOU VERY MUCH."
AND THEN YOU BUY ME SOMETHING PRETTY.
COME ON, WE'RE GOING TO PUT OUR HANDS IN THIS BOWL
AND WE'RE GOING TO START SQUISHING THE TOMATOES.
OH, THIS FEELS VERY WEIRD.
YOU TOUCH PEOPLE'S EYEBALLS EVERY DAY
AND THIS FEELS WEIRD?
YEAH, WELL, SURE, I TOUCH THEM
BUT I SPENT YEARS LEARNING NOT TO SQUISH THEM.
THAT'S MY HAND.
OH.
OKAY.
GOT TO KEEP SQUISHING.
THE TOMATOES ARE SQUISHING.
OH.
OH, GOSH
YOU GOT SOME ON YOUR SHIRT.
HOLD ON A SEC.
OKAY, WE JUST PUT A LITTLE CLUB SODA ON IT.
IF WE GET TO IT RIGHT AWAY
IT SHOULD... DO...
THE TRICK.
WHAT?
UM, YOU'VE GOT SOME ON YOUR PANTS.
I'LL JUST THROW THEM OUT.
THESE LITTLE WOMEN...
WOW!
YOU'RE LIKING IT, HUH?
OH, YEAH.
AMY JUST BURNED JO's MANUSCRIPT.
I DON'T SEE HOW HE COULD EVER FORGIVE HER.
UM, JO's A GIRL.
IT'S SHORT FOR JOSEPHINE.
BUT JO's GOT A CRUSH ON LAURIE.
OH.
YOU MEAN IT'S, LIKE, A GIRL GIRL THING?
BECAUSE THAT IS THE ONE THING MISSING FROM THE SHINING.
NO, ACTUALLY, LAURIE'S A BOY.
NO WONDER RACHEL HAD TO READ THIS SO MANY TIMES.
HEY.
HEY, HOW'D THE BASKETBALL GO?
OH, OKAY, I LEARNED HOW TO SHOOT A LAYUP
A FOUL SHOT AND A 23 POINTER.
YOU MEAN A THREE POINTER?
I GET MORE BECAUSE I'M DAINTY.
SO IS THERE A PHONE HERE I CAN CHECK MY MESSAGES?
YEAH, IN THE BACK.
DO YOU WANT A QUARTER?
OH, NO, THANKS.
I ALWAYS CARRY ONE IN MY SOCK.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
GET BACK OVER ON YOUR SIDE OF THE...
HELLO!
HI. I'M JOEY.
WE HAVEN'T MET.
GOOD TO MEET YOU. ROBERT.
OKAY...
WHAT?
WHAT, YOU GUYS?
WHAT IS GOING ON?
DO YOU NOT LIKE ROBERT?
WHY ARE YOU LAUGHING?
CALM DOWN.
THERE'S NO REASON
TO GET TESTY.
YOU GUYS, COME ON.
WE'RE SORRY.
IT JUST SEEMS THAT ROBERT ISN'T AS CONCEALED
IN THE SHORTS AREA
AS, UH... ONE MAY HAVE HOPED.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
HEY.
UH, ROBERT, COULD YOU, UH...
UH, PASS ME THOSE COOKIES?
SURE.
BALL?
YEAH.
SO HOW DID THE LASAGNA GO OVER?
REALLY?
GOOD.
SO YOU OWE ME THREE PRETTY THINGS.
YEAH. I'VE BEEN THINKING A LOT ABOUT YOU, TOO.
I KNOW.
IT'S HARD, THIS PLATONOMY THING.
IT'S A WORD.
YEAH.
I DO THINK IT'S BETTER THIS WAY.
YEAH, WE'RE BEING SMART.
YES, I'M SURE.
YOU'RE REALLY SURE?
I'LL CALL YOU BACK.
SO WE CAN BE FRIENDS WHO SLEEP TOGETHER.
ABSOLUTELY.
THIS WILL JUST BE SOMETHING WE DO
LIKE... RACQUETBALL.
YEAH. SOUNDS SMART AND HEALTHY TO ME.
SO, UM... JUST OUT OF, UH, CURIOSITY
UM, DO YOU CURRENTLY
HAVE ANY OTHER RACQUETBALL BUDDIES?
JUST YOUR DAD.
ALTHOUGH THAT'S ACTUALLY RACQUETBALL.
YOU KNOW, I I DO HAVE...
A BLIND DATE WITH MY SISTER'S NEIGHBOR
NEXT... TUESDAY.
OH.
YOU WANT ME TO CANCEL IT?
NO.
OKAY.
BECAUSE IF YOU DID
THAT MEANS YOU'D BE CANCELING FOR ME...
AND WE'RE JUST FRIENDS.
EXACTLY.
AND BESIDES, YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT WOULDN'T BE FAIR ANYWAY
BECAUSE MY MOTHER'S TRYING TO SET ME UP WITH SOME LAWYER.
SO WHO'S THIS LAWYER?
OH, NO, SHE DOESN'T ACTUALLY HAVE ONE
BUT SHE'S LOOKING.
HEY.
OH, DON'T SIT DOWN.
READY TO GO TO THE BATTING CAGE?
YEAH, YOU BET, AND FIRST, HERE'S A GIFT.
OH.
WOW!
HEY...
STRETCHY PANTS!
THOSE ARE THE GREATEST THINGS IN THE WORLD.
IF I WERE YOU, I'D WEAR THEM EVERY DAY, EVERY DAY.
GEEZ, THANK YOU.
REALLY, THAT'S SO NICE
BUT, UM, TO BE HONEST
I DON'T THINK I CAN WEAR THESE--
THEY'RE SO TIGHT.
I'D FEEL LIKE I'M ON DISPLAY.
I'M SORRY.
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'LL... FIGURES.
HEY!
HI.
HOW'S IT GOING?
HEY, RACH... GOOD.
HOW ARE YOU DOING WITH THE SHINING?
OH, DANNY JUST WENT INTO ROOM 217.
OOH... THE NEXT PART'S THE BEST
WHEN THAT DEAD LADY IN THE BATHTUB...
OH, NO, NO, NO! COME ON, YOU'RE GOING TO RUIN IT.
ALL RIGHT. I'LL TALK IN CODE.
REMEMBER...
WHEN THE KID SEES THOSE TWO BLANKS IN THE HALLWAY?
YEAH. THAT'S VERY COOL.
OH! ALL BLANK AND NO BLANK
MAKES BLANK A BLANK BLANK.
NO, NO, NO. NO, THE END--
WHEN JACK ALMOST KILLS THEM ALL WITH THAT BLANK
BUT THEN, IN THE LAST SECOND, THEY GET AWAY.
OH! OH, OH!
JOEY, I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU JUST DID THAT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE SHE CRACKED YOUR CODE.
ALL RIGHT. OKAY.
LAURIE PROPOSES TO JOE, AND SHE SAYS NO
EVEN THOUGH SHE'S STILL IN LOVE WITH HIM
AND THEN HE ENDS UP MARRYING AMY.
HEY!
MINE WAS BY ACCIDENT!
ALL RIGHT. THE BOILER EXPLODES
AND DESTROYS THE HOTEL
AND KILLS THE DAD.
BETH DIES.
BETH...
BETH DIES?
MM HMM.
IS THAT TRUE?
IF I KEEP READING, IS BETH GOING TO DIE?
NO, BETH DOESN'T DIE.
SHE DOESN'T DIE.
DOES SHE, RACHEL?
WHAT?!
JOEY'S ASKING IF YOU'VE JUST RUINED
THE FIRST BOOK HE'S EVER LOVED
THAT DIDN'T STAR JACK NICHOLSON.
NO.
SHE DOESN'T DIE.
THEN WHY WOULD YOU SAY THAT?
BECAUSE...
I WANTED TO HURT YOU.
OH, THERE THEY ARE.
I I DROPPED MY KEYS.
OH, MY!
GOT THEM.
HI. AAH!
SORRY.
I'M SORRY.
YOU WOULD NOT BELIEVE MY DAY.
I HAD TO WORK TWO SHIFTS
AND THEN, TO TOP IT OFF
I LOST ONE OF MY FAKE BOOBS...
IN A GRILL FIRE.
WHAT ARE YOU SMILING AT?
I'M SORRY, I WAS JUST THINKING
YOUR DAY COULD STILL PICK UP.
YEAH, RIGHT.
HELLO.
I LOVE THIS FRIEND THING!
LISTEN, ROBERT'S GOING TO BE HERE ANY SECOND.
SO COULD ONE OF YOU JUST TELL HIM?
PLEASE. RIGHT NOW...
NO, EVERY TIME I SEE HIM
IT'S LIKE, "IS IT ON THE LOOSE?
IS IT WATCHING ME?"
LOOK, WE CAN'T TELL HIM.
YOU CAN'T GO UP TO A GUY YOU BARELY KNOW
AND TALK ABOUT HIS...
STUFF.
HE'S RIGHT--
EVEN IF IT'S TO SAY SOMETHING COMPLIMENTARY.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST TELL HIM?
YOU'RE GOING OUT WITH HIM.
OH, WAY TOO AWKWARD.
NO. I HAVEN'T EVEN SEEN IT WITH PERMISSION YET. NO.
I MEAN, SO WHAT... WHAT DO I DO?
JUST, YOU KNOW, BREAK UP WITH HIM?
I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK THIS IS AN UNSOLVABLE PROBLEM.
IT'S ACURIAT MARIAH.
THE UNSOLVABLE PROBLEM THEY GAVE TO CAPTAIN KIRK
AS PART OF HIS TRAINING TO BE A STARFLEET COMMANDER.
YOU MEAN YASHI MARU.
WHAT'S ACURIAT MARIAH?
THE PLACE WITH THE CHEAP ROOMS
WHERE WE STAYED IN ISRAEL.
HEY.
SO, YOU READY FOR THE GYM?
THEY GOT THIS NEW ROCK CLIMBING WALL.
WE CAN SPOT EACH OTHER.
YOU KNOW, I CAN SPOT YOU FROM HERE.
WHAT?
OKAY.
LISTEN, ROBERT...
HEY, DON'T WE HAVE TO...?
YEAH, WE GOT... YEAH. MM HMM.
UM...
I THINK YOU'RE REALLY, REALLY GREAT.
OH, GOD.
HERE WE GO AGAIN.
WHY DOES THIS KEEP HAPPENING TO ME?
IS IT SOMETHING I'M PUTTING OUT THERE?
IS THIS MY FAULT?
OR AM I JUST NUTS?
I... I I I I DON'T KNOW...
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
HEY, BUDDY, THIS IS A FAMILY PLACE.
PUT THE MOUSE BACK IN THE HOUSE.
OH...
REALLY?
IT'S JUST LIKE EVERYONE ELSE'S APARTMENT.
IT'S GOT ROOMS AND WALLS AND CEILINGS.
I WANTED TO SEE WHERE YOU LIVE.
NOW, GIVE ME THE TOUR.
OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD!
THIS IS THE LIVING ROOM...
THAT'S NICE.
ALL RIGHT.
AND THIS IS THE KITCHEN.
THAT'S REAL PRETTY.
WAIT A MINUTE.
DON'T I GET TO SEE THE BEDROOM?
THE BEDROOM...
OH, IT'S PRETTY MUCH
YOUR TYPICAL...
BEDROOM.
WE'RE STILL ON THIS SIDE OF THE DOOR.
MM HMM.
YEAH, BUT I DIDN'T GET TO SEE IT.
OH, SHOOT.
MAYBE NEXT TIME.
THANKS FOR A LOVELY EVENING.
SO, UM, WHO IS SHE?
OH. THAT WAS THE BLIND DATE THAT I TOLD YOU ABOUT.
SHE CALLED AND SWITCHED IT FROM TUESDAY.
OH.
DID YOU LIKE HER?
AND I'M JUST ASKING AS A FRIEND
BECAUSE I AM TOTALLY FINE WITH THIS.
WELL, YOU SEEM FINE.
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I I'M NOT FINE.
I'M NOT.
HOW CAN I BE FINE?
HEARING YOU COME IN WITH HER...
SHE WANTS TO SEE YOUR BEDROOM...
YOU KNOW WHAT?
WHAT IF WE'RE FRIENDS...
WHO DON'T SEE OTHER PEOPLE?
YOU MEAN, LIKE EXCLUSIVE FRIENDS?
WHY NOT? HMM?
I MEAN, THIS HAS BEEN THE MOST AMAZING WEEK.
I MEAN, WOULD IT BE SO TERRIBLE?
EVEN IF WE WERE FRIENDS WHO...
WHO LIVED TOGETHER.
OR... MAYBE, SOMEDAY
FRIENDS WHO...
WHO STOOD UP IN FRONT OF THEIR OTHER FRIENDS
AND VOWED TO BE FRIENDS FOREVER.
WOW.
DO YOU KNOW WE'RE BACK WHERE WE WERE?
HONEY, I WOULD LOVE TO DO ALL THAT
BUT NOTHING'S CHANGED.
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
YOU DON'T HAVE A MUSTACHE.
OKAY, OKAY.
ONE THING'S CHANGED.
BUT WE STILL WANT DIFFERENT THINGS
AND WE KNOW HOW THIS IS GOING TO END.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I GOT TO WALK OUT OF HERE RIGHT NOW...
BECAUSE GETTING OVER YOU IS THE HARDEST THING
THAT I HAVE EVER HAD TO DO.
UM... I DON'T THINK I COULD DO IT AGAIN.
I KNOW I COULDN'T.
YEAH.
SO...
HOW ABOUT ONE LAST GAME OF RACQUETBALL, HMM?
WATCH THE THORNS.
OW!
WHAT?
BETH IS REALLY, REALLY SICK.
OH...
OH, OH...
JO'S THERE...
BUT I DON'T THINK THERE'S ANYTHING SHE CAN DO.
OH...
JOEY?
YEAH?
YOU WANT TO PUT THE BOOK IN THE FREEZER?
OKAY.