JANICE HAS A QUESTION: WHO OF THE SIX OF YOU
HAS SLEPT WITH WHO OF THE SIX OF YOU?
WOW, IT'S LIKE A DIRTY MATH PROBLEM.
UM, SORRY, THE ANSWER THERE WOULD BE:
NONE OF US.
YEAH. AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
IF THAT DOESN'T CHANGE SOON
I'M GOING TO DUMP YOU FOR SOMEBODY WHO PUTS OUT.
COME ON. OVER THE YEARS, NONE OF YOU EVER GOT
YOU KNOW, DRUNK AND STUPID?
WELL, THAT'S REALLY A DIFFERENT QUESTION.
I'M SORRY.
I FIND IT HARD TO BELIEVE THAT A GROUP OF PEOPLE
WHO SPENDS AS MUCH TIME TOGETHER AS YOU GUYS DO
HAS NEVER BUMPED UGLIES.
THERE WAS THAT ONE TIME
THAT MONICA AND RACHEL GOT TOGETHER.
WHAT?!
EXCUSE ME.
THERE WAS NO "TIME."
OKAY, BUT LET'S SAY THERE WAS.
HOW MIGHT THAT GO?
OKAY, OKAY.
WELL, THEN ANSWER ME THIS.
HAVE ANY OF YOU EVER...
ALMOST?
DOES ANYBODY NEED ANY MORE COFFEE?
HEY, THERE'S A DOG OUT THERE.
OH, THAT IS SO UNFORTUNATE.
WHAT?
CUTE NAKED GUY'S REALLY STARTING TO PUT ON WEIGHT.
OKAY, I'LL BE BA CK IN JUST A MINUTE.
OH, PHOEBE, I'M SORRY
THAT I LEFT LIPSTICK MARKS ON THE PHONE.
YOU DIDN'T LEAVE LIPSTICK MARKS ON THE PHONE.
OH. THEN IT MUST HAVE BEEN YOU.
BYE.
BYE BYE.
THAT'S WHY I MOVED OUT.
HEY, YOU KNOW, WHILE WE'RE ON THAT
WHEN ARE YOU GOING TO TELL MY SISTER
THAT YOU DON'T LIVE HERE ANYMORE?
I THINK ON SOME LEVEL SHE ALREADY KNOWS.
PHOEBE, SHE DOESN'T KNOW T YOU SNEAK OUT EVERY NIGHT
SHE DOESN'T KNOW THAT  YOU SNEAK BACK EVERY MORNING
AND SHE DOESN'T KNOW THAT THAT YOU'VE BEEN LIVING
AT YOUR GRANDMOTHER'S FOR A WEEK NOW.
OKAY, WELL, MAYBE NOT ON THOSE LEVELS.
YOU HAVE GOT TO TELL HER.
OKAY, THE LONGER YOU WAIT
THE HARDER IT'S GOING TO BE ON HER.
YOU'RE RIGHT, YOU'RE RIGHT.
ANYWAY, LISTEN.
TONIGHT'S BAG IS REALLY BULKY
SO COULD YOU SNEAK SOME STUFF OUT FOR ME?
IT'S JUST, LIKE, A CLOCK RADIO AND SOME CEMETERY DIRT.
HEY.
I'M NEVER GOING TO FIND A ROOMMATE EVER.
WHOA. NOBODY GOOD?
WELL, LET'S SEE.
THERE WAS THE GUY WITH THE FERRETS.
THAT'S PLURAL.
THE SPITTER.
OH, AND, YES, THE GUY WHO ENJOYED MY NAME SO MUCH
HE FELT HE NEEDED TO MAKE A LITTLE NOISE
EVERY TIME HE SAID IT.
"NICE TO MEET YOU, CHANDLER BING.
BING!"
"GREAT APARTMENT, CHANDLER BING.
SO HOW MANY MORE DO YOU HAVE TOMORROW?
TWO. THIS PHOTOGRAPHER WHO SEEMS REALLY DULL
AND THIS ACTOR GUY, WHO I'M NOT SURE ABOUT
BECAUSE, UH, WHEN HE CALLED
AND I ANSWERED THE PHONE "CHANDLER BING"
HE SAID, "WHOA! SHORT MESSAGE."
UH, ROSS?
FOOT ON THE FLOOR
OR COME OVER NO MORE.
SURE. YOUR DRESSER IS MISSING
BUT THIS SHE NOTICES.
WHAT?
I HAVE TO GO.
YEAH, CAROL SHOULD BE HOME BY NOW.
HMM. HOW'S IT GOING WITH YOU GUYS?
OH, BETTER, ACTUALLY.
YOU KNOW, I THINK I FINALLY FIGURED OUT
WHY WE WERE HAVING SO MUCH TROUBLE LATELY.
OH, REALLY?
YOU KNOW HOW I HAVE YOU GUYS?
WELL, SHE DOESN'T HAVE ANY CLOSE FRIENDS
THAT ARE JUST HERS
BUT,LAST WEEK, SHE MET THIS WOMAN
AT THE GYM-- SUSAN SOMETHING--
AND THEY REALLY HIT IT OFF
AND I THINK IT'S GOING TO MAKE A DIFFERENCE.
SO, UH, ERIC...
WHAT KIND OF PHOTOGRAPHY DO YOU DO?
OH, MOSTLY FASHION.
SO THERE MAY BE MODELS HERE FROM TIME TO TIME.
I HOPE THAT'S COOL.
YES, IT IS COOL...
UH, BECAUSE I HAVE MODELS HERE, YOU KNOW...
NEVER.
WHAT ELSE? OOH, YEAH.
DURING THE SUMMER, I SPEND MOST WEEKENDS
AT MY SISTER'S BEACH HOUSE
WHICH YOU ARE WELCOME TO USE, BY THE WAY.
ALTHOUGH I SHOULD
PROBABLY TELL YOU
SHE'S A PORN STAR.
WELL, LISTEN, I, UH, STILL HAVE
ONE MORE PERSON TO, UH, MEET
BUT UNLESS IT TURNS OUT TO BE YOUR SISTER...
I THINK YOUR CHANCES ARE PRETTY GOOD.
ALL RIGHT.
BEDROOM, BATHROOM, LIVING ROOM
THIS RIGHT HERE'S THE KITCHEN
AND, UH, THANKS FOR COMING BY. BYE BYE.
DON'T YOU, UH, DON'T YOU WANT TO ASK ME ANY QUESTIONS?
SURE. UH, HMM...
WHAT'S UP?
WELL, UH, I'M AN ACTOR.
I'M FAIRLY NEAT.
I, UH, I GOT MY OWN TV.
OH, AND DON'T WORRY.
I'M TOTALLY OKAY WITH THE GAY THING.
WHAT GAY THING?
UH, JUST, YOU KNOW, IN GENERAL--
THE WHOLE PEOPLE BEING GAY... THING.
TOTALLY COOL WITH THAT.
WELL, OKAY, JERRY.
THANKS FOR STOPPING BY.
HI.
HEY.
HEY, MON.
YOU WANT TO HEAR SOMETHING THAT SUCKS?
DO I EVER.
CHRIS SAYS THEY'RE CLOSING DOWN THE BAR.
NO WAY.
YEAH, APPARENTLY, THEY'RE TURNING IT
INTO SOME KIND OF COFFEE PLACE.
JUST COFFEE?
WHERE ARE WE GOING TO HANG OUT NOW?
GOT ME.
CAN I GET A BEER, PLEASE?
DID YOU PICK A ROOMMATE?
YOU BETCHA.
IS IT THE ITALIAN GUY?
YEAH, RIGHT.
OHH... HE'S SO CUTE.
OH, YES, THAT'S WHAT I WANT--
A ROOMMATE THAT I CAN WALK AROUND WITH
AND BE REFERRED TO AS "THE FUNNY ONE."
OH, LOOK. POOL TABLE'S FREE.
RACK THEM UP. I'LL BE BACK IN A MINUTE.
GET READY FOR ME TO WHIP YOUR BUTT.
OKAY, BUT AFTER THAT, WE'RE SHOOTING SOME POOL.
OH. NO, NO, NO.
EXCUSE ME.
HELLO. HI.
MY FRIEND
ORDERED AN ONION
NOT AN OLIVE.
AND, UH, I ORDERED A RUM AND DIET COKE
WHICH I DON'T THINK THIS IS.
I AM SO SORRY.
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
I MEAN, HOW HARD IS IT
TO GET A COUPLE DRINKS RIGHT, HUH?
WELL...
I WOULD LIKE TO PROPOSE A TOAST.
OH!
TO THE WOMAN WHO, IN ONE YEAR FROM TODAY
WILL BECOME MRS. DR. BARRY FARBER, D.D.S.
MMM. I THINK IT'S TIME TO SEE THE RING AGAIN.
ISN'T IT EXCITING?
I MEAN, IT'S LIKE HAVING A BOYFRIEND FOR LIFE.
YEAH.
I KNOW.
WHAT?
OHH... I DON'T KNOW.
WELL, MAYBE IT'S JUST
THE IDEA OF BARRY FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE.
I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK I I FEEL LIKE I NEED TO HAVE ONE LAST FLING, YOU KNOW?
JUST TO SORT OF GET IT OUT OF MY SYSTEM.
RACHEL, STOP.
YOU'RE SO BAD.
I'M SERIOUS.
I REALLY... I THINK I NEED TO JUST HAVE SOME...
MEANINGLESS... SEX, YOU KNOW?
WITH THE NEXT GUY I SEE.
EXCUSE ME.
I... SEEM TO HAVE DROPPED MY BALL.
YEAH, SO?
AND NOW I'VE PICKED IT UP AGAIN.
OH, MY GOD.
I WENT TO HIGH SCHOOL WITH HER.
RACHEL!
HI.
MONICA!
IS SHE GIVING ME THE FINGER?
LOOK. HI.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
OH, MY GOD.
YOU CAN'T EVEN SEE WHERE THE TITANIC HIT IT.
YES. HIS NAME IS BARRY.
HE'S A DOCTOR, THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
AW, JUST LIKE YOU ALWAYS WANTED.
CONGRATULATIONS.
THANK YOU.
SO HOW ABOUT YOU?
ARE YOU SEEING ANYBODY?
OH, NOT RIGHT NOW.
OH, WELL, THAT'S OKAY.
I KNOW.
WELL, SO I THINK I'LL GET BACK TO MY FRIEND.
OH, YEAH, SURE, SURE.
SURE, SURE, SURE.
LISTEN. CAN WE PLEASE HAVE LUNCH
THE NEXT TIME I'M IN THE CITY?
OH, THAT'D BE GREAT.
OKAY. THANKS.
BYE. BYE.
TEN BUCKS SAYS I NEVER SEE THAT WOMAN AGAIN IN MY LIFE.
NO, REAL... HONEY, REALLY.
IT'S FINE.
JUST...
GO WITH SUSAN.
REALLY, I THINK...
NO, I THINK GIRLS' NIGHT OUT IS A GREAT IDEA.
OKAY. OKAY, BYE.
SO WHAT ARE THEY DOING?
I DON'T KNOW.
SOMETHING GIRLY.
HEY.
HEY, YOU'RE EARLY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING WITH THE LAMP?
I'M JUST TAKING IT TO GET REWIRED.
DON'T TAKE IT TO THE SAME PLACE YOU TOOK THE STEREO
BECAUSE THEY'VE HAD THAT THING
FOR OVER A WEEK.
NO.
NO, MR. HECKLES.
NO ONE IS MAKING ANY NOISE UP HERE!
YOU'RE DISTURBING MY OBOE PRACTICE.
YOU DON'T PLAY THE OBOE.
I COULD PLAY THE OBOE.
THEN I'M GOING  TO HAVE TO ASK YOU TO KEEP IT DOWN.
WHO ARE YOU?
HI. I'M ERIC.
I'M GOING TO BE CHANDLER'S NEW ROOMMATE.
I'M CHANDLER'S NEW ROOMMATE.
I DON'T THINK SO.
I COULD BE CHANDLER'S NEW ROOMMATE.
BUT HE TOLD ME OVER THE PHONE...
HE TOLD ME IN PERSON.
OH. THAT'S WEIRD.
WELL, I'M GOING TO, UH, GO INTO MY NEW APARTMENT NOW.
HUH?
HI AGAIN.
HEY.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
OH, NO, NO, NO. DON'T THANK ME.
THANK THE JERK THAT DIDN'T SHOW UP.
OKAY, I GOT TO GET TO WORK.
AND NOT JUST FOR THE MONEY.
BUT ALSO BECAUSE, EVERY NOW AND THEN
SOMEBODY WALKS OUT OF THE BATHROOM
WITH A LITTLE BIT OF TOILET PAPER
ON THEIR SHOE.
YOU NEED SOME HELP WITH THAT?
OH, NO THANKS. I GOT IT.
OH, NO, I DON'T.
WHOA!
OKAY.
WHOO!
I STOOD UP TOO FAST.
GOT A LITTLE HEAD RUSH.
IT'S THE HEAT.
AND THE HUMIDITY.
THAT'S A, UH...
THAT'S A TOUGH COMBINATION.
DO YOU WANT TO COME IN FOR SOME LEMONADE?
LIKE YOU WOULDN'T BELIEVE.
OHH...
WOW.
THIS IS A GREAT PLACE.
OH, THANK YOU.
JUST... MAKE YOURSELF COMFORTABLE.
GOTCHA.
SO THIS PLACE
IS REALLY MY GRANDMOTHER'S.
I GOT IT FROM HER WHEN SHE MOVED TO FLORIDA.
OTHERWISE I COULD NEVER AFFORD A PLACE LIKE THIS.
SO IF THE LANDLORD EVER ASKS
I'M AN 87 YEAR OLD WOMAN WHO'S AFRAID OF HER VCR.
YOU THIRSTY?
YOU BET I AM.
OKAY.
HERE'S YOUR... PENIS!
OH, MY GOD!
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?!
YOU SAID, "YOU WANT TO COME IN FOR SOME LEMONADE?"
SO?!
WERE... AH! WERE YOU JUST GOING TO GIVE ME LEMONADE?
YEAH HUH!
WOULD YOU COVER YOURSELF UP?!
OH, RIGHT. SORRY.
GOD, I DON'T BELIEVE THIS.
SOMEONE ASKS YOU IN FOR LEMONADE
AND TO YOU, THAT MEANS THEY WANT TO HAVE SEX?!
UM, USUALLY...
YEAH. WELL, NOT JUST LEMONADE.
ICED TEA... SOMETIMES JUICE.
LOOK, I'M... SORRY.
I JUST... THOUGHT YOU LIKED ME.
I'M SUCH A JERK.
IT'S OKAY.
I SUPPOSE IT COULD HAPPEN TO ANYONE.
NOT ANYONE I KNOW, BUT...
BY THE WAY, I CAN STILL SEE IT.
PHEEBS?
HUH?
WHERE'S YOUR BED?
IT'S NOT IN THE APARTMENT?
OH, NO.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS IS HAPPENING AGAIN.
WHAT?
OKAY, ENOUGH OF THE THIRD DEGREE!
I I I DON'T LIVE HERE ANYMORE.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I'M SORRY.
I... I... I...
I DON'T LIVE HERE ANYMORE.
I I DIDN'T KNOW HOW TO TELL YOU, BUT, YOU KNOW
EVERYBODY ELSE KNOWS.
EVERYBODY KNOWS?
THAT WAS SUPPOSED TO BE A GOOD THING.
I FORGET WHY.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND THIS.
I THOUGHT WE WERE DOING SO MUCH BETTER LATELY.
YEAH, BECAUSE I MOVED OUT.
MONICA, I...
DO YOU KNOW...
OKAY, DO YOU KNOW I COULDN'T SLEEP FOR, LIKE, A MONTH
BECAUSE I GOT A DOT OF INK ON ONE OF THE SOFA CUSHIONS?
WELL, YOU COULD HAVE JUST TURNED THE CUSHION OVER.
I WOULD HAVE, EXCEPT I HAD
A BIG SPAGHETTI STAIN ON THE OTHER SIDE.
WHAT?!
THIS IS WHAT  I'M TALKING ABOUT.
I NEED TO LIVE IN A LAND WHERE PEOPLE CAN SPILL.
WELL, YOU CAN SPILL...
IN THE SINK.
AW, HONEY, IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT, YOU KNOW.
THIS IS WHO YOU ARE
AND I LOVE YOU
AND I WANT US TO BE FRIENDS
AND IF I KEEP LIVING HERE
I DON'T SEE THAT HAPPENING.
I LOVE YOU, TOO.
OH, GOOD.
HMM...
WHAT?
WHAT? I'M JUST SAD.
NO, YOU'RE NOT.
YOU'RE WONDERING WHICH CUSHION IT IS.
WELL, WHY CAN'T I THINK OF BOTH?
I MEAN, I CAN THINK TWO THINGS.
GO AHEAD. LOOK.
YOU KNOW YOU WANT TO. GO.
OH, MY GOD!
SO, UH...
WHAT YOU WATCHING?
BAYWATCH.
Move south towards the pier!
WHAT'S IT ABOUT?
UH... LIFEGUARDS.
WHAT?
WELL, IT SOUNDS KIND OF STUPID.
WHO'S SHE?
NICOLE EGGERT.
WE LIKE HER.
WOW, LOOK AT THEM RUN.
YEAH...
THEY DO THAT A LOT.
HEY, YOU WANT A BEER?
YEAH. I'LL GO GET ONE.
NO, NO, DON'T GET UP.
I GOT A COOL ER RIGHT HERE.
HELLO.
HEY.
DO YOU HAVE ANY BEERS?
WE'RE OUT OF BEERS.
HELP YOURSELF.
YOU OKAY?
PHOEBE MOVED OUT.
RIGHT.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
AM I SO HARD TO LIVE WITH?
IS THIS WHY I DON'T HAVE A BOYFRIEND?
NO! YOU DON'T HAVE A BOYFRIEND BECAUSE...
I DON'T... I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU DON'T HAVE A BOYFRIEND.
YOU SHOULD HAVE A BOYFRIEND.
WELL, I THINK SO.
OH, COME HERE.
COME HERE.
LISTEN.
YOU ARE ONE OF MY FAVORITE PEOPLE
AND THE MOST BEAUTIFUL WOMAN
I'VE EVER KNOWN IN REAL LIFE.
OH...
HI.
WHERE IS EVERYBODY?
OH, IT'S ALREADY CLOSED.
CHRIS GAVE ME THE KEYS TO LOCK UP.
WHAT IS WRONG?
MY MARRI...
I THINK MY MARRIAGE IS, UM...
IS KIND OF OVER.
OH, NO! WHY?
BECAUSE CAROL'S A LESBIAN.
AND... AND I'M NOT ONE...
AND, APPARENTLY, IT'S NOT A MIX AND MATCH SITUATION.
OH, MY GOD!
I DON'T BELIEVE IT!
OH, YOU POOR BUNNY.
I'M AN IDIOT.
I MEAN, I SHOULD HAVE SEEN IT.
I MEAN, CAROL AND I'D BE OUT
AND SHE'D SEE SOME BEAUTIFUL WOMAN, AND...
AND SHE'D BE, YOU KNOW, "ROSS, LOOK AT HER."
AND I'D THINK...
"GOD, MY WIFE IS COOL."
OH...
HEY, DO YOU THINK THAT SUSAN PERSON IS HER LOVER?
WELL, NOW I DO.
OH, GOD!
I'M SORRY.
SEVEN YEARS.
I MEAN... WE'VE BEEN TOGETHER SEVEN YEARS.
SHE'S THE ONLY WOMAN WHO'S EVER LOVED ME.
SHE'S THE ONLY WOMAN I I'VE EVER...
OH. OH, ROSS.
OH...
MMM... THIS IS NICE.
I KNOW. IT IS, ISN'T IT?
NO, I MEAN IT.
THIS FEELS REALLY GOOD.
IS IT 100% COTTON?
YEAH...
AND I GOT IT ON SALE, TOO.
I MEAN, IT LOOKS NUBBY
BUT... BUT IT'S NOT.
ANYWAY, I SHOULD GO.
ONE OF THE LIFEGUARDS
WAS JUST ABOUT TO DISMANTLE A NUCLEAR DEVICE.
IF YOU WANT TO GET A DRINK LATER, WE CAN.
YEAH. THAT SOUNDS GREAT. OKAY.
OH, AND LISTEN, IT'S... IT'S GOING TO BE...
I KNOW.
THANKS.
MAYBE THIS WOULDN'T HAVE HAPPENED
IF I'D BEEN MORE NURTURING OR...
I'D PAID MORE ATTENTION OR I'D...
HAD A UTERUS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
NO, NO, YOU KNOW, YOU DON'T DESERVE THIS.
YOU DON'T. ROSS. YOU'RE YOU'RE REALLY...
YOU'RE SO GOOD.
THANKS.
AND YOU'RE SO... SWEET AND...
YOU'RE KIND AND...
THANKS.
COME HERE.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
HUH?
OKAY. IT'S OKAY.
OH!
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
MY FOOT IS STUCK IN THE POCKET.
WHAT?
I CAN'T GET IT OUT.
THAT'S NOT SOMETHING A GIRL WANTS TO HEAR.
DON'T START.
OKAY.
OW.
WHAT?
STUPID BALLS ARE IN THE WAY.
OH, WELL.
IT PROBABLY WOULDN'T
HAVE BEEN THE MOST CONSTRUCTIVE SOLUTION.
YOU HAVE CHALK ON YOUR FACE.
OH, ROSS, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I DON'T KNOW WHY I ALWAYS THOUGHT
THIS WAS REAL GRASS.
HONEY, YOU OKAY?
MY WIFE'S A LESBIAN.
COOL.
ROSS, JOEY.
JOEY, ROSS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU CAME BACK.
DON'T SAY ANYTHING.
I DON'T WANT TO SPEAK.
I DON'T WANT TO THINK.
I JUST WANT YOU TO TAKE ME
AND KISS ME AND MAKE LOVE TO ME
RIGHT HERE, RIGHT NOW.
RACHEL...? RACHEL!
WHAT?
YOU MISSED THE EXIT.
OH. SORRY.
MY GOD, WHAT WERE YOU THINKING ABOUT?
UM... BARRY.
AW... AW...
?? IT'S THE TIME OF THE SEASON FOR LOVING... ??