SO, WHOSE IDEA WAS IT
TO PUT EVERYBODY IN THE DINER ON SKATES?
SOME IDIOT CUSTOMER
PUT A SUGGESTION IN THE SUGGESTION BOX.
OH, MY GOD!
THEY TOOK MY IDEA!
THAT WAS YOU?
YEAH.
OKAY, THERE YOU GO.
RACHEL, I MADE YOU A COCOA.
OH, MY G... IT'S SO NICE...!
OW!
OH, MY GOD!
ARE YOU GUYS OKAY?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
OH, MY.
?  ?
HEY.
YOU KNOW, WITH THAT GOATEE
YOU KIND OF LOOK LIKE SATAN.
OH, SO THAT'S WHY THE PRIEST THREW HOLY WATER ON ME.
OKAY, LISTEN
YOU HAVE TO CHEER UP, OKAY?
YOU SHOULD COME OUT
WITH ROSS AND ME.
I MEAN, ANYTHING IS BETTER THAN SITTING AROUND HERE
CRYING ALL DAY ABOUT KATE.
HEY, I WAS CRYING BECAUSE...
BECAUSE NOBODY BELIEVED QUINCY'S THEORY, OKAY?
HEY. HEY.
I'M GOING TO BE ON TV!
NO WAY! YEAH.
THEY'RE PUTTING TOGETHER THIS PANEL
TO TALK ABOUT THESE FOSSILS THEY JUST FOUND IN PERU
AND THE DISCOVERY CHANNEL'S GOING TO FILM IT.
OH, MY GOD!
WHO'S GOING TO WATCH THAT?
THANKS. YOU READY TO GO?
YEAH.
SAW A GIRL WITH THAT VEST.
THANKS.
While most of us think
of chocolate bunnies and baskets
as traditional Easter gifts
some people insist on giving live chicks as presents.
Unfortunately, the sad fact remains
that most of these little guys won't live
to see the Fourth of July.
Because, as a result
of improper care, they will be dead.
YEAH, HI. YOU GUYS GOT ANY OF THOSE BABY CHICKS?
BECAUSE I WAS WATCHING THIS COMMERCIAL ON TV
AND, MAN, THOSE THINGS ARE CUTE!
HI.
HI. PETE, YOU'RE BACK.
HEY, CHECK THIS OUT.
WOW, SKATES.
WHOA!
WOW.
YOU'RE A LOT STURDIER THAN CHANDLER.
HE CRUMPLED LIKE A PIECE OF PAPER.
SO HOW WAS YOUR TRIP?
WHAT'D YOU BRING ME?
AW...
HOTEL TOILETRIES FROM JAPAN!
OH!
THESE ARE GOING TO GO
IN MY PERMANENT COLLECTION.
YOU KNOW WHAT THAT SAYS IN ENGLISH?
"MADE IN TEXAS."
YOU WANT SOME COFFEE?
YEAH, SURE.
THAT WOULD BE GREAT.
REGULAR OR DECAF?
UH... WHICHEVER'S CLOSEST.
SO, ASK ME WHAT I DID TODAY.
SO, WHAT DID YOU DO TODAY, PETE?
I BOUGHT A RESTAURANT
AND I WOULD LIKE YOU TO BE THE HEAD CHEF.
WHAT?! OH...!
CAN YOU BELIEVE
HE JUST OFFERED ME A RESTAURANT?
WHAT A JERK.
WANT ME TO KICK HIS ASS?
THIS HAS BEEN, LIKE, MY DREAM
SINCE I GOT MY FIRST EASY BAKE OVEN
AND OPENED EASY MONICA'S BAKERY.
I MEAN, I WOULD KILL FOR THIS JOB.
I MEAN, I CAN TOTALLY DO THIS JOB
AND, GOD KNOWS, I'VE PAID MY DUES.
BUT PETE'S JUST DOING THIS
BECAUSE HE HAS A CRUSH ON ME.
AND YOU'RE STILL NOT ATTRACTED TO HIM AT ALL?
NO. I MEAN, HOW CAN I ACCEPT A RESTAURANT FROM HIM?
I I CAN'T.
I COULDN'T EVEN ACCEPT A NECKLACE
FROM STU VINCENT IN THE SEVENTH GRADE.
BUT, MON, THAT WAS TOTALLY DIFFERENT.
HE WAS YOUR HEALTH TEACHER.
OH, PLEASE. OW!
WHAT, HONEY?
OW.
MY SIDE STILL HURTS
FROM WHEN YOU CRASHED INTO ME YESTERDAY.
GOD, I'M SO SORRY. OW!
OH, GOD!
HEY, YOU GUYS, GUESS WHAT.
GOT A JOB ON A RIVERBOAT?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I DIDN'T WEAR THIS SUIT FOR A YEAR
BECAUSE YOU HATED IT.
WELL, GUESS WHAT.
YOU'RE NOT MY GIRLFRIEND ANYMORE, SO...
OH, I SEE. SO THIS SUIT IS MAKING A POINT.
NOW THAT YOU'RE ON YOUR OWN
YOU'RE FREE TO LOOK AS STUPID AS YOU'D LIKE.
YOU LIKE IT, RIGHT?
ABSOLUTELY.
I LIKE IT EVEN MORE ON YOU
THAN I DID ON COLONEL SANDERS.
ROSS, ROSS, I'M KIDDING.
WHAT WERE YOU
GOING TO TELL US?
WAS IT HOW YOU INVENTED THE COTTON GIN?
OKAY, GOOD BYE.
WAS THAT A LITTLE HARSH?
OH, COME ON. ARE YOU KIDDING?
DON'T YOU REMEMBER WHEN YOU WERE KIDS
AND YOU USED TO WEAR THAT GRAY SWEATSUIT
AND THEY USED TO CALL YOU THE HINDENBURG?
NO.
MY MISTAKE.
SO, UM, AFTER YOU PUT THE SUGGESTION IN THE BOX
HOW LONG DID IT TAKE FOR THE ROLLER SKATING THING TO HAPPEN?
UM, ABOUT THREE MONTHS.
OKAY, SO I GUESS
THAT'S ABOUT, UH...
TWO WEEKS BEFORE THE TOPLESS THING KICKS IN.
HEY.
I GOT YOU SOMETHING.
OPEN IT! OPEN IT!
OKAY.
IT'S A CHICKEN.
IT'S CUTE, HUH?
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, YOU GUYS
DO YOU KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT CHICKS?
FOWL? NO.
WOMEN?
NO.
HEY, WELL, THEY ARE A HUGE RESPONSIBILITY.
ESPECIALLY AT THIS AGE, THEY REQUIRE CONSTANT CARE.
THEY NEED JUST THE RIGHT FOOD
AND LOTS AND LOTS OF LOVE.
OH, WELL, NO PROBLEM.
EASY, LENNY.
SO?
I MEAN, HAVE YOU THOUGHT ABOUT IT?
OKAY, HERE'S THE THING.
OH, NO, NOT THE THING.
I HATE THE THING.
WHAT'S THE THING?
I CAN'T DO IT.
I'M SORRY.
I WISH I COULD
BUT, UM...
SEE, YOU HAVE THESE FEELINGS FOR ME...
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
THAT'S WHAT YOU'RE WORRIED ABOUT?
IF THAT'S THE PROBLEM, WE'VE GOT NO PROBLEM.
HUH?
NO, LIKE, I WAS GOING TO TELL YOU THIS OVER DINNER
BUT I MET SOMEBODY ELSE ON MY TRIP.
OH?
HER NAME'S ANNE.
SHE'S A JOURNALIST. WE MET ON THE PLANE.
SHE ASKED ME IF SHE COULD FINISH OFF MY PEANUTS.
I THOUGHT SHE SAID SOMETHING ELSE.
WE HAD A BIG LAUGH...
YEAH, I JUST...
I MEAN, I GOT TIRED OF WAITING.
THAT'S GREAT!
I MEAN, I'M I'M SORRY.
BUT I'M SO HAPPY FOR YOU.
AND NOW I CAN WORK FOR YOU.
I GUESS YOU CAN.
OH, MY GOD!
OH, THIS IS INCREDIBLE!
OH!
ALL RIGHT, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M JUST GOING TO ROLL RIGHT INTO THAT OFFICE
AND QUIT!
ALL RIGHT.
COULD YOU GIVE ME A LITTLE PUSH?
YEAH, SURE.
GOOD LUCK.
I'M QUITTING!
WHOO HOO!
I'M OKAY! I'M ALL RIGHT!
WOW. THAT'S EXCITING.
YOU WENT TO JAPAN, MADE UP A WOMAN.
WHAT?
I'M JUST SAYING-- THIS WOMAN--
I MEAN, SHE'S FICTITIOUS, NO?
WHY WOULD YOU SAY THAT?
BECAUSE YOU'RE STILL INTO MONICA.
SO YOU TOLD HER THERE WAS SOMEBODY ELSE
SO SHE WOULD AGREE TO WORK WITH YOU
BECAUSE YOU FIGURE IF YOU SPEND A LOT OF TIME TOGETHER
MAYBE SOMETHING MIGHT HAPPEN.
YOU'RE GOOD. YOU'RE GOOD.
YEAH. NO, I'M FAIRLY INTUITIVE
AND PSYCHIC.
IT'S A SUBSTANTIAL GIFT.
LISTEN, CAN YOU PROMISE ME
THAT YOU WON'T TELL HER, THOUGH?
ABSOLUTELY.
OH, I PROMISE.
TELL HER WHAT?
THANKS A LOT.
NO, I'M SERIOUS.
I MEAN, I'M INTUITIVE, BUT MY MEMORY SUCKS.
OKAY, BUT THIS IS THE LAST TIME.
? WITH A CHICK CHICK HERE AND A CHICK CHICK THERE ?
? HERE A CHICK, THERE A CHICK, EVERYWHERE ?
? A CHICK CHICK... ?
CHICKEN...
HEY.
HOW'S SHE DOING?
SHE?
WELL, YEAH. DON'T YOU THINK IT'S A SHE?
I DON'T KNOW.
I CAN'T TELL.
WHATEVER IT WAS WENT BACK IN TOO QUICKLY.
WELL, ANYWAY, I GOT TO GO CHANGE.
I'M MEETING SOME OF THE CAST FOR DRINKS.
EXCUSE ME?
WHAT?
I STAYED HOME FROM WORK TODAY
WHILE YOU WERE AT REHEARSAL
SO SOMEBODY COULD BE HERE WITH OUR CHICK.
HEY, WHO WAS UP FROM 2:00 THIS MORNING
UNTIL 5:00 THIS MORNING TRYING TO GET HER BACK TO SLEEP?
YOU DON'T THINK I GET UP WHEN YOU GET UP?
OH, HERE IT COMES.
YES.
HERE IT COMES.
I'M STUCK HERE ALL DAY
AND THEN YOU COME IN
AND SPEND TWO SECONDS WITH US...
AND THEN EXPECT TO GO OFF GALLIVANTING
WITH YOUR FRIENDS?
WELL, I DON'T THINK SO, MISTER.
HEY, I NEED TO RELAX.
OKAY?
I WAS WORKING ALL DAY.
AND YOU DON'T THINK
TAKING CARE OF OUR CHICK IS WORK?
THAT'S NOT WHAT I SAID.
OKAY?
I JUST MEANT...
I KNOW WHAT YOU MEANT.
HAVE YOU NOTICED THAT EVER SINCE WE GOT THIS CHICK
WE'VE BEEN FIGHTING A LOT MORE THAN WE USED TO?
I DON'T KNOW--
MAYBE WE WEREN'T READY TO HAVE A CHICK.
I SURE WANT ONE SOMEDAY, THOUGH.
I KNOW, I KNOW.
I'LL TAKE HER BACK TOMORROW.
DO YOU THINK WE'LL GET OUR THREE BUCKS BACK?
HEY.
OH, HEY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU STILL HAVE THAT.
WE'RE TAKING HER BACK TOMORROW.
NO. NO. THAT RIDICULOUS THING
ON YOUR FACE.
THANK YOU.
LISTEN, I HAVE THAT TV THING IN, LIKE, TWO HOURS
AND I NEED YOUR HELP, OKAY?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
THIS BLUE SUIT OR THIS BROWN ONE?
WELL...
THE BROWN ONE BRINGS OUT YOUR EYES.
BUT YOUR BUTT LOOKS GREAT IN THE BLUE ONE.
REALLY?
OW!
OH!
WOW.
THAT ASPIRIN DANCE REALLY WORKS.
OW!
OH, MY GOD, DOES THAT STILL...?
I'M FINE, I'M FINE.
NO, YOU'RE NOT.
YES, I AM. RACH...
LOOK, I'M FINE. WATCH.
LOOK AT THAT.
UH UH...
OH...!
OKAY, OKAY, LOOK
YOU'VE GOT TO GO TO A DOCTOR, OKAY?
NO. I HAVE TO GET READY
AND GO TO A DINNER AT MY BOSS'S HOUSE.
IT'S A VERY BIG DEAL.
THERE'S A LOT OF PEOPLE THERE THAT I HAVE TO MEET.
YEAH, AND I'M SURE YOU'RE GOING TO MAKE A GREAT IMPRESSION.
"HI. I'M RACHEL GREEN.
IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU."
COME ON.
YOU PROBABLY HAVE A BROKEN RIB.
WELL, I WILL GO TO THE HOSPITAL TOMORROW.
IT WILL STILL BE BROKEN THEN.
YOU KNOW, I COULD USE A HAND GETTING READY.
RACHEL...
LOOK, EITHER HELP ME OR GO.
FINE, I'LL GO.
OKAY, BUT BEFORE YOU GO, COULD YOU HELP ME FIRST?
SURE.
I'LL HELP YOU.
OH, GOOD. GOOD.
DO YOU GUYS KNOW HOW TO GET A CHICK
OUT OF A VCR?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I CANNOT DO THIS WITH MY LEFT HAND.
WOULD YOU PLEASE HELP ME WITH THIS, TOO?
OH...
OKAY, LET'S USE THIS BRUSH.
OKAY.
THIS STUFF?
YEAH. BE CAREFUL.
NOW, YOU WANT TO JUST SWEEP IT ACROSS THE LID.
JUST SWEEP IT.
OKEY DOKEY.
WHOA! SORRY.
THAT'S JUST POKING ME IN THE EYE.
I'M SORRY... CLOSE, CLOSE.
OKAY, JUST SWEEP IT.
I'M SWEEPING.
SWEEP, SWEEP.
OKAY, NOW, MAKE IT EVEN, BECAUSE WE DON'T...
WHAT? WHAT?
WE DON'T WANT IT TO BE TOO MUCH.
WE WANT IT TO BE SUBTLE.
NO, NO. YOU KNOW
YOU DON'T WEAR ENOUGH OF THIS.
SINCE WHEN...
SINCE WHEN DO YOU THINK
I DON'T WEAR ENOUGH OF THIS?
WELL, I... CLOSE YOUR EYES.
I JUST THINK YOU'RE GOING TO LIKE THIS A LITTLE BETTER
BECAUSE... CLOSE, CLOSE...
BLOW IT OFF.
SORRY. BECAUSE, UM, I THINK THIS WILL MAKE YOU
A LITTLE MORE SOPHISTICATED.
SOPHISTICATED LIKE A HOOKER?
HEY.
GUESS WHAT I'M DOING TONIGHT.
WHAT?
I'M CHECKING OUT THE RESTAURANT WITH PETE.
OH, MONICA, I AM SO EXCITED FOR YOU.
OOH, I HAVE TO TELL YOU SOMETHING.
WHAT?
WELL, I CAN'T TELL YOU.
OKAY, BUT WOULDN'T IT BE EASIER
IF YOU HAD TO TELL ME SOMETHING
THAT YOU COULD TELL ME?
WELL, SURE, IN A PERFECT WORLD.
BUT, NO
I PROMISED I WOULDN'T TELL
AND I SWORE TO, LIKE, ALL MY GODS.
OKAY.
DOES IT HAVE TO DO WITH ROSS AND RACHEL?
NO.
DOES IT HAVE TO DO WITH JOEY?
DOES IT HAVE TO DO WITH CHANDLER
AND THAT SOCK THAT HE KEEPS BY HIS BED?
NO, BUT LET'S COME BACK TO THAT LATER.
UH... UH... HUH.
THERE YOU GO.
GOOD ENOUGH FOR YOUR PARTY, HUH?
SURE.
SURE, I'LL JUST SIT NEXT TO THE TRANSSEXUAL FROM PURCHASING.
COME ON.
OKAY, COME ON.
ALL RIGHT, I GOT TO GO.
SO GOOD LUCK AT THE PARTY, OKAY?
ROSS, COULD YOU JUST STAY AND HELP ME GET DRESSED?
SURE.
OKAY.
OKAY, GREAT.
UM, OKAY, JUST...
TURN AROUND.
WHAT?
I DON'T WANT YOU TO SEE ME NAKED.
RACHEL, I'VE SEEN YOU NAKED A MILLION TIMES.
I ATE HOT FUDGE OFF YOU NAKED.
REMEMBER I SUCKED THAT MINI MARSHMALLOW
OUT OF YOUR BELLY BUTTON?
YEAH, BUT THAT WAS DIFFERENT, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, WE WERE GOING OUT THEN.
NOW I THINK IT'S WEIRD.
RACH, YOU KNOW, I CAN SEE YOU NAKED
ANYTIME I WANT.
WHAT?
ALL I HAVE TO DO IS CLOSE MY EYES.
SEE? WHOO HOO!
ROSS, STOP THAT!
COME ON.
I DON'T WANT YOU THINKING OF ME LIKE THAT ANYMORE.
UH, SORRY. NOTHING YOU CAN DO ABOUT IT.
IT'S ONE OF MY RIGHTS AS THE EX BOYFRIEND.
HUH? UH... OH, YEAH.
STOP IT.
CUT IT OUT, CUT IT OUT!
OKAY, OKAY, I'M SORRY.
IT WILL NEVER HAPPEN...
UH OH! WAIT A MINUTE! WAIT, WAIT...
NOW THERE ARE 100 OF YOU, AND I'M THE KING.
ROSS...
OH, COME ON.
WOULD YOU GROW UP?
IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
ALL RIGHT.
FINE.
YOWSAH!!!
OKAY!
SEE WHAT YOU DID?
I'M GOING TO BE DOING IT BY MYSELF NOW.
THAT'S IT. OW! OH! OW, OW!
LOOK, LOOK, OKAY, RACH, EASY, EASY.
YOU HAVE TO GO TO THE HOSPITAL, OKAY?
OKAY, I DO. I REALLY DO.
I'M GOING TO GET YOUR COAT, AND THEN I'LL PUT YOU IN A CAB.
OH, YOU'RE NOT GOING TO COME WITH ME?
OF COURSE I AM.
I JUST HAVE TO MAKE A CALL.
OKAY?
THANK YOU.
OW! GAH...!
WHAT? WHAT'S WRONG?
I'M SORRY. I JUST CAN'T GO TO THE HOSPITAL
LOOKING LIKE THIS.
DOES IT INVOLVE TRAVEL?
NO!
DOES IT INVOLVE CLOGS?
WAIT, WAIT. CLOGS OR CLAWS?
CLOGS.
NO.
CLAWS?
OKAY, SO IT DOESN'T INVOLVE ROSS OR RACHEL
OR CHANDLER OR JOEY.
WHAT ABOUT PETE?
NO!
WHAT IS IT?!
WHAT ABOUT PETE?
I DON'T KNOW.
OKAY, I FEEL LIKE I'M TALKING TO LASSIE.
GREAT. PHOEBE, WOULD YOU JUST TELL ME?
I CAN'T!
OKAY. I GOT TO GO.
YOU'RE SO CLOSE. NO!
DOES IT INVOLVE SOMETHING TO DO WITH PETE'S COMPUTER COMPANY?
UGH! JUST GO! YOU'RE NEVER
GOING TO GET IT.
I KNOW.
SEE, YES, THAT'S YASMINE BLEETH.
SHE'S A COMPLETELY DIFFERENT KIND OF CHICK.
I LOVE YOU BOTH...
BUT IN VERY DIFFERENT WAYS.
HEY.
OH, AH! WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I THOUGHT YOU WERE GOING TO TAKE HER
BACK TO THE STORE TODAY.
I DID, BUT THE STORE WOULDN'T TAKE HER BACK
SO THEN I TOOK HER TO THE SHELTER
AND YOU KNOW WHAT I FOUND OUT?
IF THEY CAN'T FIND A HOME FOR HER
THEY KILL HER!
AND I'M NOT GOING TO LET THAT HAPPEN
TO LITTLE YASMINE.
OKAY, GOOD, GOOD, GOOD
BECAUSE I WAS KIND OF  HAVING SECOND THOUGHTS, TOO.
OKAY.
AND IT'S NOT JUST CHICKS, YOU KNOW.
IT'S ALL KINDS OF OTHER ANIMALS.
THAT'S HORRIBLE!
WELL, YOU DID THE RIGHT THING, MAN.
THANKS. I'M GLAD YOU SEE IT THAT WAY.
OH, FUNNY STORY.
I DON'T BELIEVE THIS!
WOW, LOOK AT THIS REFRIGERATOR!
IT'S GIGANTIC!
I COULD LIVE IN THIS THING!
I'D BE COLD, BUT I'M ALWAYS COLD.
OH, MY GOD, LOOK AT THESE SPIDER BURNERS!
I LOVE SPIDER BURNERS!
SO YOU LIKE IT?
OH, IT IS SO PERFECT!
THANK YOU SO MUCH!
YOU'RE WELCOME.
DID YOU JUST SMELL MY HAIR?
NO.
NO WAY. WHAT? NO.
OH, GOD.
WHAT?
YOU STILL HAVE FEELINGS FOR ME, DON'T YOU?
NO. NO.
I'M JUST EXCITED ABOUT THE RESTAURANT, THAT'S ALL.
PETE...
OKAY, I LOVE YOU.
IS THAT SO BAD?
NO, IT'S NOT BAD.
IT'S NOT BAD AT ALL.
IT'S... IT'S REALLY NICE.
LOOK, THE ONLY ONE WHO STANDS TO GET HURT IS ME
AND I'M OKAY WITH THAT.
YEAH, YOU MAY BE OKAY WITH GETTING HURT
BUT I AM NOT OKAY WITH BEING THE ONE WHO HURTS YOU.
THAT'S WHY I CAN'T TAKE THIS JOB.
WHAT?
WE PROBABLY SHOULDN'T SEE EACH OTHER ANYMORE.
I'M SORRY.
OKAY. YEAH.
I MEAN, IF THAT'S REALLY WHAT YOU WANT, OKAY.
OKAY. BYE.
I'M SORRY THINGS DIDN'T WORK OUT...
SHUT UP FOR A SECOND, AND LET ME JUST SEE SOMETHING.
OH, WOW!
YOU'D TELL ME THE TRUTH, RIGHT?
RACH, YOU CAN'T LOOK FAT IN AN X RAY.
OKAY, NOW, YOU STAY OUT HERE
AND YOU THINK ABOUT WHAT YOU DID!
THAT'S A DUCK.
THAT'S A BAD DUCK!
HOW DID THE THING GO TONIGHT, ROSS?
UH, IT WAS... NAH, WELL...
WHAT THING? WHAT THING?
NOTHING. THERE WAS THIS THING AT THE MUSEUM.
COME ON.
EASY.
OKAY
NOW, WHEN YOU COME BACK, I HOPE YOU REMEMBER
THAT THAT CHICK IS NOT A TOY!
WHAT THING? WHAT IS THIS THING?
UH, I WAS KIND OF SUPPOSED TO BE ON TV TONIGHT
FOR THE DISCOVERY CHANNEL.
OH, MY GOD!
ROSS, WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME THAT?
AH, BECAUSE I KNEW THAT IF I TOLD YOU
YOU'D MAKE ME GO, AND I KNEW
YOU NEEDED SOMEONE TO BE WITH YOU TONIGHT.
COME ON.
I CANNOT BELIEVE YOU.
WHAT?
THAT IS THE SWEETEST THING.
I JUST...
YOU SHOULD GET SOME SLEEP.
OKAY.
I'M SORRY I SPOILED YOUR EVENING.
NO. AS LONG AS YOU'RE OKAY.
OH, YEAH.
SO, I'LL, UH...
I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW.
MM HMM. YEAH.
SEE YOU.
WHAT DID YOU DO?
WHAT YOU DOING?
HAVING A SWIM.
WHAT ABOUT THE CHICK?
CHICKS DON'T SWIM.
ARE YOU SURE?
I DON'T KNOW.
SHOULD WE TRY?
SURE.
SEE? I TOLD YOU-- THEY DON'T SWIM.
WAIT. WAIT. GIVE HIM A MINUTE.
NO! OH, IT'S OKAY, IT'S OKAY. PEEP PEEP PEEP.