I'M TELLING YOU, THAT GIRL TOTALLY WINKED AT ME.
SHE DID NOT WINK AT YOU.
NOBODY'S WINKING AT YOU.
HUH.
I HAVE TO SAY "TUPELO HONEY" BY VAN MORRISON.
NO WAY.
THE MOST ROMANTIC SONG EVER WAS "THE WAY WE WERE."
SEE, I THINK THE ONE THAT ELTON JOHN WROTE
FOR, UM, THAT GUY ONWHO'S THE BOSS?
WHAT SONG IS THAT, PHEEBS?
UM...
HOLD ME CLOSE, YOUNG TONY DANZA...
HI, MONICA.
HEY, MON.
OH, MY GOD, HAS SHE SLEPT AT ALL?
NOPE.
NO. IT'S BEEN THREE NIGHTS IN A ROW.
YEAH, SHE FINALLY STOPPED CRYING YESTERDAY
BUT THEN SHE FOUND ONE
ONE OF RICHARD'S CIGAR BUTTS
OUT ON THE TERRACE...
OKAY. THAT EXPLAINS IT.
I GOT A CALL AT 2:00 IN THE MORNING
AND ALL I COULD HEAR WAS LIKE THIS HIGH SQUEAKY SOUND
SO I THOUGHT, "OH, OKAY.
SO IT'S LIKE A MOUSE OR A POSSUM."
THEN I REALIZED LIKE, OKAY
WHERE WOULD A MOUSE OR A POSSUM
GET THE MONEY TO MAKE THE PHONE CALL?
MORNING.
HEY, YOU MADE PANCAKES?
YEAH. LIKE THERE'S ANY WAY I COULD EVER DO THAT.
MONICA AND RACHEL HAD SYRUP
UH UH, NOW I CAN GET
MY MAN TO CHEER UP...
GOOD MORNING, JOEY.
GOOD MORNING.
OOH, SOMEONE'S WEARING GRUMPY PANTS.
IT'S GOT TO BE YOU, MAN.
I'M WEARING SMARTY PANTS.
OKAY, HERE WE  GO.
ONE, TWO, AND HERE'S MY CHANCE
TO GIVE YOU A THIRD ONE.
JOEY?
NO, NO.
I'LL JUST HAVE JUICE.
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
HERE'S A THOUGHT.
WHY DON'T YOU STAY HOME FROM WORK TODAY
AND HANG OUT WITH ME?
OH, I WISH.
LISTEN, HONEY, YOU HAVE THAT REPORT TO FINISH
AND I'VE GOT TO  GO SEE MY LAWYER.
I CANNOT BELIEVE I'M GOING OUT
WITH SOMEBODY WHO'S GETTING DIVORCED.
I'M SUCH A GROWNUP.
JOEY, HEY! GO TO YOUR ROOM!
CHANDLER, HEY! UP YOURS!
I GOT TO GO. I GOT TO GO.
OKAY, NOT WITHOUT A KISS.
WELL, MAYBE I WON'T KISS YOU, AND THEN YOU'LL HAVE TO STAY.
KISS HER. KISS HER.
MMM WA. MMM.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER, SWEETIE.
BYE, JOEY.
BYE BYE, JANICE.
MMM... MMM...
SO, WHEN YOU DUMPING HER?
NOPE.
NOT THIS TIME.
COME ON. QUIT YANKING ME.
I'M NOT YANKING YOU.
THIS IS JANICE.
YEAH. I KNOW.
SHE MAKES ME HAPPY.
OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
YOU LOOK ME IN THE EYE AND TELL ME WITHOUT BLINKING
THAT YOU'RE NOT BREAKING UP WITH HER.
NO BLINKING.
I'M NOT BREAKING UP WITH HER.
HEY...
OH, GOD, LOOK WHAT I FOUND IN THE DRAIN.
WHAT?
IT'S SOME OF RICHARD'S HAIR.
WHAT DO I DO WITH THIS?
GETTING IT AWAY FROM ME WOULD BE JOB ONE.
IT'S WEIRD , BUT, YOU KNOW
I DON'T WANT TO THROW THIS AWAY.
I MEAN, THIS IS LIKE ALL I HAVE LEFT OF HIM--
GROSS... DRAIN HAIR.
EWW!
COOL. OH, IT LOOKS LIKE A TINY LITTLE PERSON
DROWNING IN YOUR CEREAL.
GOD, WHAT IS WRONG WITH ME?
YOU NEED TO GET SOME SLEEP.
I NEED TO GET SOME RICHARD.
MONICA, YOU BROKE UP WITH HIM FOR A REASON.
I KNOW. I KNOW.
I'M JUST SO TIRED OF MISSING HIM.
I'M TIRED OF WONDERING WHY HE HASN'T CALLED.
WHY HASN'T HE CALLED?
MAYBE BECAUSE YOU TOLD HIM NOT TO?
WHAT ARE YOU? THE MEMORY WOMAN?
THEY'RE NOT BREAKING UP.
CHANDLER AND JANICE-- THEY'RE NOT BREAKING UP.
HE DIDN'T BLINK OR ANYTHING.
WELL, YOU KNOW, I'M NOT SURPRISED.
I MEAN, HAVE YOU SEEN THEM TOGETHER?
THEY'RE REALLY CUTE.
CUTE?
THIS IS JANICE.
YOU REMEMBER JANICE?
YES, JOEY. I REMEMBER.
SHE'S ANNOYING, BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
SHE'S HIS GIRLFRIEND NOW.
I MEAN, WHAT CAN WE DO?
THERE YOU GO.
THAT'S THE SPIRIT I'M LOOKING FOR.
WHAT CAN WE DO?
HUH?
ALL RIGHT, WHO'S FIRST?
HUH? ROSS?
WELL, I'M THINKING CHANDLER'S OUR FRIEND
AND JANICE MAKES HIM HAPPY.
SO I SAY WE ALL JUST BE ADULT ABOUT IT AND ACCEPT HER.
YEAH. WE'LL CALL THAT PLAN "B," ALL RIGHT?
COME ON, PEOPLE, WE NEED SOME INSPIRATION.
YEAH, OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
YOU WANT A PLAN? HERE WE GO.
ALL RIGHT. SO, UM...
OKAY, ROSS, YOU GO IN THROUGH THE AIR DUCT
AND DISABLE THE ALARM, OKAY?
AND THEN, YOU KNOW, THE REST OF US WILL JUST RAPPEL DOWN ROPES--
WE'RE IN AND OUT IN TEN MINUTES AND DISAPPEAR INTO THE NIGHT.
HUH? HUH?
HONEY, I WAS WONDERING...
HMM?
DO YOU STILL HAVE THAT, UM, NAVY UNIFORM?
NO. I HAD TO RETURN IT TO THE COSTUME PLACE.
I THINK I HAVE
AN OLD BAND UNIFORM FROM HIGH SCHOOL.
YOU REMEMBER NOT HAVING SE X IN HIGH SCHOOL, RIGHT?
YEAH.
WELL, HONEY, WHAT ABOUT YOU?
I MEAN... WHAT?
ANY FUN, YOU KNOW, FANTASY TYPE THINGS?
NO.
COME ON. YOU GOT TO HAVE ONE.
NOPE.
ROSS, YOU KNOW WHAT?
WHAT?
IF YOU TELL ME , I MIGHT DO IT.
OKAY.
UM... DID YOU EVER SEE
UM,RETURN OF THE JEDI?
YEAH.
DO YOU REMEMBER THE SCENE WITH, UM...
JABBA THE HUT?
HE WAS THIS, UH... REALLY FAT WORM GUY.
WOW.
MEN AND WOMEN REALLY ARE DIFFERENT.
NO, NO. NO, SEE, JABBA HAD AS HIS PRISONER
PRINCESS LEIA.
OH...
PRINCESS LEIA WAS WEARING THIS, UM...
GOLD BIKINI THING.
IT WAS PRETTY COOL.
SO, ARE YOU SAYING THAT YOU WOULD LIKE ME TO, UM...
DRESS UP LIKE PRINCESS LEIA...
IN A GOLD BIKINI?
OKAY.
OH, YEAH. PRINCESS LEIA AND THE GOLD BIKINI?
OH, EVERY GUY OUR AGE LOVED THAT.
REALLY?
MM HMM. IT'S HUGE.
YEAH, THAT'S THE MOMENT WHEN, YOU KNOW
SHE STOPPED BEING A PRINCESS
AND SHE BECAME LIKE A WOMAN, YOU KNOW?
DID YOU EVER...? DO THE...? THE LEIA THING?
OH, YEAH. MM HMM.
OOH!
REALLY?
THAT... THAT GREAT, HUH?
NO. IT'S JUST THAT I GOT THIS NEW PAGER
AND I HAVE IT ON VIBRATE.
SEE YOU.
HEY...
HI, YOU GUYS.
LOOK WHO I FOUND
STANDING OUTSIDE THE SZECHUAN DRAGON
STARING AT A PARKING METER.
MON.
HI.
WHY AREN'T YOU AT WORK?
OH, THEY... THEY SENT ME HOME.
WHY?
BECAUSE I DON'T WORK AT THE SZECHUAN DRAGON.
OKAY.
YOU REALLY, REALLY NEED TO GET SOME SLEEP.
I KNOW I DO.
HI. HI.
GUESS WHAT. WHAT?
THEY PUBLISH ED MY PAPER.
REALLY?
YEAH. STATISTICAL DEVIATIONS
IN THE CARBON DATING OF FOSSILIZED ALGAE
COLONHISTORY OR MYSTERY?
RACH, LOOK.
NO.
OOH, HI.
WHERE IS MY STRONG ROSS SKYWALKER
TO COME RESCUE ME?
THERE HE IS.
WHEEL OF
Fortune...
Is there a T? THIS GUY'S SO STUPID.
IT'S COUNT RUSHMORE.
YOU KNOW, YOU SHOULD REALLY GO ON THIS SHOW.
ALL RIGHT, LISTEN.
I GOT THREE TICKETS TO THE RANGERS TONIGHT.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
I SAY I AM THERE.
COOL. OH... IS ROSS GOING TOO?
NO. JANICE.
JANICE?
BECAUSE I JUST... I FEEL BAD FOR ROSS, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, WE ALWAYS GO TOGETHER.
WE'RE LIKE THE THREE HOCK A TEERS.
YOU KNOW, I MAY BE WAY OUT ON A LIMB HERE
BUT DO YOU... DO YOU HAVE A PROBLEM WITH JANICE?
NO.
YES.
GOD, HOW DO I SAY THIS?
HI. UH, OH...
YOU KNOW THAT GIRL FROM THE GREEK RESTAURANT
WITH THE HAIR?
EWW, THAT GIRL THAT I HATE?
EWW, SHE DRIVES ME CRAZY.
EWW, OH.
LOOK, I DON'T HATE JANICE.
SHE'S JUST A LOT TO TAKE, YOU KNOW?
WELL, THERE YOU GO.
OH, HEY, COME ON, MAN.
DON'T LOOK AT ME LIKE THAT.
SHE USED TO DRIVE YOU NUTS BEFORE TOO, REMEMBER?
YEAH, WELL, I'M CRAZY ABOUT HER NOW.
I THINK THIS COULD BE THE REAL THING.
CAPITAL "R," CAPITAL "T."
DON'T WORRY.
THOSE ARE THE RIGHT LETTERS.
LOOK... WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO SAY?
I WANT YOU TO SAY THAT YOU LIKE HER.
I CAN'T. LIKE HER!
NO.
SO YOU'RE NOT EVEN GOING TO TRY?
WHAT'S THE POINT?
IT'S LIKE THIS CHEMICAL THING, YOU KNOW?
EVERY TIME SHE STARTS LAUGHING
I JUST WANT TO...
PULL MY ARM OFF
JUST SO I HAVE SOMETHING TO THROW AT HER.
THANKS FOR TRYING.
OH, AND BY THE WAY, THERE IS NO COUNT RUSHMORE.
YEAH? THEN WHO'S THE GUY THAT PAINTED THE FACES
ON THE MOUNTAIN?
HOW COULD YOU HAVE TOLD HER?
ROSS, I DIDN'T THINK IT WOULD BE THAT BIG A DEAL.
OH, SHE DIDN'T THINK IT WOULD BE THAT BIG A DEAL.
OKAY, WHO ARE YOU TALKING TO WHEN YOU DO THAT?
LOOK, THAT WAS SUPPOSED TO BE
LIKE A PRIVATE, PERSONAL THING BETWEEN US.
OKAY, ROSS, PHOEBE  IS MY GIRLFRIEND, OKAY?
WE TELL EACH OTHER EVERYTHING, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, COME ON.
GUYS DO THE SAME THING.
WHAT ABOUT ALL THAT LOCKER ROOM STUFF?
THAT'S DIFFERENT, OKAY?
THAT'S LIKE WHO DATED A STRIPPER
OR WHO DID IT ON THE BACK OF THE STATEN ISLAND FERRY?
BOTH OF THOSE JOEY?
YEAH.
BUT YOU DON'T TALK ABOUT
LIKE, YOU KNOW, YOUR GIRLFRIEND
AND THE INTIMATE STUFF YOU DO WITH HER.
NOT EVEN WITH YOUR BEST FRIEND?
NO.
THAT IS SO SAD.
YOU'RE MISSING OUT
ON SO MUCH, ROSS.
I MEAN, THE BONDING AND THE SHARING, YOU KNOW
AND KNOWING THAT SOMEONE ELSE
IS GOING THROUGH THE SAME THING YOU ARE.
SO... WHAT... YOU TELL EACH OTHER EVERYTHING?
YEAH... PRETTY MUCH.
DID YOU TALK ABOUT "THE NIGHT OF FIVE TIMES?"
DO YOU TELL PEOPLE ABOUT "THE NIGHT OF FIVE TIMES?"
UH, HONEY... YEAH, THAT WAS WITH CAROL.
I KNOW, BUT IT'S STILL WORTH MENTIONING, I THINK.
RELAX EVERY MUSCLE IN YOUR BODY.
LISTEN TO THE PLINKY PLUNKY MUSIC.
OKAY, NOW CLOSE YOUR EYES
AND THINK OF A HAPPY PLACE.
OKAY, TELL ME YOUR HAPPY PLACE.
RICHARD'S LIVING ROOM, DRINKING WINE.
ALL RIGHT, NO, NO.
NOT A RICHARD THING.
JUST PUT DOWN THE GLASS... AND GET OUT!
I'M SORRY, BUT THAT'S MY HAPPY PLACE.
WELL, OKAY, FINE, USE MY HAPPY PLACE, OKAY?
I'M JUST GOING TO HAVE TO ASK
THAT YOU DON'T MOVE ANYTHING IN THERE.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL TRY NOT TO.
ALL RIGHT, SO, YOU'RE IN A MEADOW
MILLIONS OF STARS IN THE SKY...
DO YOU THINK BREAKING UP WITH HIM WAS A HUGE MISTAKE?
OKAY, THERE ARE NO QUESTIONS IN THE HAPPY PLACE.
OKAY, JUST
THE WARM BREEZE
AND THE MOONLIGHT FLOWING THROUGH THE TREE...
I'LL BET HE'S TOTALLY OVER ME.
I'LL BET HE'S FINE.
ALL RIGHT, BETTING AND WAGERING OF ANY KIND
ARE, I'M SURE, NOT PERMITTED IN THE HAPPY PLACE.
OKAY? THERE'S JUST, YOU KNOW
THE THE LOVELY WATERFALLS
AND THE, THE TRICKLING FOUNTAINS
AND THE CALMING SOUNDS OF THE BABBLING BROOK...
OKAY, THIS ISN'T WORKING.
I'M STILL AWAKE AND NOW I HAVE TO PEE.
OH.
GUESS WHO.
JANICE.
HI. YOU JUST MISSED CHANDLER
BUT, UH, WON'T YOU COME IN BEFORE YOU GO?
SO...
I HEAR... YOU HATE ME.
HEY, I NEVER SAID "HATE."
I WAS VERY CAREFUL ABOUT THAT.
A LITTLE BIRDIE TOLD ME
SOMETHING ABOUT YOU WANTING TO RIP YOUR ARM OFF
AND THROW IT AT ME.
AND YOU GOT A "HATE" FROM THAT?
YOU'RE TAKING A BIG LEAP THERE.
ALL RIGHT. FINE, FINE, FINE, FINE, FINE.
WE HAVE GOT TO DO SOMETHING
ABOUT OUR LITTLE SITUATION HERE, JOEY.
SO, THIS IS MY IDEA.
YOU AND ME SPENDING SOME QUALITY TIME TOGETHER.
BUT WHAT DOES THAT...?
FOR CHANDLER!
OKAY. I'M IN.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT, THIS IS WHAT WE'RE GOING TO CALL IT.
"JOEY AND JANICE'S DAY OF FUN."
DOES IT HAVE TO BE A WHOLE DAY?
YES! BECAUSE THAT'S HOW LONG IT TAKES TO LOVE ME.
YEAH. I KNOW.
I SLEEP IN THE NEXT ROOM.
SO, DO YOU GUYS ALL HATE JANICE, TOO?
OH, YOU HATE JANICE NOW?
OH! JOEY'S GOING TO BE SO RELIEVED.
OH, MY GOD.
OH, GOD...
OH, LOOK, EVERYBODY, IT'S WEEPY...
THE MIME THAT CARES TOO MUCH.
AND THEN I WENT DOWN TO THE POST OFFICE.
IT TURNS OUT IT WAS THOSE VIDEOS THAT I ORDERED FOR RICHARD
ABOUT THE CIVIL WAR.
HE LOVED THE CIVIL WAR.
MONICA, DO YOU WANT  US TO TAKE YOU HOME?
UH HUH.
OR MAYBE TO A GALAXY FAR, FAR AWAY.
WOMEN TELL EACH OTHER EVERYTHING.
DID YOU KNOW THAT?
HMM, YEAH.
NO, CHANDLER, EVERYTHING... LIKE...
STUFF YOU LIKE.
STUFF SHE LIKES.
TECHNIQUE, STAMINA, GIRTH.
GIRTH?
WHY, WHY, WHY, WHY
WHY, WHY WOULD THEY DO THIS?
RACHEL SAYS SHARING'S GREAT
AND SUPPOSEDLY , YOU KNOW
WE OUGHT TO BE DOING IT.
UH, DO YOU WANT TO?
WE'RE NOT GOING TO TALK ABOUT GIRTH, ARE WE?
NO!
YEAH, OKAY.
YEAH?
ALL RIGHT, YOU GO FIRST.
OKAY, OKAY. I'LL GO FIRST.
SO, UH, THE OTHER NIGHT
RACHEL AND I ARE IN BED TALKING ABOUT FANTASIES.
AND I HAPPENED TO DESCRIBE A PARTICULAR...
STAR WARS THING.
PRINCESS LEIA AND THE GOLD BIKINI.
YES!
I KNOW.
YES.
WELL, WOW...
WELL, THAT WAS EASY.
GO. OKAY, YOU
OKAY. OKAY.
OKAY, WELL, YOU KNOW
WHEN YOU'RE IN BED WITH A WOMAN...
HMM.
AND YOU KNOW
YOU'RE FOOLING AROUND WITH HER
AND YOU GET
ALL THESE, LIKE, MENTAL IMAGES IN YOUR BRAIN.
YOU KNOW LIKE, ELLE MacPHERSON
OR THAT GIRL AT THE XEROX PLACE.
WITH THE BELLY BUTTON RING?
OH...MM WAH.
AND THEN, ALL OF A SUDDEN
YOUR MOM POPS IN YOUR HEAD.
AND YOU'RE LIKE
"MOM, GET OUT OF HERE."
BUT, OF COURSE, AFTER THAT
YOU CAN'T POSSIBLY THINK OF ANYTHING ELSE
AND YOU CAN'T, YOU KNOW, STOP WHAT YOU'RE DOING
SO IT'S KIND OF LIKE YOU'RE... YOU KNOW...
YOU DON'T KNOW.
YOUR... MOM?
YOU'RE, YOU'RE TELLING  ME ABOUT YOUR MOM?
WHAT IS THE MATTER WITH YOU?
YOU SAID...
I SAID, "SHARE," NOT "SCARE."
GO SIT OVER THERE.
WE'RE BACK!
HEY!
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING TOGETHER?
"JOEY AND JANICE'S DAY OF FUN."
REALLY?
YEAH, YEAH.
WE WENT TO A METS GAME.
WE GOT CHINESE FOOD
AND, YOU KNOW, I LOVE THIS WOMAN.
YOU HAVE GOT COMPETITION, BUDDY.
I JUST CAME BY TO GIVE YOU A KISS.
I HAVE TO GO PICK UP THE BABIES
SO I'LL SEE YOU LATER, SWEETHEART.
YOU TOO, CHANDLER.
YOU STILL CAN'T STAND HER, CAN YOU?
I'M SORRY, MAN.
I TRIED. I REALLY DID.
WELL, YOU KNOW, I APPRECIATE YOU GIVING IT A SHOT.
BUT, HEY, LOOK, YOU KNOW, THE GOOD THING IS
IS THAT WE SPENT THE WHOLE DAY TOGETHER
AND I SURVIVED.
AND WHAT'S EVEN MORE AMAZING, SO DID SHE.
I MEAN, IT WAS "BAT DAY" AT SHEA STADIUM.
YEAH, I...
I GUESS THAT'S SOMETHING.
OH, MAN.
THAT'S HUGE.
NOW I KNOW I CAN STAND TO BE AROUND HER
WHICH MEANS, I GET TO HANG OUT WITH YOU
WHICH IS KIND OF THE WHOLE POINT ANYWAY.
OKAY.
OH, HEY, CHANDLER
WE STOPPED BY THE COFFEE SHOP
AND RAN INTO ROSS.
OH, GOD.
IF IT MAKES YOU FEEL ANY BETTER
I DO IT TOO.
REALLY?
OH, YEAH.
I ALWAYS PICTURE YOUR  MOM WHEN I'M HAVING SEX.
April 12, 1861...
... United States garrison ]at Fort Sumter was fired upon.
It is now under bombardment...
HEY, DAD.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
WELL, IT'S YOUR MOTHER'S BRIDGE NIGHT
SO I THOUGHT I'D COME INTO THE CITY
FOR A LITTLE MONI CUDDLE.
SINCE WHEN DID YOU START SMOKING CIGARS?
I DON'T.
I JUST...
I JUST LIKE THE SMELL OF THEM.
SO, UH...
WHAT ARE YOU REALLY DOING HERE, DAD?
WELL, I JUST WANTED TO MAKE SURE
THAT YOU'RE OKAY.
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK THAT I MIGHT NOT BE OKAY?
I SAW RICHARD.
OH?
SO, HOW YOU DOING?
FINE.
JUST A LITTLE TIRED.
I'M OKAY.
HOW'S RICHARD DOING?
YOU DON'T WANT TO KNOW.
NO, I REALLY, REALLY DO.
WELL, HE'S DOING TERRIBLE.
REALLY?
WORSE THAN WHEN HE BROKE UP WITH BARBARA.
YOU'RE NOT JUST SAYING THAT, ARE YOU?
NO, THE MAN IS A MESS.
WAS HE CRYING?
NO.
WELL, DO YOU THINK
HE WAS WAITING UNTIL AFTER YOU LEFT
SO HE COULD CRY?
MAYBE.
I THINK SO.
HONEY, RELATIONSHIPS ARE HARD.
LIKE WITH YOUR MOM AND ME.
AFTER WE GRADUATED FROM COLLEGE, WE BROKE UP FOR A WHILE.
IT SEEMS HER FATHER, YOUR GRANDFATHER
WANTED HER TO TRAVEL AROUND EUROPE LIKE HE DID.
OF COURSE, HE GOT TO DO IT ON UNCLE SAM'S NICKEL
BECAUSE HE WAS ALSO STRAFING GERMAN TROOP TRAINS AT THE TIME.
HOWEVER...
OKAY, HERE WE  GO.
I'M JABBA'S PRISONER
AND YOU
HAVE A REALLY WEIRD LOOK ON YOUR FACE.
WHAT? WHAT IS  IT?
DID I GET IT WRONG?
DID I GET THE HAIR WRONG?
DID YOU JUST PICTURE IT DIFFERENTLY?
COME ON, WHAT?
NO, NO. IT'S NOT YOU.
IT'S, UM, IT'S...
WELL, WHAT IS IT?
COME ON, SWEETIE, YOU'RE KIND OF, LIKE, FREAKING ME OUT HERE.
I HATE CHANDLER.