NEW WALLET, HUH?
YEAH. IT WAS TIME.
THE OLD CONDOM RING IN THE LEATHER
JUST DOESN'T SAY "COOL"
ANYMORE, YOU KNOW?
RACHEL, YOU JUST PUT AN EMPTY CARTON
BACK IN THE FRIDGE.
YEAH, I KNOW, BUT THE GARBAGE
WAS FULL.
HAVE YOU EVER TAKEN OUT THE TRASH?
YEAH.
SINCE YOU'VE LIVED HERE?
WELL, I, UH... THOUGHT
YOU LIKE DDOING IT.
THIRD DOOR ON THE LEFT.
RIGHT.
OH, HEY, MR. TREEGER.
HEY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
UM...
OH! OH!
SORRY.
IT'S A LITTLE OLD, BUT...
YOU'RE CLOGGING  UP THE CHUTE
I JUST SPENT A HALF HOUR UNCLOGGING.
OH, I'M SORRY. I DIDN'T...
I DON'T COME IN HERE A LOT.
OF COURSE YOU DON'T.
BECAUSE YOU'RE A LITTLE PRINCESS.
"DADDY, BUY ME A PIZZA."
"DADDY, BUY ME A CANDY FACTORY."
"DADDY, MAKE THE CAST OF CATS
SING 'HAPPY BIRTHDAY' TO ME."
BUT I...
YOU THINK YOU CAN JUST MAKE A MESS
THE BIG MAN IN THE COVERALLS
WILL COME AND CLEAN IT UP, HUH?
WHY DON'T YOU THINK
OF SOMEONE ELSE FOR A CHANGE?
OKAY. I'M SORRY.
GOD! IF YOU'RE GOING TO CRY ABOUT IT...
WHOA! TREEGER MADE YOU CRY?
YES.
HE SAID REALLY MEAN THINGS
THAT WERE ONLY PARTLY TRUE.
I'M GOING TO GO DOWN THERE AND TEACH THAT GUY A LESSON.
PLEASE, IT'S BEST IF WE FORGET ABOUT IT.
THAT'S EASY FOR YOU TO SAY.
YOU WEREN'T ALMOST JUST KILLED.
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S IT.
SCHOOL IS IN SESSION!
YOU GUYS, IS THIS A GYM CARD?
OH, YEAH. GYM MEMBER.
I TRY TO GO FOUR TIMES A WEEK
BUT I'VE MISSED THE LAST 1,200 TIMES.
SO WHY DON'T YOU QUIT?
YOU DON'T THINK I'VE TRIED?
YOU THINK I LIKE
HAVING $50 DOLLARS TAKEN OUT OF MY BANK ACCOUNT EVERY MONTH?
THEY MAKE YOU GO ALL THE WAY DOWN THERE.
THEN THEY USE ALL THESE PHRASES AND PEPPINESS
TO TRY TO CONFUSE YOU.
AND THEN THEY BRING OUT MARIA.
WHO IS MARIA?
AH, MARIA...
YOU CAN'T SAY NO TO HER.
SHE'S LIKE THIS LYCRA, SPANDEX COVERED GYM TREAT.
YOU NEED ME TO GO DOWN THERE WITH YOU
AND HOLD YOUR HAND?
NO.
YOU'RE STRONG ENOUGH TO FACE HER ALONE?
OH, NO.
YOU'LL HAVE TO COME.
TRIBBIANI.
HOLD ON. I'LL GET THE PLUNGER.
HEY, YOU HOLD ON, PAL.
NOW, YOU MADE MY FRIEND RACHEL CRY
SO NOW YOU'RE GOING TO GO UP THERE
AND YOU'RE GOING TO APOLOGIZE TO HER
UNLESS YOU WANT ME TO CALL THE LANDLORD.
AND TELL HIM WHAT?
MAYBE YOU HAVEN'T HEARD OF "NOT MAKING GIRLS CRY."
MAYBE YOU HAVEN'T HEARD OF A LITTLE SOMETHING
CALLED "THE RENT STABILIZATION ACT OF 1968."
I HAVE ACTUALLY NOT HEARD OF THAT.
YEAH? WELL, YOUR FRIENDS ARE IN VIOLATION OF IT.
I BEEN A NICE GUY UP UNTIL NOW
BUT I DON'T NEED THIS GRIEF.
I'M GOING TO CALL THE LANDLORD
AND TELL HIM THAT MONICA IS ILLEGALLY SUBLETTING
HER GRANDMOTHER'S APARTMENT.
YOUR FRIENDS ARE OUT OF HERE, PAL.
WHY DON'T YOU TELL ME SOMETHING I DON'T KNOW?
PLEASE, SOMEBODY TELL ME I DON'T HAVE TO WORK TODAY.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
MY FIRST MASSAGE
IS THIS INCREDIBLY GORGEOUS GUY
AND EVERY TIME I SEE HIM
I JUST WANT TO DO THINGS TO HIM
THAT I'M NOT ALLOWED TO CHARGE FOR.
SO DO THEM FOR FREE.
OH, NO. IT IS FORBIDDEN.
NO, NO. MRS. CARTER FIRES PEOPLE FOR MESSING AROUND WITH CLIENTS.
AND IT'S AGAINST MY OATH AS A MASSEUSE.
THEY MAKE YOU TAKE AN OATH?
NO. I MADE MYSELF TAKE ONE.
YEAH, NO FOOLING AROUND WITH CLIENTS
AND, UM... ALWAYS BE PREPARED.
THAT ONE'S ACTUALLY FROM THE BOY SCOUTS
BUT IT JUST MAKES GOOD SENSE.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST GIVE HIM
TO SOMEBODY ELSE?
NO, I CAN HANDLE IT.
NO, I'M A PROFESSIONAL.
OH, PHEEBS, IS THAT A NEW ANKLE BRACELET?
AND YOU GOT A PEDICURE.
YOUR FEET ARE ALL DRESSED UP.
BECAUSE THAT'S THE ONLY PART OF YOU HE CAN SEE
WHEN HE'S ON THE TABLE.
YOU'RE GOING TO DO SOME FEET FLIRTING.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
THEN HOW DO YOU EXPLAIN THE TOE RING?
BECAUSE IT'S ARABIAN PRINCESS DAY AT WORK, OKAY?
LEAVE ME ALONE.
OH!
MY HERO! WHAT HAPPENED?
WELL, UH...
I WENT DOWN AND TOLD HIM
NO ONE TREATS MY FRIENDS LIKE THAT
AND HE'D BETTER COME UP HERE AND APOLOGIZE.
WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT DID HE SAY?
UH... HE SAID HE WASN'T GOING TO APOLOGIZE
BECAUSE YOU GUYS ARE LIVING HERE ILLEGALLY.
INSTEAD, WHAT HE'S GOING TO DO IS HAVE YOU EVICTED.
WHAT? EVICTED?
I TOLD YOU NOT TO GO DOWN THERE.
HE MADE RACHEL CRY!
RACHEL ALWAYS CRIES!
THAT'S NOT TRUE!
JOEY, YOU GO DOWN THERE
AND YOU SUCK UP TO HIM.
I MEAN, YOU SUCK
LIKE YOU'VE NEVER SUCKED BEFORE!
ALL RIGHT, I'LL TRY.
BUT, IF I CAN'T, YOU STAY WITH CHANDLER AND I
UNTIL YOU GET SETTLED.
GO!
I'LL CHECK
WITH HIM FIRST
BUT I THINK HE'LL BE COOL.
JOEY!
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
NOW REMEMBER WHAT WE TALKED ABOUT:
YOU GOT TO BE STRONG.
YES.YES.
NOW ONE MORE TIME:
"HEY, DON'T YOU WANT A WASHBOARD STOMACH
AND ROCK HARD PECS?"
NO. I WANT A FLABBY GUT
AND SAGGY MAN BREASTS.
GOOD. THAT'S GOOD.
I WANT TO QUIT THE GYM.
YOU WANT TO QUIT?
YOU DO REALIZE YOU WON'T HAVE ACCESS
TO OUR NEW FULL SERVICE SWEDISH SPA?
I WANT TO QUIT THE GYM.
OKAY. DAVE, IN THE MEMBERSHIP OFFICE, HANDLES QUITTERS.
EXCUSE ME.
ARE YOU A MEMBER?
ME?
NO.
SORRY. MEMBERS ONLY.
I WANT TO QUIT THE GYM.
IT'S OKAY, MAN. BE STRONG.
SO, ARE YOU A MEMBER OF ANY GYM?
NO, AND I'M NOT GOING TO BE
SO YOU CAN SAVE YOUR LITTLE SPEECH.
OKAY. NO PROBLEM.
COULD YOU COME HERE FOR A SECOND?
HI. I'M MARIA.
HI, M...
WOW, YOU HAVE REALLY PRETTY FEET.
THESE OLD THINGS?
WOULD YOU SPEND SOME TIME ON MY SCIATIC AREA?
IT'S BEEN KILLING ME TODAY.
YOU MEAN THE...
BY "SCIATIC," YOU MEAN THE...
TOWEL COVERED PORTION.
YEAH.
SURE. YEAH. NO, I CAN DO THAT...
YEAH. BECAUSE, UH...
YOU KNOW, USUALLY THE MUSCLES IN THE SCIATIC AREA
CAN GET, YOU KNOW, REAL NICE AND TIGHT.
YEAH. SO, UM.... TELL ME, RICK
HOW, UM... HOW DID YOU INJURE THE AREA?
OH, A 16 HOUR SIT IN FOR GREENPEACE.
OH.
OW!
DID YOU JUST BITE ME?
NO.
WHAT?
PLEASE DON'T KICK MONICA AND RACHEL OUT.
THIS WASN'T THEIR FAULT. IT WAS MINE.
SHOULD I KICK YOU GUYS OUT INSTEAD?
NO. YOU CAN'T DO THAT.
WHERE WOULD THE CHICK AND THE DUCK LIVE?
YOU HAVE PETS?
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
THOSE ARE, UH... NICKNAMES.
YEAH, I'M THE CHICK AND CHANDLER'S THE DUCK.
HUH. I WOULD HAVE THOUGHT
IT WAS THE OTHER WAY AROUND.
COME ON, MAN.
JUST... JUST LET THE GIRLS STAY.
I'LL DO WHATEVER YOU WANT.
REALLY?
YOU'D DO ANYTHING?
YEAH, YEAH. ABSOLUTELY.
I GOT SOMETHING YOU CAN DO.
WHAT? WHAT IS IT?
CAN YOU BE MY DANCING PARTNER?
THAT'S NOT PRISON LINGO, IS IT?
I WANT TO QUIT THE GYM.
NOW, CAN YOU HONESTLY TELL ME
THAT YOU'RE 100% SATISFIED WITH YOUR BODY?
YES, MOST OF THE TIME.
SURE, I HAVE MY BAD DAYS
BUT THEN I REMEMBER WHAT A CUTE SMILE I HAVE.
WE WERE VOTED BEST EQUIPPED GYM IN NEW YORK
TWO YEARS RUNNING.
DO YOU REALLY WANT TO GIVE THAT UP?
YES. I HATE IT HERE!
EVERYTHING THAT YOU HAVE IN HERE IS VERY HEAVY.
YEAH.
REALLY?
OKAY.
YOU DON'T WANT TO MAKE YOUR FRIEND WORK OUT ALONE, DO YOU?
WHAT FRIEND?
YOUR FRIEND, ROSS, JUST JOINED.
HIS DANCING PARTNER? YEAH.
THERE'S THIS SUPERINTENDENTS' DANCE--
THE SUPER BALL...
AND HE WANTS TO IMPRESS MARGE
THIS LADY SUPER THAT HE'S GOT A CRUSH ON.
WHY DOESN'T HE JUST PRACTICE WITH A GIRL?
HE'S TOO SHY.
HE DOESN'T THINK HE'S GOOD ENOUGH
TO DANCE WITH GIRLS YET.
YEAH, RIGHT.
HE ALMOST DANCED ME RIGHT DOWN THAT...
GARBAGE CHUTE.
OH, WOULD YOU LET IT GO, ALREADY?
YOU'RE FINE.
HEY.
HEY. SO, DID YOU QUIT?
NO. I ALMOST DID.
COULDN'T LEAVE ROSS THERE WITHOUT A SPOTTER.
WAIT, NOW, SO YOU JOINED THE GYM?
OH...
AND THAT'S FUNNY WHY?
OH, UM...
I WAS JUST, YOU KNOW, PICTURING YOU
WORKING OUT, AND, UM...
OH, THAT'S IT.
WE'RE DOOMED, OKAY?
THEY'RE GOING TO TAKE 50 BUCKS A MONTH
OUT OF OUR ACCOUNTS FOR THE REST OF OUR LIVES.
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
YOU COULD ACTUALLY GO TO THE GYM.
OR...
OR WE COULD GO TO THE BANK
CLOSE OUR ACCOUNTS
AND CUT THEM OFF AT THE SOURCE.
YOU'RE A GENIUS.
OH, MAN, BUT THEN WE WON'T BE BANK BUDDIES.
NOW THERE'S TWO REASONS.
HEY. HEY. HEY.
HEY. HEY.
OH, YOU GUYS.
REMEMBER THAT CUTE CLIENT I TOLD YOU ABOUT?
I BIT HIM.
WHERE?
ON THE TUSHIE.
AND THAT'S NOT AGAINST YOUR OATH?
NO. I KNOW.
I'M SORRY, BUT THE MOMENT I TOUCH HIM
I JUST WANT TO THROW OUT MY OLD OATH
AND TAKE A NEW DIRTY ONE.
WELL, NEXT TIME YOU'RE MASSAGING HIM
YOU SHOULD TRY TO DISTRACT YOURSELF.
YEAH, YEAH.
LIKE, WHEN I'M DOING SOMETHING EXCITING
AND I DON'T WANT TO GET TOO... EXCITED
I JUST TRY AND THINK OF OTHER THINGS
LIKE, UH, SANDWICHES
AND, UH, BASEBALL
AND, UH...
CHANDLER.
THANK YOU, JOEY.
OH, NO. THANK YOU.
ALL RIGHT, I'M HERE.
LET'S, UH, GET THIS OVER WITH.
OKAY, WELL
JUST FOLLOW MY LEAD.
DON'T WE NEED TO DO SOME KIND OF PREPARATION FIRST?
LIKE, UH, GET REALLY DRUNK?
ALL RIGHT, COME ON.
JUST PUT YOUR ARMS AROUND ME.
YEAH. OKAY.
I I I'M SORRY.
NO, IT'S OKAY
BUT, IF I'M MARGE
MY BREASTS ARE COMING OUT MY BACK.
AW, FORGET IT.
I'M NOT GOING TO BE ANY GOOD AT THIS.
MY MOM WAS RIGHT.
I'M JUST A BIG POTATO
WITH ARMS AND LEGS AND A HEAD.
COME ON, MAN.
YOU'RE NOT A POTATO.
I'M SURE AS HELL NOT A DANCER.
IT'S NO USE.
MARGE WILL NEVER GO FOR ME.
AW, COME ON, TREEGER.
DON'T SAY THAT.
YOU JUST, UH...
YOU JUST NEED MORE PRACTICE.
HERE. COME ON.
LET'S TRY IT AGAIN.
COME ON.
PLUS, IT WAS PROBABLY MOSTLY MY FAULT.
I MEAN, I'M NOT REALLY THAT COMFORTABLE
DANCING WITH A...
WHOO HOO!
HEY!
YEAH!
SO HOW GOES THE DANCING?
GAY YET?
HA, HA, HA.
YOU GUYS OWE ME BIG TIME.
WHAT WAS THAT?
WHAT?
YOU JUST DID A LITTLE DANCE Y THING.
NO, I DIDN'T.
YES, YOU DID.
YOU DID, LIKE, A LITTLE HOP.
YOU ARE SO ENJOYING THIS.
NO, I'M NOT.
AND IT WASN'T A HOP.
IT WAS APAS DE BOURREE.
OH!
YOU KNOW THE WORDS!
YOU ARE SO INTO THIS.
ALL RIGHT. MAYBE I'M ENJOYING IT A LITTLE BIT.
I MEAN, I'M GETTING PRETTY GOOD AT IT.
OH, THIS IS SO SWEET.
JOEY-- OUR LITTLE TWINKLE TOES.
HEY, HEY. HOLD ON.
THIS ISN'T SOME KIND OF GIRLIE DANCE.
IT'S, LIKE, A SPORT. IT'S MANLY.
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, COME HERE.
SHOW ME SOME MANLY MOVES.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO LEAD.
HELLO.
HI.
WE'D LIKE TO CLOSE OUR ACCOUNTS.
CLOSE YOUR ACCOUNTS?
IS THERE SOME PROBLEM?
NO, NO.
NO. WE'D JUST LIKE TO CLOSE THEM.
OKAY.
MS. LAMBERT HANDLES ALL OUR CLOSURES.
WOULD YOU COME OVER HERE
PLEASE?
HI. I'M KAREN.
I WANT TO QUIT THE BANK!
OKAY, BASEBALL.
RICK PLAYING BASEBALL.
OKAY, HE SLIDES INTO SECOND.
MAYBE EVEN HIS PANTS COME DOWN A LITTLE.
OH, NO! WAIT! NO!
NO, NO.
ALL RIGHT, SANDWICHES, SANDWICHES.
UM, OKAY, ON A PLATE.
MAYBE RICK'S PANTS COME DOWN A LITTLE.
NO, NO!
CHANDLER.
OKAY, CHANDLER.
OOH, THAT'S WORKING.
CHANDLER'S... KNEES.
CHANDLER'S ANKLES.
CHANDLER'S ANKLE HAIR.
OH, NO.
OKAY, YOU'RE ALL SET.
OH, WOW.
THAT WAS AMAZING.
WAS THAT REALLY JUST AN HOUR?
YEAH...
IN REALLY LONG HOUR WORLD.
WHAT?
OKAY.
I HAVE AN ENORMOUS CRUSH ON YOU
BUT, BECAUSE YOU'RE A CLIENT, I CAN'T ASK YOU OUT
EVEN THOUGH YOU GIVE ME, YOU KNOW, THE FEELINGS.
WOW.
I HAD NO IDEA
BUT, UH, HEY
I CAN ALWAYS FIND ANOTHER MASSEUSE.
REALLY?
YEAH, REALLY.
WHAT?
SUDDENLY, I'M VERY AWARE THAT I'M NAKED.
OKAY, QUIET DOWN.
MR. SIMON'S BEEN WAITING FOR... OH, MY GOD.
WHY WASN'T I OFFERED THAT?
I'D DEFINITELY PAY MORE FOR THAT.
PHOEBE, WE HAVE RULES HERE.
THIS IS NOT THAT KIND OF PLACE.
NO, YEAH, OH, AND I KNOW
BUT THIS ISN'T HOW IT LOOKS AT ALL
BECAUSE RICK IS, UM... MY HUSBAND.
OH, REALLY?
WELL, THEN, YOU BETTER TELL HIS OTHER WIFE
BECAUSE SHE CALLED THREE TIMES
ASKING WHERE HE IS.
YES, I WILL TELL... HER.
SO YOU DIDN'T LEAVE THE BANK?
NO...
AND, SOMEHOW, WE ENDED UP
WITH A JOINT CHECKING ACCOUNT.
WHAT ARE YOU EVER GOING TO USE THAT FOR?
TO PAY FOR THE GYM.
HEY. HEY.
HEY!
SO, I HAD A GREAT DAY.
RICK AND I HIT IT OFF.
WE STARTED MAKING OUT
AND THEN MY BOSS WALKED IN AND FIRED ME FOR BEING A WHORE.
WHAT? WHAT?
YOU GOT FIRED?
IT'S SO WEIRD.
I HAVE NEVER BEEN FIRED FROM ANYTHING BEFORE.
SWEETIE.
I JUST STARTED WALKING AROUND
NOT KNOWING WHAT TO DO NEXT, YOU KNOW?
I STARTED ASKING PEOPLE ON THE STREET
IF THEY WANTED MASSAGES.
THEN THESE POLICEMEN THOUGHT I WAS A WHORE, TOO.
OH!
IT'S REALLY BEEN A BAD DAY, WHORE WISE.
HEY, DUCK.
IS CHICK HERE?
YEAH...
BUNNY RABBIT.
YOU READY FOR OUR LAST PRACTICE?
YEAH, BUT I THINK THE REASON
WE'RE NOT GETTING THAT SPIN RIGHT
IS BECAUSE MY APARTMENT'S TOO SMALL.
WANT TO USE OUR PLACE?
NO.
I HAD ANOTHER IDEA.
?? NIGHT AND DAY ??
?? YOU ARE THE ONE ??
?
?? ONLY YOU BENEATH THE MOON ?
?? OR UNDER THE SUN ??
?
?? WHETHER NEAR TO ME OR FAR ?
?? IT'S NO MATTER, DARLING , WHERE YOU ARE ??
?? I THINK OF YOU ??
?? NIGHT AND DAY. ??
WE DID IT!
I KNOW! WE DID IT!
HEY, THAT WAS INCREDIBLE, HUH?
THAT WAS AMAZING!
I MEAN, WE TOTALLY NAILED IT!
IT WAS BEAUTIFUL.
HEY, LISTEN.
THANKS A LOT, TRIBBIANI.
OH, MY GOD.
LOOK AT THE TIME.
I GOT TO CATCH THE BUS TO THE BALL.
OH. OKAY.
GOOD LUCK.
YEAH.
UNLESS YOU WANT TO PRACTICE THE FOX TROT AGAIN
OR THE TANGO?
UH, THANKS, BUT NO.
YOU SEE, I THINK I'M READY TO DANCE WITH GIRLS.
OKAY.
GO GET THEM, TREEGER.
RIGHT.
HEY, UH...
YOU WANT TO COME?
MARGE HAS A GIRLFRIEND.
REALLY?
YEAH.
YOU COULD DANCE WITH HER.
SHE'S THE SAME SIZE AS ME.
NO. I'M GOOD.
?? NIGHT AND DAY. ??
SO, IT LOOKS LIKE YOU'VE GOT SOME GREAT EXPERIENCE HERE.
LET'S SEE.
REASON FOR LEAVING LAST JOB?
YEAH. THEY THOUGHT I WAS A WHORE.
OKAY.
WE'LL GIVE YOU A CALL IF ANYTHING COMES UP.
GREAT.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.