?? MORNING'S HERE ??
?? THE MORNING'S HERE ??
?? SUNSHINE IS HERE ??
?? THE SKY IS CLEAR ??
?? THE MORNING'S HERE ??
?? THE MORNING'S HERE... ??
HEY!
DO YOU HAVE TO DO THAT?
IT'S SATURDAY!
OH, COME ON.
MORNING'S HERE!
?? MORNING'S HERE ??
?? THE MORNING'S HERE ??
?? SUNSHINE IS HERE ??
?? LA DA DA DAH DAH DAH DAH DAH... ??
I HATE THIS APARTMENT!
I HATE THE COLOR OF THESE WALLS.
I HATE THE FACT THIS PLACE STILL SMELLS LIKE BIRD.
I HATE THAT SINGING GUY.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
I LOVE THAT GUY.
?? MORNING'S HERE ??
?? MORNING IS... ??
STOP IT!
I WILL KILL YOU.
GOD.
I HATE THE FACT THAT MY ROOM IS SO SMALL.
HEY, I HAVE ALL THE SPACE I NEED.
JUST DO WHAT I DID.
MONICA, YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE A BED.
YOU SLEEP IN A BALL ON THE FLOOR.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I AM REALLY TIRED OF YOUR BELLYACHING, OKAY?
I'VE WORKED REALLY HARD AT MAKING THIS
A NICE PLACE FOR US TO LIVE.
I KNOW.
I'M SO SORRY.
I'M SORRY, OKAY?
SEE, THIS IS A GREAT APARTMENT.
SHUT UP! THIS PLACE IS A HOLE!
OH, BLIMEY!
I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'VE GOT AN EARRING.
I KNOW, I KNOW. WHO AM  I:
DAVID BOWIE?
HE DOES THAT?
I DON'T KNOW. WHATEVER.
I THINK IT MAKES YOU LOOK REALLY DANGEROUS.
OH, I KNOW.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I NEVER WOULD HAVE GOTTEN THIS
IF IT WEREN'T FOR YOU.
NO, REALLY.
WHEN I'M WITH YOU, I'M LIKE THIS THIS WHOLE OTHER GUY.
I LOVE THAT GUY.
I MEAN, I LOVE YOU, TOO, A LOT
BUT THAT GUY.
I LOVE THAT GUY.
I LOVE BOTH OF YOU.
YEAH?
I WISH I DIDN'T HAVE TO GO.
THEN DON'T.
STAY HERE.
JUST DON'T GO SO SOON TO LONDON.
JUST ONE MORE DAY.
OH, ROSS, PLEASE DON'T DO THIS TO ME AGAIN. ONE MORE DAY.
YOU KNOW I'D STAY IN A MINUTE
BUT I'VE ALREADY MISSED SO MUCH OF MY WORK
THEY'D FIRE ME.
SO? THEN YOU COULD STAY AS LONG AS YOU WANT.
I WISH I COULD.
OH, NO, DON'T DON'T. .. DON'T START PACKING.
COME ON.
I DON'T THINK YOU UNDERSTAND PACKING.
LOOK, I JUST DON'T WANT TO LEAVE IT TILL THE LAST MINUTE.
THE LAST TIME I PACKED IN A RUSH, I LEFT MY KNICKERS.
YEAH, I KNOW.
I, UH, I TRIED THEM ON.
YOU DIDN'T!
NO, I DIDN'T.
I DIDN'T WANT TO BE THAT GUY.
HELLO.
HO, HO, HO!
EXCUSE ME?
YOUR PANTS.
OH, YEAH!
YOU LIKE THEM?
I WENT TO A USED CLOTHES STORE
AND GOT, LIKE, A BUNCH OF MATERNITY STUFF.
THESE ARE SO COMFORTABLE.
UH, PHEEBS, THOSE ARE SANTA PANTS.
WHAT?
SANTA PANTS.
SANTA CLAUS'S PANTS.
NUH UH.
THEY'RE MATERNITY PANTS.
THEY EVEN CAME WITH A LIST OF BABY NAMES.
SEE?
THESE NAMES ARE GOOD AND THESE ARE BAD.
OH.
HEY.
HEY, PHEEBS.
S? SO, HOW ARE THE ELVE
I DON'T KNOW.
HOW ARE THE...
YOU KNOW.
YOUR CLOTHES AREN'T FUNNY.
HEY, GUYS, WHAT SHOULD I WEAR TO A KNICKS GAME?
UH, A T SHIRT THAT SAYS, "I DON'T BELONG HERE."
YOU HAVE KNICKS TICKETS?
YEAH. MY MOM GOT MY DAD'S
SEASON TICKETS IN THE DIVORCE
SO SHE JUST GAVE THEM TO ME.
APPARENTLY, THEY'RE PRETTY GOOD SEATS.
OH, MY GOD!
THESE ARE ALMOST RIGHT ON THE FLOOR!
I COULD SLIP WOODY ALLEN MY RESUME.
DO YOU GUYS WANT THESE?
YEAH! YEAH, WE DO!
OH, WELL, YOU GOT THEM.
ALL RIGHT!
JUST GIVE US
OUR APARTMENT BACK.
WHOA! I DIDN'T SEE THAT COMING.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
COME ON.
WE KNOW WHAT THESE ARE WORTH.
WHAT, DO YOU THINK WE'RE STUPID?
NOT STUPID.
YOU'RE MEANER THAN I THOUGHT.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
FORGET IT, OKAY?
I'M NOT GIVING  UP MY BACHELOR PAD
FOR SOME BASKETBALL SEATS.
YOUR BACHELOR PAD?
HAVE YOU EVEN HAD A GIRL UP HERE?
NO.
BUT, UH... JOEY HAS
AND I USUALLY TALK TO THEM IN THE MORNING TIME.
YEAH, YOU DO.
COME ON.
YES, GUNTHER, CAN I GET TWO CUPS OF CHINO, PLEASE?
GOOD ONE.
HEY, COME ON-- SEASON TICKETS.
SEASON TICKETS.
YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS?
FORGET IT. I'M NOT GIVING UP THE APARTMENT.
LOOK, WHEN I WAS A LITTLE KID
MY DAD'S COMPANY GAVE SEASON TICKETS
TO THE NUMBER ONE SALESMAN EVERY YEAR.
MY DAD NEVER WON.
OF COURSE, HE WASN'T IN THE SALES DIVISION
BUT STILL, I NEVER EVER, EVER FORGOT THAT.
HEY, GUYS.
HEY.
OH, MY GOD.
WE DON'T MAKE ENOUGH FUN OF YOU ALREADY?
OH, YEAH.
EMILY CONVINCED ME TO DO IT.
YOU DO KNOW THAT WHAM! BROKE UP?
YEAH, WELL, I LIKE  IT AND EMILY LIKES IT
AND THAT'S WHAT COUNTS.
SO, UH, HOW ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
DON'T TRY AND TALK ALL NORMAL
WITH THAT THING IN YOUR EAR.
WHERE'S EMILY?
SHE'S SAYING GOOD BYE TO HER UNCLE.
MAN, DIDN'T SHE, LIKE, JUST GET HERE?
YEAH! YEAH!
EASY, TIGER.
I JUST... I HATE THIS SO MUCH.
I MEAN, EVERY TIME I GO PICK HER UP AT THE AIRPORT
IT'S SO GREAT, BUT AT THE SAME TIME
I'M THINKING, WELL, I'M GOING TO BE RIGHT BACK THERE
IN A COUPLE OF DAYS DROPPING HER OFF.
SO, WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
THERE'S NOTHING TO DO.
I MEAN, SHE LIVES THERE, I LIVE HERE.
I MEAN, SHE'D HAVE TO MOVE HERE.
SHE SHOULD MOVE HERE.
WHAT?
I COULD ASK HER TO LIVE WITH ME.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
WHY NOT? I MEAN, WHY NOT?
BECAUSE YOU'VE ONLY KNOWN HER SIX WEEKS.
OKAY, I'VE GOT A CARTON OF MILK IN MY REFRIGERATOR
I'VE HAD A LONGER RELATIONSHIP WITH.
BUT, GUYS, WHEN I'M WITH HER, IT'S LIKE...
SHE BRINGS OUT THIS THIS THIS GREAT SIDE OF ME.
I MEAN, I LOVE HER, YOU KNOW?
AND I LOVE THE MILK!
BUT I'M NOT GOING TO ASK
SOME BRITISH GIRL TO MOVE IN WITH ME.
JOEY, YOU SAY THINGS NOW.
LOOK, ROSS, HE'S RIGHT.
EMILY IS GREAT.
SHE'S GREAT
BUT THIS IS WAY TOO SOON.
YOU'RE ONLY GOING TO SCARE HER.
I DON'T WANT TO DO THAT. NO.
YOU DON'T WANT TO WRECK IT.
YOU DON'T WANT TO GO TOO FAST.
YEAH. NO, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I KNOW YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'M NOT GOING TO DO IT.
THANKS, GUYS.
OKAY, NO PROBLEM.
JUST REMEMBER TO WAKE US UP
BEFORE YOU GO GO.
OH, IT'S TOO HARD.
TOO HARD!
ALL RIGHT, BOYS--
LAST CHANCE FOR THE TICKETS.
OTHERWISE, I GIVE THEM TO MY NEW BOYFRIEND JOSHUA.
NO, THANK YOU.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
COME ON, COME ON-- LET'S TRADE.
THE TIMING'S PERFECT.
I JUST CLOGGED THE TOILET!
LOOK, I WANT THOSE BASKETBALL SEATS
AS MUCH AS YOU DO, OKAY?
BUT WE CAN'T LIVE IN THE SMALL APARTMENT
AFTER WE'VE LIVED HERE!
DIDN'T YOU EVER READ FLOWERS FOR ALGERNON?
YES...
DIDN'T YOU EVER READ SPORTS ILLUSTRATED?
NO, I DIDN'T READ YOURS.
LOOK, COME ON, WE CAN GO TO THE GAME TONIGHT.
LOOK, THE ONLY WAY I WILL EVEN CONSIDER THIS
IS IF THEY OFFER A LOT MORE THAN JUST SEASON SEATS.
BUT IT'S THE KNICKS!
KS! SCREW THE KNIC
WHOA...
I DIDN'T MEAN THAT.
I JUST MEANT
THAT THE APARTMENT IS WORTH SO MUCH MORE.
HUH.
AND THE KNICKS RULE ALL.
YEAH! THE KNICKS RULE ALL.
HEY, SO ARE YOU GOING TO DO IT?
NO. NO, WE'RE NOT.
YOU KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE IT'S NOT AN EVEN TRADE.
ALL RIGHT, OKAY, LOOK, WHAT IF YOU COULD KEEP THE APARTMENT
AND GET THE TICKETS?
DONE!
LET ME FINISH.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT A BET-- WINNER TAKES ALL.
WE COULD END UP WITH NOTHING.
OR YOU CAN END  UP WITH EVERYTHING.
OOH, I LIKE THAT.
ALL RIGHT, SO WHAT DO YOU SAY?
NO! OH, JUST DO IT!
OH! OH, I'M CONVINCED.
COME ON, MAN.
YOU KNOW I'D DO IT FOR YOU.
BECAUSE YOU'RE MY BEST FRIEND.
ALL RIGHT, BUT YOU CAN'T USE THAT AGAIN
FOR A WHOLE YEAR.
I'M IN.
OOH! THIS IS SO EXCITING!
OH, GOD, WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO BET?
OH, OKAY. WELL, I THINK WE SHOULD
LET PHOEBE DECIDE
BECAUSE SHE'S THE ONLY ONE WHO'S IMPARTIAL
AND SHE'S SO PRETTY.
OKAY.
UM... OOH, OOH...
OH, I HAVE A GAME!
OH, THIS IS GREAT!
WHAT'S THE GAME, WHAT'S THE GAME?
UM, WELL, IT DOESN'T HAVE A NAME.
BUT NO, OKAY: "PHOEBE BALL."
NO, IT DOESN'T HAVE A NAME.
UM...
OKAY, MONICA, WHAT IS YOUR FAVORITE THING
ABOUT TREES?
THEY'RE GREEN?
GOOD! GOOD! FIVE POINTS!
ALL RIGHT!
GREAT! ALL RIGHT
JOEY...
SAME QUESTION.
UH...
OH!
HMM. THEY'RE TALL.
OOH! THREE POINTS.
NO. BOTH FINE ANSWERS
BUT WE WERE LOOKING FOR "LEAFY."
"LEAFY."
THAT'S NOT EVEN A GAME.
SHUT UP!
WE'RE WINNING.
YOU WANT TO FINISH THIS RIGHT NOW?
WE GET A DECK OF CARDS.
HIGH CARD WINS.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
FINE. LET'S DO IT.
OOH! I HAVE CARDS.
OH, GOOD.
YEAH! HERE.
OH, NO. THESE ARE THE TRICK DECK.
OKAY... HERE, YES.
OKAY.
OKAY, YOU GUYS... YOU GUYS PICK FIRST.
FOUR.
YES! THAT'S A LOW ONE NAH!
ALL RIGHT.
PHOEBE, YOU LOOK.
I CAN'T DO IT.
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK I CAN?!
OKAY, OKAY.
ACE!
WHY ARE YOU SCREAMING AND HUGGING?
WELL, BECAUSE WE WON OUR APARTMENT BACK!
WHAT?
ACE IS HIGH: JACK, QUEEN, KING, ACE.
NO, ACE IS LOW: ACE, TWO, THREE, FOUR.
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT, BUT, OOH!
OOH!
LOOK IT! AH!
PICK AGAIN, PICK AGAIN!
ALL RIGHT, GIMME, GIMME.
OKAY. OKAY.
COME ON, APARTMENT!
I KNOW QUEEN IS HIGH!
AH, NOT AS HIGH AS...
IT WORKED! KING!
WE WIN!
WE PICK AGAIN, WE PICK AGAIN!
WHY? I DON'T KNOW.
TICKETS, PLEASE.
THAT'S COURT SIDE, BABY!
YEAH!
SERIOUSLY, GOOD GAME, THOUGH!
GOOD GAME...
WHAT ARE THEY SO MAD ABOUT?
THEY GOT THE APARTMENT BACK.
NO, THEY DIDN'T.
HEY.
PACKED WHILE YOU WERE GONE.
I LEFT SOME KNICKERS UNDER YOUR PILLOW.
MOVE IN WITH ME.
WHAT?
DON'T BE SCARED.
I I KNOW IT SOUNDS CRAZY
AND PEOPLE WILL SAY IT'S TOO SOON
BUT JUST, JUST THINK.
THINK HOW GREAT IT WOULD BE.
OH...
OW. I DON'T KN
OH, LEAVING LONDON. UH...
MY WHOLE FAMILY LIVES THERE.
MY JOB.
WELL, SO YOU'LL GET A JOB HERE.
I MEAN, I'M ALWAYS HEARING
ABOUT THEM FOREIGNERS COMING IN AND STEALING AMERICAN JOBS.
THAT COULD BE YOU.
YEAH, BUT I IT'S MY WHOLE LIFE.
YOU COME TO ENGLAND.
NO, I CAN'T.
I WOULD, I REALLY WOULD, BUT MY SON IS HERE.
I CAN'T LEAVE HIM. ISN'T...?
YOU DON'T THINK THERE'S ANY WAY?
SO. OH, I DON'T THINK
I MEAN, IT WOULD BE DIFFERENT IF IT WAS WAY INTO THE FUTURE
AND, AND WE WERE GETTING MARRIED, OR SOMETHING.
WHAT?
OH. NO. NO, RIGHT.
UH, I SHOULDN'T HAVE SAID "MARRIED."
UH, PLEASE DON'T GET FREAKY ON ME.
UH... I DIDN'T MEAN IT.
I DIDN'T SAY IT. I TAKE IT BACK.
NO, NO, DON'T.
WHY DON'T WE?
WHY DON'T WE WHAT?
GET MARRIED.
YOU ARE MAD.
NO, NO! I'M NOT.
IT'S IT'S IT'S PERFECT!
I MEAN, IT'S BETTER THAN YOU JUST MOVING HERE
BECAUSE IT'S US TOGETHER FOREVER
AND THAT'S, THAT'S WHAT I WANT.
WE'VE ONLY KNOWN EACH OTHER FOR SIX WEEKS.
I KNOW. SO WHAT?
I MEAN, WHO'S TO SAY?
DOES THAT MEAN WE, WE CAN'T DO IT?
LOOK, I WAS WITH CAROL FOR FOUR YEARS
BEFORE WE GOT MARRIED
AND I WOUND UP DIVORCED FROM A PREGNANT LESBIAN.
I MEAN, THIS...
THIS MAKES SENSE FOR US.
COME ON!
I MEAN, OUR FIRST DATE
WE ENDED UP SPENDING THE WHOLE WEEKEND IN VERMONT.
I MEAN, LAST NIGHT, I GOT MY EAR PIERCED.
ME!
IT JUST FEELS RIGHT.
DOESN'T IT?
MY PARENTS ARE GOING TO BE REALLY MAD.
IS THAT... ARE YOU SAYING "YES"?
IS THAT "YES"?
YES.
YES!
YES? WE'RE GETTING...?
WE'RE GETTING MARRIED?
OH, MY GOD!
WE'RE GETTING MARRIED!
WE, WE...
COME HERE, COME HERE.
OW!
EMILY, WILL YOU MARRY ME?
YES.
OH, IT'S A BIT SMALL.
DAMN! I THOUGHT THAT WAS GOING TO BE ROMANTIC AS HELL.
IT WAS.
THOSE WERE, LIKE, THE BEST SEATS EVER.
OH, YEAH. HEY! SHOULD WE GIVE THESE SHIRTS TO THE GIRLS
YOU KNOW, KIND OF LIKE A PEACE OFFERING?
OH, YEAH. THAT'S VERY NICE.
PLUS, YOU KNOW, THEY WERE FREE AND THEY'RE TOO SMALL.
OH... OH, GOD!
HEY, YOU WANT A BEER?
WHOA!
I KNOW!
OPEN UP! OPEN UP! OPEN UP!
WE'LL DISCUSS IT IN THE MORNING.
WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON?
WE TOOK OUR APARTMENT BACK.
I HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH IT.
OKAY. IT WAS MY IDEA
BUT I DON'T FEEL GOOD ABOUT IT.
OH! OH!
WE ARE SWITCHING BACK RIGHT NOW.
NO, WE'RE NOT.
WE'RE NOT LEAVING.
WELL, YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO LEAVE SOMETIME
BECAUSE YOU BOTH HAVE JOBS
AND AS SOON AS YOU DO, WE'RE SWITCHING IT BACK.
THERE'S NOTHING YOU CAN DO TO STOP US.
RIGHT, JOE?
I DON'T KNOW. I...
WHAT?!
I DON'T WANT TO MOVE AGAIN.
I DON'T CARE.
THIS IS OUR APARTMENT AND THEY STOLE--
YOU STOLE!-- OUR APARTMENT.
WE WON THAT APARTMENT FAIR AND SQUARE TWICE
AND I AM GETTING IT BACK RIGHT NOW.
I'M GETTING IT BACK RIGHT NOW!
ALL RIGHT...
WE FIGURED YOU MIGHT RESPOND THIS WAY
SO WE HAVE A BACKUP OFFER.
OH, NO, NO, NO. NO MORE OFFERS.
YOU CAN'T OFFER ANYTHING TO US.
LET US KEEP THE APARTMENT AND...
AS A THANK YOU...
RACHEL AND I WILL KISS FOR ONE MINUTE.
TOTALLY WORTH IT.
THAT WAS ONE GOOD MINUTE.
GOOD NIGHT.
MEN ARE SUCH IDIOTS.
I KNOW. CAN YOU BELIEVE
SOMETHING THAT STUPID
ACTUALLY GOT US OUR APARTMENT BACK?
IT'S SO FUNNY TO THINK--
IF YOU HAD JUST DONE THAT RIGHT AFTER THE LAST CONTEST
NO ONE WOULD'VE HAD TO MOVE AT ALL.
L L LET'S PRETEND THAT'S NOT TRUE.
YEAH.
OKAY... SCARF'S DONE.
COME ON, COME ON, COME ON.
OKAY.
HI.
HEY. HEY.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
ROSS HAS SOME BIG THING TO TELL EVERYONE.
UH... UH, OKAY...
IT'S, UH...
EMILY AND I...
WE DECIDED TO, UH... TO GET MARRIED.
WHAT?!
OH! ARE YOU PREGNANT, TOO?
UH, NO.
WHEN... WHEN DID...?
HOW... HOW DID YOU...?
WE WE JUST DECIDED TO... TO GO FOR IT.
I MEAN, WE KNOW IT'S A BIT HASTY
BUT, UH...
IT JUST FEELS SO RIGHT, SO...
UM... I WAS JUST TELLING THE GUYS...
YEAH. I... I HEARD.
I THINK IT'S GREAT!
OH, I'M SO HAPPY FOR YOU.
WELL, YEAH... CONGRATULATIONS.
OH, YEAH, YEAH.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE GETTING MARRIED.
YEAH.
MONICA AND RACHEL MADE OUT.
Singing  ?? MORNING'S HERE ??
?? THE MORNING'S HERE ??
?? SUNSHINE IS HERE ??
?? THE SKY IS CLEAR ??
?? THE MORNING'S HERE... ? ?
HEY! YOU'RE BACK!
HEY!
?? GET INTO GEAR ??
?? BREAKFAST IS NEAR ??
?? THE DARK OF NIGHT HAS DISAPPEARED. ??
I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW MORNING.
OKAY.