HEY. HI.
SORRY I'M LATE.
DID I MISS ANYTHING?
WELL, JOEY STUFFING 15 OREOS IN HIS MOUTH.
FIFTEEN?
YOUR PERSONAL BEST. YEAH.
MM MM.
SO, WHERE WERE YOU?
OH, ON A DATE.
I MET THIS GIRL ON THE TRAIN
GOING TO A MUSEUM UPSTATE.
OH, YEAH, HOW'D YOU MEET HER? WHICH MUSEUM?
NO. ANSWER HIS.
OKAY, IT WAS JUST ME AND HER AT THE BACK OF THE TRAIN
AND I SAT NEAR THE DOOR SO SHE'D HAVE TO PASS BY ME
IF SHE WANTED TO, LIKE, SWITCH CARS.
SHE WAS TOTALLY AT MY MERCY.
WERE YOU SO LATE BECAUSE YOU WERE BURYING THIS WOMAN?
NO, I'M GETTING BACK NOW
BECAUSE SHE LIVES IN POUGHKEEPSIE.
SHE SEEMS REALLY GREAT
BUT SHE'S, LIKE, TWO AND A HALF HOURS AWAY.
HOW CAN SHE BE GREAT IF SHE'S FROM POUGHKEEPSIE?
OKAY, THAT JOKE WOULD'VE KILLED IN ALBANY.
DONE.
I DID IT.
HUH. WHO'S STUPID NOW, HUH?
HEY, THEY'RE LIGHTING
THE BIG CHRISTMAS TREE TONIGHT.
UM, THAT PAPER'S TWO WEEKS OLD.
ALL RIGHT, WHO KEEPS LEAVING OLD NEWSPAPERS IN THE TRASH?
I REALLY WANTED TO TAKE KATHY TO THIS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I MISSED IT.
HEY, YOU KNOW, AT LEAST
YOU HAVE SOMEBODY TO MISS THAT STUFF WITH.
I HATE BEING ALO NE THIS TIME OF YEAR.
NEXT THING YOU KNOW, IT'LL BE VALENTINE'S DAY
THEN MY BIRTHDAY, THEN BANG--
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT , THEY'RE LIGHTING THAT DAMN TREE AGAIN.
OH, I WANT SOMEBODY.
YOU KNOW? I WANT AMAN.
I MEAN
IT DOESN'T EVEN HAVE TO BE A BIG RELATIONSHIP.
YOU KNOW, JUST A FLING WOULD BE GREAT.
REALLY? I DIDN'T THINK GIRLS EVER JUST WANTED A FLING.
WELL, LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING.
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME SINCE I'VE BEEN FLUNG.
WELL, I KNOW WHAT I'M GIVING YOU FOR CHRISTMAS.
THERE ARE SOME NICE GUYS
AT MY OFFICE.
YOU WANT ME TO SET YOU UP?
YEAH. WAIT A MINUTE.
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIM E THAT I'VE BEEN SINGLE.
HOW COME YOU'VE NE VER OFFERED THIS BEFORE?
WELL, I HAVE A GIRLFRIEND.
I'M... I'M HAPPY.
SO, I NO LONGER FEEL THE NEED TO GO OUT OF MY WAY
TO STOP OTHERS FROM BEING HAPPY.
OKAY.
BUT NO ACCOUNTANTS.
OH, AND NO ONE FROM, LIKE, "LEGAL."
I DON'T LIKE GUYS WITH BORING JOBS.
OH, AND ROSS WAS LIKE, WHAT, A LION TAMER?
HEY! HEY.
WHAT'S WRONG, MON?
EVERYBODY AT THE RESTAURANT STILL HATES ME.
IS IT BECAUSE OF THE REVIEW YOU WROTE
OR SOMETHING NEW?
IT'S THE REVIEW. YEAH.
I THOUGHT I WAS MAKING HEADWAY.
EVERYONE WAS SMILING AT ME ALL DAY
AND THEN I GET OFF WORK
AND FIND OUT THAT THEY WROTE THIS...
ON MY CHEF'S HAT.
HEY, MAYBE THEY MEANT TO WRITE "QUIET, BITCH."
HEY, HONEY, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
FINE, JUST TRYING TO BE NICE.
I HAVE NOT BEEN PICKED ON THIS MUCH
SINCE I WAS IN KINDERGARTEN
AND THEY HAD TO BRING IN SOMEONE FROM JUNIOR HIGH
TO DO THE SEESAW WITH ME.
AW...
THEY'RE DOING EVERYTHING THEY CAN TO MAKE ME QUIT.
IF IT WERE ANY OTHER JOB, I WOULD
BUT THIS IS SOMETHING
I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR MY WHOLE LIFE.
HONEY, YOU'RE THE BOSS.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST YELL AT THEM?
OR FIRE THEM?
I WOULD LOVE TO, BUT I CAN'T.
YOU KNOW I'M NOT GOOD AT CONFRONTATION.
YOU KNOW WHAT YOU COULD DO?
I REMEMBER READING ABOUT THIS DIRECTOR--
I THINK IT WAS ORSON WELLES--
WHO, AT THE BEGINNING OF A MOVIE, WOULD HIRE SOMEBODY
JUST SO HE COULD FIRE THEM IN FRONT OF EVERYBODY.
THEN THEY WOULD ALL KNOW WHO WAS BOSS.
HEY, MON, I'M NOT DOING ANYTHING.
WHY DON'T YOU
FIRE ME?
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
DO YOU KNOW HOW TO WAITER?
GOOD ENOUGH TO GET FIRED.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE HIRED.
HEY. OH.
THAT MUST BE WHY I GOT FIRED LAST WEEK.
DOES THIS ORSON WELLES GUY DIRECT BURGER KING COMMERCIALS?
YES.
I SAY, DREW
ARE YOU SEEING ANYBODY RIGHT NOW?
UH, UH, I'M NOT ASKING FOR ME. UH...
I'M, I'M NOT, I'M NOT GAY.
I'M NOT ASKING YOU OUT.
I I I'M NOT GAY.
I DIDN'T THINK YOU WERE GAY.
I DO NOW.
SEE, MY FRIEND, MY FRIEND, RACHEL
SHE WANTS TO BE SET UP.
AH. I JUST GOT OUT OF A BIG RELATIONSHIP.
I'M NOT LOOKING FOR ANYTHING SERIOUS.
OH, WELL, YOU KNOW
THAT MIGHT BE OKAY.
EVEN IF IT WAS JUST KIND OF A FLING
THAT MIGHT BE ALL RIGHT WITH RACHEL.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
IS THIS "HOT RACHEL THAT YOU TOOK
TO THE CHRISTMAS PARTY" RACHEL?
OH, BY THE WAY, THAT IS HER FULL NAME.
OH, WOW. I'M FREE FOR HER.
WAIT A SECOND.
I DIDN'T SAY I WASN'T FREE.
WHY DON'T WE
TALK THIS OVER
AT THE RANGER GAME TOMORROW?
HOLD ON.
YOU KNOW, I JUST GOT A BOX OF CUBANS.
MAYBE I BRING THEM BY YOUR OFFICE
AROUND, UH, 5:00?
WELL, THAT'S A LITTLE LATER
THAN I, UH, GENERALLY CARE TO STAY
BUT SURE.
MAYBE, BEFORE THE GAME
WE CAN ENJOY SOME EIGHT YEAR OLD SMALL BATCH BASIL HAYDENS.
WELL, I DON'T REALLY KNOW WHAT THAT IS
BUT THAT'S A PRETTY NICE JACKET.
I KIND OF LIKE THAT TIE, TOO.
KEEP YOUR PANTS ON, MAN.
HEY, YOU GUYS, I'M WRITING A HOLIDAY SONG FOR EVERYONE.
DO YOU WANT TO HEAR IT?
YEAH. YES.
OKAY.
??
?? HAPPY HANUKKAH, MONICA
?? MAY YOUR CHRISTMAS BE SNOWY , JOEY ??
?? HAPPY NEW YEAR, CHANDLER AND ROSS ??
?
?? SPIN THE DREIDEL, RACHEL. ?
PHEEBS, IT'S GREAT.
OH, YAY!
BUT YOU KNOW, UH...
"RACHEL" DOESN'T RHYME WITH "DREIDEL."
I KNOW, BUT IT'S SO HARD.
NOTHING RHYMES WITH YOUR STUPID NAME.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
LOTS OF THINGS RHYME WITH RACHEL.
BAGEL, MALE, JAIL, BAIL, CABLE
MAY POLE...
ALL GOOD. THANKS.
DO YOU MAYBE HAVE A NICKNAME
THAT'S EASIER TO RHYME?
DIDN'T YOUR DAD
USED TO CALL YOU "PUMPKIN?"
OH, YEAH. PUMPKIN? YEAH?
BUT DID HE EVER CALL YOU, LIKE, "BOODOLPH?"
HELLO, CHILDREN.
HAVE I GOT THE 50 GUYS FOR YOU!
REALLY?
I SHOWED THEM THIS PICTURE OF YOU
AND GUYS WERE BUYING ME DRINKS
GIVING ME STUFF.
KNICKS TONIGHT?
SURE. WHERE ARE THE SEATS?
WHEREVER. I'VE GOT, LIKE, 20.
SO, WILL I LIKE ANY OF THESE GUYS?
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M GOING TO, UH...
I'M GOING TO PLAY THE FIELD JUST A LITTLE BIT MORE.
CHANDLER...
GUYS ARE SIGNING OVER THEIR 401s TO ME.
YOU WORK WITH ROBOTS?
YES.
OKAY, THERE IS THIS ONE GUY, PATRICK.
HE'S REALLY NICE, HE'S FUNNY, HE'S A SWIMMER.
OH, I LIKE SWIMMERS' BODIES.
AND HIS FATHER
INVENTED THAT MAGNETIC STRIP ON CREDIT CARDS.
OH! I LIKE CREDIT CARDS.
SEE? NOT BAD
AT THIS "FIXING UP" THING, HUH?
SO, WHAT DOES HE DO?
HE WORKS IN THE FINE FOODS DIVISION.
YOUR COMPANY HAS A FINE FOODS DIVISION?
IT'S A BIG COMPANY.
I... IF YOU...
NOW, WAIT A SECOND.
YOU MAKE FOOD AND ROBOTS?
NO.
NO, THE ROBOTS JUST WORK FOR THEM.
ALL RIGHT, I'M GOING TO GO TO WORK.
DOES ANYBODY HAVE A PROBLEM WITH THAT?
YEAH, LADY, I DO.
I GOT
A PROBLEM WITH THAT.
YOU WANT A PROBLEM?
I'LL GIVE YOU A PROBLEM.
OH, WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO, FIRE ME?
YOU BET YOUR ASS I'M GOING TO FIRE YOU.
SEE YOU LATER.
THANKS.
OH, WOW, I SHOULD GET GOING.
I'VE GOT A DATE TONIGHT.
OH, YEAH? WITH WHO?
YOU KNOW THAT GIRL WHO LIVES IN POUGHKEEPSIE?
YEAH.
NOT HER.
YEAH, THIS IS SOMEONE ELSE I MET
AND I I CAN'T DECIDE BETWEEN THE TWO OF THEM.
YOU KNOW, THE ONE FROM POUGHKEEPSIE
EVEN THOUGH SHE'S A TWO HOUR TRAIN RIDE AWAY
IS REALLY PRETTY, REALLY SMART, AND A LOT OF FUN
BUT THIS OTHER GIRL...
WELL, SHE LIVES RIGHT UPTOWN.
WELL, SHE'S...
WELL, SHE'S, SHE'S JUST AS PRETTY.
I GUESS SHE'S SMART.
SHE'S NOT FUN.
IF SHE'S NO FUN
WHY DO YOU WANT TO DATE HER AT ALL?
WELL, I WANT TO GIVE HER ANOTHER CHANCE, YOU KNOW?
SHE LIVES SO CLOSE.
AND, AT THE END OF THE DATE THE OTHER TIME
SHE SAID SOMETHING THAT WAS-- IF SHE WAS KIDDING--
WAS VERY FUNNY.
ON THE OTHER HAND
IF SHE WASN'T KIDDING, SHE'S NOT FUN, SHE'S STUPID
AND KIND OF A RACIST.
HEY. HEY.
HEY, MAN.
OOH, HOW WAS YOUR FIRST DAY WORKING AT THE RESTAURANT?
DAMN!
HEY. HEY.
OH, WHAT HAPPENED TO YOUR FANCY CHEF JACKET?
THEY BAKED IT.
I CAN'T TAKE THIS ANYMORE.
I'M GOING TO CALL A MEETING.
I'M GOING TO FIRE YOU TONIGHT.
YOU GOT IT.
OH, OH!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU'RE STILL A TINY BIT ON FIRE THERE.
OH... THANKS.
LISTEN, I THINK YOU GOT IT.
OH, CHANDLER!
YOU HAVE THE BEST TASTE IN MEN.
WELL, LIKE FATHER, LIKE SON.
PATRICK AND I HAD SUCH A GREAT TIME LAST NIGHT.
I MEAN, I THINK THIS
COULD TURN INTO SOMETHING SERIOUS.
REALLY? I THOUGHT YOU WEREN'T EVEN LOOKING
FOR SOMETHING SERIOUS.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE LOOKING FOR SOME KIND OF A FLING.
WELL, YOU KNOW, POSSIBLY.
YOU DIDN'T... TELL HIM THAT, THOUGH... RIGHT?
W'UH...
NO?
YOU TOLD THIS GUY THAT I WAS LOOKING FOR A FLING?!
YOU DON'T TELL THE GUY THAT!
I'D BE THRILLED IF I HEARD
THAT SOME HOT GIRL WAS JUST LOOKING TO GET...
OH, I SEE.
OH! BETWEEN YOU TELLING HIM I WANTED TO HAVE A FLING
AND ME PUTTING OUT ON THE FIRST DATE
OH, HE'S SO GOING TO GET THE WRONG IDEA!
JOEY, COULD YOU PASS THE CHEESE?
YEAH. LISTEN, I'D PREFER IT
IF YOU WOULDN'T
CALL ME JOEY.
SINCE I DON'T KNOW ANYONE HERE
I THOUGHT IT MIGHT BE FUN
TO TRY OUT A COOL WORK NICKNAME.
HEY, DRAGON.
HERE'S YOUR TIPS FROM MONDAY AND TUESDAY.
OH. LOOKS LIKE THERE'S, LIKE, 300 BUCKS IN THIS ONE.
YEAH, PEOPLE GET PRETTY GENEROUS
AROUND THE HOLIDAYS.
AND IT NEVER HURTS TO WEAR TIGHT TROUSERS.
OKAY.
WOULD THE WAITERS GATHER 'ROUND
TO HEAR TONIGHT'S SPECIALS?
FIRST, THERE'S A CHILEAN SEA BASS
PREPARED WITH A MANGO RELISH ON A BED...
WHY IS NOBODY WRITING THESE DOWN?
BECAUSE WE CAN REMEMBER THEM.
AND BECAUSE YOU'RE ALL GOING TO MAKE UP FAKE SPECIALS
AND MAKE ME COOK THEM
LIKE YOU DID THE OTHER NIGHT?
WELL, SURE, THAT, TOO.
OKAY. FORGET THE SPECIALS FOR A MINUTE.
UM, ALL RIGHT, HERE'S THE THING.
FOR THE LAST TWO WEEKS, I HAVE, UH...
TRIED REALLY HARD TO CREATE A POSITIVE ATMOSPHERE.
CAN'T HEAR YOU.
A POSITIVE ATMOSPHERE...
BUT I I'VE HAD IT UP TO HERE.
FROM NOW ON, IT IS GOING TO BE MY WAY...
OR THE HIGHWAY, ALL RIGHT?
DOES ANYBODY HAVE A PROBLEM WITH THAT?
HEY, NEW GUY?
I SAID...
DOES ANYBODY HAVE A PROBLEM WITH THAT?
NO, MA'AM.
HEY, HE HAS A NAME.
IT'S DRAGON.
YOU WANT TO KNOW YOUR NAME?
CHECK YOUR HAT.
WE DID THE HAT, RIGHT?
WHAT HAPPENED? I AM SO SORRY.
I WAS GOING TO DO IT. REALLY.
BUT THEN I WAS STANDING THERE
WITH $327 DOLLAR IN ONE HAND
AND $238 DOLLAR IN THE OTHER HAND
AND I WAS THINKING, "WOW.
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME SINCE I HAD..."
327 PLUS $238 DOLLAR.
JOEY, WE HAD A DEAL.
THAT'S WHY YOU'RE HERE.
I'VE GOT TO FIRE YOU.
AND I'VE GOT TO PAY RENT.
LOOK.
HOW ABOUT THIS?
YOU DON'T FIRE ME.
INSTEAD, I STAY HERE, I GAIN THEIR TRUST
AND THEY'LL START LISTENING TO ALL THE NICE THINGS
I'VE BEEN SAYING ABOUT YOU.
WHAT KIND OF THINGS YOU BEEN SAYING?
NOTHING YET.
THEY REALLY HATE YOU
AND I WANT TO FIT IN.
?? HAPPY, HAPPY HANUKKAH ??
?
?? CHANDLER AND MONICA ?
?? MERRY, MERRY... ?
OOH, YOU KNOW... YOU KNOW WHAT, PHEEBS?
I'M NOT JEWISH, SO...
SO ROSS DOESN'T REALLY DECORATE HIS TREE WITH FLOSS
BUT YOU DON'T HEAR HIM COMPLAINING, DO YOU? GOD!
WHAT?
BAD DREAM?
I WASN'T SLEEPING.
OH, YEAH?
THEN WHAT WAS PHOEBE'S SONG ABOUT?
THE ONE WITH THE CAT.
I GOT TO GO.
I GOT ANOTHER DATE.
OH, SO DID YOU PICK ONE YET?
NO.
IT TURNS OUT THE ONE FROM UPTOWN WAS MAKING A JOKE
BUT IT WAS A DIFFERENT JOKE THAN I THOUGHT.
IT WASN'T THAT FUNNY.
SO I'M STILL TORN.
YOU DON'T REALLY LIKE THE ONE UPTOWN
AND YOU'RE TOO EXHAUSTED FROM DATING THE ONE IN POUGHKEEPSIE
SO I SAY YOU END THEM BOTH.
TAKE A TRAIN UP TO POUGHKEEPSIE AND YOU BREAK UP WITH HER
AND, ON YOUR WAY BACK, YOU BREAK UP WITH UPTOWN
AND THEN, BY THE TIME YOU GET HOME TONIGHT
YOU'RE DONE.
YOU KNOW WHAT? YOU'RE RIGHT.
THANK YOU.
YEAH. I HAD A SIMILAR PROBLEM WHEN I LIVED IN PRAGUE.
PRAGUE?
SO MUCH YOU DON'T KNOW.
CHANDLER
PATRICK JUST ENDED THINGS WITH ME.
DID YOU OR DID YOU NOT TELL HIM
THAT I WAS LOOKING FOR A SERIOUS RELATIONSHIP?
I DID! I ABSOLUTELY DID!
YOU IDIOT!
I'M SURE YOU'RE RIGHT, BUT WHY?
YOU DON'T TELL A GUY
THAT YOU'RE LOOKING FOR A SERIOUS RELATIONSHIP.
YOU DON'T TELL THE GUY THAT!
NOW YOU SCARED HIM AWAY.
OH, MAN, I AM SORRY.
I AM SO, SO SORRY.
YOU KNOW, YOU SHOULD NEVER BE ALLOWED TO TALK TO PEOPLE.
I KNOW! I KNOW!
NOW I'M RIGHT BACK WHERE I STARTED.
OH, THIS SUCKS.
BEING ALONE SUCKS!
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU'RE GOING TO MEET SOMEBODY.
YOU'RE A GREAT CATCH.
WHEN I WAS TELLING ALL THOSE GUYS ABOUT YOU
I DIDN'T HAVE TO LIE ONCE.
REALLY?
YEAH.
YOU GRADUATED MAGNA CUM LAUDE, RIGHT?
NO.
AW, IT DOESN'T MATTER.
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I GOT TWO TICKETS TO TONIGHT'S RANGER GAME.
YOU WANT TO COME WITH ME?
CUTE GUYS IN LITTLE SHORTS?
SURE.
WELL, ACTUALLY, IT'S A HOCKEY TEAM
SO IT'S ANGRY CANADIANS WITH NO TEETH.
WELL, THAT SOUNDS FUN, TOO.
THANK YOU.
OKAY.
HAVE YOU EVER BEEN WITH A WOMAN?
WHAT?
CHANDLER, WHAT IS THE MATTER WITH YOU?
SO THERE IS NO GOOD TIME TO ASK THAT QUESTION.
THE STATION IS POUGHKEEPSIE.
POUGHKEEPSIE.
ROSS?
WAKE UP.
ROS... ROSS!
ROSS! ROSS!
I NEED MORE SWORDFISH.
CAN YOU GET ME SOME MORE SWORDFISH?
I DON'T SPEAK ENGLISH.
YOU DID A MINUTE AGO.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO TELL YA.
FINE.
OKAY, VERY FUNNY.
CAN SOMEBODY LET ME OUT, PLEASE?
COME ON, I'M COLD!
AND COVERED IN MARINARA SAUCE!
COME ON, LET ME OUT!
YOU FOUND THAT HANDLE, DID YA?
THAT'S NOT FUNNY.
WELL, THAT'S NOT TRUE.
I'M A GOOD PERSON
AND I'M A GOOD CHEF
AND I DON'T DESERVE TO HAVE MARINARA SAUCE ALL OVER ME.
IF YOU WANT ME TO QUIT THIS BAD
ALL YOU HAVE TO...
HEY! CHEF GELLER.
YOU KNOW THAT LITTLE SPEECH YOU MADE THE OTHER DAY?
WELL, I GOT A PROBLEM WITH IT.
YOU DO?
YOU BET I DO.
I JUST, UH...
WASN'T LISTENING THEN, IS ALL.
WELL, IF YOU WANT A PROBLEM
I'LL GIVE YOU A PROBLEM.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO, FIRE ME?
YOU BET YOUR ASS I'M GOING TO FIRE YOU.
NOW, GET OUT OF MY KITCHEN!
GET OUT!
ALL RIGHT
ANYBODY ELSE GOT A PROBLEM?
HOW ABOUT YOU, CHUCKLES?
YOU THINK THIS IS FUNNY NOW?
NO.
HOW ABOUT IF I DANCE AROUND
ALL COVERED IN SAUCE, HUH?
YOU THINK IT'S FUNNY NOW?
NO. IT'S REALLY GOOD.
GOOD.
NOW, TAKE THOSE SALADS TO TABLE FOUR
AND YOU, GET THE SWORDFISH
AND YOU...
GET A HAIRCUT.
LAST STOP, MONTREAL.
THE STOP IS MONTREAL.
WHAT?
I MADE A BET WITH MYSELF THAT YOU HAD BEAUTIFUL EYES.
NOW THAT I SEE THEM, I WIN.
WHAT?
WE'RE AT MY STOP
BUT WOULD YOU LIKE TO HAVE COFFEE?
ARE WE REALLY IN MONTREAL?
YES, WE ARE.
SO, COFFEE?
COFFEE SOUNDS GREAT.
WAIT. SO, YOU LIVE IN MONTREAL?
NO, BUT IT'S JUST A TWO HOUR FERRY RIDE TO NOVA SCOTIA.
WELL, I SHOULD HAVE THOUGHT ABOUT MY WIFE AND KIDS
BEFORE I TALKED BACK TO CHEF GELLER.
THANKS.
YEP, LOOKS LIKE IT'S GOING TO BE A LEAN CHRISTMAS
AT THE DRAGON HOUSE THIS YEAR.
ENOUGH.
OKAY.
LEAN, LEAN, LEAN.
SO, THIS IS A VERY SPECIAL
HOLIDAY SONG THAT I WROTE
FOR SOME VERY IMPORTANT PEOPLE TO ME.
?? WENT TO THE STORE, SAT ON SANTA'S LAP ??
?? ASKED HIM TO BRING MY FRIENDS ALL KINDS OF CRAP ??
?? HE SAID ALL YOU NEED IS TO WRITE THEM A SONG ??
?? THEY HAVEN'T HEARD IT YET SO DON'T TRY TO SING ALONG ? ?
?? NO, DON'T SING ALONG ??
?? MONICA, MONIC A ??
?? HAVE A HAPPY HANUKKAH ? ?
?? SAW SANTA CLAUS ??
?? HE SAID HELLO TO ROSS ? ?
?? AND PLEASE TELL JOEY ??
?? CHRISTMAS WILL BE SNOWY...  ??
?? AND RACHEL AND CHANDLER ? ?
?? HAS A... HANDLER. ??
HAPPY HOLIDAYS, EVERYBODY!