HEY!
HEY. WOW, IT IS TRUE WHAT THEY SAY
PREGNANT BELLIES LOOK LIKE A DRUM.
HA, HA.
NO, IT'S JUST, I'M SO PREGNANT
THAT MY GUITAR DOESN'T FIT ANYMORE
SO I THOUGHT, TILL I'M NOT
I'M JUST GOING  TO PLAY ALL MY SONGS
ON THIS DRUM.
IT SOUNDS REALLY COOL.
OH, YEAH?
LISTEN, LISTEN.
OKAY.
?? SMELLY CAT, SMELLY CAT ??
?? WHAT ARE THEY FEEDING YOU? ??
WOW, PHEEBS, THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
I KNOW, I KNOW! AND I'VE ONLY BEEN PLAYING
FOR, LIKE, AN HOUR.
PHOEBE. PHOEBE, HI.
HI. HI. HEY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
ACTUALLY, I CAME DOWN
TO ASK YOU A BIG FAVOR.
OH. WELL, DON'T TELL ME
YOU WANT TO KEEP MORE OF YOUR STUFF
IN MY UTERUS.
NO, NO, NO.
OH.
...
OKAY, NOW, SEE
I WANT TO NAME THE GIRL BABY "LESLIE"
AND, UM, FRANK WANTS
TO NAME ONE OF THE BOY BABIES...
"FRANK JR., JR."
WOULDN'T THAT BE "FRANK THE THIRD"?
DON'T GET ME STARED.
ANYWAY, UM, SINCE THERE ARE THREE BABIES
AND, UM, WE BOTH GOT TO PUT OUR NAMES IN
WE WOULD BE TRULY HONORED
IF YOU WOULD NAME THE OTHER BOY BABY.
OH, WOW!
THAT'S SO NICE.
OH! OH! "COUGAR."
YOU THINK ABOUT IT.
YEAH.
I LEFT A BRA DRYING ON THE SHOWER ROD.
YOU DON'T THINK YOUR SON WILL THINK IT'S YOURS
AND BE HORRIBLY TRAUMATIZED?
HEY, MOMMY CAN HAVE A WIFE
DADDY CAN HAVE A BRA.
OH, IT'S TIME TO GO.
OH, NO, NO, NO.
SEE, THAT THAT CLOCK'S A LITTLE FAST.
UH, WE... WE STILL HAVE 17 MINUTES.
HUH. WHAT CAN WE DO IN 17 MINUTES... TWICE?
WOW, THAT'S AMBITIOUS.
MMM...
OKAY, YOU CAN IGNORE THAT. IT'S...
THAT'S CAROL WITH YOUR SON.
UH, BELIEVE ME
WHEN HE'S OLDER, HE'LL UNDERSTAND.
ROSS?
I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
HELLO! HI.
HELLO. HELLO.
HI. HEY.
EMILY, THIS IS CAROL AND SUSAN.
IT'S SO NICE TO FINALLY MEET YOU.
YOU, TOO.
SUSAN'S SHOOTING A COMMERCIAL
IN LONDON NEXT WEEK.
YEAH. I'M SO EXCITED.
I'VE NEVER BEEN THERE.
I'LL SHOW YOU AROUND.
THAT'D BE GREAT.
ALSO, I WAS HOPING TO CATCH A SHOW.
SO, IF YOU CAN MAKE ANY SUGGESTIONS...
THERE'S TONS OF TERRIFIC STUFF.
I'LL GO WITH YOU.
AH.
OH, I'M SORRY.
OH, WOW.
OH, LOOK AT YOU TWO, BONDING
MAKING US LATE FOR THE AIRPORT, SO...
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
HE'S FINE. HE'S FINE.
IT'S JUST US GETTING ALONG
IS DIFFICULT FOR HIM
BECAUSE HE DOESN'T LIKE ME.
WHAT... OH...
COME ON, THAT'S, THAT'S... IT'S TRUE.
HOW DID WE... LOSE?
HI. HEY.
HEY, DO WE HAVE A BABY NAME YET?
OH, NO. IT'S SO HARD.
I WENT THROUGH THIS WHOLE BOOK AND FOUND NOTHING.
I WANT A NAME THAT'S REALLY, LIKE, YOU KNOW
STRONG AND CONFIDENT, YOU KNOW, LIKE, LIKE "EXXON."
WELL, IT CERTAINLY WORKED
FOR THAT VALDEZ KID.
OH, OH! PHEEBS, YOU WANT A STRONG NAME?
HOW ABOUT "THE HULK"?
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M I'M NOT SURE ABOUT "HULK"
BUT I LIKE THE IDEA OF A NAME STARTING WITH "THE."
OH, YOU WANT A GOOD NAME?
GO WITH "JOEY."
JOEY IS YOUR PAL.
JOEY IS YOUR BUDDY.
"WHERE IS EVERYBODY?"
"WELL, THEY'RE HANGING OUT WITH JOEY."
IF YOU'RE GOING TO DO THAT--
IF YOU'RE GOING TO NAME HIM "JOEY"--
YOU SHOULD NAME HIM
"CHANDLER."
OH, COME ON-- CHANDLER'S FUNNY
HE'S SOPHISTICATED, AND HE'S VERY LOVABLE
ONCE YOU GET TO KNOW HIM.
OH, WELL,  HEY
JOEY'S LOVABLE, TOO
BUT THE THING ABOUT JOEY IS
IF YOU NEED HIM, HE'LL BE THERE.
WELL, CHANDLER WILL BE THERE FOR YOU, TOO.
I MEAN, HE MIGHT BE A LITTLE LATE, BUT...
BUT HE'LL BE THERE
AND HE'LL BRING YOU SOME COLD SODA
IF WHAT YOU NEED HIM FOR IS THAT YOU'RE REALLY HOT.
HEY, WHAT DO YOU SAY?
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
WELL, I... I LIKE THE IDEA
OF NAMING HIM AFTER SOMEONE I LOVE
AND "JOEY" AND "CHANDLER" ARE BOTH GREAT NAMES...
BUT... ALL RIGHT, I DON'T...
MAYBE I WILL JUST NAME HIM "THE HULK."
I KNEW I SHOULDN'T HAVE MENTIONED IT.
THAT'S WHAT I WANTED TO NAME MY KID.
IF YOU WERE HOPING TO SLEEP WITH JOSHUA
FOR THE FIRST TIME TONIGHT
WHICH ONE OF THESE WOULD YOU WANT TO BE WEARING?
YOU KNOW WHAT? IT REALLY CREEPS ME OUT
CHOOSING OTHER PEOPLE'S SEX CLOTHES.
OH. I'M SORRY.
I'M JUST SO EXCITED.
I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR THIS FOR MONTHS.
GOT MY HAIR COLORED.
GOT NEW SHEETS.
MAKING HIM A VERY FANCY MEAL.
MM HMM...
WHAT AM I MAKING HIM, BY THE WAY?
WELL, YOU'RE MAKING HIM A FRISEE SALAD
WITH GOAT CHEESE AND PINE NUTS
WILD RICE, ROASTED ASPARAGUS
AND SALMON EN CROUTE.
I THOUGHT I WAS MAKING HIM FILET MIGNON.
YEAH, YOU WERE, BUT THEN YOU DECIDED TO MAKE SALMON
BECAUSE YOU HAD SOME LEFT OVER AT THE RESTAURANT
AND THEN YOU REALIZED IF YOU BITCHED ABOUT IT
THEN YOU WOULD STOP COOKING
AND YOU WOULD HAVE TO MAKE YOUR FAMOUS BAKED POTATO
AND DIET COKE.
WOW, I REALLY GET CRABBY WHEN I COOK.
I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU'RE GOING
THROUGH ALL THIS TROUBLE ANYWAY-- HE'S A GUY.
YOU COULD ACTUALLY SERVE THE POTATO
AND HE'D STILL WANT TO HAVE SEX WITH YOU.
YEAH? WELL, THAT IS NOT HOW I OPERATE.
WE GOT TO GET A NEW GAME.
HEY.
HEY. HEY. HEY.
SO, UH, EMILY CALLED LAST NIGHT.
AND NOW YOU'RE GIVING ME THE MESSAGE?
TURNS OUT THAT EMILY IS JUST CRAZY ABOUT SUSAN. YEAH.
THEY'RE GOING TO THE THEATER TOGETHER...
THEY'RE GOING TO DINNER...
THEY'RE GOING HORSE BACK RIDING.
GOD, SUSAN IS SO FUN.
LOOK, THIS IS JUST A LITTLE TOO FAMILIAR, OKAY?
FOR FOR, LIKE, SIX MONTHS BEFORE CAROL AND I SPLIT UP
ALL I HEARD WAS, "MY FRIEND SUSAN IS IS SO SMART."
"MY FRIEND SUSAN IS SO FUNNY."
"MY FRIEND SUSAN IS SO GREAT."
YOU ACTUALLY THINK
THAT SOMETHING COULD HAPPEN
BETWEEN EMILY AND SUSAN?
HEY, THEY'RE GOING TO THE GYM TOGETHER.
TWO WOMEN?
STRETCHING?
YOU KNOW, THEY TAKE
A STEAM TOGETHER, THINGS GET A LITTLE PLAYFUL...
DIDN'T YOU SEE PERSONAL BEST?
NO, BUT I'M GOING TO.
HI! HI! YOU'RE CRAZY.
THIS IS EMILY.
EMILY IS STRAIGHT.
HOW DO YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, WE THOUGHT CAROL WAS STRAIGHT
BEFORE I MARRIED HER.
YEAH, DEFINITELY
I DON'T LIKE THE NAME "ROSS."
WHAT A WEIRD WAY TO KICK ME WHEN I'M DOWN.
NO, NO. I JUST... I MEANT FOR THE BABY.
OH.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH "ROSS"?
WELL, IT'S JUST, YOU KNOW
SOMETHING LIKE THIS WOULD NEVER HAPPEN
TO, LIKE, THE HULK, YOU KNOW.
ACTUALLY, THAT- THAT'S NOT TRUE.
IN THE INCREDIBLE HULK, UH, NUMBER 72
DR. BRUCE BANNER FOUND FOUND...
YOU KNOW... NEVER MIND.
MY GIRLFRIEND'S A LESBIAN.
SO, I DECIDED
I'M DEFINITELY GOING TO GO
WITH EITHER "JOEY" OR "CHANDLER."
OH!
OH, OH, OH, OH!
YOU GOT TO PICK "JOEY."
I MEAN, NAME ONE FAMOUS PERSON NAMED "CHANDLER."
RAYMOND CHANDLER.
SOMEONE YOU DIDN'T MAKE UP.
OKAY, THERE ARE NO FAMOUS "JOEYS," EXCEPT FOR...
JOEY BUTTAFUOCO.
YEAH, THAT GUY REALLY HURT US.
AH. YE
WELL, HOW ABOUT A COMPROMISE, THEN, OKAY?
WHAT IF IT'S, YOU KNOW... "CHANOEY"?
OKAY, LOOK-- "JOEY"?
COME ON, THINK ABOUT IT.
FIRST OF ALL, HE'LL NEVER BE PRESIDENT.
I MEAN, THERE'S NEVER GOING TO BE
A PRESIDENT JOEY.
ALL RIGHT, MAN, I DIDN'T WANT TO BRING THIS UP
BUT "CHANDLER" IS THE STUPIDEST NAME
I EVER HEARD IN MY LIFE.
IT'S NOT EVEN A NAME.
IT'S BARELY EVEN A WORD, OKAY?
IT'S KIND OF LIKE "CHANDELIER"
BUT IT'S NOT.
AND THEN, YOU PUT IT TOGETHER WITH "BING"
AND FORGET ABOUT IT.
IT'S A STUPID, STUPID NON NAME.
WOW, YOU'RE... YOU'RE RIGHT.
I HAVE A HORRIBLE, HORRIBLE NAME.
I'M SORRY, MAN. I DIDN'T...
I'M I'M SORRY. I'M SORRY.
SO, I GUESS IT'S "JOEY," THEN.
THIS IS SO NICE.
THANK YOU FOR DOING THIS.
OH, PLEASE. COOKING SOOTHES ME.
SO, DIG IN.
RIGHT. OH, IT  ALL LOOKS SO GOOD.
MMM.
MMM!
OH, MY GOD.
OH, I KNOW.
MY GOD, THIS IS SO...
THIS RICE IS SO...
I AM SO GOOD.
BEHIND YOU.
OH, YEAH, SORRY.
THEY USED TO LIVE HERE
AND SOMETIMES THEY MIGRATE BACK OVER.
IS THERE, UH... IS THERE SOME WAY
THAT THEY COULD, UH... NOT BE HERE?
IT'S JUST THAT, UH, FARM BIRDS REALLY KIND OF FREAK ME OUT.
YEAH, SURE, OKAY. OKAY.
OKAY, GREAT.
COME ON. SHOO. SHOO.
HERE WE GO. HERE WE GO. WHOA!
SHOO. SHOO.
ALL RIGHT. WHOA!
OH, SORRY. COME HERE.
GOOD. THERE YOU GO.
OKAY.
HEY, HOW'D YOU DO THAT?
COME ON.
COME HERE.
ALL GONE.
SO, FARM BIRDS, HUH?
YEAH. IT'S, UH, IT'S MY ONLY WEIRD THING, I SWEAR.
AND I I I WOULD'VE TOLD YOU ABOUT IT
BUT I DIDN'T KNOW THAT THEY WOULD... BE HERE.
OH, OKAY.
SO, ALL RIGHT...
OKAY.
SO, CAN I SERVE YOU A LITTLE OF...
WHAT? WHAT'S...? WHAT?
NOTHING. I, UH...
IT'S JUST THAT I KNOW THAT THEY'RE STILL OUT THERE.
BUT THEY'RE ACROSS THE HALL.
I MEAN, THAT'S TWO DOORS AWAY.
IT'S GOING TO TAKE THEM A LONG TIME
TO PECK THEIR WAY BACK OVER HERE.
HEY, THAT'S THAT'S NOT FUNNY.
UH...
OKAY, YOU KNOW...
WOULD YOU FEEL BETTER
IF WE WENT SOMEPLACE ELSE?
I MEAN, WE COULD PACK ALL THIS STUFF UP
AND, YOU KNOW, GO TO YOUR APARTMENT.
OH, THEY'RE WORKING ON IT THIS WEEK.
IT'S A TOTAL MESS.
BUT I'M STAYING  AT MY PARENTS' HOUSE.
WE COULD GO THERE.
YOUR PARENTS?
THEY'RE OUT OF TOWN.
OH.
YEAH, IT'S A HUGE PLACE, AND AND IT'S GOT
THIS GORGEOUS VIEW OF THE PARK.
IT'D BE VERY , VERY ROMANTIC.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
YEAH, THAT WORKS.
YEAH, THEY THEY CAN SMELL THE FEAR.
HEY. HI.
HOW'S BEN?
WELL, I ASKED HIM IF HE WANTED TO EAT
HE SAID, "NO."
I ASKED HIM IF HE WANTED TO SLEEP
I ASKED HIM WHAT HE WANTED TO DO
HE SAID, "NO," SO HE'S SWEEPING.
HEY, BUDDY.
HEY.
SO, UM...
ANY WORD FROM SUSAN?
OH, YEAH. SHE SAID
SHE'S HAVING SO MUCH FUN WITH EMILY.
UH HUH, UH HUH.
UH, BY THE BY, DID IT, UH...
DID IT EVER OCCUR TO YOU THAT, I DON'T KNOW
MAYBE THEY MIGHT BE HAVING A LITTLE TOO MUCH FUN?
WHAT'S "TOO MUCH FUN"?
YOU KNOW, THE KIND OF FUN YOU AND SUSAN HAD
WHEN WE WERE MARRIED.
OH, MY GOD, YOU ARE SO PARANOID.
AM I?
YES.
AMI?
I CAN'T SPEAK FOR EMILY
BUT SUSAN IS IN A LOVING, COMMITTED RELATIONSHIP.
UH HUH, CAROL, SO WERE WE.
ALL RIGHT, JUST IMAGINE, FOR A MOMENT
THAT SUSAN MEETS SOMEONE, AND THEY REALLY HIT IT OFF.
SAY THEY'RE COMING BACK FROM THE THEATER
AND THEY STOP AT A PUB FOR A COUPLE OF DRINKS.
THEY'RE LAUGHING, YOU KNOW.
SOMEONE INNOCENTLY TOUCHES SOMEONE ELSE.
THERE'S ELECTRICITY.
IT'S NEW, IT'S EXCITING.
ARE YOU TELLING ME
THERE ISN'T EVEN THE SLIGHTEST POSSIBILITY
OF SOMETHING HAPPENING?
MAYBE.
OH, MY GOD!
I DIDN'T REALLY BELIEVE IT UNTIL YOU SAID IT!
...AND EVEN THOUGH NONE OF THE KIDS BELIEVED ME
I SWEAR TO GOD, THAT DUCK PUSHED ME.
YEAH.
WOW, THIS PLACE IS FABULOUS!
LET ME SHOW YOU AROUND.
THIS IS THE DOWNSTAIRS LIVING ROOM...
WHAT? THERE'S TWO LIVING ROOMS?
GOD, GROWING UP HERE
THIS PLACE MUST HAVE BEEN A REAL BABE MAGNET.
YEAH, WELL, IT WOULD HAVE BEEN
BUT MY PARENTS JUST MOVED HERE.
OH, WELL, YOU SHOULD KNOW
THIS PLACE IS A REAL BABE MAGNET.
WANT TO MAKE OUT?
HERE'S AN IDEA.
WHY DON'T I PUT THE FOOD IN THE FRIDGE
AND WE CAN EAT IT LATER?
THAT SOUNDS LIKE A PLAN.
UM, IS THERE A PLACE THAT I COULD GO FRESHEN UP?
YEAH, YEAH.
UM, JUST DOWN THE HALL
AND, UH, SECOND DOOR TO YOUR LEFT.
OH, HI, DARLING.
MOM, DAD! WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING HERE?
WE CUT THE TRIP SHORT.
FRANCE SUCKS!
UM, THIS MAY BE A LITTLE WEIRD
BUT I... I'VE GOT A DATE HERE.
WELL, SAY NO MORE.
WE'LL GRAB SOME FOOD AND TAKE IT UPSTAIRS
AND BE OUT OF YOUR HAIR.
OH, THAT'D BE GREAT.
SO, YOU DIDN'T GET TO ITALY?
YEP. SUCKS!
HI, YOU.
OH, MY GOD...
I KNOW.
I CAN DO MORE THAN COOK.
UH...
I LIKE HER.
SHE SEEMS SMART.
UH... RACHEL, MY PARENTS.
OH, SO NICE TO MEET YOU.
HI, RACHEL.
HELLO. HELLO.
OH, JOSHUA...
THAT $500 DOLLAR WAS FOR GROCERIES.
WHAT? TH TH THIS? NO.
OH, NO, THIS IS NOT...
THAT'S NOT WHAT... THAT'S NOT WHAT IT IS.
YOU SEE, OKAY, I WORK IN FASHION.
SEE, AND AND THIS IS A REAL DRESS, ACTUALLY.
IT IS... THEY'RE THEY'RE
WEARING IT IN MILAN.
IT'S TH... AND...
SEE, OH, PART OF MY JOB IS TO WEAR THE CLOTHES
AND THEN I SEE HOW PEOPLE RESPOND
AND THEN I REPORT BACK
TO MY SUPERIORS AT BLOOMINGDALE'S.
SO...
AND, OBVIOUSLY, IN, UH, IN IN THIS CASE
I AM AM GOING TO REPORT BACK
"U.S.A. NOT READY."
MAYBE IN L.A.
YES.
THERE YOU GO.
SO, HAVE YOU KIDS EATEN YET?
WELL, WE WERE GOING TO DO THAT AFTER.
I MEAN, UM...
NEXT.
WELL, WE'RE STARVING.
WHY DON'T WE GET SOMETHING TO EAT?
OH... YEAH.
WELL...
YEAH, NO USE WASTING THIS BABY
JUST LYING AROUND THE HOUSE.
SO... WE'LL GO EAT.
YEAH.
YOU'LL WEAR THAT.
WE'LL BE EATING AND, OF COURSE
YOU'LL BE... WEARING THAT.
DUDE, I AM SORRY ABOUT WHAT I SAID.
NOPE. NOPE. YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT IS A RIDICULOUS NAME.
IT'S NOT THAT BAD.
YES, IT IS.
FROM NOW ON, I HAVE NO FIRST NAME.
SO...
YOU'RE JUST BING?
I HAVE NO NAME.
ALL RIGHT, SO, WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSED TO CALL YOU?
OKAY, UH, FOR NOW, TEMPORARILY
YOU CAN CALL ME...
CLINT.
NO WAY ARE YOU COOL ENOUGH TO PULL OFF CLINT.
OKAY, SO, WHAT NAME AM I COOL ENOUGH TO PULL OFF?
UM... GENE.
IT'S CLINT.
IT'S CLINT!
SEE YOU LATER, GENE. BYE, GENE.
CLINT!
WHAT'S UP WITH GENE?
YOU WORE YOUR NIGHTIE
TO DINNER?
OH, YEAH.
AND, UH, THE BEST PART, THOUGH
WAS WHEN THE, UH, WAITER SPILLED WATER DOWN MY BACK.
I JUMPED UP AND MY BOOB POPPED OUT.
OH, MY GOD. OH, NO.
IT'S ALL RIGHT-- I GOT NICE BOOBS.
SO, I JUST PICKED UP A MESSAGE FROM EMILY.
SHE AND SUSAN ARE GOING TO A POETRY READING TOGETHER.
SO?
POETRY?
SUSAN'S GAY.
THEY'RE BEING GAY TOGETHER!
EMILY'S STRAIGHT.
OH, WAKE UP!
WOW...
CAROL REALLY MESSED YOU UP.
EXCUSE ME?
YEAH, SHE TURNED YOU
INTO THIS THIS THIS UNTRUSTING, CRAZY, JEALOUS SYCOPHANT.
ALL RIGHT, SO I DON'T KNOW WHAT "SYCOPHANT" MEANS
BUT THE REST IS RIGHT.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
I AM NOT A CRAZY, JEALOUS PERSON.
HUH.
WHAT?
SHE'S TOTALLY RIGHT.
WHEN WE WERE TOGETHER
YOU GOT ALL FREAKED OUT ABOUT MARK
AND THERE WAS NOTHING GOING ON.
THIS TOTALLY MAKES SENSE.
IT DOES NOT.
OL SURE IT DOES -- IN HIGH SCHO
YOU WEREN'T JEALOUS AT ALL
EVEN THOUGH ALL YOUR GIRLFRIENDS
WERE CHEATING ON YOU.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT
SO, UP UNTIL 92, 93, HE WAS VERY TRUSTING.
THEN 94 HIT, CAROL LEFT HIM
AND BAM, PARANOID CITY.
YEP. ABSOLUTELY.
ABSOLUTELY.
THIS IS SO MUCH FUN.
THIS IS NOT FUN!
ALL RIGHT, LOOK...
ALL WE'RE TRYING TO SAY IS
DON'T LET WHAT HAPPENED WITH CAROL
RUIN WHAT YOU'VE GOT WITH EMILY.
THE 92 ROSS WOULDN'T.
THANKS.
STILL THINK I WAS RIGHT
ABOUT THAT WHOLE MARK THING THOUGH.
WHA... YA... WHA... YOU KNOW WHAT?
I HOPE EMILY IS A LESBIAN.
DRUMROLL.
OKAY, OKAY...
ALL RIGHT.
HELP.
AM I A MARK OR A JOHN?
WELL, YOU'RE NOT TALL ENOUGH TO BE A MARK...
BUT YOU MIGHT MAKE A GOOD BARNEY.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, I'M SERIOUS, OKAY?
TOMORROW AT 3:30
I'M GOING DOWN TO THE COURTHOUSE.
YOU'LL ACTUALLY  GO THROUGH WITH THIS?
HEY, LOOK, THIS NAME HAS BEEN HOLDING ME BACK MY ENTIRE LIFE.
OKAY, IT'S PROBABLY WHY KIDS PICKED ON ME IN SCHOOL
AND WHY I NEVER DO WELL WITH WOMEN.
SO, AS OF 4:00 TOMORROW, I'M EITHER GOING TO BE
MARK JOHNSON OR JOHN MARKSON.
YOU'VE GOT PROBLEMS BECAUSE OF YOU, NOT YOUR NAME.
ALL RIGHT, THIS HAS GOT TO STOP.
CHANDLER IS A GREAT NAME.
IN FACT...
YES.
I'M... I'M SORRY.
I KNOW YOU REALLY WANTED ME
TO NAME THE BABY JOEY, BUT...
SO, I'M I'M GOING TO...
I'M GOING TO NAME THE BABY CHANDLER.
REALLY?
YEAH, BUT YOU HAVE TO KEEP THE NAME, TOO.
OKAY.
THANKS. OKAY.
YOU WANT TO HUG IT OUT?
YEAH.
YAY.
YAY. OH, YAY!
OKAY, I GOT TO GO TELL FRANK AND ALICE RIGHT NOW.
OOH.
BYE, PHEEBS.
OKAY, BYE.
Flight 004 is now arriving at Gate 17.
THAT'S NICE LUGGAGE.
YEAH, I WAS GOING TO SAY.
HEY!
HI! HI!
I MISSED YOU.
OH, I MISSED YOU, TOO.
HEY, THANKS
FOR EVERYTHING.
I HAD SUCH A GREAT TIME.
OH, SO DID I.
THERE'S NO TONGUE.