O. HELL
HEY.
WHOO HOO, CEREAL KILLER!
CEREAL KILLER?
COME ON, I SAY MORE DUMB THINGS BEFORE 9 A.M.
THAN MOST PEOPLE SAY ALL DAY.
UGH. WHAT?
NOTHING! I CAN'T FIND ANYTHING THAT I WANT TO EAT.
EVERYTHING MAKES ME NAUSEOUS.
BEING PREGNANT IS NO PIECE OF CAKE.
OOH, CAKE.
NO.
SEE?
OH, HONEY, I'M SORRY.
GOD... OOH!
WHAT IS THAT SMELL?
IT'S COMING FROM THE BATHROOM. OOH!
WOW, PREGNANCY DOES GIVE YOU SOME WEIRD CRAVINGS.
YEAH?
IT'S ME, PHOEBE.
THERE'S SOMETHING IN HERE I WANT TO EAT.
WHAT, WHAT...?
WHAT SMELLS SO GOOD?
IS IT THE SHAMPOO?
IT'S GUAVA.
NO!
EWW!
OH, WAIT, WAIT!
IS IT MY BOLOGNA SANDWICH?
YES. YES, YES, YES!
I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT THE BABY WANTS BOLOGNA.
THE BABY WANTS ME TO EAT MEAT!
I CAN'T EAT MEAT!
OH, WAIT, WAIT!
MAYBE IT'S THE PICKLE.
WHAT ARE YOU WRITING?
WELL, JOSHUA'S COMING IN TOMORROW
AND SINCE I DON'T HAVE THE GUTS TO ASK HIM OUT
I'M GOING TO SELL HIM A COAT
AND PUT THIS NOTE IN THE POCKET.
OH, YEAH?
"JOSHUA, GIVE ME A CALL SOMETIME.
"GUYS LIKE YOU...
NEVER GO OUT OF STYLE."
WHAT DID YOU THROW AWAY?
HI, GUYS.
HI.
HEY, WHAT HAVE YOU GUYS BEEN UP TO?
OH, WE WENT TO SEE A COLLECTION OF VICTORIAN DOOR KNOBS
AT THE COOPER HEWITT MUSEUM.
WITHOUT ME?!
YEAH. MY UNCLE DRAGGED US THERE
BUT IT ACTUALLY TURNED OUT TO BE REALLY INTERESTING.
THEY WERE SO ORNATE AND BEAUTIFUL.
I MEAN, LOOK AT THAT.
I DON'T KNOW HOW MUSEUMS WORK IN ENGLAND
BUT HERE, YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO TAKE STUFF.
I, UH, I GOT IT FROM THE GIFT SHOP.
THEY HAVE REALLY LAX SECURITY THERE.
IT'S A JOKE.
ANYONE FOR MORE TEA?
NO? JUST ME, THEN.
HEY, RINGO.
EVERY TIME EMILY'S AROUND, YOU TALK LIKE HER.
WOULD YOU PLEASE CUT IT OUT?
HO, HO, HO. I THINK YOU LIKE IT.
I THINK YOU CAN'T RESIST ME WHEN I DO IT.
YOU WANT TO EAT ME UP LIKE A CREAM PUMPET.
WHAT?
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, I DON'T KNOW ALL THE WORDS.
ALL RIGHT.
RIGHT. I'VE GOT TO BE OFF.
WELL, SEE YOU. BYE BYE, THEN.
BYE BYE, THEN.
HEY, SO YOU GUYS SEEM TO BE HAVING A GOOD TIME, HUH?
OH, YEAH.
SHE'S SHE'S AMAZING
AND AND SHE'S SO MUCH FUN, YOU KNOW?
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
WHEN I'M WITH HER,I'MFUN.
I DO THINGS LIKE LIKE RUN OFF TO VERMONT AND...
YOU GUYS SAW THE DOORKNOB.
I EVEN SIGNED UP FOR HELICOPTER CLASSES.
SHE'S LEAVING IN TWO DAYS.
I DON'T HAVE TO DO IT.
WOW. TWO DAYS.
YOU MUST BE BUMMED.
YEAH. SHE'S GOT TO GO BACK TO LONDON
BUT I'VE BEEN PREPARED FOR THIS FROM THE START.
WE BOTH KNEW WE HAD TWO WEEKS TOGETHER
AND THEN THAT'S IT, YOU KNOW?
HEY, THAT'S WHAT ALL MY RELATIONSHIPS ARE LIKE.
YES, BUT IN ROSS'S CASE
THEY BOTH KNOW IN TWO WEEKS THAT'S IT.
PHEEBS!
HEY!
OH, HELLO! HELLO!
I KNOW, I KNOW. YEAH.
SO, THE BABY IS TOTALLY CRAVING MEAT.
THIS AFTERNOON, I TRIED TRICKING IT.
I MADE IT A SOY BURGER
SO MAYBE IT WOULD THINK IT WAS GETTING MEAT
AND I GOT NAUSEOUS.
WELL, MAYBE THAT'S BECAUSE SOY BURGERS SUCK.
BUT I'M NO OBSTETRICIAN.
BEING PREGNANT IS HARD ON YOUR TUMMY.
HEY, BUT AT LEAST YOU GOT THAT COOL, "PREGNANT LADY GLOW."
OH, THAT'S SWEAT.
YOU THROW UP ALL MORNING.
YOU'LL HAVE THAT GLOW, TOO.
OKAY.
OH, UH, HERE'S THAT TRENCH COAT THAT YOU WANTED.
OH, GREAT, GREAT.
WOW. YEAH.
IT'S COMFORTABLE.
YEAH. MAN...
I COULD REALLY FLASH SOMEBODY IN THIS THING.
OH, NO, NO. THEY DON'T WANT YOU
TO PUT YOUR HANDS IN THE POCKETS
UNTIL YOU ARE OUT OF THE STORE.
WHY NOT?
WELL, BECAUSE...
WE GET A LOT OF...
YOU KNOW, THEY RUIN IT FOR EVERYBODY.
I KNOW.
I WORE THAT CASHMERE SWEATER ON A DATE LAST NIGHT.
OH. YEAH.
IT WAS THE FIRST DATE SINCE THE DIVORCE.
WELL, CONGRATULATIONS.
SO, DO YOU LOVE HER?
NO, NO, NO.
SHE'S NICE, BUT IT JUST MADE ME REALIZE
I'M JUST NOT READY TO... TO BE DATING, YOU KNOW?
HUH.
WELL...
UH...
THAT'S, UH...
THAT'S INTERESTING.
HEY, WHOA. HEY...
WHAT WAS THAT?
OH, IT'S JUST AN ANTI THEFT DEVICE.
THEN, UH, WH WHAT'S THIS?
WELL, YOU NEED THAT, YOU NEED THAT, TOO
BECAUSE, OBVIOUSLY, A THIEF COULD JUST TEAR THIS RIGHT UP.
OH. LISTEN, WE HAVE TO HAVE A PARTY TONIGHT.
ACTUALLY, WE HAVE TO HAVE ONE IN FIVE MINUTES
SO EVERYBODY CANCEL YOUR PLANS.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
WE HAVE TO HAVE A SURPRISE BON VOYAGE PARTY FOR EMILY
BUT IT'S ACTUALLY FOR JOSHUA.
THAT SUCKS.
NOBODY'S EVER THROWN ME A BON VOYAGE EMILY PARTY.
LOOK. HE SAID HE'S NOT READY TO DATE
SO I HAD TO INVITE HIM TO A PARTY
IF I WANTED TO SEE HIM OUTSIDE OF WORK
AND NOW I HAVE CREATED
THE PERFECT OPPORTUNITY TO SEDUCE HIM.
WELL, AS MUCH AS I'D LIKE TO MEET JOSH
AND WARN HIM...
EMILY AND I AREN'T GOING TO BE HERE.
I MEAN, SHE'S GOING TO COME BY FIRST TO SAY GOOD BYE
AND THEN I'VE GOT A WHOLE SPECIAL EVENING PLANNED
SO, SORRY, NO PARTY.
AW!
HELLO.
SURPRISE!
SURPRISE! SURPRISE!
NO ONE'S EVER THROWN ME A SURPRISE PARTY BEFORE!
WELL, IT WAS ALL ROSS'S IDEA.
YOU'RE SO SWEET...
AND I'M SO SURPRISED.
YOU REALLY DIDN'T KNOW?
WHY ARE YOU OVER HERE
IF JOSHUA'S ALL THE WAY OVER THERE?
UH, BECAUSE I'M TRYING TO PLAY HARD TO GET.
HE'S LOOKING.
SAY SOMETHING FUNNY.
LIKE WHAT?
WH WH WHAT'S SO FUNNY?
I SAID "LIKE WHAT?"
WELL, THAT'S A THINKER.
OKAY. THIS PLAYING HARD TO GET THING
IS NOT WORKING.
HAND ME THOSE CHERRIES.
OKAY.
HI. HEY.
CARE FOR A CHERRY?
OH, NO, THANKS.
YOU KNOW, I CAN TIE ONE OF THESE INTO A KNOT
USING JUST MY TONGUE.
YOU OKAY?
YOU ALL RIGHT?
SO, WE SHOULD PROBABLY GET GOING SOON.
OH, BUT THE PARTY'S ONLY JUST GETTING STARTED.
WE HAVE TO BE AT THE FOUR SEASONS FOR DRINKS
IN-- OH!-- 15 MINUTES, AND THEN, UH, YOU KNOW
THEN THE PLAZA FOR DINNER.
SO, WHY DID YOU PLAN A PARTY AT THE SAME TIME?
NO, NO, NO. NO.
UM, ACTUALLY, AMERICAN SURPRISE PARTIES
ARE ARE ARE VERY SHORT.
IT'S USUALLY "SURPRISE!"
AND THEN, "OH, MY GOD, I'M SO SURPRISED. GOOD BYE."
ROSS, I'M HAVING SUCH A GREAT TIME.
YOUR SISTER HAS JUST BEEN TELLING ME
THAT YOU USED TO DRESS UP LIKE LITTLE OLD LADIES
AND HOST MAKE BELIEVE TEA PARTIES.
MONICA SAID THAT, DID SHE?
YEAH.
OH, OH, DID SHE TELL YOU THAT WHEN SHE WAS LITTLE
SHE WAS PARTIALLY RESPONSIBLE FOR NEW LEGISLATION
REGULATING THE STRENGTH OF SWING SETS?
OH, YEAH.
THEN WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO PUT ON TOP OF THAT?
A LITTLE SALAMI.
OOH, YEAH, YEAH.
THEN, UM, WHAT GOES ON TOP OF THE SALAMI?
OH, PASTRAMI.
OOH, YEAH.
YOU'RE A GENIUS.
OH, COULD SOMEBODY GIVE ME A HAND WITH THE ZIPPER?
YEAH.
UP!
YOU CHANGED?
YEAH. I DECIDED I NEEDED MY LUCKY DRESS.
AND "LUCKY" MEANS MORE CLEAVAGE?
IT DOES FOR ME.
OH, GOD, LOOK AT HIM!
HE'S SO CUTE!
I JUST WANT TO GO
OVER THERE AND GRAB HIM AND KISS HIM!
HOW COULD I KISS HIM
WITHOUT LETTING HIM KNOW THAT I LIKE HIM?!
OH, HEY, I KNOW HOW YOU CAN GET HIM.
TAKE OFF YOUR BRA.
WHAT?
THERE WAS THIS SCENE IN FOOT LOOSE...
FLAS HDANCE.
YEAH. WITH THAT PLUMBER GIRL...
SHE WAS A WELDER.
WERE YOU, LIKE, IN THE MOVIE, OR...?
ANYWAY, SHE TAKES OFF HER BRA UNDER THE SHIRT
AND PULLS IT OUT THE SLEEVE.
VERY SEXY, AND CLASSY.
OR, IF YOU WANT TO KISS HIM
UM, YOU COULD USE MISTLETOE.
IT'S NOT CHRISTMAS.
SPIN THE BOTTLE.
HE'S NOT 11.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR THIS.
IT WAS REALLY SO THOUGHTFUL OF YOU.
WHAT, YOU'RE LEAVING?!
YES. WE HAVE SOMETHING WE HAVE TO GET TO.
YEAH. I THINK I'M GOING TO TAKE OFF, TOO, ACTUALLY.
OH, YOU GUYS, YOU CAN'T LEAVE YET!
YOU HAVE TO STAY!
WE... WE'VE GOT THE WHOLE BIG THING PLANNED.
WHAT BIG THING?
SO, SPIN THE BOTTLE WORKS LIKE THIS:
I SPIN THE BOTTLE...
LANDS ON GUNTHER, SO I WOULD HAVE TO KISS GUNTHER.
ALL RIGHT.
WHO WANTS TO GO FIRST?
I'LL GO.
OKAY!
EMILY! WHOO!
WELCOME TO AMERICA.
ALL RIGHT.
TWO IN A ROW.
YOU GOT TO USE YOUR TONGUES NOW.
ALL RIGHT.
WHAT ARE THE ODDS?
OKAY. TH THAT'S ENOUGH, YOU KNOW?
LET'S LET SOMEONE ELSE PLAY.
IF YOU DIDN'T WANT TO PLAY
THEN WHY'D YOU COME TO THE PARTY?
ALL RIGHT, I'LL GO, I'LL GO.
SOMEBODY LOOSE. SOMEBODY LOOSE.
STORY OF MY LIFE.
GO AGAIN.
STORY OF MY FATHER'S LIFE.
OKAY. MY TURN!
OH!
LOOK AT THAT!
OH, MY GOD!
OH, MY GOD, THE BABY JUST KICKED!
OH!
IT'S OKAY, IT'S OKAY!
IF IT KICKED ONCE, IT'LL KICK AGAIN!
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, EVERYBODY JUST REMEMBER WHERE THEY WERE SITTING.
IT WAS A BUG.
DOESN'T MATTER HOW MUCH I'M CRAVING IT.
YOU KNOW WHY I'M NEVER GOING TO EAT MEAT?
BECAUSE IT'S MURDER. IT'S COLD BLOODED MURDER.
OKAY.
THERE'S A PHOEBE ON MY SANDWICH.
PHOEBE, WH WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I CAN'T HELP IT.
I NEED THE MEAT.
THE BABY NEEDS THE MEAT.
YOU KNOW HOW WHEN YOU'RE DATING SOMEONE
AND YOU DON'T WANT TO CHEAT ON THEM
UNLESS IT'S WITH SOMEONE REALLY HOT?
YEAH. TOTALLY.
ALL RIGHT. OKAY.
WELL, THIS IS THE SAME KIND OF DEAL.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO DO SOMETHING WRONG...
DO IT RIGHT.
I'LL BE BACK IN A MINUTE.
OKAY.
SHE...
WHAT ARE YOU DOING TO ME?
I MEAN, I'M TRYING  TO GET EMILY OUT OF HERE
AND YOU KEEP TALKING TO HER, BEING, OH
INTERESTING AND MAKING HER LAUGH.
FROM NOW ON, I DON'T WANT YOU TO BE FUNNY ANYMORE.
YOU KNOW WHAT? RACHEL WANTS ME TO BE FUNNY.
YOU DON'T WANT ME TO BE FUNNY.
FROM NOW ON, I'M GOING TO BE FUNNY SOMETIMES
AND NOT FUNNY OTHERS!
YOU FEEL BETTER NOW?
YEAH, BUT AT WHAT COST?
SIX MORE MONTHS, THREE MEALS A DAY.
I'M GOING TO EAT, LIKE, YOU KNOW...
MILLIONS OF COWS.
MOMMY COWS, DADDY COWS, BABY COWS...
NO. NO, I WILL NEVER EAT BABY COWS.
NO VEAL.
OH, BUT VEAL...
HEY, WHAT IF I SAID I COULD EVEN THINGS OUT FOR YOU...
MEAT WISE?
WHAT?
I EAT A LOT OF MEAT, RIGHT?
BUT SUPPOSE, UNTIL THE BABY'S BORN
I LAID OFF IT.
NO EXTRA ANIMALS WOULD DIE.
YOU'D JUST BE EATING MY ANIMALS.
JOEY, I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU WOULD DO THAT FOR ME.
ABSOLUTELY.
I COULD BE A VEGETARIAN.
THERE'S NO MEAT IN BEER, RIGHT?
OKAY, WE CAN STILL MAKE DINNER IF WE SKIP APPETIZERS
AND ASK FOR OUR CHECK RIGHT AWAY.
WELL, WE CAN'T GO NOW.
LOOKS LIKE RACHEL'S GOING TO PUT ON A SKIT.
OH, MY GOD.
HAVE YOU LOST YOUR MIND?
NO. NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
I AM FINALLY THINKING CLEARLY.
MY LUCKY DRESS WASN'T WORKING OUT TOO WELL FOR ME
BUT FOR FOUR YEARS, THIS BABY NEVER MISSED.
RACHEL, RACHEL, RACHEL, I CANNOT... I CAN'T LET...
ACTUALLY, I KIND OF WANT TO SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
HEY. HI.
NICE, UH... COSTUME.
OH, YEAH.
WELL, I WANTED TO GIVE EMILY
A BIG, AMERICAN GOOD BYE CHEER.
SO, OKAY.
WHOO!
READY?
OKAY.
GIVE ME AN "E."
"E"
GIVE ME AN "M." "M"
GIVE ME AN "I." "I"
GIVE ME AN "L." "L"
GIVE ME A "Y."
"Y"
WHAT DO YOU GET?
EMILY.
WHOO!
EMILY!
OKAY, SO THAT'S ME AS A CHEERLEADER.
TA DUM!
YOU ALL RIGHT?
FINE. I'M FINE.
I JUST LOOSENED A TOOTH.
IT'S NO BIG DEAL. I HAVE A DENTIST.
I'LL GO PUT SOME ICE ON IT.
EXCUSE ME.
OKAY. WHAT DO I DO NOW?
I THINK YOU'RE DONE.
OKAY. TIME TO TAKE OFF THE BRA.
UH, THAT WAS... REALLY, UH, GREAT
BUT I I GOT TO TAKE OFF, ACTUALLY.
TAKE THE BRA OFF.
ALL RIGHT. COME ON.
LET'S GO GET YOUR COAT.
OKAY.
RACHEL IS MY GIRLFRIEND.
SO, THIS WAS, UH, REALLY FUN.
OH, YEAH. IT'S REAL FUN.
YOU KNOW, THIS BRA...
IS REALLY BOTHERING ME.
YOU KNOW, THIS USED TO BE MY BEDROOM.
YEAH.
LOT OF MEMORIES IN HERE.
LOT OF MEMORIES.
IF THESE WALLS COULD TALK, YOU KNOW WHAT THEY'D SAY?
WANT TO HEAR SOME MEMORIES?
NEED A... NEED A LITTLE HAND THERE?
OH, NO, NO. I GOT THIS ALL UNDER CONTROL.
YOU REALLY DON'T SEEM LIKE YOU DO.
THAT'S...
FORGET IT!
THIS IS... FOR...
THIS IS NOT HOW THIS WAS SUPPOSED TO HAPPEN.
WHAT WAS SUPPOSED TO HAPPEN?
CAN YOU NOT LOOK AT ME WHEN I SAY THIS?
I THOUGHT THAT IF I COULD GET YOU HERE
I COULD SEDUCE YOU.
UH, EXCUSE ME?
SEDUCE YOU.
HUH.
UH... I I DON'T WEAR... SUITS TO WORK
AND I BOUGHT SIX OF THEM FROM YOU.
WELL, I'M SORRY.
I THOUGHT YOU NEEDED THEM.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
MY POINT IS, I KEPT COMING BACK
BECAUSE... I WANTED TO SEE YOU.
WHY?
BECAUSE I I LIKE YOU.
YOU LIKE ME?
YEAH.
I MEAN, YOU'RE YOU'RE BEAUTIFUL AND SMART AND SOPHISTICATED.
LOT OF THIS ISN'T, YOU KNOW, BASED ON TONIGHT.
BUT BUT YOU LIKE ME?
OH, MY GOD, I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
ALL THIS TIME I LIKED YOU AND YOU LIKED ME.
BUT...
NO, NO. DON'T SAY "BUT."
NO, NO. BUT'S NEVER GOOD.
JUST LET'S LEAVE IT AT I LIKE YOU AND YOU LIKE ME.
OKAY. UH, HOWEVER...
NOW, SEE, THAT'S A FANCY "BUT."
MY MARRIAGE, LIKE, JUST ENDED
AND I'M REALLY NOT READY TO GET INTO ANYTHING YET.
BUT...
I'M SORRY.
I... I JUST NEED A LITTLE TIME.
OKAY.
OH, THERE YOU ARE.
I WAS LOOKING FOR YOU BEFORE.
JOSHUA'S GONE, SO YOU AND EMILY ARE FREE TO GO.
IT'S OKAY.
SHE'S STILL IN THERE ENJOYING HER FAKE PARTY
AND, UH, IT'S TOO LATE
TO DO ANY OF THE STUFF I HAD PLANNED, SO...
OH, ROSS, I'M SORRY.
I COMPLETELY RUINED YOUR EVENING.
YEAH.
WELL, IF IT MAKES YOU
FEEL ANY BETTER, I MADE A FOOL OF MYSELF.
HELPS A LITTLE.
IS THERE ROOM ON THAT STEP FOR A PATHETIC LOSER?
YEAH. HAVE A SEAT.
OH...
I'M SO SORRY.
IT'S OKAY.
I MEAN, IT WAS JUST A TWO WEEK THING ANYWAY.
I JUST DIDN'T WANT IT TO END THIS WAY, YOU KNOW?
OR MAYBE YOU DIDN'T WANT IT TO END.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOU SEEM TO REALLY LIKE HER.
YEAH. I REALLY DO.
YEAH, BUT WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?
I MEAN, WE BOTH AGREED
IT WAS GOING TO BE A TWO WEEK THING.
YOU KNOW, NO COMMITMENT.
ROSS, THAT GIRL JUST SPENT THE ENTIRE EVENING
TALKING TO YOUR FRIENDS
YOU ASKING TO HEAR STORIES ABOUT
LOOKING THROUGH MONICA'S PHOTO ALBUMS.
I MEAN, YOU DON'T DO THAT
IF YOU'RE JUST IN IT FOR TWO WEEKS.
YOU THINK?
LOOK, YOU'VE GOT, LIKE, 14 HOURS
UNTIL SHE HAS  TO BE AT THE AIRPORT
AND YOU'RE SITTING HERE IN A HALLWAY WITH A...
28 YEAR OLD CHEERLEADER WITH A FAT LIP.
YEAH. YOU'RE RIGHT.
YEAH.
THANKS.
WHAT PHOTO ALBUM WAS IT?
I DON'T KNOW.
IT WAS YOU AND A BUNCH OF ALBINO KIDS.
OH, MY GOD.
THOSE WEREN'T ALBINO KIDS.
THAT WAS COMPUTER CAMP.
RACH.
HEY.
YOU'RE A PATHETIC LOSER, RIGHT?
OH, YEAH.
SIT.
HI.
OH, MY GOD.
JOSHUA.
LOOK...
ALL THOSE THINGS I SAID ABOUT NOT BEING READY...
THEY'RE NOT TRUE.
NO. THEY'RE THEY'RE ALL TRUE.
OH.
BUT...
."
OH, I LOVE THAT "BUT
UM, DO YOU WANT TO GO INSIDE AND GET SOME COFFEE?
YEAH.
OKAY.
THANKS.
YEAH.
EVERY TIME.
OOH, WHAT DO YOU GOT THERE?
PASTRAMI.
YEAH.
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT GOES GOOD WITH THAT?
MM HMM. CORNED BEEF.
OOH, I WAS GOING TO SAY BOLOGNA
BUT THAT'S MUCH BETTER.
HEY, HOW ABOUT A LITTLE OF THAT SMOKED TURKEY?
OKAY.
OH, MAMA.
HOW... WHEN WHEN IS THE BABY DUE?
SIX MONTHS.
OH... HEY, NOW
IF A COW SHOULD DIE OF NATURAL CAUSES
I CAN HAVE ONE OF THOSE, RIGHT?
NOT IF I GET THERE FIRST.