OKAY, SHE IS THE STAR OF THE PLAY
AND SHE IS MY GIRLFRIEND.
I GET TO HAVE SEX
WITH THE STAR OF THE PLAY.
PEOPLE CAN HEAR YOU.
I KNOW!
WOW, SHE LOOKS GREAT, DOESN'T SHE?
HI.
THAT IS ONE GOOD LOOKING MAN.
IS IT JUST ME
OR CAN YOU ACTUALLY SEE HIS ABS
THROUGH HIS OVERCOAT?
SO, YOU BEEN DOING THIS LONG?
NO, YOU'RE MY FIRST.
PUT THE MONEY ON THE TABLE.
OH, YEAH. OOH, THAT'S NICE.
DUDE.
IS THAT AN EXPENSIVE BLOUSE?
IF YOU WANT IT TO BE.
OH!
HERE'S YOUR GIRLFRIEND'S BUTTON.
OH, HEY, MON, DO YOU STILL HAVE
YOUR OLD BLOUSES AND DRESSES FROM HIGH SCHOOL?
YEAH. I THINK I HAVE SOME AROUND HERE SOMEWHERE. WHY?
IT'S JUST MATERNITY CLOTHES ARE SO EXPENSIVE.
RACH, I MADE A PILE OF YOUR STUFF
ON THIS SIDE OF THE ROOM.
IF YOU COULD JUST...
THROW YOUR PURSES AT IT.
BLOOMINGDALE'S ELIMINATED MY DEPARTMENT.
GOD! ARE YOU OUT OF A JOB?
NO, BUT THEY STUCK ME IN PERSONAL SHOPPING
WHICH IS JUST A HUGE STEP DOWN.
"PERSONAL SHOPPING"-- WHAT IS THAT?
LIKE, WHERE YOU WALK AROUND WITH SNOOTY RICH PEOPLE
AND TELL THEM WHAT TO BUY?
UH HUH.
THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
HEY.
UM... EXCUSE ME.
WE SWITCHED APARTMENTS.
YOU CAN'T EAT OUR FOOD ANYMORE.
THAT GRAVY TRAIN HAS ENDED.
THERE'S GRAVY?
IF YOU HAVE THE BIG APARTMENT
YOU HAVE TO DEAL WITH PEOPLE COMING OVER ALL THE TIME.
THAT FRIDGE HAS GOT TO BE STOCKED, OKAY?
THAT'S YOUR DEPARTMENT NOW.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I THINK I LEFT A DOUGHNUT UP HERE.
HEY.
HEY. HEY.
OH, HOW WAS KATHY'S PLAY?
WELL, KATHY GETS HALF NAKED AND SIMULATES SEX
WITH A REAL GOOD LOOKING GUY.
IT WAS LIKE SOMEBODY LITERALLY WROTE DOWN MY WORST NIGHTMARE
AND THEN CHARGED ME $32 TO SEE IT.
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA FOR A BUSINESS.
I'M TOTALLY SCREWED, OKAY?
THEY'RE GOING TO BE HOT AND HEAVY
ON STAGE EVERY NIGHT
AND THEY'RE GOING TO GO TO THEIR CAST PARTIES
AND HE'LL TRY TO UNDERMINE ME.
"SO, WHERE'S YOUR BOYFRIEND-- WHAT HIS NAME-- CHESTER?"
AND SHE'LL GO, "NO, IT'S CHANDLER."
AND HE'LL GO, "WHATEVER."
THAT THAT IS A GOOD TRICK.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, LOOK, WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?
LOOK, THEY'RE THERE TO DO A JOB.
JUST BECAUSE THEY WORK TOGETHER
DOESN'T MEAN THEY'LL GET TOGETHER.
JUST BECAUSE IT HAPPENED
WITH SUSAN SARANDON AND TIM ROBBINS
DOESN'T MEAN IT'LL HAPPEN WITH THEM.
OH, OH...
ALEC BALDWIN AND KIM BASINGER.
OH! TOM CRUISE AND NICOLE KIDMAN.
YEAH.
MEL GIBSON AND CLINT EASTWOOD.
THEY'RE NOT A COUPLE.
OH, OKAY. I GET THE GAME NOW.
ALL THESE PEOPLE WERE IN MOVIES TOGETHER.
IT'S MUCH DIFFERENT WITH PLAYS.
YOU GUYS WERE JUST IN ACTING CLASS TOGETHER
AND SHE SLEPT WITH YOU.
ACTING CLASS IS A LOT MORE
LIKE A MOVIE THAN A PLAY.
OKAY, LOOK.
LET ME ASK YOU A QUESTION:
WHEN THEY WERE DOING IT ONSTAGE
WAS IT, LIKE, REALLY HOT?
OH, YEAH.
WELL, OKAY
SO THEN YOU'RE FINE.
LOOK, THE RULE IS
WHEN TWO ACTORS ARE ACTUALLY DOING IT OFFSTAGE
THEN ALL THE SEXUAL TENSION BETWEEN THEM IS GONE, OKAY?
SO AS LONG AS IT'S HOT ON STAGE
YOU GOT NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
IT'S WHEN THE HEAT GOES AWAY--
THAT'S WHEN YOU'RE IN TROUBLE.
REALLY?
YOU HAVE BEEN TO EVERY PLAY I'VE BEEN IN.
HAVE I EVER HAD CHEMISTRY?  NO.
NO!
SO, MAN, ARE YOU GOING TO GO SEE THE PLAY
WITH ME TONIGHT?
I DON'T KNOW HOW COMFORTABLE I AM
GOING TO SEE HOW HOT THE SEX IS
BETWEEN SOME GUY AND YOUR GIRLFRIEND.
YEAH, I KNOW, BUT...
NO, NO. OH, I'M THERE.
HEY. HEY, MON.
WANT PANCAKES?
YOU MADE PANCAKES?
YEP. GRAB A PLATE.
NO, NO. STAY RIGHT THERE.
GETTING CLOSER.
OKAY, OKAY, BUT DON'T WORRY
BECAUSE WE ALSO HAVE CEREALS, MUFFINS, WAFFLES
AND JAMS, JELL IES AND MARMALADES --
WHICH, I'M FAIRLY CERTAI N, ARE THE SAME THING.
PLEASE EAT, BECAUSE JOEY OPENED EVERYTHING.
LISTEN, ALSO, WE'RE WATCHING
THE GAME HERE SATURDAY NIGHT IF PEOPLE WANT TO COME OVER.
OH, YEAH.
I WAS THINKING ABOUT HAVING PEOPLE OVER.
OH, YEAH? WHO'S PLAYING?
THE PLAYERS.
SOMEBODY SEEMS TO BE MISSING
BEING THE HOSTESS.
PLEASE.
IT'S A RELIEF, IS WHAT IT IS
IS WHAT IT IS.
PHEEBS, STICK OUT YOUR PLATE.
MONICA, I'M QUITTING.
I JUST HELPED AN 81 YEAR OLD WOMAN PUT ON A THONG
AND SHE DIDN'T EVEN BUY IT.
I'M TELLING YOU, I'M QUITTING.
THAT'S IT.
I'M TALKING TO MY BOSS RIGHT NOW.
YES, I AM.
YES, I AM. YES, I AM. YES, I AM. YES, I AM.
CALL ME WHEN YOU GET THIS MESSAGE.
OH, MR. WALTHAM.
I, UH... REALLY NEED TO TALK TO YOU.
IN A MOMENT, PLEASE.
I'M IN THE MIDDLE OF A TASK
AND YOU HAVE A CUSTOMER.
HI.
HI. I'M JOSHUA.
HI. I'M RACHEL GREEN.
WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU, JOSHUA?
WELL, I NEED A WHOLE NEW WARDROBE.
MY WIFE... WELL, MY EX WIFE...
OH, I'M SO SORRY.
ANYWAY, SHE BURNED ALL OF MY CLOTHES.
I GOT AWAY WITH TWO THINGS-- THIS SUIT
AND WHAT TURNED OUT TO BE A SKIRT.
WELL, AT LEAST THAT'S A GREAT SUIT.
BUT IT WASN'T MUCH FUN DROPPING IT OFF
AT THE DRY CLEANERS IN THE SKIRT.
I NEED EVERYTHING DOWN TO UNDERWEAR
SO IF YOU'RE WILLING
I'M, UH... I'M ALL YOURS.
OKAY.
RACHEL, YOU NEEDED TO SPEAK TO ME?
NO, NO, THAT WASN'T ME.
WELL...
WE SHOULD GET STARTED.
LET ME SHOW YOU MY UNDERWEAR--
THE SELECTION OF UNDERWEAR THAT WE CARRY.
OH, IT'S THIS WAY.
IT'S THIS WAY.
IT'S THIS WAY?
YEAH. SORRY.
I'M RIGHT, RIGHT?
THERE WAS, LIKE, NO CHEMISTRY BETWEEN THEM.
BEFORE, THEY HAD HEAT.
NOW THERE'S NO HEAT.
NOW, YOU KNOW WHAT THIS MEANS.
JOEY TOLD US WHAT THIS MEANS.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S NOT JUMP TO ANY CONCLUSIONS.
THERE WAS SOME SEXUAL CHEMISTRY BETWEEN THEM.
COME ON, IT WAS LIKE COUSINS HAVING SEX.
HERE SHE COMES.
DON'T SAY A WORD. JUST BE COOL.
DON'T BE, YOU KNOW, YOU.
HEY, YOU GUYS.
HEY. HEY.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR COMING AGAIN.
DID YOU LIKE IT?
ABSOLUTELY.
MM HMM. WASN'T NICK FUNNY
WHEN HE COULDN'T GET HIS MATCH LIT?
IT'S A GOOD PLAY, ISN'T IT?
MMM.
I LOVED THE PLAY.
UH... YEAH, YOU WERE GREAT
AND NICK-- DITTO.
CLEARLY, YOU'RE HAVING SEX WITH HIM.
OKAY...
CLEARLY, I'M HAVING SEX WITH HIM?
IT WAS SO OBVIOUS.
THERE WAS NO CHEMISTRY BETWEEN YOU.
OKAY, LET ME JUST GET THIS STRAIGHT:
YOU'RE ACCUSING ME OF CHEATING ON YOU
AND YOU'RE INSULTING MY PERFORMANCE?
I CAN SEE HOW THIS COULD HAPPEN.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE UP THERE EVERY NIGHT
NAKED, TOUCHING, KISSING.
ACTING.
CHANDLER, THIS IS MY JOB.
I I'M PLAYING A PART IN A PLAY.
HOW CAN YOU NOT TRUST ME?
WELL, YOU CAN UNDERSTAND, GIVEN HOW WE STARTED.
OH, WOW.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE THROWING THAT IN MY FACE.
THAT IS WHAT HAPPENED
AND I DON'T EVEN SEE YOU DENYING THIS.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT, CHANDLER.
WHY DON'T YOU CALL ME WHEN YOU GROW UP?
YEAH, WELL
DON'T EXPECT THAT TO HAPPEN ANYTIME SOON.
OH! I HAVE THE BEST JOB IN THE ENTIRE WORLD.
THE MOST ADORABLE GUY CAME OVER TODAY
AND I GOT TO DRESS HIM UP ALL DAY.
RACHEL HAS A NEW DOLL.
OH, I WISH HE WAS A DOLL.
THEN I COULD GET A "RACHEL" DOLL
AND I'D BUMP THEM TOGETHER AND MAKE KISSING NOISES.
OH, AND HE'S GOT THE MOST BEAUTIFUL NAME.
I NEVER REALIZED. JOSHUA. JOSH... U A.
JOSHUA. JOSH...
UH... HELLO.
HI...
OH, WHAT DO I SMELL?
I DON'T KNOW, BUT IT SMELLS GOOD.
FRESH COOKIES, HOT FROM THE OVEN.
PLEASE, HAVE SOME.
OH, YO...
I'VE JUST BEEN FIDDLING AROUND IN HERE
MAKING DELICIOUS TREATS
FOR EVERYONE.
OH. THE NEW PLAYBOY.
YEAH. JUST SOMETHING I PICKED UP.
COOKIES AND PORN. YOU'RE THE BEST MOM EVER!
WHAT? WHAT?
NOTHING. JUST SOMETHING JOSHUA SAID ABOUT V NECKS
BUT YOU HAD TO BE THERE.
YEAH, HOW DOES, UH, JASON LOOK IN A V NECK?
IT'S JOSHUA.
OH, WHATEVER.
WAIT... WAIT. THIS... THIS ISN'T TAKEOUT.
WELL, HATE TO EAT AND RUN.
NO, WAIT. PLEASE DON'T GO.
I'VE GOT PORN FOR YOU, TOO.
ME, I DON'T NEED IT.
PEOPLE ARE SUPPOSED TO WANT TO HANG OUT HERE.
WHY? HONEY, WHAT IS THE BIG DEAL?
I'M THE HOSTESS, NOT THOSE GUYS.
I'M ALWAYS THE HOSTESS.
I MEAN, EVEN WHEN I WAS LITTLE, I MEAN THE...
THE GIRLS BROUGHT THEIR DOLLIES TO MY TEA PARTY.
I SERVED THE BEST AIR.
WELL, WHY DID YOU
MAKE, LIKE, A WHOLE BIG THING
OUT OF, YOU KNOW, EVERYONE HAS TO HANG OUT
IN THE BIG APARTMENT?
BECAUSE THEY TOOK OUR APARTMENT.
I WANTED TO PUNISH THEM.
I'M I'M DONE NOW.
THEY THEY THEY'VE SUFFERED ENOUGH.
BUT IF YOU WANTED TO PUNISH THEM
YOU SHOULD HAVE JUST MADE THEM HANG OUT HERE.
ALL RIGHT THEN, WHEN I'M FINISHED
WITH THIS PLACE
IT'S GOING TO BE TEN TIMES BETTER
THAN THAT PLACE.
OH, ARE WE GOING
TO TRASH THEIR PLACE?
STEPS!
SLUT!
YOU WILL ALL BE VERY HAPPY TO HEAR
THAT KATHY IS SLEEPING WITH THAT GUY.
OH, GOD. OH, NO. WHAT?
SO, YOU WERE RIGHT?
I CONFRONTED HER, AND SHE DIDN'T DENY IT.
I DON'T LIVE HERE.
CHANDLER...
CHANDLER, WHAT DID SHE SAY?
WAIT A MINUTE. ARE YOU SURE?
I MAY BE DRUNK, BUT I KNOW WHAT SHE SAID
SO THEN I WENT OVER TO BEEFSTEAK CHULIE'S...
BEEFSTEAK CHARLIE'S?
YES!
SEE, YOU AND I HAVE ALWAYS BEEN, LIKE...
I DON'T BELIEVE THIS.
OH, MAN, I AM SO SORRY.
THE BARTENDER TAUGHT ME A TRICK, THOUGH.
I DON'T REMEMBER IT.
WHOOPS.
OH, HEY, DO YOU
NEED HELP WITH THAT?
NO.
I GOT IT.
OH, I JUST FEEL BAD.
I NEVER VACUUM.
HEY.
HEY. HEY.
SO, I WAS WITH JOSHUA FOR AN HOUR TODAY
AND HE HAS NOT ASKED ME OUT.
JUST SO FRUSTRATING.
WHY DON'T  YOU ASK HIM OUT?
OH, YEAH. TOTALLY. THAT'S SUCH A TURN ON.
REALLY?
IT DOESN'T SEEM DESPERATE?
THAT'S THE TURN ON.
hE JUST GOT A DIVORCE, RIGHT?
SO HE'S PROBABLY REALLY NERVOUS
AROUND WOMEN, YOU KNOW?
MAYBE YOU JUST NEED TO MAKE THE FIRST MOVE.
I'VE NEVER ASKED A GUY OUT BEFORE.
YOU'VE NEVER ASKED A GUY OUT?
NO. HAVE YOU?
THOUSANDS OF TIMES.
THAT DOESN'T MAKE ME SOUND TOO GOOD, DOES IT?
I DON'T EVEN KNOW HOW I WOULD GO ABOUT IT.
OH, WELL, WHAT I DO IS, UH... I LOOK A WOMAN UP AND DOWN
AND I SAY, "HEY... HOW YOU DOING?"
OH, PLEASE.
HEY... HOW YOU DOING?
I'M GOING TO DO THAT.
I'M GOING TO CALL HIM UP AND I'M GOING TO ASK HIM OUT.
I CAN DO THAT... ASK HIM OUT.
HOW YOU DOING?
HI, JOSHUA... IT'S RACHEL GREEN FROM BLOOMINGDALE'S.
YEAH, UM...
I WAS JUST WONDERING IF YOU, UM... IF YOU, UM...
LEFT YOUR WALLET AT THE STORE TODAY?
OH, WELL
WE FOUND A WALLET AND WE...
THE LICENSE... WELL, THAT IS A GOOD IDEA.
UH, WELL, LET'S SEE.
THIS LICENSE BELONGS TO A, UH...
BELONGS TO A MR.... UH, PHEEBS...
AND, UM... YEAH.
SO, OKAY... SO SORRY TO BOTHER YOU AT HOME.
I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW.
BYE.
YOU'VE DONE THAT A THOUSAND TIMES?
I'VE NEVER DONE THAT.
OH, GOD. I JUST GOT SO NERVOUS THAT HE WAS GOING TO SAY NO.
WELL, YOU'VE GOT TO GIVE HIM SOMETHING HE CAN'T SAY NO TO
LIKE, UH, KNICKS TICKETS.
INVITE THE GUY TO A KNICKS GAME.
YOU'RE GUARANTEED HE'LL SAY YES.
THAT WILL WORK?
ABSOLUTELY. IF IT DOESN'T
CAN I GET THE EXTRA TICKET?
WHAT THE HECK IS THAT?
DID SHE CALL?
NO. SORRY.
WELL, MAY... MAYBE I SHOULD CALL HER.
FORGET HER, MAN.
YOU DON'T NEED HER. YOU DON'T NEED THAT.
HE'S RIGHT. WHAT SHE DID WAS UNFORGIVABLE.
WELL, YEAH, BUT... YOU KNOW, WHAT WHAT IF I WAS WRONG?
HOW MIGHT YOU BE WRONG?
WELL, YOU KNOW, WHAT IF SHE
DIDN'T ACTUALLY SLEEP WITH THE GUY?
TELL ME SHE ACTUALLY TOLD YOU.
SHE DID NOT HAVE TO TELL ME.
I SAW THE PLAY, AND THERE WAS NO HEAT.
BACK ME UP, ROSS.
THAT'S ALL YOU'RE
BASING THIS ON?
THAT'S NOT BACKING ME UP!
YOU SAID WITH THE OFFSTAGE AND THE HEAT
AND THE ON STAGE AND HEAT...
WHOA WHOA! THAT WAS JUST A THEORY.
THERE'S A LOT OF THEORIES THAT DIDN'T PAN OUT...
LONE GUNMAN... COMMUNISM... GEOMETRY.
OH, MY GOD!
WOULD YOU LIKE TO GO TO A BASKETBALL GAME WITH...
YOU KNOW, IT'S FUNNY... BASKETBALL
BECAUSE I HAPPEN TO HAVE TICKETS TO THE...
OKAY... UM...
WHO LIKES THE KNICKS?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
OH... WELL, AS A SINGLE WOMAN...
WHO IS AVAILABLE
I THINK YOU LOOK GREAT.
HUH... YEAH?
YEP. OH, YEAH. YOU LOOK GREAT.
OH, YEAH. YEAH, THIS LOOKS GREAT.
UM, SO, YOU LIKE IT?
I DO. I DO. I LOVE IT.
IN FACT, I I THINK I'M GOING TO WEAR IT HOME.
GREAT.
ALL RIGHT. WELL, THANK YOU SO MUCH...
OH... SURE. FOR ALL YOUR HELP.
WELL, I GUESS, UH, I GUESS THIS IS IT.
YEEAAH!
THANKS.
MAYBE I'LL SEE YOU IN THE SPRING
UH, FOR THE BATHING SUITS.
YOU DON'T WANT TO DO THAT NOW?!
OH, THAT'S OKAY... I...
OH...
ANYWAY, HOPEFULLY I I'LL SEE YOU AROUND SOMETIME.
BASKETBALL!
SORRY?
I, UH... I HAVE TWO TICKETS TO THE KNICKS GAME TONIGHT
IF YOU'RE INTERESTED...
JUST AS A THANK YOU FOR THIS WEEK.
WOW! THAT WOULD BE GREAT.
REALLY?
YEAH, THAT WOULD BE FANTASTIC.
OH...
MY NEPHEW IS CRAZY ABOUT THE KNICKS.
THIS IS FANTASTIC.
THANK YOU
SO MUCH, RACHEL.
GOOD MORNING.
HI.
HEY.
HEY... I JUST... I JUST WANTED TO COME OVER
TO... TO SAY THAT I'M SORRY, YOU KNOW.
I KNOW... I ACTED LIKE THE BIGGEST IDIOT IN THE WORLD
AND I CAN COMPLETELY UNDERSTAND WHY YOU WERE SO UPSET.
OH, WOW.
I REALLY WISH YOU'D CALLED ME.
YEAH, I KNOW. I WISH I HAD, TOO
BUT, YOU KNOW, I I THINK THIS IS A GOOD THING, YOU KNOW
BECAUSE WE'VE HAD
OUR FIRST FIGHT
AND NOW WE CAN MOVE ON.
YOU KNOW, I MEAN
I KNOW FOR ME...
NICK'S PANTS?
YEAH.
WELL...
I THINK OUR SECOND FIGHT IS GOING TO BE A BIG ONE.
OKAY...
FOR NEXT TIME, WHAT DO YOU SAY?
I HAVE AN EXTRA TICKET--
AN EXTRA TICKET-- NOT TWO TICKETS.
I HAVE AN EXTRA TICKET.
RIGHT.
SO, THE FIRST TIME YOU ASKED A GUY OUT
HE HE TURNED YOU DOWN?
HE DIDN'T TURN ME DOWN.
HE'S AT THE GAME, ISN'T HE?
I GOT THE DATE-- I'M JUST NOT ON IT.
OKAY... IT'S READY.
COME ON.
WHAT'S READY?
JUST COME.
OH, MY GOD...
WOW!
HEY...
MONICA...
THIS IS BEAUTIFUL.
OH, DID YOU WHAT, DID YOU WORK FOR TWO DAYS STRAIGHT?
PRETTY MUCH.
SO, WHAT WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THE FLOOR?
I DON'T KNOW. LOOKS THE SAME.
YOU USED TO HAVE CARPET.
OH, YEAH.
SO, I I MADE SNACKS.
OH.
PLEASE, JUST HANG OUT, OKAY.
I I'M JUST GOING TO REST MY EYES FOR JUST A LITTLE BIT.
MON, DO YOU WANT US TO, UH, COME BACK LATER?
OH, NO, NO, NO. STAY, STAY, STAY.
JUST KEEP TALKING.
I AM ALWAYS THE HOSTESS.
HEY.
HOW DID IT GO?
WELL, SHE WASN'T SLEEPING WITH HIM.
OH, GOOD.
SHE IS NOW.
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
I'M SAYING THAT SHE IS A DEVIL WOMAN.
YOU KNOW, I MEAN, YOU THINK YOU KNOW A PERSON.
THEN THEY TURN AROUND, THEY SLEEP WITH NICK.
NICK AND HIS ROCK HARD PECS AND HIS GIANT MAN NIPPLES.
I HATE HIM... AND I HATE HER.
WELL, I DON'T HATE HER. I LOVE HER.
THIS IS ALL MY FAULT, REALLY.
HOW? HOW IS IT YOUR FAULT?
BECAUSE... AAH! I... I SHOULD HAVE CALLED.
YOU KNOW, IF I HAD JUST CALLED HER
AFTER OUR BIG, STUPID FIGHT
SHE NEVER WOULD HAVE GONE OUT WITH NICK
AND THEY WOULDN'T HAVE ENDED UP IN BED TOGETHER.
I THREW HER
AT HIS MAN NIPPLES.
HONEY, THIS IS NOT YOUR FAULT.
JUST BECAUSE YOU GUYS HAD A FIGHT
DOES NOT JUSTIFY HER SLEEPING WITH SOMEONE.
WELL, IF IF SHE THOUGHT THEY WERE ON A BREAK...
ONE OF YOUR CUSTOMERS SEEMS
TO HAVE LEFT HIS BILLFOLD-- A JOSHUA BURGIN.
REALLY?
WILL YOU CALL HIM?
YES. I WILL, ABSOLUTELY.
HELLO, RACHEL.
HI, JOSHUA.
I LEFT MY WALLET HERE ON PURPOSE.
REALLY?
YES. I JUST WANTED TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
OH, I'M GLAD.
RACHEL, I'D LIKE TO SAY SOMETHING TO YOU.
YES?
HOW YOU DOING?