I JUST WALKED IN THE BATHROOM
AND SAW KATHY NAKED.
IT WAS LIKE TORTURE.
YOU KNOW, IF WE EVER GO TO WAR AND YOU'RE CAPTURED
YOU'RE IN FOR A BIG SURPRISE.
IT JUST KEEPS GETTING WORSE.
IT'S BAD ENOUGH THAT I'M IN LOVE WITH MY ROOMMATE'S GIRLFRIEND
WHICH I THINK
SHE KNOWS.
EVERY TIME WE'RE IN THE SAME ROOM TOGETHER
THERE'S THIS WEIRD ENERGY BETWEEN US.
AND CALL ME CRAZY
BUT I THINK SHE LIKES ME, TOO.
AND NOW... I HAVE SEEN HER NAKED.
AT LEAST, WHEN I'D SEEN HER WITH CLOTHES ON
I COULD IMAGINE THAT HER BODY
WAS COVERED IN BOILS
OR SOMETHING.
BUT THERE ARE NO BOILS.
SHE'S SMOOTH.
SMOOTH!
WOW.
COULD EVERYONE TOTALLY SEE UP HIS ROBE?
YEAH, RIGHT UP IT. OH, MY GOD!
GREAT. ALL RIGHT.
SO I'LL CALL YOU LATER.
GREAT.
HEY, HEY, HEY.
WHO WAS THAT?
THAT WOULD BE CACEY.
WE'RE GOING OUT TONIGHT.
GOING OUT, HUH?
WOW! WOW!
SO, THINGS DIDN'T WORK OUT WITH KATHY, HUH?
BUMMER.
NO, THINGS ARE FINE WITH KATHY.
I'M HAVING A LATE DINNER WITH HER TONIGHT
RIGHT AFTER MY EARLY DINNER
WITH CACEY.
WHAT?
AND THE CRAZIEST THING IS I JUST ATE A WHOLE PIZZA
MYSELF.
BUT...
YOU'RE GOING OUT WITH KATHY.
YEAH.
WHY ARE YOU GETTING SO UPSET?
WELL, I'M UPSET...
FOR YOU.
YOU KNOW, I MEAN
HAVING SEX WITH AN ENDLESS LINE OF BEAUTIFUL WOMEN
MUST BE VERY UNFULFILLING
FOR YOU.
WH WHAT IS THE BIG DEAL?
IT'S NOT LIKE WE'RE EXCLUSIVE.
LOOK, JOEY.
KATHY IS CLEARLY NOT FULFILLING YOUR EMOTIONAL NEEDS
BUT CACEY...
I MEAN, GRANTED, I JUST SAW THE BACK OF HER HEAD
BUT I GOT THIS SENSE THAT SHE'S SMART
AND FUNNY AND GETS YOU.
YOU GOT ALL THAT FROM THE BACK OF HER HEAD?
I JUST THINK IT'S TIME FOR YOU TO SETTLE DOWN--
YOU KNOW, MAKE A CHOICE, PICK A LANE.
WHO'S ELAINE?
?? LITTLE TINY TARZAN ??
?
?? SWINGING ON A NOSE HAIR ?
?? SWINGING WITH THE GREATEST OF EASE... ??
DARN IT. I DON'T KNOW HOW TO GET TO THE NEXT VERSE.
YOU COULD JUST GO, UH...
??
?? GREATEST OF EASE
?? BUM A NUMMA NUMMA...
AND THEN GO RIGHT INTO IT.
YEAH.
OOH, I LIKE THAT.
WAIT. HOW DO YOU KNOW ABOUT "BUM A NUMMA NUMMAS"?
WELL, UH... YOU KNOW, I USED TO PLAY.
OH, YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
THE KEYBOARDS, HUH?
YEAH. JUST A LITTLE IN HIGH SCHOOL.
I REALLY GOT INTO IT IN COLLEGE.
THAT'S WHEN I REALLY FOUND MY SOUND.
OH, GOD. ORANGE JUICE JUST CAME OUT OF MY NOSE
BUT IT WAS TOTALLY WORTH IT.
OH, MY GOD!
I COMPLETELY FORGOT ABOUT YOUR SOUND.
YEAH.
HE USED TO LOCK HIMSELF IN THE BASEMENT FOR HOURS.
NO ONE WAS EVER ALLOWED TO HEAR "THE SOUND."
I WANT TO HEAR "THE SOUND."
NO. I MEAN...
NO. I HAVEN'T PLAYED IN SO LONG
AND, AND...
WELL, IT'S REALLY PERSONAL STUFF, YOU KNOW?
COME ON. PLAY THAT FUNKY MUSIC, WHITE BOY.
YEAH, COME ON.
NO, YOU GUYS.
MY KEYBOARDS ARE ALL THE WAY... YEAH, OKAY.
WHO WANTS TO GET DINNER LATER?
I WANT TO TRY THAT NEW ITALIAN RESTAURANT.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE REALLY GOOD.
SAW A LOT OF CHINESE PEOPLE EATING IN THERE.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
REMEMBER YOU SAID SOME RESTAURANT MUST BE REALLY GOOD
BECAUSE YOU SAW ALL THESE CHINESE PEOPLE EATING IN THERE?
THAT'S BECAUSE IT WAS A CHINESE RESTAURANT.
OH. WELL... I STILL WANT TO GO,
WHO WANTS TO COME?
OH, I CAN'T.
I GOT TWO DINNER DATES TONIGHT
SO I GOT TO GET READY.
ALL RIGHT. GIRLS' NIGHT OUT.
SORRY, HONEY, BUT WE GOT TO PREP
THAT CATERING THING WE HAVE TOMORROW.
OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
I WISH I WAS ONE OF THOSE PEOPLE
WHO COULD EAT IN RESTAURANTS ALONE.
YOU SHOULD TRY IT.
IT'S A REALLY GOOD THING TO DO.
I THINK I WOULD FEEL REALLY SELF CONSCIOUS.
LIKE I WAS ON DISPLAY OR SOMETHING.
I WAS ON DISPLAY ONCE.
IT WAS NOTHING LIKE EATING ALONE.
I JUST HAD A GREAT TIME WITH MYSELF.
WELL, THIS COULD BE A GOOD STORY.
AT DINNER.
IT WAS SO LIBERATING, YOU KNOW?
I DON'T NEED PEOPLE TO HAVE FUN.
I'M FUN. I'M A FUN GIRL.
ARE YOU A NAUGHTY GIRL?
NO, JUST FUN. FUN. GOOD. FUN. YEAH.
SEE? I TOLD YOU YOU'D HAVE FUN.
ALTHOUGH I MUST SAY THAT I TOTALLY JUDGE
ANY WOMAN I SEE EATING ALONE.
WHAT IS WRONG WITH A WOMAN EATING ALONE?
OBVIOUSLY SOMETHING-- SHE'S EATING ALONE.
OKAY, GUYS.
ALL RIGHT, BRING IT ON, YOU.
HERE WE GO.
YOU KNOW, I'VE NEVER PLAYED MY STUFF
FOR ANYONE BEFORE
SO IT'S IMPORTANT THAT YOU UNDERSTAND
IT'S ABOUT COMMUNICATING...
VERY PRIVATE EMOTIONS.
YOU KNOW, UM...
YOU SHOULD THINK OF, UM...
MY WORK
AS WORDLESS SOUND POEMS.
THAT'S WHAT...
OH, MY GOD. PLAY!
BOY, YOU KNOW, TH THAT WAS, UH...
TERRIFIC.
REALLY...
BITCHING.
WOW!
IT WAS SO... WOW!
REALLY? I MEAN, REALLY?
OH, YEAH!
I MEAN, YOU SHOULD... PLAY IN PUBLIC.
WOW! THANKS, YOU GUYS!
THAT'S, OH...
OH, I WANT TO PLAY YOU ANOTHER PIECE.
UM... OH!
I LEFT MY HELICOPTER SOUNDS ON ANOTHER DISK.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK, OKAY?
OH, THIS IS...
THIS IS SO NICE.
I MEAN, I AM SO...
OH, GOD BLESS MY DAD FOR SOUND PROOFING THE BASEMENT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I EVER LET HIM TOUCH ME WITH THOSE FINGERS.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I LOVED IT!
IT WAS SO MOVING.
PLUS, IT'S SO DIFFERENT
FROM THE STUFF YOU USUALLY HEAR.
YOU MEAN MUSIC?
YEAH, I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE THINKING.
YES, YES. YOUR BREASTS ARE JUST AS FIRM AND JUICY.
COME IN.
HEY.
OH, GOD. IS THAT BAYWATCH?
UH, YES, BUT, UH, I JUST WATCH IT FOR THE ARTICLES.
SO, IS JOEY AROUND?
NO. HE'S NOT BACK YET, BUT HE'S GOING TO BE HERE ANY MINUTE.
HAVE A SEAT. BOW OR STERN?
I DON'T REALLY HAVE A PREFERENCE. YOU?
WELL, I LIKE IT IN THE STERN.
OF THE BOAT.
HELLO.
HEY, IT'S ME.
LISTEN, CACEY AND I HAD A LITTLE CAR TROUBLE.
WHAT HAPPENED?
We broke down
ON THE PARKWAY.
I HAVE TO GET SOME TRANSMISSION FLUID.
COULD YOU PLEASE TELL KATHY I'M SORRY AND I'LL BE THERE SOON?
WHY CAN'T YOU TELL HER?
Because I only have one quarter and my time is about to...
JOEY? JOEY?
YEAH?
I THOUGHT YOUR TIME RAN OUT.
ME, TOO, BUT I GUESS I DO HAVE A COUPLE OF...
UH, THAT WAS JOEY.
HE'S RUNNING A LITTLE LATE AND HE SAYS HE'S SORRY.
SO I GUESS IT'S JUST YOU AND ME, THEN.
OH. OKAY.
YEAH. I THINK IT IS.
SO, WHAT DID YOU DO TODAY?
I HAD AN APPOINTMENT TO GET MY HAIR CUT...
IT LOOKS GREAT.
AND THEN IT GOT CANCELED.
WELL, I COULD CUT IT.
REALLY? DO YOU DO THAT?
YEAH, I DO.
I LEARNED IT IN MY AUNT'S DOG GROOMING SHOP
BUT WHAT DO YOU SAY?
DOG GROOMING, HUH?
OKAY, JUST DON'T MAKE MY TAIL TOO POOFY.
YOU HAVE REALLY GREAT HAIR.
WELL, THANKS.
I GROW IT MYSELF.
MMM!
MMM...
YOU KNOW WHO ALSO HAS GREAT HAIR IS JOEY.
YES. YEAH, JOEY HAS GREAT HAIR.
UM, I'M BASICALLY DONE HERE.
LET ME JUST GET THIS HAIR OFF YOUR NECK.
WH WHAT'RE YOU DOING?
CHECKING TO SEE IF IT'S EVEN.
OKAY.
LOOKS GOOD.
AH, IT'S THE PHONE!
THE PHONE'S MAKING SOUNDS!
HELLO.
HEY, DUDE, IT'S ME.
HEY, IT'S JOEY.
OH.
WE'RE GOING TO BE STUCK HERE FOR A WHILE.
I GOT THE TRANSMISSION FLUID, WENT TO PUT IT IN THE CAR--
THE TRANSMISSION WASN'T THERE.
WHAT?
It must've fallen out
A FEW BLOCKS BACK.
I FIGURED WE HIT A DOG.
OH. OKAY.
Could you put Kathy on?
I want to apologize to her.
OH. YEAH, MAN. JOEY.
HEY.
OH, NO. IT'S FINE.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
NO, STOP APOLOGIZING.
IT'S OKAY.
YEAH. I'LL TALK TO YOU TOMORROW.
I SHOULD, UH, PROBABLY GO.
YEAH. YES. YEAH.
I FORGOT MY PURSE.
OH.
OH! I REALLY DID.
I FORGOT MY PURSE.
OH, NO, NO, NO!
IT'S BAD. IT'S BAD. THIS IS BAD.
HORRIBLE.
WAIT, THE, UH, THE KISS, OR THE SITUATION?
NO, THE KISS WAS GOOD.
NO, BUT THAT'S BAD!
OH, YES! OKAY, HERE'S WHAT WE DO.
WE FORGET IT HAPPENED.
WHAT?
WE SWALLOW OUR FEELINGS
EVEN IF IT MEANS WE'RE UNHAPPY FOREVER.
SOUND GOOD?
CAN YOU REALLY DO THAT?
I HAVE TO.
HE'S MY BEST FRIEND...
AND YOU'RE SEEING HIM.
OH, CHANDLER, I LIKE JOEY A LOT
BUT WITH YOU...
OH, NO, NO, DON'T. SEE?
SEE, YOU'RE GETTING ME CONFUSED.
I'M STARTING TO YEARN.
I'M SORRY.
IF YOU WANT TO PRETEND THAT NOTHING HAPPENED
I CAN TRY.
I I THINK WE HAVE TO.
OKAY.
BYE.
ARE YOU STILL OUT THERE?
NO.
ELECTRIFYING...
INFINITE TIME...
TIME... TIME... TIME...
YOU KNOW, THERE'S A STARBUCKS ABOUT THREE BLOCKS DOWN.
HE'S SO INSPIRED.
JUST LOOK AT HIM.
LOOK AT HIM GO.
THANK YOU, NEW YORK... NEW YORK... NEW YORK...
HEY, AREN'T YOU UP NEXT?
OH, NO. I'M NOT PLAYING TONIGHT.
WHY NOT?
I CAN'T FOLLOW ROSS.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
THAT WOULD BE LIKE THOSE POOR BICYCLE RIDING CHIMPS
WHO HAD TO FOLLOW THE BEATLES. NO.
PHOEBE, ROSS SUCKS.
PHOEBE, THE PLACE HAS EMPTIED
BECAUSE OF HIM.
OH, MY GOD, HE'S NOT EVEN APPRECIATED
IN HIS OWN TIME.
I WOULD GIVE ANYTHING
TO NOT BE APPRECIATED IN MY OWN TIME!
OKAY. UM, PHOEBE...
YOU SUCK, TOO.
YEAH, PHOEBE, YOU'RE...
AWFUL!
YOU GUYS.
"YEAH, YOU SUCK, TOO."
OH, MAN!
I CAN'T BELIEVE I LOCKED MYSELF OUT AGAIN!
HANG ON, BUDDY.
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT HAPPENED HERE?
DID YOU DO ALL THIS?
I SURE DID.
WHY?
I JUST THOUGHT IT WOULD MAKE ME FEEL GOOD
TO DO SOMETHING NICE FOR MY FRIEND.
YOU'RE AMAZING.
NO, NO, NO.
THIS IS AMAZING.
A TV THAT APPEARS AS IF FROM NOWHERE!
THAT'S THE DREAM!
HOW DID YOU AFFORD ALL THIS STUFF?!
WELL, YOU KNOW, I'M 29.
I MEAN, WHO NEEDS A SAVINGS ACCOUNT?
YOU ARE THE BEST FRIEND ANYONE HAS EVER HAD.
OH, I DON'T KNOW.
NO, NO, NO. YOU ARE.
YOU DO THIS, YOU GIVE ME THE GREAT ADVICE
AND LISTEN, I WAS THINKING ABOUT WHAT YOU SAID YESTERDAY
ABOUT FOCUSING ON ONE WOMAN?
I'M GOING TO DO THAT.
YOU MEAN WITH CACEY?
NO. I THINK I'LL SEE HOW THINGS GO WITH KATHY.
SHE'S PRETTY COOL.
OR CACEY.
NO, NO, KATHY.
COULD BE CACEY.
CONSIDER CACEY.
YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK?
I THINK SOMEBODY'S
GOT A LITTLE CRUSH ON CACEY.
HOW ABOUT I FIX YOU TWO UP?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
THAT ALL THE PIECES OF MY LIFE
ARE FALLING RIGHT INTO PLACE.
HEY.
HEY. YOU WERE REALLY GREAT.
YOU WERE REALLY, REALLY GREAT.
THANKS.
SO, MONICA TELLS ME
THAT, UH, YOU DON'T WANT TO PLAY ANYMORE
BECAUSE OF ME
AND, YOU KNOW, MY TALENT.
IS THAT TRUE?
WELL...
KIND OF, YEAH. YEAH.
PHEEBS...
YEAH, I MEAN, YOU KNOW
AND I WAS TRYING TO BE REALLY, YOU KNOW, OKAY AND UPBEAT ABOUT IT
BUT I FEEL SO... DWARFED BY YOUR MUSICAL GIFT.
I...
SEE, BUT PHEEBS
THAT IS THE EXACT OPPOSITE INTENT
OF MY MUSIC.
MY MUSIC IS MEANT TO INSPIRE
AND IF IT BOTHERS YOU THIS MUCH
THEN I...
I WON'T PLAY ANYMORE.
OH, NO.
NO, NO, NO. DON'T DO THAT.
HOW COULD I LIVE WITH MYSELF
IF I KNEW I WAS DEPRIVING THE WORLD OF YOUR MUSIC?
YEAH, OKAY.
I'D LOVE TO, BUT I HAVE PLANS ON SUNDAY.
MAYBE SOME OTHER TIME.
SURE. GIVE ME A CALL.
I'M IN THE BOOK.
OKAY. THANKS A LOT.
SEE YOU.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
HE IS CUTE AND HE'S A DOCTOR.
HOW DO YOU KNOW?
HONEY, I EAVESDROP BECAUSE I CARE.
WELL, I HAVE PLANS ON SUNDAY.
WITH WHO?
ME.
OH, GOD.
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO TOLD ME
HOW IMPORTANT IT IS TO SPEND TIME ALONE.
I CAN'T JUST GO OUT WITH THAT GUY
WHEN I HAVE PLANS WITH MYSELF.
IT WOULDN'T BE FAIR TO ME.
SO, BASICALLY, YOU'RE SAYING
YOU DON'T WANT TO CHEAT ON YOURSELF.
WELL, IF YOU WANT TO MAKE ME SOUND CRAZY...
SAW THE NEW FURNITURE.
VERY NICE.
YEAH. JOEY HAS THE BEST BOYFRIEND EVER.
I KISSED KATHY.
ARE YOU SERIOUS? MY GOD!
DOES JOEY KNOW?
NO.
IS THERE ANY WAY--
ANY WAY YOU THINK HE WILL UNDERSTAND THIS?
YOU OBVIOUSLY HAVEN'T SCREWED OVER
A LOT OF YOUR FRIENDS.
WHICH WE ALL APPRECIATE.
YOU KNOW, THE SAD THING IS
IF YOU HAD TOLD HIM HOW YOU FELT BEFORE YOU KISSED HER
KNOWING JOEY, HE PROBABLY JUST WOULD'VE STEPPED ASIDE.
OH, DON'T SAY THAT.
DON'T SAY THAT.
THAT'S NOT TRUE, IS IT?
YEAH. HE LOVES YOU. YEAH.
WELL, WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME TO DO THAT?!
I DON'T KNOW.
I I SAID SOMETHING TO PHOEBE.
THAT'S RIGHT, AND I THOUGHT IT WAS A REALLY GOOD IDEA.
YEAH, I REMEMBER.
YOU DID.
OH, MY GOD!
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?
WELL, CHANDLER
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO TELL HIM.
WHY? WHY DO I HAVE TO TELL HIM?
BECAUSE YOU DO.
YEAH, I KNOW.
HEY.
WOULD IT BE OKAY IF I WROTE A SONG ABOUT THIS?
I DON'T KNOW IF THIS IS WORKING OUT.
I THINK... I THINK I WANT TO SEE OTHER PEOPLE.
WOW! DIDN'T SEE THAT COMING.
IT'S NOT THAT I DON'T ENJOY THIS.
I DO.
I JUST WANT TO SEE WHAT ELSE IS OUT THERE.
HEY. HEY, GUY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I WORK ACROSS THE STREET.
YOU KNOW WHAT? IT TURNS OUT I'M GOING TO BE FREE SUNDAY.
OH, YOU KNOW, I WISH YOU HAD CALLED ME.
I JUST TOLD THEM I'D WORK THIS WEEKEND.
OH. OKAY. WELL, MAYBE NEXT WEEKEND.
DEFINITELY.
I'LL SEE YOU. OKAY.
YEAH, YOU'LL BE TALKING TO ME NEVER
BECAUSE YOU'RE A FREAK WHO EATS ALONE.
HEY.
Wonder  Steve?
SAMBUCA MARGARITA?
Are you here?
IS THAT A REAL THING?
WELL, WE ONLY HAD SAMBUCA, SO IT IS NOW.
LISTEN, UH, JOE, I I NEED TO--
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT SOMETHING.
WHAT'S UP?
IT'S, IT'S ABOUT KATHY.
UM...
UH...
I LIKE HER.
I LIKE HER A LOT, ACTUALLY.
YOU DO?
YEAH.
WELL, YOUR TIMING COULDN'T BE BETTER
BECAUSE SHE'S NOT MY GIRLFRIEND ANYMORE.
WHAT?
YEAH, SHE BROKE UP WITH ME.
OH, UH... WHEN?
JUST NOW, AFTER ACTING CLASS.
AT FIRST, I THOUGHT SHE WAS DOING SOME KIND OF SCENE.
THAT'S WHY I LET PEOPLE WATCH.
OH... MAN, I AM SO SORRY.
ARE YOU, ARE ARE YOU OKAY?
I'VE BEEN BETTER, YOU KNOW, BUT I'M ALL RIGHT.
SO, YOU LIKE HER, HUH?
YES, BUT I, I, I DON'T HAVE TO.
NO, NO, NO.
IT'S, UH...
IT'S OKAY.
YEAH?
YEAH.
YOU KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE YOU CAME TO ME FIRST.
WELL, I THOUGHT THAT WOULD BE THE BEST THING TO DO.
BUT, HEY, LISTEN, JUST SO YOU KNOW--
YOU MIGHT HAVE YOUR WORK CUT OUT FOR YOU
BECAUSE, WHEN I TALKED TO HER
I KIND OF GOT THE FEELING
SHE'S INTO SOME OTHER GUY, SO...
SEE, UH, THAT'S, THAT'S ACTUALLY
WHAT I WANTED TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT.
I I THINK I KNOW WHO THE OTHER GUY IS.
WHO?
IT'S ME.
I'M THE OTHER GUY.
WHAT?
YEAH, I MEAN, WHEN YOU WERE LATE LAST NIGHT
KATHY AND I GOT TO TALKING AND...
ONE THING LED TO ANOTHER AND...
AND WHAT?
DID YOU SLEEP WITH HER?
NO! NO, NO, I JUST KISSED HER.
WHAT?! THAT'S EVEN WORSE!
HOW IS THAT WORSE?!
I DON'T KNOW, BUT IT'S THE SAME!
LOOK, I'M SORRY, BUT THERE WAS NOTHING I COULD DO.
I THINK I'M IN LOVE WITH HER.
WHO CARES! YOU WENT BEHIND MY BACK?!
I'D NEVER DO THAT TO YOU!
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I HAVE NO EXCUSES.
I WAS TOTALLY OVER THE LINE.
"OVER THE LINE"?
Y Y YOU'RE, YOU'RE SO FAR PAST THE LINE
THAT YOU CAN'T EVEN SEE THE LINE!
THE LINE IS A DOT TO YOU.
YES.
YES, RIGHT, AND I FEEL HORRIBLE.
YOU HAVE TO BELIEVE ME.
OH, MY GOD.
IS THAT WHY YOU BOUGHT ALL THIS STUFF?!
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I WILL NOT WATCH YOUR TV, I WILL NOT LISTEN TO YOUR STEREO
AND THERE'S A CINNAMON RAISIN LOAF IN THE NEW BREAD MAKER
THAT I'M NOT GOING TO EAT!
YOU KNOW WHY?
PROBABLY BECAUSE...
BECAUSE IT'S ALL TAINTED
WITH YOUR BETRAYAL.
FROM NOW ON, THIS APARTMENT IS EMPTY TO ME!
I'M NOT HAPPY ABOUT YOU EITHER.
OH, AND JUST SO YOU KNOW...
I MADE THAT BREAD FOR YOU.
OH, MY GOD. HE'S LOST IT.
HE'S TOTALLY LOST IT.
WHAT?
PHOEBE, THIS IS MUSIC
THAT CANNOT GET ANY WORSE.
THERE ARE RATS IN THE BASEMENT
THAT ARE HANGING THEMSELVES.
THANK YOU.
THANKS.
YEAH, I LOST IT.
YOU KNOW, I'M NOT GOING TO PLAY ANYMORE.
WOULD YOU...?
CAN YOU FINISH MY SET?
AFTER THAT? YEAH!
NO, I MEAN, IF I CAN HELP, YEAH.
YEAH, LIKE I COULD LOSE IT.
WHAT?
I PLAYED BAD ON PURPOSE, GUYS.
OH! OH!
OKAY, SO YOU WERE TRYING TO PLAY BAD THIS WHOLE TIME?
NO, JUST THAT LAST SONG.