OH, MAN!
WHAT IS THAT?
TREEGER'S SNAKING THE SHOWER DRAIN.
OH.
WHAT IN THE NAME
OF HELL...?!
HEY, MAYBE HE FOUND YOUR FLIP FLOP.
HEY...
WHOA.
IS THIS PORN?
WHAT DID I DO?
I MUST'VE HIT SOMETHING ON THE REMOTE.
DO WE PAY FOR THIS?
NO. WE DIDN'T EVEN PAY OUR CABLE BILL.
MAYBE THIS IS HOW THEY PUNISH US.
MAYBE WE SHOULDN'T PAY OUR PHONE BILL.
FREE PHONE SEX.
MAYBE WE SHOULDN'T PAY OUR GAS BILL.
WHOA, HEY, THAT LADY'S ALL KINDS OF NAKED.
YEAH. JOEY JUST PRESSED SOMETHING ON THE REMOTE
AND IT JUST... CAME ON.
HEY, THAT HAPPENED TO ME ONCE.
I WAS JUST FLIPPING THROUGH THE CHANNELS, AND BAM!
IT WAS LIKE FINDING MONEY.
LIKE FINDING MONEY WITH NAKED PEOPLE ON IT.
THEN I MADE THE MISTAKE OF TURNING OFF THE TV.
I NEVER GOT IT BACK AGAIN.
AND I'M SAD.
WHY WOULD HE TURN OFF THE TV?
TELEVISION
ALL RIGHT, YOU KNOW WHAT?
COME ON, DO WE REALLY HAVE TO WATCH THIS WHILE WE EAT?
NO! NO! NO! NO! NO! NO! NO!
WE DON'T KNOW WHAT COULD MAKE THIS GO AWAY.
YEAH, SO NO ONE TOUCHES THE REMOTE
AND NO ONE TOUCHES THE TV.
AND NO ONE TOUCHES THE AIR... AROUND THE TV.
IMAGINE A PROTECTIVE PORN BUBBLE, IF YOU WILL.
OKAY?
I'M AT LEAST GOING TO MUTE IT.
NO NO NO! NO NO NO!
WE STILL HAVE PORN. YEAH.
HI. HEY.
HONEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
THAT'S TOO HEAVY.
COME HERE.
THANKS.
OH, GOD...
OKAY.
OH, HONEY...
I'M GETTING TOO PREGNANT FOR THIS...
LUGGING AROUND A STUPID MASSAGE TABLE.
I HAVE TO FIND A JOB WHERE I CARRY A SMALLER TABLE.
OR A JOB
WHERE YOU DON'T HAVE TO CARRY A TABLE.
YOU MEAN
LIKE A DOCTOR?
PHEEBS, YOU'RE BLOCKING THE PORN.
LOOK OUT.
OHH.
OH, MY.
OH, THAT REMINDS ME-- I HAVE TO SEE MY OB GYN TODAY.
HI.
SO, UH, EMILY JUST WENT TO THE AIRPORT.
OH. WHY DIDN'T YOU TAKE HER?
HER UNCLE HAD ALREADY PLANNED ON DOING IT
AND, YOU KNOW, WE SAID OUR GOOD BYES THIS MORNING, SO...
YOU MUST FEEL HORRIBLE.
HEY, THE GUYS HAVE FREE PORN.
NO...
HEY, CHEER UP.
YOU'RE GOING TO SEE HER AGAIN, RIGHT?
WELL, I... THAT'S THE THING.
I DON'T KNOW.
WHEN I BROUGHT IT UP, SHE SAID "THIS IS SO FANTASTIC.
"WHY DO WE HAVE TO TALK ABOUT THE FUTURE?
LET'S JUST ENJOY..."
NO, YOU... D DON'T DO THE ACCENT.
IT REALLY BUMS ME OUT.
EMILY SAID I WAS PRETTY GOOD.
WELL, THAT'S SOMEONE YOU SHOULD HANG ON TO.
YOU HAVE TO SEE HER AGAIN.
WHY DO YOU CARE SO MUCH?
BECAUSE...
YOU COULD GET TO LIVE OUT MY FANTASY.
YOU'VE HAD FANTASIES ABOUT EMILY?
NO. YOU KNOW.
THE FANTASY.
MEET SOMEONE FROM A STRANGE LAND, FALL IN LOVE
AND SPEND THE REST OF YOUR LIVES TOGETHER.
IS THAT WHY, IN JUNIOR HIGH, YOU WERE THE ONLY ONE
WHO HUNG OUT WITH THAT UKRAINIAN KID?
YEAH, THAT, BUT...
PLUS HIS MOM USED TO PUT SOUR CREAM ON EVERYTHING.
AH...
DO YOU LOVE HER?
WE SAID IT WAS ONLY GOING TO BE TWO WEEKS, YOU KNOW?
YOU LOVE HER.
WHA WHAT IS LOVE, REALLY?
OH...
I KNEW YOU LOVED HER.
YOU NEED TO GO TO THE AIRPORT AND TELL HER.
YOU'LL PROBABLY CATCH HER
JUST AS SHE'S ABOUT TO GO TO THE GATE.
YOU'RE GOING TO CALL OUT HER NAME, AND YELL
"I LOVE YOU," AND SHE'S GOING TO SAY "I LOVE YOU, TOO"
AND THEN YOU GUYS ARE GOING TO HAVE
THE MOST AMAZING KISS.
EVERYONE AT THE GATE WILL APPLAUD.
I AM A GOOD KISSER.
WELL, THEN YOU TWO CAN...
CAN SNEAK INTO THE COCKPIT...
THINGS'LL START TO HEAT UP...
THEN A STEWARDESS COMES IN...
I'VE BEEN WATCHING TOO MUCH PORN.
IS THAT THE HEARTBEAT? THAT'S IT.
OH, MY GOD!
OH, WOW, THIS IS SO COOL.
HAVE WE TALKED ABOUT THE POSSIBILITY
OF MULTIPLE BIRTHS?
WELL, WHY DON'T WE JUST TAKE CARE OF THIS ONE
AND SHOULD I GET PREGNANT AGAIN, I'LL HOLD ON TO YOUR CARD, OKAY?
NO.
I'M GETTING THREE SEPARATE HEARTBEATS.
THREE? YOU GUYS WERE WORRIED I WOULDN'T EVEN HAVE ONE.
DOCTORS ARE WRONG ALL THE TIME.
WELL...
WELL, SO ARE YOU SURE THAT THERE ARE THREE?
DEFINITELY.
OH, MY GOD.
SO... SO IN A FEW MONTHS
I'M GOING TO HAVE THREE FULL GROWN BABIES
JUST WALKING AROUND INSIDE ME?
OH, OH! AND IT'S GOING TO BE LIKE ONE OF THOSE LOG RIDES
WHERE THEY JUST COME SHOOTING OUT.
GIVING BIRTH TO THREE BABIES
IS NOT THAT DIFFERENT THAN GIVING BIRTH TO ONE.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
HAVE YOU EVER HAD TRIPLETS?
NO. I'M SORRY. I HAVEN'T.
I'M GOING TO USE THIS A LOT.
OH, OH... PHOEBE.
OH! HI.
HI!
SO, HOW'D IT GO AT THE DOCTOR'S?
OH, WELL, OKAY.
HEY, YOU KNOW HOW WHEN YOU'RE
UM, YOU'RE WALKING DOWN THE STREET
AND YOU SEE THREE PEOPLE IN A ROW
AND YOU SAY, "OH, THAT'S NICE"?
YES! OKAY.
YEAH, WELL
GOOD NEWS-- YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE THREE BABIES. AH!
THREE BABIES?
UH HUH.
OH... I FINALLY GOT MY BAND!
OH, OH...
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE A BIG FAMILY.
I ALWAYS WANTED A BIG FAMILY!
OH, GOD
I'M SO GLAD YOU GUYS ARE HAPPY.
I WAS SO AFRAID YOU WERE GOING TO BE ALL FREAKED.
WHY WOULD WE BE FREAKED?
NO, BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, MAYBE IT'S HARDER
TO RAISE THEM, AND THE ADDED EXPENSE AND, UGH!
OH.
RIGHT.
NO. BACK TO HAPPY.
BACK TO HAPPY!
NO, NO, NO, NO...
IT'S GOING TO BE FINE BECAUSE, UM...
BECAUSE I TEACH HOME EC
AND, UH, I CAN HAVE 30 KIDS
MAKING BABY CLOTHES ALL YEAR LONG.
YOU KNOW, IT'LL BE LIKE...
MY VERY OWN LITTLE SWEATSHOP.
I BEEN THINKING, EVER SINCE YOU SAID
THAT WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TRIPLETS...
THE BEST THING FOR ME TO DO IS
DROP OUT OF COLLEGE AND GET A JOB.
NO, FRANK.
NO, YOU CAN'T QUIT COLLEGE. NO.
YOU'RE IN COLLEGE, REALLY?
YEAH. REFRIGERATOR COLLEGE.
YEAH.
YEAH, YOU KNOW
WHEN WE FOUND OUT
WE WERE GOING TO HAVE A BABY, YOU KNOW
I FIGURED, YOU KNOW, LIKE, I SHOULD HAVE...
LIKE A CAREER, YOU KNOW
AND I LOVE REFRIGERATORS.
YOU CAN'T GIVE UP ON YOUR DREAM.
NO, IT'S OKAY.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE THREE KIDS
AND THAT'S A DIFFERENT KIND OF DREAM.
THREE KIDS AND NO MONEY.
This is the boarding call
for flight 0-0-9.
EMILY...
OH, MY GOD, WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I JUST... I HAD TO SEE YOU ONE MORE TIME
BEFORE YOU TOOK OFF.
YOU ARE SO SWEET.
THAT'S THAT'S A BIG CANDY BAR.
I HAD THE MOST AMAZING TIME WITH YOU.
ME, TOO.
This is the final boarding call
for flight 0-0-9.
WELL, THAT'S ME.
HERE, HAVE THIS-- I'M ONLY ALLOWED
ONE PIECE OF CARRY ON ANYWAY.
WAIT.
UH... LISTEN, I I...
I HAVE TO TELL YOU SOMETHING. UM...
I'VE BEEN THINKING.
I'M JUST GOING TO COME OUT AND SAY IT, OKAY?
UH... I... I THINK...
I LOVE YOU.
OH.
THANK YOU.
IT'S NO PROBLEM.
?? BOW CHICKA BOW WOW ??
?? BOW CHICKA BOW WOW. ??
WHAT IS THAT SONG?
IT'S BEEN IN MY HEAD ALL DAY.
IT'S THE THEME FROM GOOD WILL HUMPING.
YOU KNOW WHO DOESN'T EVEN LIKE DIRTY MOVIES?
MY NEW BOYFRIEND, JOSHUA.
YEAH, RIGHT.
NO, HE TOLD ME
HE PREFERS TO LEAVE CERTAIN THINGS
TO THE IMAGINATION.
OH, OH, YEAH, AND DID HE ALSO SAY
THAT HE THOUGHT THAT SOME OF THE DIALOGUE WAS CORNY
AND THAT HE ACTUALLY FOUND IT FUNNY, NOT SEXY?
YES!
YEAH, HE LIKES PORN.
WHERE YOU GOING?
I'M GOING TO FIND OUT IF HE REALLY THINKS
SUPER MODELS ARE TOO SKINNY.
HEY. HEY.
HI.
HOW'D IT GO WITH FRANK AND ALICE?
WELL, FRANK HAS TO QUIT COLLEGE
BECAUSE HIS SUPER FERTILE SISTER'S
HAVING THREE BABIES. UGH.
SO I NEED TO MAKE A LOT OF MONEY REALLY FAST
AND I HAD AN IDEA THAT I WANTED TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT
BECAUSE YOU WORK FOR A BIG COMPANY.
OKAY. INSIDER TRADING.
WHAT INFORMATION IS THERE
THAT YOU CAN GIVE ME?
THEY DON'T REALLY TALK TO US ABOUT THAT STUFF.
I COULD GET YOU SOME FREE WITE OUT, THOUGH.
DID YOU DO WHAT I SAID?
DID YOU TELL HER? I DID.
AND...? WHAT'D SHE SAY?
THANK YOU.
YOU'RE TOTALLY WELCOME.
WHAT'D SHE SAY?
SHE SAID, "THANK YOU."
I SAID, "I LOVE YOU"
AND SHE SAID...
"THANK YOU."
WELL, THAT'S NOT RIGHT.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
DID YOU SAY YOU LOVE HER?
YEAH, WHAT WERE YOU TRYING TO GET HER TO DO?
WHAT DO I DO NOW?
YOU PLAY HARD TO GET.
SHE ALREADY LIVES IN LONDON.
SO YOU GO TO TOKYO.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK. FORGET IT.
OKAY? FORGET IT.
YOU TOLD HER YOU LOVE HER. IT'S OVER.
IT IS NOT OVER.
YOU'RE OVER.
WHAT?
YOU KNOW.
OKAY.
GOOD ONE.
IT IS NOT OVER BECAUSE SHE'S GOING TO CALL YOU
AND TELL YOU SHE LOVES YOU, AND THE REASON SHE COULDN'T
IS HER FEELINGS WERE SO STRONG IT SCARED HER.
GO HOME AND WAIT FOR HER CALL.
SHE COULD BE CALLING FROM THE PLANE.
COME ON, NOW. GO, GO.
OKAY, OKAY
BUT IF SHE DOESN'T CALL, IT IS DEFINITELY OVER.
NO, WAIT, WAIT-- UNLESS, EVENTUALLY
I CALL HER, YOU KNOW, TO TO SEE WHAT'S GOING ON
AND AND SHE SAYS SHE'LL CALL ME BACK
BUT THEN SHE DOESN'T
THEN... IT'S OVER.
WAY TO BE STRONG, MAN.
HI.
HI. HEY.
CAN WE WATCH CARTOONS ON YOUR TELEVISION?
WE NEED A PORN BREAK.
WE SPENT THE LAST TWO HOURS
WATCHING IN AND OUT AND IN AGAIN.
WELL, SO, WHY DON'T YOU JUST TURN IT OFF?
BECAUSE THEN WE'D BE THE GUYS
WHO TURNED OFF FREE PORN.
YEAH, BUT THAT'S NOT, LIKE, WHAT YOU GO BY.
RACH, LOOK, I'M GOING TO HAVE A KID SOMEDAY, OKAY?
AND, SOMEDAY, THAT KID IS GOING TO ASK ME
IF I EVER TURNED OFF FREE PORN.
I DON'T WANT
TO HAVE TO TELL HIM THAT I DID.
DID YOU EVER ASK YOUR DAD THAT?
I DON'T WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT.
OH! GOOD. YOU'RE HERE.
HI. HEY, HI.
WHAT YOU GOT THERE?
OH, THIS?
WELL, I'M GLAD YOU ASKED.
NOW, DON'T YOU HATE IT
WHEN YOU HAVE TO CUT A TIN CAN
WITH AN ORDINARY STEAK KNIFE?
HA.
NOW, I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE THINKING.
PREGNANT WOMAN SLAYS FOUR?
PHOEBE, THEY DIDN'T
MAKE YOU PAY FOR THOSE KNIVES, DID THEY?
NO.
ARE YOU SURE?
HONEY, YOU WON'T MAKE
ENOUGH MONEY TO HELP FRANK AND ALICE
JUST BY SELLING KNIVES.
NO, NO. I KNOW THAT.
I JUST NEED TO MAKE ENOUGH FOR THE SECOND PART OF MY PLAN.
WHAT'S THE SECOND PART?
MY SATURN DEALERSHIP.
HELLO.
ROSS.
EMILY, HI.
UH...
HOW WAS, HOW WAS YOUR FLIGHT?
It was dreadful.
I FELT TERRIBLE ABOUT HOW I ACTED
WHEN YOU SAID THOSE WONDERFUL THINGS.
NO, NO. TH THAT'S THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
UM... I'M JUST GLAD YOU CALLED.
Ross, um...
there's something that I I've got to tell you.
UH, THERE'S THERE'S SOMEONE ELSE.
DOES THAT MEAN THE SAME THING IN ENGLAND
AS IT DOES IN AMERICA?
SHE DOESN'T KNOW WHICH ONE OF US SHE WANTS--
ME OR THIS COLIN GUY.
SO I TOLD HER, WHEN SHE FIGURES IT OUT
GIVE ME A CALL.
MAYBE I'LL STILL BE AROUND.
OKAY, JUST SO I KNOW, WHEN YOU SAY "STILL AROUND"
DO YOU MEAN STILL AROUND
LIKE YOU MIGHT BE IN A RELATIONSHIP
OR STILL AROUND LIKE YOU MIGHT HAVE DIED
WAITING FOR THE PHONE TO RING?
OH, IT WAS SO RIGHT.
THIS ISN'T HOW IT WAS SUPPOSED TO GO.
THERE CAN'T BE ANOTHER GUY.
WELL.
OF COURSE THERE'S ANOTHER GUY!
THIS IS EVEN MORE PERFECT.
NOW YOU HAVE TO PROVE YOUR LOVE.
I'M NOT PROVING ANYTHING, OKAY?
I'M DONE LISTENING TO YOU.
IF I HADN'T LET YOU TALK ME INTO GOING
TO THE AIRPORT IN THE FIRST PLACE
I NEVER WOULD HAVE PUT MY FIST THROUGH THE WALL.
YOU PUT YOUR FIST THROUGH THE WALL?
NO, I MISSED AND HIT THE DOOR...
BUT IT OPENED REALLY HARD.
YOU HAVE TO GO TO LONDON.
WHAT?
YEAH, YOU HAVE TO GO FIGHT FOR HER.
OH, YEAH, THAT MAKES SENSE.
YOU ALREADY TOLD HER YOU LOVED HER
AND SHE DIDN'T SAY IT BACK.
THEN SHE CALLED AND TOLD YOU THERE WAS ANOTHER GUY
SO, YEAH, GO TO LONDON; THAT'LL SCARE HER.
WHEN RACHEL WAS WITH PAOLO, WHAT DID YOU DO?
I MADE FUN OF HIS ACCENT.
YOU SAT BACK AND LET HIM HAVE HER.
YOU DIDN'T FIGHT AT ALL; AM I RIGHT?
I JUST TOLD YOU
I MADE FUN OF  HIM BEHIND HIS BACK.
OH, I SEE.
YOU WANT THE SAME THING
TO HAPPEN WITH EMILY?
NO. ALL RIGHT, THEN.
GO FIGHT FOR HER. WHOA!
OH, MAN.
IT'S LIKE A SNAKE PIT.
THAT COULD BE YOU AND EMILY.
THAT, BUT BUT NICER.
JUST GO TO LONDON.
REALLY?
COME ON, SURPRISE HER.
SHOW UP AT HER DOORSTEP.
DON'T LET HER GO WITHOUT A FIGHT.
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, I'M GOING TO DO IT.
I'M GOING TO... I'M GOING TO GO TO LONDON
AND I AM GOING TO FIGHT FOR HER.
OKAY. GOOD LUCK.
ROSS. ROSS!
IF YOU'RE GOING TO THE AIRPORT
CAN YOU PICK ME UP ANOTHER ONE OF THOSE TOBLERONE BARS?
OH, OH! I DID IT. I DID IT.
I FIGURED OUT A WAY TO MAKE MONEY.
I'M GOING TO OPEN UP MY OWN MASSAGE PLACE
AND FRANK'S GOING TO HELP ME.
AND WE CAN WORK IT  AROUND HIS SCHEDULE
SO HE DOESN'T HAVE TO QUIT SCHOOL.
?? LA LA LA LA! ??
THAT SOUNDS GREAT, BUT HOW ARE YOU GOING TO AFFORD IT?
WE WERE WALKING DOWN THE STREET
AND SAW THAT VAN YOU USED FOR CATERING
AND WE REALIZED THAT...
I'M TELLING IT!
OKAY.
OKAY, YOU KNOW HOW PEOPLE NEED TRANSPORTATION
BUT THEY ALSO NEED MASSAGES TO RELAX.
SO I JUST FIGURED WE CAN COMBINE THE TWO.
OKAY? I GIVE THE MASSAGES AND FRANK DRIVES.
I CAN FIX UP THE VAN
BOLT A TABLE IN BACK, AND YOU KNOW WHAT I'VE GOT?
A PLACE THAT NO ONE WILL EVER GET OUT OF ALIVE?
WELL, NO.
THINK ABOUT IT.
IT'S A TAXI THAT PEOPLE TAKE WHEN THEY NEED TORELAX.
IT'S A RELAXI TAXI.
THE NAME IS MY FAVORITE PART!
WELL WELL, I CAME UP WITH IT.
YOU DID NOT!
OH! WHAT?!
NO!
YOU CAME UP WITH "RELAXI CAB."
THAT'S NOT GOOD.
WELL...
HELLO.
OH, MY GOD.
ROSS, ARE YOU IN ENGLAND?
WAS EMILY SURPRISED?
NO, BECAUSE SHE HASN'T COME HOME YET.
SHE HASN'T BEEN HOME ALL NIGHT.
SHE'S OBVIOUSLY STAYING WITH THAT OTHER GUY
AND I'M THE STUPID MORON
WHO SPENT THE WHOLE NIGHT OUTSIDE HER PLACE.
WHAT WAS THAT?
I JUST PUT MY FIST THROUGH ANOTHER WALL.
TELL THE GUY.
ALL RIGHT, WHEN IS THE NEXT FLIGHT OUT?
ABOUT FOUR HOURS.
Stay a couple more hours
and if she doesn't show up by then, just come home.
OH, I JUST REMEMBERED.
THERE'S A GIRL AT THE RESTAURANT
THAT WOULD BE PERFECT FOR YOU.
HEY, TELL HIM ABOUT RELAXI TAXI
AND ASK HIM IF HE THINKS THAT'S BETTER THAN RELAXI CAB.
OKAY, IT'S NOT RELAXI CAB.
IT'S RELAXI CAB-- LIKE TAXICAB.
OH, THAT IS BETTER.
DO YOU HAVE ANY EIGHTS?
NOPE.
ARE WE IN LONDON?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
YOU CAN'T BE HERE.
I'VE, UH... I'VE COME TO TALK TO ROSS.
WHAT?
NOTHING. NO, NOTHING.
UM, I WAS GOING TO CALL HIM, BUT...
HA! YOU CAME TO TELL HIM YOU LOVE HIM.
I KNEW IT!
I WAS RIGHT!
I'M RIGHT, RIGHT?
I'D REALLY RATHER TALK TO HIM.
I, UH... I'VE BEEN TO HIS APARTMENT
AND HE'S NOT THERE AND, UH, I NEED TO TALK TO HIM, SO...
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA WHERE HE IS?
Ross, are you there?
Ross...
I don't know if you can hear this
but I'm going to talk anyway.
I'M IN THE STATES
WITH YOUR SISTER AND YOUR FRIENDS
AND... IT'S ALL OVER WITH COLIN.
I came here to tell you that and to tell you--
What?
Yes, Joey, you can have all the chocolate you want.
Just take it.
UM...
I CAME HERE TO TELL YOU...
THAT I LOVE YOU.
I LOVE YOU, TOO!
I'M I'M GOING TO CALL YOU RIGHT NOW
FROM THE PHONE BOOTH.
YOU CAN'T HEAR ME...
I WISH I COULD KNOW IF YOU'D HEARD THAT.
I'VE EITHER TOLD YOU I LOVE YOU
OR GIVEN MY NEIGHBORS A GOOD LAUGH.
MRS. NEWMAN, IF YOU'RE LISTENING, BUGGER OFF.
THIS IS NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS.
I SUPPOSE THERE'S NOT MUCH CHANCE
YOU DID HEAR THAT AND...
THERE'S THE CALL WAITING, SO...
I SHOULD GO.
OH, WELL.
HELLO.
Hi.
ROSS, I LOVE YOU.
OH...
THANK YOU.
HEY.
I WAS JUST AT THE BANK
AND THERE WAS THIS REALLY HOT TELLER
AND SHE DIDN'T ASK ME TO GO DO IT WITH HER IN THE VAULT.
SAME KIND OF THING HAPPENED TO ME.
WOMAN PIZZA DELIVERY GUY COMES OVER
GIVES ME THE PIZZA, TAKES THE MONEY AND LEAVES.
WHAT? NO, LIKE, "NICE APARTMENT.
BET THE BEDROOMS ARE HUGE"?
NO. NOTHING.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
WE HAVE TO TURN OFF THE PORN.
I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT. READY?
ONE...
TWO...
THREE. THREE.
THAT'S KIND OF NICE.
YEAH, IT'S KIND OF A RELIEF.
YEAH.
YOU WANT TO SEE IF WE STILL HAVE IT?
FREE PORN! WE HAVE FREE PORN!
YEAH! YES!
THERE'S ONE, TWO, AND THREE...
OH, MY GOD...
OH, THAT'S SO BEAUTIFUL.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
YEAH, I KNOW.
I LIKE THE MID DLE ONE THE BEST.
DON'T WORRY. I WON'T LET THE OTHER TWO KNOW.