OKAY, SO WE WENT TO THE BEACH
BECAUSE PHOEBE FOUND OUT ABOUT THIS LADY
WHO KNEW HER MOM AND DAD.
AND I DON'T REALLY KNOW WHAT HAPPENED WITH THAT.
I'M YOUR MOTHER.
HUH?
THEN MONICA JOKED THAT SHE WOULDN'T GO OUT
WITH A GUY LIKE CHANDLER
AND HE COULDN'T LET GO.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED WITH THAT EITHER.
THEN ROSS' NEW GIRLFRIEND BONNIE SHOWS UP
AND RACHEL CONVINCED HER TO SHAVE HER HEAD.
THEN ROSS AND RACHEL KISS.
NOW ROSS HAS TO CHOOSE BETWEEN RACHEL AND THE BALD GIRL.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED THERE EITHER.
YOU KNOW WHAT? HOLD ON.
I'M GOING TO GO GET CHANDLER.
HI.
HEY. HI.
RACHEL WAS JUST HELPING ME OUT.
MY HEAD GOT ALL SUNBURNED.
AW.
THANKS A MILLION.
OH, YOU'RE WELCOME A MILLION.
SMELL IT.
MMM! MINTY.
OKAY, I'LL BE IN OUR ROOM.
OKAY.
OH, MY GOD.
I KNOW.
OKAY, I GOT TO GO.
ROSS... WHAT?
I GOT TO GO BREAK UP WITH BONNIE.
HERE? NOW?
WELL, YEAH.
I CAN'T STAY HERE ALL NIGHT.
IF I GO IN THERE, SHE'S GOING TO WANT TO...
DO STUFF.
CAN'T YOU JUST TELL HER
THAT YOU ARE NOT IN THE MOOD?
NO, SHE LIKES THAT.
FAKING SLEEP DOESN'T WORK EITHER.
I CAN'T TELL YOU HOW MANY MORNINGS I WOKE UP WITH HER...
EW.
OKAY.
WHY AM I TELLING YOU THAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
UM...
IT WASN'T EVERY MORNING.
OH, MAKING IT WORSE.
OKAY.
SO I GUESS YOU'D LIKE TO KNOW HOW IT ALL HAPPENED.
I I MEAN, I THINK I CAN FIGURE IT OUT.
I GUESS I WAS BORN
AND THEN EVERYONE STARTED LYING THEIR ASSES OFF.
NO, NO, NO. IT WASN'T LIKE THAT.
REMEMBER HOW I TOLD YOU HOW LILY AND FRANK AND I--
WE WERE CLOSE?
WELL, WE WERE VERY CLOSE.
HOW CLOSE?
WELL, THE THREE OF US--
WE WERE KIND OF A COUPLE.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW HOW THAT WOULD WORK.
WELL, WE WOULD...
I'M NOT ASKING.
WELL, ANYHOW, SOMEHOW, I GOT PREGNANT
AND I WAS...
SCARED.
I WAS STUPID AND SELFISH AND...
I WAS 18 YEARS OLD.
I MEAN, YOU REMEMBER WHAT IT WAS LIKE
TO BE 18 YEARS OLD, DON'T YOU?
YEAH.
LET'S SEE...
MY MOM HAD KILLED HERSELF AND MY DAD HAD RUN OFF
AND I WAS LIVING IN A GREMLIN WITH A GUY NAMED CINDY
WHO TALKED TO HIS HAND.
OH, I'M SO SORRY.
I THOUGHT I WAS LEAVING YOU
WITH THE BEST PARENTS IN THE WORLD.
I DIDN'T EVEN HEAR ABOUT YOUR MOM AND DAD
TILL A COUPLE OF YEARS AGO.
BY THEN, YOU WERE ALREADY GROWN UP.
I DON'T KNOW, YOU'RE HERE
AND I WOULD REALLY...
I WOULD LIKE TO GET TO KNOW YOU.
YEAH, WELL, EVERYBODY DOES.
I'M A REALLY COOL PERSON.
AND, YOU KNOW, YOU HAD 29 YEARS TO FIND THAT OUT
BUT YOU DIDN'T EVEN TRY.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU WALKED OUT ON ME.
I'M DOING THE SAME TO YOU.
WAIT.
I DON'T EVER WANT TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
WHERE'S MY PURSE?
SHOOT. WE'RE OUT OF SODA.
I'LL GO OUT AND GET YOU SOME.
REALLY?
NOPE, BECAUSE I'M NOT YOUR BOYFRIEND.
HEY, PHEEBS, HOW'D IT GO?
WELL...
MY MOM'S FRIEND PHOEBE
IS ACTUALLY MY BIRTH MOM.
I FOUND A DRIED UP SEA HORSE.
SWEETIE, WHAT ARE
YOU TALKING ABOUT?
OH, MY NEW MOM
WHO'S A BIG, FAT ABANDONER.
WELL, PHEEBS, WAIT A SECOND.
DON'T YOU WANT TO STAY HERE AND TALK ABOUT IT?
NO. I WANT...
I NEED TO BE ALONE.
MONICA?!
OH.
MAN.
HEY, WHAT IF YOU FOUND OUT
THAT YOUR MOM WASN'T REALLY YOUR MOM
AND YOUR NEW MOM TURNED OUT TO BE REALLY HOT?
OH, MAN, HUH?
M. BUT IT'S YOUR MO
NO. I'M TALKING ABOUT YOUR MOM.
IT'S OVER.
OH. WAS IT AWFUL?
WELL, IT WAS LONG.
I DIDN'T EVEN REALIZE HOW LATE IT WAS
TILL I NOTICED THE 5:00 SHADOW
ON HER HEAD.
ANYWAY, SHE DIDN'T WANT TO STAY.
I CALLED A CAB.
SHE JUST LEFT.
I WROTE YOU A LETTER.
OH, THANK YOU.
I LIKE MAIL.
THERE'S JUST SOME THINGS I'VE BEEN THINKING ABOUT--
THINGS ABOUT US-- AND, BEFORE I CAN EVEN THINK
ABOUT THE TWO OF US GETTING BACK TOGETHER
I JUST NEED TO KNOW HOW YOU FEEL
ABOUT THIS STUFF.
OKAY.
IT'S...
IT'S 5:30 IN THE MORNING.
SO... I BETTER GET CRACKING ON THIS BABY.
SO, I'LL BE WAITING FOR YOU.
JUST COME UP WHEN YOU'RE DONE.
OKAY.
I'LL BE UP IN...
18 PAGES.
FRONT AND BACK.
IT'S VERY EXCITING.
OH, OH, OH.
HEY.
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
WHY DIDN'T YOU COME UP?
DONE.
YOU JUST FINISHED?
WELL, I WANTED TO BE THOROUGH.
I MEAN, THIS IS CLEARLY
.
VERY, VERY IMPORTANT TO YOU..
TO US.
.
SO I WANTED TO READ EVERY WORD CAREFULLY..
TWICE.
SO, UM...
DOES IT?
SORRY?
DOESIT?
YEAH, I WANTED TO GIVE THAT WHOLE "DOES IT" PART
JUST ANOTHER GLANCE.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT, ROSS?
YOU JUST SAID YOU READ IT TWICE.
LOOK, IT EITHER DOES OR IT DOESN'T
AND IF YOU HAVE TO EVEN THINK ABOUT IT...
NO, NO, RACH, NO, I DON'T.
I DON'T HAVE TO THINK ABOUT IT. I DON'T.
IN FACT...
I'VE DECIDED.
I HAVE DECIDED THAT...
THAT IT...
DOES.
ARE YOU SURE?
SURE, I'M SURE.
ALL RIGHT, THERE'S A NUCLEAR HOLOCAUST.
I'M THE LAST MAN ON EARTH.
WOULD YOU GO OUT WITH ME?
EHH.
I'VE GOT CANNED GOODS.
HEY, GUYS, TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
CHECK THIS BABY OUT.
DUG ME A HOLE.
EXCELLENT HOLE, JOE.
OH, NO!
MY HOLE!
OW! OW!
WHAT IS IT?
JELLYFISH STING!
IT HURTS! IT HURTS!
CAN WE HELP YOU?
YOU WANT US TO TAKE YOU BACK TO THE HOUSE?
IT'S, LIKE, TWO MILES.
AND I'M A LITTLE TIRED FROM DIGGING THE HOLE.
OW! OW!
DAMN THE JELLYFISH!
DAMN ALL THE JELLYFISH!
WE'VE GOT TO DO SOMETHING.
THERE'S ONLY ONE THING YOU CAN DO.
WHAT? WHAT IS IT?
YOU HAVE TO PEE ON IT.
WHAT?!
GROSS!
DON'T BLAME ME.
I SAW IT ON THE DISCOVERY CHANNEL.
YOU KNOW WHAT? HE'S RIGHT.
THERE'S SOMETHING LIKE AMMONIA IN THAT
THAT KILLS THE PAIN.
WELL, FORGET IT.
IT DOESN'T HURT THAT...
BAD!
IF YOU WANT SOME PRIVACY, YOU CAN USE MY HOLE.
WELL, I'M READY TO GET THE HELL OUT OF HERE.
OH...
ARE YOU...?
ARE YOU?!
OH, THAT'S SO GREAT!
OOH, NOT FOR BONNIE.
BUT FOR YOU, YAY.
HEY.
HOW WAS THE BEACH?
NOTHING. I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT HAPPENED?
NOTHING.
I'M GOING TO TAKE A SHOWER.
ME, TOO.
OKAY, I'M GOING TO PUT THIS IN THE CAR.
OH, I HAVE TO GO PACK.
OH.
AND IT REALLY DOES?
IT DOES.
IT REALLY AND TRULY DOES.
IT SO DOES NOT!
SHE WANTS ME TO TAKE RESPONSIBILITY
FOR EVERYTHING THAT WENT WRONG IN OUR RELATIONSHIP.
I MEAN, SHE GOES ON FOR FIVE PAGES
ABOUT HOW I WAS UNFAITHFUL TO HER.
WE WERE ON A BREAK!
OH, MY GOD! IF YOU SAY THAT ONE MORE TIME
I'M GOING TO BREAK UP WITH YOU.
FINE, FINE. BUT THIS BREAKUP WAS NOT ALL MY FAULT
AND SHE SAYS HERE
"IF YOU ACCEPT FULL RESPONSIBILITY..."
FULL RESPONSIBILITY!
"I CAN BEGIN TO TRUST YOU AGAIN.
"DOES THAT SEEM LIKE SOMETHING YOU CAN DO?
DOES IT?!"
NO?
YOU HAVE WHAT YOU WANT. YOU HAVE WHAT YOU WANT.
YOU'RE BACK WITH RACHEL.
IF YOU BRING THIS UP NOW
YOU WILL WRECK THE BEST THING THAT EVER HAPPENED TO YOU.
YEAH, I KNOW.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YEAH, I GUESS I'LL LET IT GO.
BUT YOU... YOU UNDERSTAND
HOW HARD IT IS TO FORGET ABOUT THIS.
SURE, IT'S HARD TO FORGET
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN YOU HAVE TO TALK ABOUT IT.
A LOT OF THINGS HAPPENED ON THAT TRIP
THAT WE SHOULD NEVER, EVER TALK ABOUT.
WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED ON THAT BEACH?
IT'S BETWEEN US AND THE SEA, ROSS.
HI, URSULA.
HEY.
OKAY, WELL, I KNOW
THAT WE HAVEN'T TALKED IN A LONG TIME
BUT, UM, OKAY...
OUR MOM IS NOT OUR BIRTH MOM.
THIS OTHER LADY IS OUR BIRTH MOM.
RIGHT. OKAY. THE ONE THAT LIVES IN MONTAUK. MM HMM.
YOU KNOW HER?
NO. I, UM, I READ ABOUT HER IN MOM'S SUICIDE NOTE.
THERE WAS A SUICIDE NOTE?
DO YOU STILL HAVE IT?
HANG ON.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU DIDN'T TELL ME
THERE WAS A SUICIDE NOTE.
YEAH. SO HOW HAVE YOU BEEN DOING?
I'VE... UH... SHUT UP.
"GOOD BYE, PHOEBE AND URSULA.
"I'LL MISS YOU.
P.S. YOUR MOM LIVES IN MONTAUK."
YOU JUST WROTE THIS!
WELL, IT'S PRETTY MUCH THE GIST...
EXCEPT FOR THE POEM.
YOU READ THE POEM, RIGHT?
NO.
ALL RIGHT. HANG ON.
PASS THE CHEESE, PLEASE.
MY GOD, YOU CAN'T EVEN LOOK AT ME, CAN YOU?
NOPE.
HEY, IT'S PHOEBE!
WE CAN TALK TO PHOEBE!
NO. I'M TOO DEPRESSED TO TALK.
I'LL GIVE YOU $1,000 TO TALK TO US.
HEY, YOU GUYS, WHAT DO YOU THINK
ABOUT MAKING THAT BEACH TRIP AN ANNUAL THING?
NO! NO! NO!
ALL RIGHT, WHAT HAPPENED OUT THERE?
WHAT?
WE TOOK A WALK.
NOTHING HAPPENED.
I CAME BACK WITH NOTHING ALL OVER ME.
COME ON.
COME ON, WHAT HAPPENED? JOEY?
ALL RIGHT. NO!
JOEY, WE SWORE WE'D NEVER TELL.
THEY'LL NEVER UNDERSTAND.
WELL, WE HAVE TO SAY SOMETHING.
WE HAVE TO GET IT OUT.
IT'S EATING ME ALIVE!
MONICA GOT STUNG BY A JELLYFISH.
ALL RIGHT!
ALL RIGHT.
I GOT STUNG.
STUNG BAD.
I COULDN'T STAND.
I... I COULDN'T WALK.
WE WERE TWO MILES FROM THE HOUSE.
WE WERE SCARED AND ALONE.
WE DIDN'T THINK WE COULD MAKE IT.
I WAS IN TOO MUCH PAIN.
AND I WAS TIRED FROM DIGGING THE HUGE HOLE.
AND THEN JOEY REMEMBERED SOMETHING.
I'D SEEN THIS THING ON THE DISCOVERY CHANNEL.
WAIT A MINUTE.
I SAW THAT.
ON THE DISCOVERY CHANNEL.
YEAH, ABOUT JELLYFISH, AND HOW IF YOU...
EWW!
YOU PEED ON YOURSELF?
EWW! EWW!
YOU CAN'T SAY THAT!
YOU DON'T KNOW!
I MEAN, I THOUGHT I WAS GOING TO PASS OUT FROM THE PAIN.
ANYWAY, I TRIED. ..
BUT I COULDN'T... BEND THAT WAY.
SO...
EWW! EWW! EWW!
THAT'S RIGHT. I STEPPED UP!
SHE'S MY FRIEND, AND SHE NEEDED HELP.
IF I HAD TO, I'D PEE ON ANY ONE OF YOU.
ONLY, UH...
I COULDN'T.
I GOT THE STAGE FRIGHT.
I WANTED TO HELP
BUT THERE WAS JUST TOO MUCH PRESSURE
SO... SO I, UH... I TURNED TO CHANDLER.
JOEY KEPT SCREAMING AT ME
"DO IT NOW! DO IT! DO IT!
DO IT NOW!"
SOMETIMES, LATE AT NIGHT
I CAN STILL HEAR THE SCREAMING.
THAT'S BECAUSE SOMETIMES
I JUST DO IT THROUGH MY WALL TO FREAK YOU OUT.
MAYBE THERE'S SOMEBODY THAT YOU GUYS COULD TO.
UP NO. WHO? IT'S NOT LIKE THEY HAVE A GRO
.
FOR PEOPLE LIKE US
YEAH, NO, THERE'S THIS GUY OWEN.
HE'S THE BEST.
I MIGHT HAVE HIS CARD.
??
?? ...AND FUCHSIA AND MAUVE
?? THOSE ARE THE 66 COLORS OF MY BEDROOM. ??
THANK YOU. THANK YOU.
OH, AND I INVITE ALL OF YOU
TO COUNT THE COLORS IN YOUR BEDROOM.
EXCEPT FOR YOU.
YOU GO AWAY.
I'LL GO IN A SECOND.
I JUST WANT TO TELL YOU
THAT THERE HASN'T BEEN A DAY
WHEN I DIDN'T REGRET GIVING YOU UP.
OKAY. BYE.
NO. I'M NOT DONE.
I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW
THAT THE REASON I NEVER LOOKED YOU UP WAS BECAUSE...
WELL, I WAS AFRAID THAT YOU WOULD REACT...
JUST, WELL, LIKE THE WAY YOU'RE REACTING RIGHT NOW
AND... CAN'T WE JUST
YOU KNOW, START FROM HERE, PLEASE?
NO.
OKAY.
SORRY.
BUT JUST ONE LAST THING.
YOU KNOW, YOU CAME LOOKING FOR FAMILY.
I'M FAMILY.
I'M IT.
WELL, NOW I'M DONE.
BUT IT'S NOT LIKE WE'RE LOSING ANYTHING, YOU KNOW?
YEAH, I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT'S NOT LIKE WE KNOW EACH OTHER OR ANYTHING
OR THAT WE HAVE ANYTHING IN COMMON.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW.
I MEAN, IT'S NOT LIKE
WE DON'T HAVE ANYTHING IN COMMON.
I MEAN, I LIKE PIZZA.
I...I LIKE PIZZA.
YOU DO? HA!
WAIT, I LIKE, UM, THE BEATLES.
OH, MY GOD, SO DO I!
OH, I KNEW IT!
WOW!
WAIT WAIT WAIT.
PUPPIES-- CUTE OR UGLY?
OH, SO CUTE.
UH HUH! WELL?
YOU SEE?
BUT I'M STILL... I'M MAD AT YOU.
I KNOW.
I'M MAD AT ME, TOO.
WELL, UM, DO YOU WANT TO GET SOMETHING TO EAT?
BECAUSE I'M KIND OF HUNGRY.
HEY! ME, TOO!
OH, UNCANNY.
GOD, LOOKS LIKE IT'S GOING TO RAIN
AND I DON'T HAVE MY UMBRELLA
ME, NEITHER. I REALLY HATE THAT.
ALL RIGHT, STOP IT. NOW YOU'RE JUST DOING IT
TO FREAK ME OUT.
OH, I MISSED YOU.
I MISSED YOU, TOO.
OH, I WAS SO NERVOUS ABOUT THAT LETTER.
BUT THE WAY YOU OWNED UP TO EVERYTHING
IT JUST... SHOWED ME
HOW MUCH YOU'VE GROWN, YOU KNOW?
I SUPPOSE.
.
NO, YOUHAVE, ROSS, YOU HAVE
YOU SHOULD GIVE YOURSELF CREDIT.
I MEAN, MY MOM NEVER THOUGHT  THIS WOULD WORK OUT.
SHE WAS ALL, "ONCE A CHEATER, ALWAYS A CHEATER."
MM HMM.
OH... I JUST WISH WE HADN'T LOST THOSE FOUR MONTHS.
BUT IF TIME WAS WHAT YOU NEEDED
JUST TO GAIN A LITTLE PERSPECTIVE...
WE WERE ON A BREAK!
COFFEE HOUSE?
YOU BET.
AND FOR THE RECORD, IT TOOK TWO PEOPLE
TO BREAK UP THIS RELATIONSHIP.
YOU AND THAT GIRL FROM THE COPY PLACE
WHICH, YESTERDAY, YOU TOOK FULL RESPONSIBILITY FOR.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT I WAS TAKING RESPONSIBILITY FOR, OKAY?
I DIDN'T FINISH THE WHOLE LETTER.
WHAT?
I FELL ASLEEP.
YOU FELL ASLEEP?
IT WAS 5:30 IN THE MORNING
AND YOU HAD RAMBLED ON FOR 18 PAGES...
FRONT AND BACK!
OH OH OH, AND BY THE WAY
Y O U APOSTROPHE R E
MEANS "YOU ARE."
Y O U R MEANS "YOUR."
HA! YOU KNOW, I CAN'T BELIEVE
I EVEN THOUGHT OF GETTING BACK TOGETHER WITH YOU.
WE ARE SO OVER.
OH... OH... OH...
FINE BY ME!
OH, AND HEY, THOSE LITTLE SPELLING TIPS
WILL COME IN HANDY
WHEN YOU'RE AT HOME ON SATURDAY NIGHTS
PLAYING SCRABBLE WITH MONICA!
HEY... SORRY!
I JUST FEEL BAD ABOUT ALL THAT SLEEP YOU'RE GOING TO MISS
WISHING YOU WERE WITH ME.
OH, NO NO NO, DON'T YOU WORRY ABOUT ME FALLING ASLEEP.
I STILL HAVE YOUR LETTER!
AND HEY, JUST SO YOU KNOW...
IT'S NOT THAT COMMON
IT DOESN'T HAPPEN TO EVERY GUY
AND IT IS A BIG DEAL!
I KNEW IT!
GIN.
WE WERE PLAYING GIN?
YOU KNOW, IF WE WERE A COUPLE
WE COULD PLAY THIS GAME NAKED.
WOULD YOU STOP?
OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
I THINK YOU'RE GREAT.
I THINK YOU'RE SWEET AND YOU'RE SMART
AND I LOVE YOU.
BUT YOU WILL ALWAYS BE THE GUY WHO PEED ON ME.