THE WALTHAM RESIDENCE.
OH, YES. IS THIS EMILY'S PARENTS' HOUSE?
This is the housekeeper speaking.
AND BY THE WAY, YOUNG LADY
THAT IS NOT HOW ONE ADDRESSES A PERSON ON THE TELEPHONE.
First, one identifies oneself
AND THEN ASKS FOR THE PERSON WITH WHOM ONE WISHES TO SPEAK.
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
NOW, LET US TRY THAT AGAIN, SHALL WE?
NO! OH!
OH, MY... GOD!
THE WALTHAM RESIDENCE.
Hello.
THIS IS PHOEBE BUFFAY.
I WAS WONDERING, PLEASE
IF IF IT'S NOT TOO MUCH TROUBLE, PLEASE
UM, IF, MIGHT I SPEAK WITH MISS EMILY WALTHAM, PLEASE?
MISS WALTHAM IS AT THE REHEARSAL DINNER
AND IT IS NOT POLITE TO MAKE FUN OF PEOPLE. GOOD BYE.
NO, NO! I'LL BE NICE, I SWEAR.
COULD YOU GIVE ME THE NUMBER WHERE THEY ARE?
I'M AFRAID I'M NOT AT LIBERTY TO DIVULGE THAT INFORMATION.
LOOK, SOMEBODY IS ON THEIR WAY TO RUIN THE WEDDING, OKAY?
AND I HAVE TO WARN SOMEBODY.
ALL RIGHT, SO IF YOU DON'T GIVE ME THAT NUMBER
THEN I'M GOING TO COME OVER THERE
AND I'M GOING TO KICK YOUR SNOOTY ASS
ALL THE WAY TO NEW... GLOUCKENSHIRE.
HELLO? HELLO? OH.
OOH, SHE KNEW I COULD KICK HER ASS.
HEY. HI...
SWEETHEART.
MOM... DAD...
OH, SORRY WE'RE LATE.
MY FAULT. I INSISTED ON RIDING THE TUBE.
JUDY, THE KIDS.
JACK, THAT'S WHAT THEY CALL THE SUBWAY.
OH. I THOUGHT...
DAD, DAD, WE GOT IT, WE GOT IT.
OH, HERE COMES  MY DAD AND STEPMOM.
MR. AND MRS. GELLER...
HI, HOW ARE YOU?
THIS IS STEVEN... AND ANDREA WALTHAM.
HOW DO YOU DO? VERY NICE TO MEET YOU.
DARLING, THE GELLERS.
DARLING, IT'S THE GELLERS.
SHE'S VERY SELF- INVOLVED, YOU KNOW.
I SHOULD NEVER HAVE MARRIED HER.
SORRY, WHAT?
IT'S THE GELLERS, DARLING.
WHERE?
WELL, THAT'S ONE
AND THERE'S ANOTHER ONE.
LOVELY TO MEET YOU.
TERRIBLY NICE OF YOU
TO OFFER TO PAY FOR HALF THE WEDDING.
OH, FORGET IT. THE HELL WITH TRADITION.
WE'RE HAPPY TO DO IT.
OH, YEAH, WE KNOW HOW EXPENSIVE WEDDINGS CAN BE.
BESIDES, THIS MAY BE THE ONLY WEDDING
WE GET TO THROW.
A JOKE THAT'S FUNNY IN ALL COUNTRIES.
SIR?
WHAT'S IN IT?
GOAT CHEESE, WATERCRESS AND PANCETTA.
THAT'S NOT FOOD.
NO, I DON'T, NO...
EVERYTHING'S DIFFERENT HERE.
I WANT TO GO HOME.
I I... MISS MY FAMILY.
I MISS THE COFFEE HOUSE.
I CAN'T EVEN REMEMBER WHAT PHOEBE LOOKS LIKE.
JOEY, IT'S BEEN THREE DAYS.
OKAY, YOU'RE JUST...
JUST A LITTLE HOMESICK.
OKAY, WOULD YOU JUST TRY TO RELAX AND JUST...
JUST ENJOY YOURSELF.
YOU'RE DIFFERENT HERE, TOO.
YOU'RE MEAN IN ENGLAND.
WHAT THE HELL!
WHAT'S UP, DAD?
THIS BILL FOR MY HALF OF THE WEDDING.
IT'S INSANE.
HOW CAN IT  BE SO MUCH?
THE RECEPTION'S AT THEIR HOUSE.
FLOWERS, LIQUOR, RECARPET FIRST FLOOR.
NEW GUEST BATH.
LANDSCAPING.
I'M PAYING TO REMODEL THIS GUY'S HOUSE.
I'M GOING TO GIVE THAT SON OF A BITCH
A PIECE OF MY MIND.
DAD.
COME ON. PLEASE
I DON'T WANT ANYTHING TO UPSET EMILY TONIGHT.
SHE'S HAD A HARD ENOUGH COUPLE OF DAYS AS IT IS.
HERE. HERE. LET ME GO TALK TO HIM, OKAY?
WELL, YOU TELL THEM
NO ONE TAKES ADVANTAGE OF THE GELLERS.
OOH, JACK.
SOMETIMES I FORGET HOW POWERFUL YOU CAN BE.
AND I'M GOING TO GO GET DRUNK.
OOH, OOH, OOH!
HI.
HELLO.
UM, WHEN IS YOUR NEXT FLIGHT TO LONDON?
THERE'S ONE LEAVING IN 30 MINUTES
AND I DO HAVE ONE SEAT LEFT.
OH, THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
THE LAST MINUTE FARE ON THIS TICKET IS $2,700 DOLLAR.
HUH. HOW ABOUT $600.00 DOLLAR?
SORRY.
HOW ABOUT $600.00 DOLLAR AND THESE EARRINGS?
THEY PREFER IT IF I DON'T BARTER.
OH. I JUST DON'T THINK.
I HAVE ENOUGH LEFT ON MY CREDIT CARD.
WELL, YOU CAN SPLIT IT WITH ANOTHER CREDIT CARD.
WELL, OKAY, HOW ABOUT FIVE?
OH, THANK YOU.
I'M JUST GOING TO NEED TO SEE YOUR PASSPORT.
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I DON'T HAVE IT, BUT I CAN TELL YOU
EXACTLY WHERE IT IS ON MY NIGHTSTAND
AND... OKAY.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
OKAY, I HAVE MY... I HAVE MY DRIVER'S LICENSE
AND I HAVE A 20.
LOOK, FACE IT: MY FATHER IS NOT GOING TO PAY
FOR THE BUILT IN BARBECUE
AND BELIEVE ME, YOU CAN KISS YOUR GAZEBO GOOD BYE.
NOW, I MIGHT BE ABLE TO GET YOU THE NEW LAWN.
AH, THEN YOU HAVE TO GIVE US THE LAWN ORNAMENTS.
I GO BACK THERE WITH LAWN ORNAMENTS
HE'S GOING TO LAUGH IN MY FACE.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
I MEAN, WE HAD AN AGREEMENT.
WILL YOU SAY SOMETHING, STEVEN?!
PLEASE.
DON'T TAKE THAT TONE WITH ME.
ALL ALL RIGHT, YOU CAN.
HI, PHEEBS.
OH, THANK GOD.
OH, YOU CHANGED YOUR MIND.
LOOK, I KNOW YOU PROBABLY WANT TO BE ALONE AND YOU DON'T WANT
TO TALK ABOUT IT. THAT'S FINE.
I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW I THINK YOU'RE DOING THE RIGHT THING.
BYE, PHEEBS!
WAIT, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING? NO! WAIT!
GOD! WHY AM I ALWAYS PREGNANT WHEN SHE DOES THAT?!
I'D LIKE TO MAKE A TOAST TO ROSS AND EMILY.
OF COURSE, MY BIG TOAST
WILL BE TOMORROW AT THE WEDDING
SO THIS IS KIND OF MY LITTLE TOAST
OR MELBA TOAST, IF YOU WILL.
OKAY.
I'VE KNOWN ROSS FOR A LONG TIME.
IN FACT, I KNEW HIM WHEN HE WAS GOING OUT
WITH HIS FIRST GIRLFRIEND
AND I THOUGHT THINGS
WERE REALLY GOING TO WORK OUT FOR THEM
UNTIL THE DAY HE OVERINFLATED HER.
OH, DEAR GOD.
WHAT?
HELLO, WALTHAM INTERIORS.
OH, HI. MRS. WALTHAM?
I NEED TO SPEAK WITH EITHER ONE OF THE BEST MEN
OR ROSS'S SISTER, MONICA.
WHO IS THIS?
OH, I'M PHOEBE BUFFAY.
I'M ONE OF ROSS'S BEST FRIENDS.
HOW DID YOU GET THIS NUMBER?
I GOT IT FROM YOUR MAID.
SHE'S A BITCH, BUT I WORE HER DOWN.
WELL, IF YOU'RE ONE OF ROSS'S BEST FRIENDS
WHY AREN'T YOU HERE?
I CAN'T FLY. I'M HAVING MY BROTHER'S BABIES.
OH.
AM I ON THE RADIO?
NO. UM...
COULD I TALK TO ONE OF THEM?
IT'S VERY, VERY IMPORTANT.
NO, I'M BORED OF YOU NOW.
I'M GOING TO CUT YOU OFF.
OH!
OKAY, I'M GOING TO HAVE TO KICK HER ASS, TOO.
AND I'M SURE WE'RE ALL VERY EXCITED
THAT ROSS AND EMILY ARE GETTING MARRIED AT MONTGOMERY HALL.
TO THINK-- MY FRIEND GETTING MARRIED IN MONTY HALL.
OH, COME ON. MONTY HALL.
LET'S MAKE A DEAL!
COME ON, YOU PEOPLE!
ALL RIGHT, FORGET IT.
CONGRATULATIONS, ROSS AND EMILY.
OKAY.
HEY, BEST MAN NUMBER TWO, JOEY TRIBBIANI.
ALL RIGHT, I'M NOT GOOD WITH THE JOKES
LIKE CHANDLER HERE.
BOY...
BUT, UH...
I JUST WANT TO SAY
CONGRATULATIONS TO THE HAPPY COUPLE.
I FIRST MET ROSS
IN THIS COFFEEHOUSE BACK HOME...
HOME... YEAH.
NEW YORK CITY.
WHERE EVERYBODY KNOWS MY NAME.
WELL, ANYWAY...
UH... I LOVE YOU GUYS...
BUT NOT AS MUCH AS I LOVE AMERICA.
COULD WE PLEASE GO HOME NOW?
ARE YOU GOING HOME?
I WAS HOPING TO GET TO KNOW YOU BETTER.
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE, SWEETHEART.
I WAS LAUGHING.
OUT LOUD?
WELL, I DIDN'T WANT EVERYONE TO THINK I WAS STUPID.
SO HOW YOU DOING?
MY MOTHER'S DRIVING ME CRAZY.
BUT ROSS IS GETTING MARRIED. I'M HAPPY.
I'M NOT GOING TO LET ANYTHING SPOIL THAT.
I JUST WANT TO SAY THAT ROSS IS A WONDERFUL YOUNG MAN.
THANKS. WE LIKE HIM.
MY GOD.
YOU MUST HAVE BEEN A TEENAGER WHEN YOU HAD HIM.
THERE'S NO WAY IN HELL I'M PAYING FOR IT.
LOOK, WE'RE DOWN TO JUST ONE POINT.
COULD WE PLEASE MAYBE JUST SETTLE IT AFTER THE WEDDING?
ALL RIGHT, FINE, BUT I JUST WANT TO SAY
I'M NOT PAYING FOR YOUR WINE CELLAR
YOU THIEVING, WOULD BE SPEAKING- GERMAN IF IT WEREN'T FOR US
CHEAP LITTLE MAN.
THE GUY WAS HAMMERED, OKAY?
THERE'S NO WAY YOU LOOK LIKE ROSS'S MOTHER.
THEN WHY WOULD HE SAY IT?
BECAUSE HE'S CRAZY, OKAY?
HE CAME UP TO ME EARLIER AND THANKED ME
FOR MY VERY MOVING PERFORMANCE IN TITANIC.
OH, MY MOTHER'S RIGHT.
I'M NEVER GOING TO GET MARRIED.
YOU KNOW WHAT? THAT IS...
WHO WOULDN'T WANT YOU?
OH, PLEASE.
I'M A SINGLE MOM WITH A 30 YEAR OLD SON.
HI. I'M BACK.
LISTEN, I NEED TO...
HELLO.
HELLO. I NEED TO GET ON THAT 11:00 FLIGHT.
OH, I'M AFRAID THAT PLANE
HAS ALREADY PULLED AWAY FROM THE GATE.
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO CALL THAT PLANE
AND TELL THEM TO SWING AROUND AND PICK ME UP.
I CAN'T DO THAT.
SURE. YOU KNOW WHAT?
WE'LL JUST TELL THEM
THERE WAS LIKE A PROBLEM WITH THE "ENGINE."
I'M AFRAID I'M GOING TO HAVE TO ASK YOU TO STEP ASIDE, MISS.
LOOK, IF I DON'T GET TO LONDON
HE'S GOING TO MARRY THAT OTHER GIRL.
I CAN'T IMAGINE WHY.
ALL RIGHT, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I AM NOT LEAVING HERE UNTIL YOU CALL THAT PLANE BACK.
I'M GETTING MARRIED TODAY!
WHOO HOO!
MORNING, ROSS.
I'M GETTING MARRIED--TODAY!
YEAH, YOU ARE!
WHOO HOO!
DO YOU THINK HE KNEW I WAS HERE?
UH... UH, EXCUSE ME.
YEAH?
IF YOU'RE PLANNING ON DOING THAT
THROUGHOUT THE ENTIRE FLIGHT
PLEASE TELL ME NOW , SO THAT I CAN
TAKE A SEDATIVE.
OR PERHAPS SLIP YOU ONE.
OH.
I'M SORRY...
I'M... VERY SORRY. I'M SORRY.
IT'S JUST THAT I'M, UH... I'M KIND OF EXCITED.
I'M, UH, I'M GOING TO LONDON
TO, UH, TO TELL THIS GUY THAT I LOVE HIM.
AND...
OKAY.
WELL, I'VE I'VE NEVER DONE THAT WITH YOU BEFORE.
NOPE.
SO, UH, HOW ARE YA?
HOW YA... HOW YA... YOU OKAY?
YEP, YEP.
YOU?
OH, YES, YES.
UH HUH.
YOU?
WE DID YOU.
WELL...
I BETTER GET GOING.
OH, YEAH, YEAH.
ABSOLUTELY, YEAH.
COULD YOU NOT LOOK?
I DON'T WANT TO LOOK.
HELLO?
HEY! WHERE THE HELL HAVE YOU BEEN?
HEY! I SPENT THE NIGHT OUT.
I MET THIS CUTE BRIDES MAID.
SHE IS SO...
I don't want
TO HEAR ABOUT HER.
AW, PHEEBS, YOU KNOW YOU'RE STILL MY #1 GIRL.
NO! NO, WE HAVE AN EMERGENCY, OKAY?
RACHEL'S COMING TO LONDON.
OH, GREAT!
NO, IT'S NOT GREAT, NO!
SHE'S COMING TO TELL ROSS THAT SHE LOVES HIM!
BUT... HE LOVES EMILY.
I KNOW THAT!
YOU HAVE TO STOP HER!
She's going to ruin the wedding!
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, SO, OKAY...
Hold on, hold on.
"RACHEL COMING."
"DO...
SOMETHING."
SO I'VE DONE MY PART, OKAY?
IT'S YOUR RESPONSIBILITY NOW.
THE BURDEN IS OFF ME, RIGHT?
RIGHT.
SO TELL ME ABOUT THIS GIRL.
...AND SO THEN I REALIZED
ALL THIS STUFF THAT I HAD BEEN DOING:
PROPOSING TO JOSHUA
LYING TO ROSS ABOUT WHY I COULDN'T COME TO THE WEDDING
WAS ALL JUST A WAY OF...
OH! OH! OH!
I'M SORRY.
CAN I INTERRUPT?
YEAH, I JUST WANT TO SAY THAT YOU...
ARE A HORRIBLE, HORRIBLE PERSON.
EH, P P PARDON ME?
YOU SAY YOU LOVE THIS MAN
YET YOU'RE ABOUT TO RUIN THE HAPPIEST DAY OF HIS LIFE.
I'M AFRAID I HAVE TO AGREE WITH YOUR FRIEND PHEEBS.
THIS IS A... THIS IS A TERRIBLE, TERRIBLE PLAN.
BUT HE HAS TO KNOW HOW I FEEL!
BUT WHY?
HE LOVES THIS... THIS EMILY PERSON.
NO GOOD CAN COME OF THIS.
WELL, I I THINK YOU'RE WRONG.
OH, NO!
WELL, HE DOESN'T REALLY LOVE HER.
I MEAN, IT'S JUST A REBOUND THING FROM ME.
YOU... YOU...
YOU'LL SEE.
FORTUNATELY, I WON'T.
AND, BY THE WAY, IT SEEMS TO BE PERFECTLY CLEAR
THAT YOU WERE ON A BREAK.
DO SOMETHING...
SOMETHING...
HEY. HEY, HAVE YOU SEEN MONICA?
I'M NOT SEEING MONICA.
WHAT?
WE GOT TO FIND HER. PHOEBE JUST CALLED.
RACHEL'S COMING TO TELL ROSS SHE LOVES HIM!
OH, MY GOD! I KNOW-- THAT'S WHY WE GOT TO
FIND MONICA-- KNOW WHERE SHE IS?
NO, OKAY?! WHAT'S WI TH THE THIRD DEGREE?!
WHY DON'T YOU JUST SHINE A LIGHT IN MY EYES?!
OH, MY GOD!
IT'S LIKE A FAIRYLAND.
I KNOW.
IT'S HORRIBLE, ISN'T IT?
WELL, I LOVE IT.
I ONLY HOPE MY WEDDING LOOKS THIS GOOD.
I JUST HOPE...
YOU CAN LET SOME OF THEM
GO BY.
PSST! MONICA!
WE REALLY NEED TO START LOOKING OUT FOR RACHEL.
I'LL COVER THE FRONT DOOR.
YOU WATCH THAT BIG HOLE AT THE BACK OF THE BUILDING
AND I GOT CHANDLER COVERING ROSS.
WHY WOULD I CARE WHERE CHANDLER IS?
YOU KNOW, UH...
SOMETIMES I DON'T EVEN LIKE CHANDLER.
OKAY.
I DO.
OH, YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT; IT'S THE SECOND ONE.
RIGHT?
HELLO, JOEY.
HEY, FELICITY.
UM, I THOUGHT ABOUT YOU ALL DAY.
YEAH...?
TALK NEW YORK TO ME AGAIN.
FUGGET ABOUT IT...
MMM....
HOW YOU DOING?
MMM!
OH, YEAH...
THERE'S NOTHING TO DISCUSS.
WE'RE NOT PAYING FOR YOUR WINE CELLAR.
YOU HAVE TO MEET ME IN THE MIDDLE HERE.
YOU KEEP PUSHING ME, MY FOOT WILL MEET THE MIDDLE OF YOUR ASS!
DAD!
WHAT'S GOING ON?!
NOTHING, NOTHING.
EVERYTHING'S UNDER CONTROL.
YOU WANT A PIECE OF ME, SIR?
IS THAT WHAT YOU'RE SAYING?
YOU WANT A PIECE OF ME?
THAT'S IT!
PARENTS! PARENTS! BACK AWAY!
ALL RIGHT, THIS IS OUR WEDDING DAY!
FROM NOW ON, EVERYONE GETS ALONG
AND IF I HEAR ONE MORE WORD
NO GRANDCHILDREN.
THAT'S RIGHT!
OKAY, OKAY.
SORRY, OLD BOY , SORRY.
SORRY, SORRY.
I COULD KILL YOU WITH MY THUMB, YOU KNOW.
WHAT WAS  ALL THAT ABOUT?
IT WAS THIS DISAGREEMENT OVER...
MY GOD, YOU... YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL.
OH...
OH! YOU WERE NOT MEANT TO SEE ME BEFORE THE WEDDING.
IT'S BAD LUCK.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK WE'VE HAD ALL THE BAD LUCK WE'RE GOING TO HAVE.
OOH...
MY GOD! RACHEL!
YOU'RE HERE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
WHAT HAPPENED?
WHY ARE YOU HERE?
WELL, I JUST CAME...
I JUST NEEDED TO TELL YOU...
CONGRATULATIONS.
HELLO, WALTHAM INTERIORS.
MRS. WALTHAM, HI.
IT'S PHOEBE AGAIN.
WHY?!
YEAH, CAN I PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE
TALK TO ONE OF THE BEST MEN?
THIS IS GOING TO BE THE LAST TIME, I PROMISE.
JOEY, THERE'S A GIRL ON THE PHONE FOR YOU.
GREAT!
HELLO.
Joey, it's Phoebe.
DID YOU STOP RACHEL?
No, but it's okay.
SHE JUST CAME IN AND GAVE HIM A HUG.
SO, NOTHING GOT RUINED?
No.
OH, THAT'S SO GREAT!
SO, WHAT'S GOING ON NOW?
UH... I'M WALK ING DOWN THE AISLE.
STILL WALKING.
I'M ABOUT TO PASS THE BRIDESMAID
I HOOKED UP WITH LAST NIGHT.
HEY!
I JUST TOLD HER "HEY."
NOW, I'M AT THE FRONT WITH ROSS.
IT'S PHOEBE.
HE LOOKS PRETTY MAD.
UH... I BETTER GO.
NO, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT!
HOLD IT UP SO I CAN LISTEN!
WHAT WE DID LAST NIGHT WAS...
STUPID.
TOTALLY CRAZY AND STUPID.
WHAT WERE WE THINKING?
I'M COMING OVER TONIGHT, THOUGH, RIGHT?
OH, YEAH, DEFINITELY.
FRIENDS
FAMILY, WE'RE GATHERED TO CELEBRATE HERE TODAY
THE JOYOUS UNION OF ROSS AND EMILY.
MAY THE HAPPINESS
we share with them today
BE WITH THEM ALWAYS.
NOW, EMILY, REPEAT AFTER ME.
I, EMILY...
TAKE THE E, ROSS...
TAKE THEE, ROSS...
AS MY LAWFULLY WEDDED HUSBAND
IN SICKNESS AND IN HEALTH
TILL DEATH PARTS US.
AS MY LAWFULLY WEDDED HUSBAND
IN SICKNESS AND IN HEALTH UNTIL DEATH PARTS US.
NOW, ROSS
REPEAT AFTER ME.
I, ROSS...
TAKE THEE, EMILY...
TAKE THEE, RACHEL...
EMILY.
UH...
SHALL I GO ON?
BUTTER, BUTTER, PITA, PITA, TAKE ONE.
OH! THE BAND'S READY!
WELL, WE GOTTA DO WHAT THE BAND SAYS, RIGHT...?
I DON'T CARE ABOUT THE STUPID BAND!
WELL, IT'S GETTING LATE. HERE WE GO.
ACTUALLY
YOU GUYS, IF... WOULD YOU MIND STAYING HERE
WITH ME FOR A WHILE?
UH... YOU KNOW, UM
WE GOT TO GET UP EARLY
AND CATCH THAT PLANE TO NEW YORK.
YEAH, IT'S A V ERY LARGE PLANE.
WHY? WHAT'S THE MATTER?