JOE, I DON'T THINK
A FOUR LETTER WORD FOR "SHIP"
CAN BE "SHIP."
I THOUGHT IT WAS A FREEBIE.
HELLO.
WHAT'S THIS?
OH, RIGHT, IT'S THAT GIRL'S PHONE NUMBER.
YEAH, YEAH, THERE IT IS.
JUST A PHONE NUMBER ARE ALLY HOT GIRL GAVE ME.
IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
I MEAN, IT IS HER HOME PHONE NUMBER, BUT...
WHOA!
WH WHOOPS.
ALMOST LOST THIS BABY.
YEAH, THE LOVELY AMANDA GIVES ME HER NUMBER
AND I,I GO AND DROP IT.
AHH... AHH...
THANK YOU.
RACHEL? YEAH.
WHEN'S YOUR BIRTHDAY?
MAY 5. WHY?
OH, I'M JUST MAKING A LIST OF PEOPLE'S BIRTHDAYS.
OH, MINE'S DECEMBER...
YEAH, WHATEVER.
OH, SHE'S PRETTY.
PRETTY, UH, PRETTY GIRL.
THE PRETTY... SHE'S PRETTY.
WELL, JUST GO UP TO HER AND ASK HER OUT.
WHAT'S THE WORST THING THAT COULD HAPPEN?
I COULD DIE.
YEAH, IT'S... IT'S TOUGH BEING SINGLE.
THAT'S WHY I'M SO GLAD I FOUND AMANDA.
ROSS, YOU GUYS WENT OUT ONCE.
YOU TOOK YOUR KIDS TO CHUCK E CHEESE
AND YOU DIDN'T EVEN KISS HER.
I TELL PEOPLE SECRETS.
IT MAKES THEM LIKE ME.
ALL I'M GOING TO SAY
IS FINALLY
IT'S NICE TO BE IN A MATURE RELATIONSHIP.
YOU KNOW, THE WORLD WOULD BE SUCH A BETTER PLACE
IF THAT ACTUALLY WAS ALL YOU WERE GOING TO SAY.
HEY.
OH, PHOEBE, YOU'RE SICK.
YOU SHOULDN'T PLAY.
YOU SHOULD JUST GO HOME AND GET IN BED
AND STAY THERE.
BUT I'M UNEMPLOYED.
MY MUSIC IS ALL I REALLY HAVE NOW.
WELL, MUSIC AND MAKING MY OWN SHOES.
PRETTY, HUH?
ALL RIGHT, I'M GOING TO DO IT.
I'M GOING TO GO GET SHOT DOWN.
A ANY ADVICE?
JUST BE YOURSELF.
BUT NOT TOO MUCH.
WISH ME LUCK.
GOOD LUCK.
WISH IT.
HI. HI, I I WAS JUST, UH, SITTING OVER THERE AND...
UH, CHANDLER. MY NAME'S CHANDLER.
DID I SAY THAT?
NO, YOU DIDN'T.
HI. I'M KATHY.
KATHY WITH A "K" OR A "C"?
WITH A "K."
H H HEY!
WOW. YOU ARE REALLY GOOD AT THIS.
HEY, COME ON, GIVE ME A BREAK.
I'M OUT ON A LIMB HERE.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I APOLOGIZE, BUT I SHOULD TELL YOU
THAT I'M WAITING FOR A DATE.
OH, AND THERE HE IS NOW.
HEY!
HEY! HEY HEY, HEY.
I SEE YOU GUYS ALREADY MET, HUH?
YES, YES. I WAS JUST TRYING TO FIGURE OUT A WAY
TO DEMONSTRATE HOW I CAN GET MY EXCEPTIONALLY LARGE FEET
INTO MY EVEN BIGGER MOUTH.
DIDN'T I TELL YOU?
ALWAYS SHOWING OFF.
BEFORE I START
I JUST WANT TO SAY THAT I HAVE A COLD.
SO IF I SNEEZE IN THE MIDDLE OF A SONG
IT'S NOT ON PURPOSE.
OH, EXCEPT THE LAST VERSE OF "PEPPER PEOPLE."
OKAY?
?? SMELLY CAT ??
?? WHAT ARE THEY FEEDING YOU...? ??
THIS CHICK SOUNDS GOOD.
?? SMELLY CAT ??
?? SMELLY... ??
HEY, GUNTHER, BE A GOOD LITTLE BOY
AND BRING ME A WHISKEY.
HI.
GEEZ, AT 2:30 IN THE MORNING
I DIDN'T EXPECT TO HAVE TO FIGHT OVER THE REMOTE.
SORRY. THERE'S THIS ERNIE KOVACS THING ON SOON
I WANTED TO WATCH.
MY GOD, THAT'S WHY I GOT UP, TOO.
YOU'RE KIDDING. I LOVE HIM.
MY DAD USED TO MAKE ME STAY UP LATE
AND WATCH RERUNS WITH HIM.
MINE, TOO. DID YOUR DAD ALSO MAKE YOU
WATCH THE MR. UNIVERSE CONTEST?
NO.
ME, NEITHER.
HEY, LISTEN, I'M SORRY ABOUT THIS AFTERNOON.
YOU KNOW, IF I HAD KNOWN YOU TWO WERE...
I NEVER WOULD HAVE...
OH, PLEASE!
SO, JOEY TELLS ME YOU TWO MET IN ACTING CLASS.
YEAH, THEY TEAMED US UP AS PARTNERS.
JOEY PICKED THREE SCENES FOR US TO DO.
ALL OF THEM HAD US MAKING OUT.
THAT'S A GOOD THING, ACTUALLY
BECAUSE, UH, HE USED TO MAKE ME REHEARSE WITH HIM.
OH OH OH OH OH!
OH, IS IT ON?
NO, BUT THIS WONDER BROOM IS AMAZING!
HEY, WAIT.
OH, MY GOD!
OH, IT'S ON, IT'S ON.
HERE WE GO, LITTLE FELLA.
WHAT ABOUT THE DUCK?
WELL, THE DUCK CAN SWIM.
OF COURSE.
?? MY STICKY SHOE ??
?? MY STICKY, STICKY SHOE??
?? WHY YOU STICK ON ME ??
?? BABY? ??
THANKS FOR THE LIGHTS, HONEY.
WAY TO GO.
YOUR COLD MAKES YOU SOUND SO GREAT.
IT'S FUN. GOD, I LOVE HOW SEXY I AM.
KATH, WE SHOULD GET GOING.
WE'RE GOING TO BUY HAMSTERS.
OH...
I LOVE THOSE LITTLE GUYS.
NO, NO, IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
I... I WORK FOR A MEDICAL RESEARCHER.
WELL, HAVE FUN.
OKAY.
WELL, I THINK IT'S NICE THAT THE MEDICAL COMMUNITY
IS FINALLY TRYING TO HELP SICK HAMSTERS.
ISN'T IT? ISN'T IT?
THAT'S GREAT.
YOU KNOW WHAT? I LIKE KATHY.
YEAH?
OH, YEAH, ME, TOO.
SHE'S SO COOL AND PRETTY.
YEAH, SHE'S...
SHE'S SMART AND... FUNNY, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, WE WERE UP ALL LAST NIGHT TALKING.
SHE SAID THE FUNNIEST THING
ABOUT... WHAT?
YOU LOVE HER.
NO, I DON'T.
YES, YOU DO.
CHANDLER LOVES KATHY.
COME ON, PHEEBS, NOW, JUST-- JUST LAY OFF HIM.
THANK YOU, ROSS.
YEAH, HE'S A LITTLE SENSITIVE RIGHT NOW
BECAUSE HE'S SO INLOVE.
ALL RIGHT.
OH, MMM! OH, KATHY!
KATHY, I LOVE YOU.
OH!
SO, I NEED TO WRITE
SOME DEPRESSING STUFF TO GO WITH MY NEW BLUESY VOICE
BUT NOTHING THAT SAD
HAS EVER REALLY HAPPENED TO ME.
WELL, HOW ABOUT YOUR MOM DYING
OR HAVING TO LIVE ON THE STREETS WHEN YOU WERE 14?
UH HUH.
OH, YEAH, I COULD WRITE ABOUT THE TIME
MY HAIR DID THAT WHOO WHOO THING.
HEY.
SO, I'M GOING OVER TO AMANDA'S TONIGHT...
RACHEL'S NOT HERE.
OH.
HOW'S IT GOING WITH HER?
GREAT, ACTUALLY.
I'M THINKING TONIGHT MAY BE THE NIGHT.
YEAH, THE KIDS ARE GOING TO PLAY TOGETHER
AND THEN, WHEN THEY'RE ASLEEP
I'M THINKING AMANDA AND I BREAK OPEN A BOTTLE OF WINE--
DO A LITTLE PLAYING OURSELVES.
HI, GUYS.
THIS IS JOSH.
JOSH, THESE ARE MY FRIENDS.
AND THAT'S ROSS.
HI, JOSH.
HI.
DUDES.
DID YOU PLAY IN COLLEGE?
OH, I STILL DO.
NEXT YEAR I HOPE TO MAKE VARSITY, THOUGH.
ROSS, DIDN'T YOU PLAY SOCCER
IN HIGH SCHOOL?
OH, NO, WAIT, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU JUST ORGANIZED THEIR GAME SCHEDULES ON YOUR COMMODORE 64.
WELL, IT'S GETTING LATE.
I GOT TO GET TO THE GAME, SO I'M GOING TO HEAD.
OKAY.
I'LL MISS YOU.
DOPE!
WOW. CUTE ONE.
VERY CUTE.
I KNOW. ISN'T HE GREAT?
IT'S SO NICE TO FINALLY BE
IN A  FUN RELATIONSHIP, YOU KNOW?
THERE'S NOTHING BORING ABOUT HIM, AND, UH...
BET HE'S NEVER EVEN SET FOOT IN A MUSEUM.
WELL, MAYBE HE'LL GET TO GO SOON--
YOU KNOW, LIKE ON A CLASS TRIP OR SOMETHING.
YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE IS REALLY GREAT ABOUT HIM?
OH, WHAT IS THE WORD FOR AN ADULT
WHO DOESN'T HAVE DINOSAUR TOYS IN THEIR BEDROOM?
OH...
WHAT WAS THAT?
MONICA KNOWS.
IT'S THIS DUMB THING THAT ROSS MADE UP
TO TRY TO FOOL OUR PARENTS.
IT'S A WAY OF GIVING THE FINGER WITHOUT ACTUALLY HAVING
TO GIVE IT.
I REMEMBER I CRIED THE NIGHT YOU MADE THAT UP.
IT WAS THE FIRST TIME I REALIZED I WAS COOLER
THAN MY BIG BROTHER.
WELL.
I'M GOING TO GO GET READY...
FOR MY DATE TONIGHT, SO, UH...
I'LL JUST HEAD.
YEAH, I SHOULD GO, TOO, BECAUSE I'M PLAYING IN ONE HOUR.
YOU GUYS SHOULD COME HEAR ME.
OOH! HEAR ME-- OOH!
?? MY STICKY SHOES... ??
EWW! EWW! OH!
I LOST MY SEXY PHLEGM.
HI. HI.
HI, BEN.
WOW, YOU-- YOU LOOK GREAT.
THANKS.
OKAY. HEY, TOMMY.
I AM SO GLAD
THAT YOU COULD COME OVER TONIGHT.
OH, NO, NO.
IT'S MY PLEASURE.
MY CELL PHONE NUMBER IS RIGHT HERE
ON THE COUNTER.
PLEASE HELP YOURSELF TO ANYTHING IN THE FRIDGE.
I APPRECIATE THIS SO MUCH.
I HAVE BEEN TRYING TO GO OUT WITH THIS GUY
FOR, LIKE, A MONTH.
I I DON'T...
OH, I DON'T MEAN
TO BE A SQUARE
BUT I'D REALLY APPRECIATE IT IF YOU'D WAIT
AND DRINK YOUR WINE AFTER THE KIDS  ARE ASLEEP.
OH, I BLOCKED THE ADULT CHANNELS
FOR THE OTHER BABY SITTERS
BUT THE CODE IS 4-3...
I'M FINE.
THANKS FOR THIS.
I HOPE I CAN DO THE SAME FOR YOU SOMETIME.
WHO WANTS TO MAKE SOME LONG DISTANCE CALLS?
KATHY!
KATHY! HI!
KATHY! KATHY!
KATHY!
FETCH! FETCH IT!
KA... KATHY.
HEY. CHANDLER, WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
WELL...
I JUST WANTED TO SAY, "HEY."
HEY.
OKAY.
OH, COME ON.
YOU'RE MAKING IT SOUND WORSE THAN IT WAS.
HER DATE TIPPED ME TEN DOLLARS.
PHEEBS, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
OKAY, I WANT TO BE SEXY AGAIN
SO, I'M TRYING TO CATCH A COLD.
SHOULD BE EASY.
THEY'RE PRETTY COMMON.
PHOEBE, YOU'LL CATCH PNEUMONIA.
OKAY, YOU WERE RIGHT.
I'M IN LOVE WITH JOEY'S GIRLFRIEND.
WHAT? ARE YOU SERIOUS?
HOW IS THAT POSSIBLE?
YOU BARELY KNOW HER.
I DON'T KNOW.
I CAN'T... I JU...
I CAN'T GET HER OUT OF MY HEAD, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, I'M A VERY BAD PERSON.
I'M A VERY, VERY BAD PER...
I'M A HORRIBLE PERSON.
NO, YOU'RE NOT, CHANDLER.
WE STILL LOVE YOU, CHANDLER.
OH... GOSH, PHOEBE
I THINK I CAUGHT YOUR COLD.
YOU MEAN YOU STOLE IT.
DON'T COVER YOUR MOUTH WHEN YOU DO THAT.
OH...
WE WERE JUST TALKING ABOUT YOU.
REALLY.
YEAH, I TOLD HER ABOUT THE TIME YOU GOT DRUNK
AND FELL ASLEEP WITH YOUR HEAD IN THE TOILET.
RIGHT IN THERE.
WHAT MOVIE DID YOU GET?
I GOT WHAT I ALWAYS GET DIE HARD.
OH... AW...
SEE? THAT'S WHAT I LIKE ABOUT JOEY--
ANY OTHER GUY WOULD WOULD HAVE BEEN
"YEAH, THE ENGLISH PATIENT IS MY FAVORITE MOVIE, TOO."
BUT JOEY GOES, "NO WAY. LET'S GET DIE HARD.
I'M NOT WATCHING THAT ENGLISH CRAP."
YEAH, HE'S DREAMY.
I GOT TO GO.
I GOT TO GO MEET SOME FRIENDS.
HE HAS OTHER FRIENDS?
99...
100.
READY OR NOT, HERE I COME!
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO OVER THE CONCEPT
ONE MORE TIME.
HEY.
LISTEN, YOU WANT TO GET SOME DINNER
WITH ME AND KATHY TONIGHT?
OH, UM, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I, UH, ALREADY ATE.
IT'S 4:30.
YEAH, WELL, I HAD A BIG MEAL ON MONDAY.
SO THAT'S JUST GOING TO GET ME
STRAIGHT THROUGH THE WEEK.
OKAY.
I SEE WHAT'S GOING ON HERE.
YOU, YOU DO?
YEAH. YOU DON'T LIKE KATHY.
YOU GOT ME.
YEAH. YOU BEEN AVOIDING HER
EVER SINCE WE STARTED GOING OUT.
I MADE AN EFFORT TO LIKE JANICE.
IT'S YOUR TURN TO MAKE AN EFFORT TO LIKE KATHY
BY COMING OUT TO DINNER WITH US.
RIGHT? YEAH, RIGHT.
GOOD. AND, HEY, MY TREAT.
BUT THAT'S ONLY BECAUSE
YOU'RE NOT EATING ANYTHING, RIGHT?
RIGHT.
SORRY, GRANDMA.
ROSS ISN'T HERE.
OH.
STOP IT!
SO, UH, I'LL SEE YOU AT THE PARTY?
FEAR'S FEAR, MAN, 24 SEVEN!
YEAH!
I AM SO GOING TO MARRY THAT GUY.
OH!
WHAT?
I THINK HE'S STEALING FROM ME.
WHY?
BECAUSE HE'S STEALING FROM ME.
OH!
HI. IT'S ME.
AND SOUP.
HEY, OH, I JUST SAW JOSH.
HE LOOKED SO YUMMY IN YOUR LEATHER JACKET.
OH!
HERE. NOW, I DON'T EAT CHICKEN
SO IT'S JUST NOODLE SOUP.
AND THERE'S
NO CHICKEN IN THE BROTH EITHER
SO, IT'S REALLY JUST NOODLE WATER.
THANK YOU SO MUCH, PHOEBE.
SURE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING WITH THOSE?
I NEED YOUR GERMS.
I WANT MY COLD BACK.
I MISS MY SEXY VOICE.
SORRY, PHOEBE.
THAT'S OKAY.
HOW'S THE SOUP?
MMM.
OHH!
GOD!
GROSS!
OH, MY GOD, YOU GUYS, CHECK IT OUT.
YOU CAN SEE THAT GIRL'S UNDERWEAR.
IS SHE GREAT OR WHAT?
SO? HUH?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
UH, SHE'S... SHE'S NOT REALLY MY TYPE.
NOT YOUR TYPE?
SHE'S GORGEOUS.
YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK IT IS?
I THINK IT'S THE FISHNET STOCKINGS, YOU KNOW?
WHENEVER I SEE A GIRL IN FISHNET STOCKINGS
IT REMINDS ME OF...
MY FATHER IN FISHNET STOCKINGS.
OKAY.
UNDERSTANDING A LITTLE MORE OF WHY YOU'RE SINGLE.
YOU KNOW, I HAVE A FRIEND YOU'D LIKE.
SHE'S REALLY PRETTY, AND THEN WE COULD DOUBLE DATE.
UH, NO, NO, THANKS.
OKAY. I'VE GOT SOME UGLY FRIENDS
AND THEY'RE ALL AVAILABLE, TOO.
LISTEN, I'M GOING TO GRAB A BEER.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK, OKAY?
WHAT WAS THAT?
WHAT?
KATHY WAS BEING NICE, AND YOU WALKED AWAY.
I THOUGHT WE HAD A DEAL.
LOOK, WHAT DO YOU WANT FROM ME?
I WANT YOU TO LIKE HER
BUT IF THAT'S TOO DAMN DIFFICULT FOR YOU
THEN THE LEAST YOU COULD DO IS PRETEND.
I AM PRETENDING.
WELL, THEN DO IT BETTER.
WHAT DO YOU SAY I GO AND TELL HER HOW MUCH I LIKE HER?
I CAN TELL HER I BEEN THINKING ABOUT HER--
THAT I HAVEN'T STOPPED THINKING ABOUT HER
SINCE THE MOMENT WE MET
THAT I'M SO FANTASTICALLY OVER THE TOP
WANT TO SLIT MY OWN- THROAT IN LOVE WITH HER
THAT FOR EVERY MINUTE OF EVERY HOUR OF EVERY DAY
I CAN'T BELIEVE MY OWN BAD LUCK THAT YOU MET HER FIRST!
YEAH, WELL, THAT'S PRETTY GOOD.
BUT YOU MIGHT WANT TO TONE IT DOWN A LITTLE.
OH, I STILL HAVE A FEVER?
YOU SURE THAT THING'S WORKING RIGHT?
WELL, WE COULD TAKE IT THE OTHER WAY.
HEY.
SO, UH, AMANDA JUST, JUST DROPPED ME OFF.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S ONE OF THE THINGS
I LOVE ABOUT HER.
SHE'S, UH, SHE'S OLD ENOUGH TO DRIVE.
SO, UH, I GUESS
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO MOM AND DAD'S TONIGHT, HUH?
NO. SORRY.
WELL, WHERE'S AMANDA?
COULD YOU GET ME SOME COUGH DROPS?
YOU KNOW, I'M THINKING YOU COULD BRING HER
AND YOU GUYS COULD GO UP TO YOUR OLD ROOM
AND NOT MAKE OUT.
ROSS, A COUGH DROP, PLEASE?
AT LEAST I KNOW SHE'S NOT GOING OUT WITH ME
TO GET INTO "R"-RATED MOVIES.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST MARRY HER?
OH, NO, WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU CAN'T. I'M SORRY. I FORGOT.
SHE'S NOT A LESBIAN.
SEE, AMANDA AND I HAVE A...
YOU HAVE NOTHING!
YOU'RE NOT EVEN GOING OUT.
YOU'RE HER BABY SITTER.
YOU HAVE A 12 YEAR OLD GIRL'S JOB.
OH, THAT IS SO SAD.
AND WHAT ARE YOU LAUGHING AT
MISS "MY KEG SUCKING BOYFRIEND IS STEALING FROM ME"?
SO HE STOLE A COUPLE BUCKS FROM ME.
BIG DEAL.
HE BOUGHT ME SOMETHING WITH IT.
THAT'S MINE!
NOW, WOULD YOU BOTH PLEASE START ACTING LIKE ADULTS?
AND GET ME MY COUGH DROPS?
FINE.
SORRY.
HERE.
THANK YOU.
AT LEAST I MADE TEN BUCKS IN MY RELATIONSHIP.
YOU KNOW...
?? PARADING GOATS ARE PARADING ??
?? PARADING DOWN THE STREET??
?? LEAVING LITTLE TREATS.??
I DON'T KNOW.
DOES IT EVEN WORK WITHOUT MY SEXY VOICE?
I LIKE IT.
GUNTHER, KISS ME.
W WHAT?
Deputy, do something!
HEY.
NOW, WE'RE NOT EXACTLY GOING TO BE SLEEPING IN HERE
BUT DO YOU MIND?
CAN I SLEEP ON YOUR COUCH?
?? AND I'M STILL WAITING FOR MY PAPIER MACHE MAN. ? ?
THANK YOU, MY BABIES.
RACHEL?
YEAH.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU HEARD ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED
BETWEEN ME AND PHOEBE THE OTHER DAY.
NO.
WELL, WE KISSED.
I I DIDN'T INITIATE THE KISS
BUT, BUT I ALSO DIDN'T STOP IT, AND...
I'VE BEEN FEELING GUILTY.
OKAY.
SO, UM...
ARE WE COOL?
OKAY.
I KNEW YOU WOULD UNDERSTAND.