I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M GETTING MY NAILS DONE
AND YOU SAID IT WAS GOING
TO BE FUN...
WHICH IT KIND OF IS.
ALSO, YOU SAID THERE WERE GOING
TO BE OTHER GUYS HERE.
THERE ARE NO OTHER GUYS HERE.
CHANDLER, THERE'S A GUY RIGHT OVER THERE.
THAT'S A MAILMAN.
THAT'S OUR MAILMAN.
: HI. HOW ARE YOU?
CHANDLER, DON'T WORRY.
THIS DOESN'T MAKE YOU ANY LESS OF A GUY.
THAT DOES.
WHAT AM I SITTING ON?
I'D HATE TO THINK WHAT THIS WOMAN WAS SCRATCHING
WHEN THIS BROKE OFF.
HEY, YOU KNOW WHO USED TO HAVE NAILS LIKE THAT?
NO. Janice: OH...
MY... GOD!
JOEY, LET ME ASK A QUESTION.
THIS HAS BEEN
DRIVING ME CRAZY.
WHAT DOES THIS LIGHT SWITCH DO?
OH, NOTHING.
DIDN'T IT DRIVE YOU CRAZY
NOT TO KNOW WHAT IT DID?
I KNOW WHAT IT DID-- NOTHING.
THEY WOULDN'T HAVE PUT IT THERE IF IT DIDN'T DO SOMETHING.
HOW CAN YOU NOT CARE?
LIKE THIS.
HERE'S ANOTHER QUESTION FOR YOU:
DO YOU KNOW WHAT THAT LITTLE SILVER KNOB
ON THE TOILET DOES?
SURE. IT FLUSHES IT.
OKAY, GOOD.
SINCE YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU COME OVER
WOULD YOU MIND ACTUALLY USING IT?
HELLO. HEY.
OH, MY GOD. WOW.
GUESS WHO WE RAN INTO TODAY.
JANICE.
IS THIS AMAZING?
HOW HAVE YOU BEEN?
WELL, UM... I'M DIVORCED.
WOW.
YEAH, I'M RIDING THE ALIMONY PONY.
AND THERE IT IS.
I JUST CAME  UP TO SAY HI.
HI.
AND YOU, SWEETIE, I'LL SEE LATER.
OKAY.
I'LL SEE YOU TONIGHT.
OKAY. BYE. BYE.
BYE. BYE. BYE. OH, BYE.
BYE BYE. BYE BYE.
BYE. BYE. OH.
I CAN'T STAND THE WOMAN.
WHAT?
I THOUGHT YOU WE RE CRAZY ABOUT HER.
I KNOW, BUT YOU KNOW ALL THOSE LITTLE ANNOYING THINGS
THAT SHE DID BEFORE WE FELL IN LOVE--
LIKE HER VOICE AND HER LAUGH AND HER PERSONALITY?
THEY'RE ALL BACK
YOU KNOW.
AND SHE'S PICKED UP, LIKE, NINE NEW ONES.
SO WHAT ARE YOU DOING BRINGING HER HERE?
THERE'S PEOPLE HERE.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
I'M TAKING CARE OF IT TONIGHT.
YOU ARE NOT.
YOU HAVE NEVER BEEN ABLE TO BREAK UP WITH HER.
I DON'T HAVE TO BREAK UP WITH HER THIS TIME.
WE'RE NOT INVOLVED.
I'M GOING TO DO A PREEMPTIVE STRIKE.
I'M GOING TO END IT WITH HER BEFORE IT STARTS.
MY ASS IS, LIKE, FROZEN.
YEAH? TRY STICKING  IT IN THE FREEZER FOR 20 MINUTES.
I'M TELLING YOU.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU REALLY WALK ALONE HERE AT NIGHT.
I MEAN, YOU HEAR SUCH STORIES ABOUT NEW YORK.
NO, IT'S REALLY NOT THAT BAD.
I MEAN, I I FOR ONE FEEL PERFECTLY SAFE.
EM! EM!
HELP! HELP!
HELP!
COME HERE, LUV.
NO NO NO, ROSS.
ROSS, THESE ARE FRIENDS OF MINE FROM HOME.
LIAM, DEVON...
THIS IS ROSS.
OH. HI, MATE.
HEY. HOW ARE YOU, MATE?
HA!
THAT WAS A GOOD ONE, HUH?
"HELP! HELP!"
SO, HOW ARE YOU?
I'VE BEEN MEANING TO RING YOU EVER SINCE I ARRIVED
BUT, UM, WELL, I'VE BEEN RATHER BUSY.
DO YOU REALIZE WE HAVE NOT SEEN
EACH OTHER SINCE THE NIGHT OF THAT U 2 CONCERT?
HUH. OH, MY GOD, I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT.
WELL, ACTUALLY, THE LAST TIME
YOU AND I SAW EACH OTHER  WAS THE NEXT MORNING.
OH, LIAM.
HA! OH, LIAM.
SO, UH, WHAT, WERE YOU GUYS PLAYING SOCCER OR SOME...?
OR OR SHOULD I CALL IT FOOTBALL?
WE WERE PLAYING RUGBY.
WE'RE PLAYING A GAME AT THE PARK TOMORROW.
YOU'RE WELCOME TO PLAY, TOO, IF YOU WANT.
ROSS PLAY RUGBY?
I DON'T THINK SO.
WHAT... WHAT'S SO FUNNY ABOUT THAT?
WELL, I MEAN...
YOU'RE AMERICAN, TO START WITH.
YOU DON'T REALLY HAVE RUGBY HERE.
WELL, WE DIDN'T HAVE FREEDOM HERE
UNTIL 1776 EITHER, SO...
SO, GOOD, THEN. WE'LL SEE YOU
AT RIVERSIDE PARK AT 2:00.
CHEERS. CHEERS. CHEERS.
OH, BOY, I JUST LOVE TO SING.
YES, I I KNOW THAT YOU DO.
I THINK ONE OF THE REASONS PEOPLE WERE COMPLAINING
WAS BECAUSE MOST OF THE PEOPLE HAD PAID
TO HEAR THE ACTOR SING "OLD MAN RIVER."
OH, LOOK AT US.
WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT
THAT CUPID HAD A STATION AT 14th STREET NAILS?
OKAY, WE HAVE TO TALK.
I'M JUST GETTING OUT OF A VERY SERIOUS RELATIONSHIP.
I KNOW...
AND I'M JUST GETTING OUT OF A MARRIAGE.
I MEAN, TALK ABOUT "MEANT TO BE."
RIGHT...
BUT I JUST THINK THIS IS HAPPENING TOO SOON.
OH, TOO SO ON, TOO SCHMOON.
FACE IT, HONEY--
I AM NOT LETTING YOU GET AWAY THIS TIME.
I HEAR YOU...
BUT...
UNFORTUNATELY, MY COMPANY...
IS TRANSFERRING ME OVERSEAS.
OH, NO.
WHERE TO?
TO PARIS?
NO.
NO, NOT NOT PARIS.
OH, TO LONDON?
OH, NO. ROME? VIENNA?
OH, OOH, BARCELONA?
OKAY, COULD YOU JUST STOP TALKING FOR A SECOND?
YEMEN.
THAT'S RIGHT, YES.
I'M BEING TRANSFERRED TO YEMEN.
WHEN?
I DON'T KNOW EXACTLY...
OH.
WELL, I WILL JUST HAVE TO SOAK UP
EVERY OUNCE OF CHANDLER BING UNTIL THAT MOMENT COMES.
BUT I DO KNOW IT'S SOMETIME TOMORROW.
DONE?
YEP.
HEY.
HEY. HEY.
WHAT'S UP?
THIS SWITCH THING HAS BEEN DRIVING ME CRAZY.
SO I TURNED IT OFF AND CHECKED EVERY OUTLET.
FOUR DON'T WORK, WHICH MEANS ONE OF THEM
HAS TO BE CONTROLLED BY THE SWITCH.
SO, I PLUGGED IN THINGS
IN ALL FOUR OUTLETS THAT MAKE NOISE.
THAT WAY, WHEN I TURN IT ON
I JUST FOLLOW THE NOISE AND FIND OUT
WHICH ONE IT IS.
I BET I STOPPED LISTENING BEFORE YOU DID.
YOU KNOW, YOU YOU ALSO COULD HAVE USED, UH, LAMPS
AND THEN FOLLOWED THE LIGHT.
YEAH, WELL, I'M USING NOISE.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT. SO, EVERYBODY READY?
HERE WE GO. OKAY.
OH, MY GOD, I HEAR SOMETHING.
I HEAR SOMETHING.
WHERE IS IT?
IT'S COMING FROM JOEY.
OH, MY GOD, THAT'S SO FREAKY.
TURN HIM OFF!
Goes back to England with the set scrum
in center field.
OOH, HEY.
HI.
CAN WE PUT ON THE NEWS?
I THINK IT MIGHT BE RAINING.
NO. JUST HOLD ON A SECOND.
I'M WATCHING THIS RUGBY THING ON ESPN.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE BIG DEAL IS.
I'M MAN ENOUGH  TO PLAY THIS SPORT.
DUDE, YOU'RE NOT EVEN MAN ENOUGH
TO ORDER THE CHANNEL THAT CARRIES THIS SPORT.
HEY, THERE, ROSS.
HEY.
JANICE.
YOU KNOW, UH...
YOU REALLY DIDN'T HAVE TO HELP ME PACK.
WHEN YOU SAID ALL YOU WERE GOING TO BE DOING BETWEEN NOW
AND THE TIME YOU LEAVE IS PACKING
YOU REALLY DIDN'T LEAVE ME MUCH CHOICE, DID YOU?
WELL, I THOUGHT I DID, BUT I I GUESS I DID NOT.
HEY.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
OH, I'M PACKING.
YOU KNOW, I I'M PACKING
BECAUSE I'M MOVING TO YEMEN TOMORROW.
WELL, THANKS FOR TELLING ME.
I'M ONLY PRETEND MOVING TO YEMEN, OKAY?
IT'S THE ONLY WAY I CAN GET RID OF HER.
OH...
GOOD ONE.
YEAH... AND YEMEN
THAT ACTUALLY SOUNDS LIKE A REAL COUNTRY.
HEY, CHANDLER, COME ON.
I'LL SHOW YOU HOW TO ROLL UP YOUR UNDERWEAR
AND STUFF IT IN YOUR SHOES.
IT'S A REAL SPACE SAVER.
YEAH, I KNOW.
I DO THAT BECAUSE IT MAKES ME
LOOK TALLER.
OKAY, CHANDLER
COME ON.
OKAY.
TRADE LIVES WITH ME.
NOPE.
MAN, LOOK AT THIS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU SAID YOU'D PLAY RUGBY.
LOOK HOW BRUTAL THIS IS.
HEY, I CAN HANDLE IT.
PLEASE, ROSS.
YOU YOU GOT HURT PLAYING BADMINTON WITH MY DAD.
THAT'S BECAUSE YOUR MOM'S DOG KEPT KEPT LOOKING AT ME.
OKAY, ROSS
LOOK LOOK LOOK LOOK.
RIGHT HERE, IT'S CALLED A SCRUM, OKAY?
IT'S KIND OF LIKE A HUDDLE.
AND IS A HUM KIND OF LIKE A SCRUDDLE?
ROSS...
THEY'RE GOING TO KILL YOU.
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS ANYWAY?
WELL, YOU SHOULD HAVE SEEN THE GUY
THAT SHE USED TO GO OUT WITH.
I MEAN, HE'S, LIKE... JOE RUGBY.
YOU'RE KIDDING... AND HE PLAYS RUGBY?
THAT'S SO FUNNY.
OH, I SEE.
YOU DID THAT. ALL RIGHT.
ANYWAY, SHE THOUGHT THE VERY IDEA OF ME
PLAYING RUGBY WITH HIM WAS, LIKE, HILARIOUS.
SO, I'M GOING TO SHOW HER HOW TOUGH I REALLY AM.
I'M SORRY. YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU ARE A TOUGH GUY.
YOU ARE THE TOUGHEST PALEONTOLOGIST I KNOW.
ALL RIGHT, COME ON.
LOOK, ROSS COULD TAKE CARE OF HIMSELF.
IT'S NOT LIKE HE'S CHANDLER.
THANKS.
LOOK, DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME, OKAY?
I'LL JUST LOOK REAL ENERGETIC
AND STAY AWAY FROM THE BALL.
OH, LOOK, I'LL BE THAT GUY
RIGHT OUTSIDE THE CIRCLE.
Ojomo to Back to Bracken.
OH!
OH! OH, GEEZ.
OH. WELL, MAYBE
THERE WAS A DOG LOOKING AT HIM.
ROSS, ROSS, YOU WANT TO STAY AWAY
FROM THAT GUY AND THAT GUY
AND THAT ONE.
DUDE, THEY'RE ALL HUGE.
THEY DON'T LOOK ANY BIGGER THAN ME.
WELL, MAYBE THAT'S
BECAUSE YOU'RE CLOSER TO YOU
SO YOU LOOK BIGGER TO YOU FROM WHERE YOU ARE.
I'M JUST GOING TO GO
AND SAY "HELLO" TO THE LADS, ALL RIGHT?
ALL RIGHT. OKAY.
HI.
OH.
I KIND OF LIKED IT.
OKAY, OKAY
I KNOW WHAT I'VE GOT TO DO.
I'VE GOT TO GO "RED ROSS"
YOU KNOW, "RED ROSS"?
TOTALLY DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
COME ON, THE TIME THAT  WE WERE ALL WAITING IN LINE
FOR DANCES WITH WOLVES
AND THAT ONE GUY CUT IN FRONT OF US
AND I I JUST LOST IT?
HUH? SCREAMED AT HIM, TURNED ALL RED?
"RED ROSS"!
NO.
YOU'LL SEE.
LIAM, DO ME A FAVOR.
YEAH?
TELL THE LADS TO GO EASY ON ROSS.
IT'S HIS FIRST TIME.
YOU DON'T SAY.
THANKS.
OKAY.
GOOD LUCK, BABE.
ROSS!
ROSS, COME ON!
ROSS, COME ON.
COME ON.
COME ON...
ROSS!
ROSS, COME ON.
GET IN THE BLOODY SCRUM.
ROSS, GETIN!
HELP! HELP!
HELP! HELP! HELP!
OH! YOU... ARE...  NOT GOING TO BELIEVE IT.
JOSHUA CAME INTO WORK TODAY.
AND GUESS WHAT HAPPENED.
HE ASKED YOU OUT?
NO. BUT I WAS SHOWING HIM SOME CUFF LINKS
AND I FELT HIS PULSE.
SAUCY.
WHAT ARE THESE?
AH! ELECTRICAL PLANS FOR THE BUILDING.
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
SHOULD I BE SCARED?
I KNOW THAT SWITCH
HAS GOT TO DO SOMETHING, OKAY?
SO SO I WENT DOWN TO CITY HALL
AND I GOT THESE.
ALL I HAD TO DO IS PAY $25 DOLLAR
AND WAIT IN LINE
FOR THREE HOURS.
WOW! IF ONLY MORE PEOPLE KNEW.
ALL RIGHT, DO YOU...
DO YOU UNDERSTAND ANY OF THIS?
NO, NO. I DON'T UNDERSTAND ANY
OF THIS ELECTRICAL STUFF.
ALL RIGHT, DOES THIS LOOK LIKE A SWITCH?
I DON'T KNOW.
HMM. IS THIS WIRING?
THAT LOOKS LIKE A BUNNY, THOUGH.
YOU KNOW, YOU...
REALLY DIDN'T HAVE TO TAKE ME TO THE AIRPORT.
OH, PLEASE. EVERY MOMENT IS PRECIOUS.
BESIDES, SOMEBODY HAD TO RIDE
IN THAT OTHER TAXI
WITH THE REST OF YOUR LUGGAGE
AND YOUR FRIENDS DON'T SEEM TO CARE VERY MUCH
THAT YOU'RE LEAVING.
WELL, WE'RE NOT REALLY THAT CLOSE.
OKAY, SO, I GUESS THIS IS, UH...
YOU KNOW, GOOD BYE, THEN.
OH, NO!
NO, IT'S NOT GOOD BYE.
I'M NOT LEAVING UNTIL
YOU GET ON THAT PLANE.
OKAY, WELL, I GUESS JUST WAIT HERE, THEN.
HI. I NEED A FAKE TICKET TO YEMEN.
ONE TICKET TO YEMEN?
OH, NO, NO.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
I JUST NEED... I JUST NEED A PRETEND TICKET.
I I'M SORRY, SIR.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHAT WOULD YOU GIVE A KID
IF HE WANTED A TICKET TO PLAY WITH?
ARE YOU TRAVELING
WITH A CHILD?
NO.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, YOU KNOW WHAT?
SHE'S GOING TO THINK
THAT I'M HANDING YOU A CREDIT CARD
BUT WHAT I'M REALLY GOING TO DO
IS HAND YOU A LIBRARY CARD.
UH... SIR, A TICKET TO YEMEN IS $2,100 DOLLAR
AND WE DON'T TAKE LIBRARY CARDS.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
DO YOU HAVE TO STAY?
AMERICAN EXPRESS?
ROSS!
OH!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THEY'RE DOING THAT TO HIM.
I TOLD THEM TO GO EASY ON HIM.
WELL, NO OFFENSE, BUT, YOU KNOW
SOMETIMES IT'S HARD TO UNDERSTAND YOU
YOU KNOW, WITH THE ACCENT, SO...
THAT'S JUST HALFTIME.
THERE'S MORE OF THIS.
OH, HEY.
HEY.
DID YOU SEE ME?
I WAS PRETTY GOOD, HUH?
THAT IS ONE FUN GAME.
RIGHT. HEY, DO ME A FAVOR.
COULD YOU JUST GRAB ME
A BOTTLE OF WATER? THANKS.
I I THINK I'M DYING.
I I REALLY DO.
OH, YOU POOR BABY...
TELL MY SON THAT I LOVE HIM.
OKAY.
OH, EXCELLENT.
OH, OKAY, GOT TO HAVE SOME MORE FUN.
ROSS, THEY ARE KILLING YOU OUT THERE.
MM MMM.
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
SHE'S RIGHT. YOU HAVE TO STOP.
WHAT? NO. NO, I'M NOT STOPPING.
I'M "RED ROSS."
DUDE, YOU GO BACK OUT THERE
YOU'RE GOING TO BE DEAD ROSS.
I DON'T CARE. I AM NOT QUITTING.
I AM GOING TO FINISH THIS GAME.
IF YOU INSIST ON DOING THIS
AT LEAST LET ME HELP YOU.
NO. GOD, NO. THAT  IS NO PLACE FOR A WOMAN.
THOSE GUYS WILL GRAB ANYTHING.
NO, THAT'S NOT WHAT I WAS SAYING.
I JUST MIGHT KNOW A FEW THINGS
THAT COULD HELP YOU INFLICT SOME PAIN.
I LIKE THAT. YEAH?
LISTEN CLOSELY: DEVON HAS GOT A WEAK ANKLE.
HUH?
ONE SWIFT KICK, AND HE'LL BACK OFF.
BAD ANKLE. GOT IT!
AND THAT BIG BLOKE WITH THE BEARD...
UH HUH?
HE'S GOT A TRICK HIP.
HUH HA!
YEAH. AND DAVID OVER THERE
I'VE HEARD THAT HE DOESN'T WEAR A CUP.
WELL, I COULD USE THAT.
TRICK HIP, NO CUP. OKAY, OKAY!
AND AND LIAM-- LIAM'S GOT BAD KNEES.
YOU HIT HIM RIGHT
AND HE'LL GO DOWN LIKE A LAMP.
BUT BUT LIAM'S ON MY TEAM.
I DON'T CARE. YOU JUST GET THEM!
I'M GOING TO GET HIM!
OKAY, I AM GOING BACK IN.
HEY, "RED ROSS," YEAH.
HI.
WHAT'RE WHAT'RE, WHAT ARE THESE?
OH, JUST SOME PICTURES I MADE AND HUNG UP.
THOUGHT THEY'D BRIGHTEN UP THE PLACE.
THEY DO, DON'T YOU THINK?
NO, NO, DON'T! DON'T!
I KNOW THERE'S NO HOLE THERE.
I JUST REALLY LIKE THAT PICTURE.
OH, MY GOD, LOOK AT THIS!
OKAY, BUT THERE IS
A WIRE BACK THERE.
THAT SWITCH IS CONNECTED TO SOMETHING.
I DON'T CARE. THE WIRES HAVE COME LOOSE IN YOUR HEAD.
I I JUST THOUGHT
IF I COULD FOLLOW THE WIRE
I COULD FIND OUT WHAT IT DID.
AND DID YOU?
NO.
DISAPPEARS BACK THERE BEHIND THAT BASEBOARD.
FOR A MINUTE THERE
I THOUGHT IT WENT DOWNSTAIRS.
SAY HELLO TO MRS. KATRAKAS.
HELLO, DARLING.
HELLO, MRS. KATRAKAS.
HEY, MRS. KATRAKAS, DO YOU KNOW KENNY?
YOU'VE GOT TO BE KID...
NOW, ARE YOU SURE
YOU DON'T WANT TO GO SEE A DOCTOR?
AW, NO. THAT'LL JUST BRING ME DOWN.
THIS WAS GREAT.
I MEAN, I I I WAS GREAT.
THIS WAS A GREAT DAY.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M BUYING EVERYONE COFFEE.
WOULD SOMEONE JUST GRAB MY WALLET?
IT'S IN MY POCKET.
YEAH, SURE. NO, NOT YOU.
OKAY. LOOK, YOUR EYE'S
STILL POPPING  OUT A LITTLE THERE.
I'M GOING TO GO GET SOME ICE.
OOH, ICE, YEAH.
I'M SO IN THE MOOD FOR ICE.
YEAH.
AAH...
YOU WERE AMAZING OUT THERE.
OH...
I KIND OF WAS, WASN'T I?
OH, MY GOD!
I MADE A MAN TWICE MY SIZE CRY.
I MEAN, I HAVEN'T DONE THAT SINCE I WAS FOUR
AND I WASHED MY DAD'S PORSCHE WITH ROCKS.
YOU REALLY ENJOYED YOURSELF, DIDN'T YOU?
PLEASE, ARE YOU KIDDING?
I I HURT THREE HUGE MEN.
I GAVE A GUY A BLOODY NOSE.
I MEAN, I'M I'M NOT PROUD OF IT, BUT...
I REALLY AM.I MEAN...
AND IT'S ALL BECAUSE OF YOU.
YEAH. WONDERFUL, AMAZING YOU.
I THINK YOU'VE GOT A CONCUSSION.
NO. NO, I'M SERIOUS.
THANK YOU.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
I'M SORRY. DID THAT HURT YOU?
IT'S WORTH THE PAIN.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU KNOW WHAT? IT'S NOT.
SORRY.
This is the final boarding call for flight 664 to Yemen.
WELL, I GUESS I GOT TO GO.
OH, MY BING A LING.
I'LL WAIT FOR YOU.
DO YOU EVEN KNOW
HOW LONG YOU'RE GOING TO BE GONE?
WELL, JUST UNTIL
WE FIND AN ENERGY SOURCE TO REPLACE FUEL.
OH. WELL, I'LL WRITE YOU EVERY DAY.
OKAY.
15 YEMEN ROAD, YEMEN.
OKAY, GOOD BYE.
GOOD BYE.
CHANDLER?
NOPE.
CHANDLER!
JANICE, THERE YOU ARE. THERE YOU ARE.
I HAD TO HAVE ONE LAST KISS
AND ALSO, YOU SAID YOU WERE GOING TO LEAVE
RIGHT AFTER I  GOT ON THE PLANE.
NO, NO. I I WANT TO SEE YOU TAKE OFF.
WELL, THEN I GUESS I'M GOING TO YEMEN.
I'M GOING TO YEMEN.
WHEN WE GET TO YEMEN
CAN I STAY WITH YOU?
ALL RIGHT. THE SUPER COULDN'T FIGURE OUT
WHAT IT DID.
A $200 DOLLAR AN HOUR ELECTRICIAN COULDN'T FIGURE OUT WHAT IT DID.
I'VE HAD SEVEN PRETTY SERIOUS SHOCKS.
I OFFICIALLY GIVE UP.
THANK GOD.
GUESS JOEY WAS RIGHT.
IT DOES NOTHING.
SEE?
I'M DOING  IT.
I AM TOTALLY DOING IT.
I LOST IT.