OKAY.
COME ON, AND NO PEEKING.
OUR EYES ARE CLOSED
AND WE'RE ABOUT TO CROSS THE STREET--
VERY GOOD.
OKAY... OPEN UP.
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO SHOW US?
BECAUSE ALL I CAN SEE IS THIS BITCHING VAN!
YEAH. IT'S FOR OUR CATERING BUSINESS.
OH.
I THINK I KNOW THAT GIRL.
ALL RIGHT. UM...
WE'RE NOT GOING TO REALLY KEEP IT THIS WAY, THOUGH.
NO?
WE'RE GOING TO PAINT OVER THE SWORD
AND REPLACE IT WITH A BAGUETTE.
OH, MY GOD.
I THINK I LOST MY VIRGINITY IN THAT VAN.
UM, ALSO, WE DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO WITH THIS.
OH, YEAH.
I DEFINITELY KNOW HER.
REMEMBER THAT GUY
FROM COOKING SCHOOL I TOLD YOU ABOUT
THAT PUT CILANTRO IN EVERYTHING?
OH, SURE. "CILANTRO" LARRY.
WELL, I'M GOING TO FILL IN FOR HIM
AS FOOD CRITIC FOR THE CHELSEA REPORTER.
WOW! MONICA, WHAT AN AMAZING OPPORTUNITY
TO INFLUENCE... DOZENS OF PEOPLE.
HOW COULD YOU HAVE SAID YES?
WHAT ABOUT OUR CATERING BUSINESS?
OH, NO, NO. IT'S JUST ONE NIGHT A WEEK.
I GET TO TAKE ALL OF YOU OUT
FOR A LOT OF FREE DINNERS.
HEY. HEY.
OH, WELL, IN THAT CASE...
HEY.
THAT WAS ME HOPPING ON BOARD.
OH.
HEY, GUYS.
HEY, ROSS, QUICK QUESTION FOR YOU.
ARE YOU READY TO PARTY?
I DON'T KNOW.
I COULD MAYBE GO OUT FOR A COUPLE OF BEERS
BUT THERE'S THIS THING ABOUT BUMBLEBEES
ON THE DISCOVERY CHANNEL...
NO, NO, NO. I DON'T THINK YOU HEARD ME.
ARE YOU READY... TO PARTY?
NO!
GANDALF?!
GANDALF IS COMING TO TOWN?
KATHY'S WITH HER PARENTS.
I HAVE NOTHING TO DO.
TOMORROW, WE ARE PARTYING WITH GANDALF, DUDE!
DUDE, WE ARE SO GOING TO PARTY.
YEAH!
WOW! OKAY. DUDE ALERT.
AND WHO IS THIS GUY?
MIKE "GANDALF" GANDERSON.
ONLY, LIKE, THE FUNNEST GUY IN THE WORLD.
I'M GOING TO CALL AND GET OFF WORK TOMORROW.
I'M GOING TO CALL AFTER YOU!
THIS IS GOING TO BE SO COOL, DUDE.
WE NEVER PARTY ANYMORE.
OOOOOOH! OOOOOOH!
WERE YOU GUYS SMOKING SOMETHING
IN THE BACK OF OUR VAN?
REALLY. WHAT DO YOU MEAN, WE NEVER HAVE FUN ANYMORE?
YOU HAVE FUN WITH ME.
REMEMBER THE TIME WE SAW THOSE STRIPPERS
AND YOU PAID ME 50 BUCKS
TO EAT THAT BOOK?
JOEY, YOU ARE GOING TO LOVE THIS GUY.
GANDALF IS, LIKE, THE PARTY WIZARD.
WHY DO YOU CALL HIM GANDALF?
GANDALF THE WIZARD.
HELLO. DIDN'T YOU READ LORD OF THE RINGS
IN HIGH SCHOOL?
NO, I HAD SEX
IN HIGH SCHOOL.
OH, UH... JOANNA?
I WAS WONDERING
IF I COULD ASK YOU SOMETHING.
THERE'S AN OPENING FOR AN ASSISTANT BUYER
IN JUNIOR MISS...
THAT WOULD BE A STEP DOWN FOR ME.
NO, ACTUALLY, I MEANT FOR ME.
THE HIRING COMMITTEE IS MEETING PEOPLE ALL DAY.
OH. WELL, I WISH I COULD SAY NO
BUT I GUESS YOU CAN'T STAY MY ASSISTANT FOREVER.
NEITHER CAN YOU, SOPHIE
BUT FOR DIFFERENT REASONS.
I'M SO GLAD YOU DON'T HAVE A PROBLEM WITH THIS
BECAUSE IF YOU DID
I WOULDN'T EVEN HAVE CONSIDERED APPLYING.
REALLY? IN THAT CASE...
THAT'S WHY I'M SO GLAD THERE'S NO PROBLEM.
IT'S FINE. ACTUALLY, I'M ON THE HIRING COMMITTEE
SO THERE'LL BE AT LEAST ONE FRIENDLY FACE.
OH, THAT'S GREAT.
JUNIOR MISS IS WHERE I STARTED.
REALLY?
HAD TO SLEEP WITH THE UGLIEST GUY
TO GET THAT JOB.
OH... REALLY?
NO!
YEAH.
I MEAN, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
DON'T YOU WORRY.
WITH YOUR QUALIFICATIONS
YOU WON'T NEED TO SLEEP WITH SOME GUY
TO GET THE JOB.
ALTHOUGH I MIGHT NEED
SOME CONVINCING.
WELL, UM...
KIDDING!
GOD, I FEEL WILD TODAY!
OH, MAN, I AM SO EXCITED
I MAY VOMIT.
WILL YOU CALM DOWN?
HE'S JUST A HUMAN GUY.
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND. GANDALF IS AMAZING.
YOU NEVER KNOW WHAT WILL END UP HAPPENING.
YOU GO OUT FOR A COUPLE OF BEERS
AND END UP ON A FISHING BOAT TO NOVA SCOTIA.
REALLY?
OH, YEAH. IT'S BEAUTIFUL COUNTRY UP THERE.
HEY! OKAY, I GOT MY PASSPORT
FRESH SOCKS
AND A SNAKEBITE KIT.
IT'S NOT GOING TO BE EXACTLY LIKE LAST TIME.
ALL RIGHT
I'LL SEE YOU GUYS.
WHOA, WHOA. WHOA, WHOA.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
I HAVE AN AUDITION. I'LL HOOK UP WITH YOU LATER.
WHERE WILL YOU BE AROUND NOON?
SOMEWHERE MAYBE ALONG THE EQUATOR.
OKAY.
HELLO.
IT'S GANDALF!
OOOOOOH! OOOOOOH!
SO, YOU IN TOWN?
OH. WELL...
WELL, MAYBE NEXT TIME THEN.
WHAT HAPPENED?
HE'S NOT GOING TO MAKE IT.
HE'S STUCK IN CHICAGO.
OH, MAN!
CHICAGO'S SO LUCKY.
STUPID, USELESS
CANADIAN MONEY!
YOU HAVE A VERY IMPRESSIVE RESUME, MS. GREEN.
I ESPECIALLY LIKE WHAT I SEE HERE
ABOUT IMPLEMENTING A NEW FILING SYSTEM.
THANK YOU.
FILING SYSTEM?
YOU MEAN THOSE LITTLE COLORED LABELS
YOU PUT ON ALL THE FOLDERS?
IT BRIGHTENED UP THE INSIDE OF THE FILING CABINETS.
WELL, THEY, UH... THEY...
THEY DID MORE THAN THAT.
I NOTICE THAT YOU'VE BEEN ENTRUSTED
WITH A LOT OF RATHER IMPORTANT RESPONSIBILITIES.
YES. JOANNA REALLY HAS BEEN AN INCREDIBLE MENTOR TO ME.
RACHEL HAS BEEN INCREDIBLE
AT GETTING MY MORNING BAGEL FOR ME.
IT'S AMAZING HOW SHE GETS IT RIGHT ALMOST EVERYTIME.
I... I... OF COURSE...
I HAVE MORE RESPONSIBILITIES THAN THAT.
OF COURSE. WELL, THERE'S THE COFFEE, TOO.
RACHEL CAN CARRY TWO THINGS AT ONCE.
THAT'S... THAT'S VERY GOOD.
NOW...
A, UH...
BIG PART OF THIS JOB
IS CULTIVATING PERSONAL RELATIONSHIPS
ESPECIALLY WITH DESIGNERS.
RACHEL SHOULDN'T HAVE ANY PROBLEM. YES, I REALIZE THAT.
HER ONLY PROBLEM
MIGHT BE GETTING TOO FRIENDLY, IF  YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
I LOVE WORKING WITH DESIGNERS.
WITH THEM, UNDER THEM.
WHAT'S THE DIFFERENCE, EH, RACH?
HEY, MY FIRST REVIEW IS OUT.
OH! OH, THE CHELSEA REPORTER.
OH, THESE USED TO KEEP ME SO WARM.
RIGHT. LOOK, I'M ON THE BACK PAGE.
OH! OKAY.
"WOULD I GO BACK TO ALESSANDRO'S?
"SURE. BUT I'D HAVE TO ORDER TWO MEALS--
"ONE FOR ME AND ONE FOR THE GUY
POINTING THE GUN TO MY HEAD."
WOW! YOU REALLY LAID INTO THIS PLACE.
THEY DON'T PAY ME A PENNY A WORD TO MAKE FRIENDS.
I GOT TO GO. I FOUND A GUY
WHO CAN FIX UP THE VAN FOR CATERING.
WANT ME TO GO WITH YOU?
NO. NO. IT'S OKAY.
BUT ARE WE SURE WE DON'T WANT THE WATERBED?
JUST BECAUSE IT WOULD
BE SILLY TO TAKE IT OUT
IF WE'RE JUST GOING TO PUT IT BACK IN AGAIN.
HAVEN'T WE MADE THIS DECISION?
YEAH. ALL RIGHT.
BYE. BYE.
WHO IS IT?
It's Alessandro, from Alessandro's.
OH, MY GOD.
I want to talk to you about your review.
OH, MY GOD. OH, MY GOD.
CALL ME ON THE PHONE.
What, so you can hang up on me?
LOOK. I'M NEVER GOING TO LET YOU UP
SO YOU MAY AS WELL JUST GO AWAY.
Give me a chance to...
You need to get in? Here you go.
NO, PHOEBE!
Hey, Monica.
I WANT A RETRACTION.
OUR FOOD IS NOT INEDIBLE SWILL!
I COULDN'T EAT IT.
I HAVE FIVE FRIENDS WHO COULDN'T EAT IT
AND ONE OF THEM EATS BOOKS.
WELL, OUR SERVICE IS NOT GROSSLY INCOMPETENT.
THE WAITER CARRIED THE BREADSTICKS IN HIS PANTS.
WELL... YOU SAID THAT WE ACCEPT THE DISCOVER CARD
WHICH WE DO NOT.
ALL RIGHT. THAT I'LL RETRACT, BUT I STAND BY MY REVIEW.
I KNOW FOOD, AND THAT WASN'T IT.
YOUR MARINARA SAUCE TASTES LIKE TOMATO JUICE.
YOU SHOULD SERVE IT WITH VODKA
AND A PIECE OF CELERY.
I'M PROUD OF THAT SAUCE. IT'S DELICIOUS.
OH, MY GOD!
YOU OWN AN ITALIAN RESTAURANT AND YOU THINK THAT TASTES GOOD?
WHERE ARE YOU EVEN FROM?
LEBANON.
HAND ME THOSE TOMATOES.
I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU WHAT IT SHOULD TASTE LIKE.
COME ON. HAND THEM TO ME.
HOW LONG IS THIS GOING TO TAKE, BECAUSE I GOT
ANOTHER CRITIC I GOT TO GO YELL AT.
UH, JOANNA?
I WANT TO TALK ABOUT THAT INTERVIEW.
I THOUGHT IT WENT VERY WELL.
NO, IT DIDN'T.
THAT'S WHAT I WANT TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT.
NOW, JUST TO BRIEF YOU...
I MAY CRY
BUT THEY ARE NOT TEARS OF SADNESS
OR OF ANGER
BUT JUST OF ME HAVING THIS DISCUSSION WITH YOU.
RACHEL, PLEASE.
DON'T MAKE A SCENE.
THERE'S NOBODY HERE.
SOPHIE, GET IN HERE!
YOU SEE? YOU'RE MAKING SOPHIE UNCOMFORTABLE.
SHE'S NOT MAKING ME UNCOMFORTABLE.
CONGRATULATIONS. YOU CROSSED THE LINE INTO COMPLETELY USELESS.
GET OUT.
DO YOU WANT ME TO QUIT?
WHAT?
WHAT WOULD MAKE YOU THINK THAT?
WELL, ALL OF THOSE THINGS THAT YOU SAID IN THE INTERVIEW.
IF YOU BELIEVE ANY OF THEM
I MUST NOT BE A VERY GOOD ASSISTANT.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I AM JUST GOING TO PACK UP MY DESK...
AND I WILL BE GONE BY THE END OF THE DAY.
WELL, I GUESS THERE'S NO USE
ME STICKING AROUND TILL THE END OF THE DAY.
ALL RIGHT. WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
YOU CAN PUT YOUR SAD LITTLE MUFFIN
BACK IN ITS DRAWER.
IF YOU MUST KNOW THE TRUTH
I DIDN'T WANT TO LOSE A PERFECTLY GOOD ASSISTANT.
WHAT?
THAT'S WHY I SAID ALL THOSE THINGS
ABOUT YOUR FLIRTING AND YOUR DRINKING.
MY DRINKING?
OH. I MUST HAVE SAID THAT AFTER YOU LEFT.
SAID WHAT, EXACTLY?
YOU ENJOY THE OCCASIONAL DRINK...ING BINGE.
OH, MY GOD!
OH! THAT IS IT! I AM LEAVING!
YOU ARE JUST A HORRIBLE PERSON.
NO, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO GET ALL SENSITIVE ABOUT IT.
I DON'T WANT TO LOSE YOU.
WHAT IF I CREATE A POSITION FOR YOU?
I'LL MAKE YOU ASSISTANT BUYER IN THIS DEPARTMENT.
SAY MORE THINGS LIKE THAT.
UM...
YOU CAN HAVE YOUR OWN OFFICE
AND A RAISE, EFFECTIVE TOMORROW.
I'D NEED AN EXPENSE ACCOUNT.
DONE.
AND AN ASSISTANT.
SOPHIE, GET IN HERE.
However, it seems like a lifetime, doesn't it?
Starting when Stefano used Kristin...
HEY. WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING HERE?
I THOUGHT YOU'D BE OUT PARTYING WITH GAN...DORF.
IT'S GANDALF
AND HE'S NOT COMING.
SO YOU BEEN SITTING AROUND ALL MORNING?
NO.
I BALANCED MY CHECKBOOK.
YEAH, AND I GAVE FIRST NAMES
TO ALL THE FOOSBALL PLAYERS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HE DIDN'T COME.
SO WHAT IF HE DIDN'T COME?
WE CAN GO OUT AND PARTY OURSELVES.
OH, NO.
YOU KNOW, WITH GANDALF, WE'D BE OUT ALL NIGHT.
YEAH. WE'D MEET...
WE'D MEET TOTAL STRANGERS AND HANG OUT WITH THEM.
WELL, WE COULD DO THAT.
THERE WAS OTHER STUFF, TOO.
WE'LL DO IT ALL, AND BETTER.
LOOK, AFTER TONIGHT
GANDALF WILL WANT
TO PARTY WITH US, DUDE. COME ON!
YEAH! YEAH!
YEAH! IT'S NOT LIKE WE DON'T KNOW HOW TO PARTY.
YEAH! ALL RIGHT! LET'S GO!
MAYBE WE COULD END UP ON A BOAT AGAIN?
YEAH! YEAH!
WELL, ALL RIGHT!
YEAH!
HEY, HEY, HEY.
WHEN, UH... WHEN WERE WE ON A BOAT?
REMEMBER THAT REALLY COLD MORNING
WHEN YOU WOKE UP AND THOSE DOGS WERE LICKING YOUR FACE?
YEAH.
THOSE WERE SEALS, MAN.
HEY, HOW DO YOU THINK
THIS SUIT WOULD LOOK ON AN ASSISTANT...?
THE OWNER OF ALESSANDRO'S CAME OVER TO YELL AT ME
BUT I MADE HIM SOME SAUCE, AND HE OFFERED ME THE JOB
AS HEAD CHEF.
OH, MY GOD! YOU JUST RUINED
WHAT I WAS PRACTICING THE WHOLE WAY HOME
BUT I'M SO HAPPY!
I KNOW! CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
I FINALLY GET TO RUN MY OWN KITCHEN.
OH, YOU'VE WAITED SO LONG. AW...
HEY.
HEY, PHEEBS, QUICK QUESTION FOR YOU:
HOW DO YOU THINK THIS SUIT WOULD LOOK
ON AN ASSISTANT BUYER AT BLOOMINGDALE'S?
I DON'T KNOW.
IT WOULD TOTALLY DEPEND
ON HER COLORING, AND...
YOU GOT THE JOB!
YOU GOT THE JOB?!
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME?
OH, IT'S GOING TO BE SO GREAT!
I'M GOING TO GET TO HELP DECIDE
WHAT WE SELL
AND I'M GOING TO HAVE AN OFFICE
WITH WALLS AND EVERYTHING.
I'M GOING TO HAVE WALLS!
OKAY. IS THIS THE DAY OF GOOD NEWS OR WHAT?
I GOT US A JOB-- THE WEDDING RECEPTION.
OH! UM...
PHOEBE, I KIND OF NEED TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT THAT.
UM... WELL, I I I THINK IT MIGHT BE TIME FOR ME
TO TAKE A STEP BACK FROM THE CATERING.
BUT WE'VE ONLY HAD ONE JOB.
I KNOW, BUT NOW WE HAVE THIS SECOND ONE
AND IT JUST... IT FEELS LIKE IT'S SNOWBALLING, YOU KNOW?
YEAH. WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
I GOT OFFERED THE HEAD CHEF JOB AT ALESSANDRO'S.
WHAT?
IT'S OKAY. IF YOU THINK ABOUT IT
YOU DON'T REALLY NEED ME
FOR THE BUSINESS.
YOU'RE THE COOK!
WITHOUT YOU, IT'S JUST ME
DRIVING UP TO PEOPLE'S HOUSES WITH EMPTY TRAYS
AND ASKING FOR MONEY.
ALL RIGHT, BUT, UM...
WELL, I'LL I'LL PAY YOU BACK ALL THE MONEY YOU INVESTED
AND YOU CAN KEEP THE VAN.
FOR WHAT?
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
I GOT TO GET OUT OF HERE.
OH, PHOEBE, WAIT A MINUTE.
I'M AN ASSISTANT BUYER!
WE'LL GET A LITTLE COFFEE
GET ENERGIZED, AND WE'LL HEAD BACK OUT.
YEAH. ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
SO, WE'RE HAVING FUN, RIGHT?
WE DON'T NEED THAT WIZARD GUY.
WE HIT A COUPLE OF CLUBS, TALKED TO SOME STRANGERS
AND, AFTER THIS
WE'LL GO DOWN TO THE DOCKS AND SEE ABOUT THAT BOAT THING.
I'M KIND OF BEAT.
ACTUALLY... ME, TOO.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
YEAH. YEAH.
THANK GOD. I'M EXHAUSTED.
SO, YOU GUYS WANT COFFEES?
YEAH, BUT I DON'T WANT TO BE UP TOO LATE
SO I'LL HAVE A DECAF.
YEAH. ME, TOO.
ACTUALLY, COULD I GET
SOME HOT WATER WITH A LITTLE LEMON?
I THINK I STRAINED MY VOICE
SCREAMING IN THERE.
DOES IT HAVE TO BE SO LOUD?
OH, I CAN'T HEAR A WORD YOU'RE SAYING
MY EARS ARE RINGING SO BAD.
I'M JUST GLAD I BROUGHT
THAT EXTRA PAIR OF SOCKS, YOU KNOW?
I USED THEM AS MITTENS.
I DIDN'T WANT TO TOUCH A THING
IN THAT LAST PLACE.
HOW SAD ARE WE?
YEAH. I KNOW.
YOU KNOW WHAT? WE'RE NOT SAD.
WE'RE NOT SAD.
WE'RE JUST NOT 21 ANYMORE, YOU KNOW?
I'M 29 YEARS OLD, DAMN IT
AND I WANT TO SIT IN A COMFORTABLE CHAIR
AND WATCH TELEVISION
AND GO TO SLEEP AT A REASONABLE HOUR.
YEAH. YEAH.
YEAH, AND I LIKE
TO HANG OUT IN A QUIET PLACE
WHERE I CAN TALK TO MY FRIENDS.
YEAH. YEAH.
AND SO WHAT IF I LIKE TO GO HOME
THROW ON SOME KENNY G
AND TAKE A BATH?
WE'RE 29, WE'RE NOT WOMEN.
OH, THERE YOU ARE.
OKAY. I'M I'M GLAD
THAT YOU DECIDED TO HEAR ME OUT.
OKAY. I'M HEARING.
OKAY. I'VE BEEN DOING A LOT OF THINKING-- A LOT--
AND, WELL, I CAME UP WITH A WHOLE BUNCH OF BUSINESSES
THAT YOU CAN DO WITH YOUR VAN.
OKAY. UM... YOU COULD BE A FLOWER DELIVERY PERSON.
WHAT?
OR...
A BAKERY DELIVERY PERSON?
PIZZA?
MONICA!
ALL RIGHT. I'VE GOT A WHOLE BUNCH OF STUFF IN THIS AREA
BUT I'M GETTING THE FEELING
THAT YOU DON'T WANT TO DELIVER.
NO.
OKAY.
I'M GUESSING IF YOU DON'T WANT TO DELIVER
YOU PROBABLY DON'T WANT TO PICK UP STUFF EITHER.
NO.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
LET'S DO THE CATERING BUSINESS.
REALLY? ARE YOU SURE?
YEAH. YOU KNOW, I I...
I MADE A COMMITMENT TO YOU, AND...
YOU KNOW, IT'D IT'D BE FUN.
OH, IT WILL BE FUN!
OH, YAY!
OKAY. LET'S PLAN THE WEDDING RECEPTION.
OKAY.
WOW.
YOU REALLY WANTED ME
TO DO SOMETHING WITH THIS VAN.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I WANT YOU TO TAKE THE CHEF JOB.
REALLY?
YEAH.
THAT'S WHAT YOU REALLY WANT.
YEAH. I DON'T WANT TO BE THE REASON YOU'RE UNHAPPY.
THAT WOULD JUST MAKE ME UNHAPPY
AND I REALLY DON'T WANT TO BE
THE REASON I'M UNHAPPY.
THANK YOU.
BESIDES, IT MIGHT BE KIND OF FUN
TO FORM THE NEW A TEAM.
OH, HI, MRS. LYNCH.
IS JOANNA IN ALREADY?
OH, MY GOODNESS. YOU HAVEN'T HEARD.
HEARD WHAT?
JOANNA... PASSED AWAY LAST NIGHT.
OH, MY GOD! HOW?
SHE WAS LEAVING WORK, AND SHE WAS HIT BY A CAB.
OH, MY GOD!
OH, I CANNOT BELIEVE IT.
OH, I KNOW.
OH, GOD. OH, GOD...
OH, GOD.
I DIDN'T REALIZE THAT YOU WERE SO CLOSE.
YES... SO CLOSE.
MRS. LYNCH, I KNOW THAT THIS IS AN EMOTIONAL
AND DIFFICULT TIME FOR ALL OF US...
BUT BY ANY CHANCE DID JOANNA SEND ANY PAPERWORK YOUR WAY
BEFORE... IT HAPPENED?
NO. NOTHING.
IMAGINE...
IF SHE'D JUST STEPPED OFF THAT CURB
A FEW SECONDS LATER.
OH, YES, YES.
JUST A FEW SECONDS AND SHE'D STILL BE WITH US.
NOTHING ABOUT AN ASSISTANT BUYER OR...?
I'M SORRY.
I HAVE TO GO.
GOOD MORNING.
OH, SOPHIE, I GUESS
YOU DIDN'T HEAR ABOUT JOANNA.
I SURE DID.
I'M SO EXCITED
ABOUT HAVING MONICA COME ON BOARD WITH US
ALTHOUGH I DO FEEL BAD ABOUT HAVING FIRED CHEF EMILIO.
IT IS LIKE LOSING A MEMBER OF THE FAMILY.
OF COURSE, THAT LITERALLY IS THE CASE
FOR SEVERAL OF YOU.
TONY, CARLOS, MARIE, PLEASE, TELL YOUR FATHER
HOW MUCH WE'RE GOING TO MISS HIM.
NOW, I KNOW THAT MONICA
HAS A LOT OF GREAT IDEAS FOR THIS PLACE--
WELL, YOU ALL READ THE REVIEW--
SO, WITHOUT MUCH FURTHER ADO
I PRESENT TO YOU OUR NEW HEAD CHEF.
UM, I JUST WANT TO SAY, UH, THAT WITH A PINCH OF EXCITEMENT
A DASH OF HARD WORK AND A DOLLOP OF COOPERATION
WE CAN HAVE THE RECIPE...
ARE YOU GOING TO KILL ME?