YOU GUYS, HURRY UP.
THE FLIGHT LEAVES IN FOUR HOURS.
IT COULD TAKE TIME TO GET A TAXI.
THERE COULD BE TRAFFIC.
THE PLANE COULD LEAVE EARLY.
WHEN WE GET TO LONDON, THERE COULD BE A LINE AT CUSTOMS.
COME ON!
SIX HOUR TRIP TO LONDON.
THAT'S A LOT OF MONICA.
WHAT DO YOU GOT THERE?
CONDOMS, DUDE.
WELL, HOW COME THE WRITING IS IN SPANISH?
DON'T READ MY CONDOMS.
PASSPORT. CHECK.
CAMERA. CHECK.
TRAVELER'S CHECKS. CHECK.
WHO ARE YOU SAYING CHECK TO?
MYSELF.
YOU KNOW, FOR REMEMBERING TO PACK THE THING.
YOU KNOW, YOU DO A GOOD THING, YOU GET A CHECK.
MY MOM DOES IT.
I NEVER REALIZED IT WAS WEIRD.
HEY, MY MOM USED TO PUT HER HEAD IN THE OVEN.
ACTUALLY, SHE ONLY DID IT THE ONE TIME
BUT IT WAS PRETTY WEIRD.
HEY.
ARE YOU READY YET?
YEP. YOU GOT THE TICKETS?
OH, GOT THEM RIGHT HERE. CHECK.
IT'S ALL LONDON, BABY.
HERE WE GO.
YOU GOT YOUR PASSPORT?
YEAH. IN MY THIRD DRAWER IN MY DRESSER.
YOU DON'T WANT TO LOSE THAT.
OH!
THERE IT IS.
OKAY, IF YOU NEED THE VACUUM
IT'S IN MY CLOSET ON THE LEFT HAND SIDE, OKAY?
THE GARBAGE BAGS ARE NEXT TO THE REFRIGERATOR.
OKAY, OKAY, BUT RACHEL'S GOING TO BE HERE, TOO.
CAN'T I JUST ASK HER THIS STUFF?
YEAH, OKAY, GIVE THAT A TRY.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S DO IT.
YEAH, CHEERIO.
LONDON, BABY.
OKAY, BECAUSE THAT'S NOT GOING TO GET ANNOYING.
LONDON, BABY!
YOU KNOW WHAT? I WAS WRONG.
WELL, WE'RE ALL HERE.
I GUESS WE SHOULD GET GOING.
OH, I WANT TO COME OVER THERE AND GIVE YOU A HUG
AND WISH YOU LUCK ON YOUR WEDDING
BUT I CAN'T GET UP.
I'LL COME HUG YOU.
GREAT, YEAH. COULD YOU BRING ME THE NEWSPAPER?
YEAH.
HAVE A GREAT WEDDING.
THANKS.
HEY, CHANDLER, I WANT TO HUG YOU, TOO.
HEY.
OH, AND GREAT, YOU MIG HT AS WELL BRING ME MY BOOK.
IT'S ON THE COUNTER IN YOUR APARTMENT.
OH.
SO, WE'RE OFF.
HAVE FUN.
THANKS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE NOT GOING TO BE THERE.
OH, I KNOW.
SO, SO, SO COME. WHY DON'T YOU COME?
WHAT? TO LONDON.
COME TO LONDON, PLEASE.
IT WOULD MEAN SO MUCH TO ME.
YEAH, I GOT TO WORK.
I'M SORRY.
WHY CAN'T YOU TAKE A COUPLE OF DAYS OFF?
BECAUSE I CAN'T, ROSS.
I TOLD YOU, NO, I CAN'T.
THIS IS MY WEDDING.
ALL RIGHT, YOU KNOW WHAT? NOW WE REALLY ARE LATE.
LET'S GO! LET'S GO! LET'S GO!
FINE. YOU'LL... YOU'LL WATCH IT ON VIDEO
WHEN WE GET BACK.
HERE YOU GO, PHOEBE.
HERE YOU GO, PHO BO, PHOO BILA, PHEE BE BOO.
THANK YOU.
YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GO.
BYE, PHEEBS.
GOOD BYE.
BYE.
LONDON, BABY!
OH, GOD.
OH, DO YOU NEED A HUG?
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BRING ME ANYTHING.
?? LONDON CALLING ??
?? YES, I WAS THERE, TOO ??
?? AND YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAID? ??
?? WELL, SOME OF IT WAS TRUE ??
?? LONDON CALLING. ??
ALL RIGHT, CHANDLER, DO SOMETHING.
COME ON, DO SOMETHING.
I AM. I'M IGNORING YOU.
OKAY, HERE.
I'M GOING TO BE THE ON CAMERA GUY.
ALL RIGHT, FIRST STOP:
WESTMINSTER ABBEY.
OH, WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
THAT'S LONDON, BABY.
ALL RIGHT, THE HOTEL'S HERE.
WAIT.
NO. WE WANT TO GO...
NO.
I KNOW.
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO GO INTO THE MAP.
OKAY, IF YOU SEE A LITTLE VERSION OF ME IN THERE
KILL IT.
I GOT IT.
HERE WE GO.
OKAY, LISTEN, LISTEN.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO HAVE TO WALK THIS WAY
THE ENTIRE TIME, ARE WE?
SHH.
OH, MAN, YOU MADE ME LOSE IT.
AND THAT WAS ALL BEFORE 10.
THE CATERER RANG TO SAY IT'S GOING TO BE CHICKEN KIEV
INSTEAD OF CHICKEN TARRAGON.
AND THEN THE FLORIST PHONED TO SAY
THAT THERE AREN'T ANY TULIPS.
OH, AND THEN THE CELLIST HAS CARPAL TUNNEL SYNDROME.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA. EMILY, HONEY, OKAY.
WELL, UP YOURS, TOO.
WHAT?
OH... THAT'S NOT WHAT IT MEANS?
NO, NO. THAT'S TIME OUT.
SORRY.
SWEETIE, YOU GOT TO RELAX.
EVERYTHING'S GOING TO BE GREAT, OKAY?
COME ON, COME ON.
CHICKEN KIEV?
MM HMM..
DOESN'T THAT SOUND DELICIOUS AT THE LAST MINUTE?
I KNOW
BUT SOMETHING LIKE SALMON
WOULD BE SO MUCH MORE ELEGANT THAN CHICKEN
AND YOU WOULDN'T HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT THE SALMONELLA.
OH, GOD.
BUT, OF COURSE, WITH SALMON
YOU'D HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT THE CHICKENELLA.
SO I CAN'T WAIT
TO SEE WHERE YOU'RE GETTING MARRIED.
YES, YES.
THIS PLACE IS BEAUTIFUL.
EMILY'S PARENTS GOT MARRIED HERE.
I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE THEY'RE TEARING IT DOWN.
IT REALLY IS THE MOST LOVELY BUILDING.
I MEAN, IT'S OVER...
OH, MY GOD.
IT'S NICE.
OH.
OH. OH, MY GOD.
HOW CAN THIS BE HAPPENING?
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
EVERYTHING'S GOING TO BE ALL RIGHT.
HOW IS IT GOING TO BE ALL RIGHT?
UH HUH, I SEE THAT.
OKAY, I TALKED TO  THE GUY WITH THE SHOVEL
AND I FOUND OUT WHAT HAPPENED.
WHAT?
THEY TORE IT DOWN A FEW DAYS EARLY.
?? ENGLAND SWINGS LIKE A PENDULUM DO ??
?? BOBBIES ON BICYCLES, TWO BY TWO ??
?? WESTMINSTER ABBEY, THE TOWER OF BIG BEN ??
?? THE ROSY RED CHEEKS OF THE LITTLE CHILDREN ??
?? NOW, IF YOU HUFF AND PUFF AND YOU FINALLY SAVE ENOUGH MONEY ??
?? TO TAKE YOUR FAMILY ON A TRIP ACROSS THE SEA ??
?? TAKE A TIP BEFORE YOU TAKE YOUR TRIP ??
?? LET ME TELL YOU WHERE TO GO... ??
?? GO TO ENGLAND ??
?? OH, ENGLAND SWINGS LIKE A PENDULUM DO ??
?? BOBBIES ON BICYCLES, TWO BY TWO ??
?? WESTMINSTER ABBEY, THE TOWER OF BIG BEN ??
?? THE ROSY RED CHEEKS OF THE LITTLE CHILDREN... ??
ALL RIGHT, WESTMINSTER ABBEY.
HANDS DOWN, BEST ABBEY I'VE EVER SEEN.
HEY.
OKAY.
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF THE ABBEY, CHANDLER?
I THINK IT'S GREAT.
THEY'RE THINKING OF CHANGING THE NAME OF THIS PLACE.
REALLY? TO WHAT?
TO PUT THE CAMERA AWAY!
MAN, YOU ARE WESTMINSTERCR ABBY.
DON'T WORRY. YOU'LL FIND SOMEPLACE TO GET MARRIED.
OW!
SORRY.
LUCKY THIS DRESS IS RED.
BUT IF WE CAN'T FIND ANOTHER PLACE...
THEN WE CAN'T HAVE THE WEDDING.
I'VE ORDERED CHICKEN AND SALAD
For 50 AND CAKE FOR 1
WHAT SHOULD BE THE MOST WONDERFUL DAY OF MY LIFE
IS RAPIDLY TURNING INTO JUST SUNDAY
WITH A SPECTACULAR AMOUNT OF FOOD.
YOU'RE GOING TO FIND A PLACE.
BUT, EVEN IF, GOD FORBID, YOU DIDN'T
SO YOU POSTPONE THE WEDDING.
IS THAT REALLY SO BAD?
I MEAN, THINK ABOUT IT.
YOU COULD TAKE ALL THE TIME YOU NEEDED
TO GET EVERYTHING THAT YOU WANT.
YOU COULD HAVE TULIPS.
YOU COULD HAVE SALMON.
MMM... SALMON.
I SUPPOSE IT WOULDN'T BE THE END OF THE WORLD.
OH...
OH, THANK YOU!
LOOK, EITHER WAY, YOU'RE GOING TO GET MARRIED
YOU'RE GOING TO BE HAPPY.
MY MOM'S GOING
TO LIKE YOU BETTER THAN ME.
OH, GOD. SHE'S TOLD YOU THAT ALREADY, DIDN'T SHE?!
OH.
OH, HONEY, DON'T GET UP.
WHAT DO YOU NEED?
NOTHING.
I AM HERE TO TAKE CARE OF YOU.
WHAT DO YOU NEED? ANYTHING.
OKAY. I HAVE A WEDGIE.
OKAY, THAT IS ALL YOU.
SO...
SO WHAT DO YOU WANT FOR LUNCH?
OH, I DON'T KNOW.
I GUESS WE HAVE TO EAT.
YEAH, I DO.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
I'M JUST BUMMED THE WAY I LEFT THINGS WITH ROSS.
WISH I DIDN'T LIE TO HIM ABOUT HAVING TO WORK.
SEEMS SO MAD AT ME.
DON'T BE SO HARD ON YOURSELF.
IF SOMEONE I WAS STILL IN LOVE WITH WAS GETTING MARRIED...
STILL IN LOVE WITH?
YEAH.
I'M NOT IN LOVE WITH ROSS.
OH.
NO, NO. GOOD.
ME NEITHER.
PHOEBE, I'M NOT GOING TO ROSS'S WEDDING
BECAUSE HE'S MY EX BOYFRIEND
AND THAT WOULD BE REALLY UNCOMFORTABLE.
NOT BECAUSE I'M STILL IN LOVE WITH HIM.
I MEAN, HEY, YOU KNOW, I LIKE ROSS AS MUCH AS THE NEXT GUY.
I MEAN, CLEARLY, I HAVE FEELINGS FOR HIM
BUT FEELINGS DON'T MEAN LOVE.
DO I STILL HAVE LOVING FEELINGS FOR ROSS?
YEAH!
BUT I HAVE CONTINUING FEELINGS OF LOVE
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN THAT I'M STILL IN LOVE WITH HIM.
YOU KNOW, I HAVE SEXUAL FEELINGS FOR HIM
BUT I DO LOVE HIM.
OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY...
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME?!
W WE THOUGHT YOU KNEW.
"WE"?
YEAH, WE ALL KNOW.
WE TALK ABOUT IT ALL THE TIME.
YOU ALL KNOW.
DOES ROSS KNOW?
OH, NO. ROSS DOESN'T KNOW ANYTHING.
I CANNOT BELIEVE YOU DIDN'T TELL ME!
WELL, BECAUSE WE THOUGHT YOU KNEW.
IT'S SO OBVIOUS.
GOD, IT, IT WOULD BE LIKE, YOU KNOW, TELLING MONICA
"HEY, YOU KNOW, YOU LIKE THINGS CLEAN."
OR, YOU KNOW, "HEY, JOEY, YOU'RE GAY."
WHAT?!
OH, PLEASE.
SHE'S ALWAYS GOT A BROOM IN HER HAND.
HI.
SO, WHAT ARE YOU
FINE GENTLEMEN IN THE MARKET FOR?
WE GOT SCARVES
SOUVENIR POSTCARDS...
CHECK THIS OUT, HUH?
OH, YEAH.
THAT'S THE STUFF.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WELL, I'M NOT GOING TO HAVE TO BUY
THAT "I'M WITH STUPID" TSHIRT ANYMORE.
WELL, I LIKE IT.
HERE YOU GO.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, YOU'RE NOT REALLY GOING TO BUY THAT, ARE YOU?
DON'T YOU THINK YOU'VE EMBARRASSED ME ENOUGH FOR ONE DAY?
OH, I EMBARRASS YOU?
HOW CAN I ANSWER THAT
WHEN I'M PRETENDING I DON'T KNOW YOU?
HE'S JUST JEALOUS. YOU'LL FIT RIGHT IN.
ALL LONDONERS WEAR THEM.
OH, REALLY? THEN HOW COME
NO ONE HERE ANYWHERE IS WEARING ONE?
THEY'RE ALL TOURISTS.
YEAH.
LOOK, IF YOU INSIST ON WEARING THAT IN PUBLIC
YOU'RE GOING TO SPEND THE REST OF THE AFTERNOON
ALL BY YOURSELF.
OH, YEAH?
IF YOU'RE GOING TO MAKE ME CHOOSE.
BETWEEN YOU AND THE HAT, I CHOOSE THE HAT.
GOOD CHOICE. THANKS.
OKAY, LOOK...
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S IT, OKAY? I'M OUT OF HERE.
I'M NOT GOING TO BE EMBARRASSED ANYMORE.
HOW YOU DOING?
JOEY TRIBBIANI, AMERICA.
HELLO?
HEY, I JUST SPOKE TO YOUR DAD, AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
INK HE SEEMS TO TH
WE'LL BE ABLE TO FIND A NEW PLACE FOR THE WEDDING.
WE DON'T HAVE TO.
WH WH WHAT, YOU FOUND A PLACE?
NO, BUT MONICA AND I WERE TALKING
AND AND I WAS SO UPSET ABOUT THE HALL BEING KNOCKED DOWN
AND SHE SUGGESTED
THAT WE JUST PUT THE WEDDING OFF FOR A BIT.
SHE SAID WHAT?
SHE SAID IF I'M NOT GOING TO BE HAPPY
GETTING MARRIED SOMEWHERE THAT WE CAN FIND IN A DAY
WELL, THEN, WE SHOULD JUST POSTPONE IT.
POSTPONE IT?
EMILY, DO YOU THINK
MONICA REALIZES HOW MUCH OUR PARENTS SPENT
ON THIS WEDDING, HUH?
DO YOU THINK MY SISTER'S TEENY, TINY, LITTLE BRAIN COMPREHENDS
THAT PEOPLE TOOK TIME OUT OF THEIR LIVES
TO FLY THOUSANDS OF MILES TO BE HERE, HUH?
THIS ISN'T RIGHT.
LOOK, I REALIZE THAT PEOPLE
ARE GOING TO BE DISAPPOINTED...
BUT I'M SURE THEY'LL COME BACK WHEN WE CAN DO IT RIGHT.
WELL, I CAN'T ASK PEOPLE TO DO THAT.
WOULD YOU ASK PEOPLE TO DO THAT?
DON'T YOU POINT
YOUR PANTS AT ME.
WE HAVE NO CHOICE.
ANYWHERE HALF DECENT WILL HAVE BEEN BOOKED MONTHS AGO.
DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND?
THIS IS OUR WEDDING I'M TALKING ABOUT.
THE ONLY THING I UNDERSTAND
IS POSTPONING IT IS NOT AN OPTION.
THIS IS WHEN WE'RE GETTING MARRIED.
SO, WHAT ARE YOU SAYING? IT'S NOW OR NEVER?
NO, I'M SAYING IT'S NOW.
OR?
THERE'S NO "OR" IN MINE.
WHAT IS WRONG WITH THESE PANTS?!
IT'S NOT THE PANTS, IT'S YOU WHO'S BACKWARDS.
IF YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND HOW IMPORTANT THIS IS TO ME
WELL, THEN, PERHAPS  WE SHOULDN'T BE GETTING MARRIED AT ALL.
WH... E EMILY, NO. WAIT.
STOP. EMILY, PLEA...
HEY.
SO, DID SHOPPING
HELP YOU FEEL ANY BETTER ABOUT ROSS?
MANHATTAN DOES NOT HAVE
ENOUGH STORES.
WELL, I THINK I CAN HELP YOU
GET OVER HIM.
YOU CAN?
YEAH. I JUST NEED YOU TO BRING ME
SOME PHOTOS OF ROSS, AND A SMALL PIECE OF CHOCOLATE
AND A GLASS OF TEPID WATER.
OOH, IS THIS ONE OF THOSE THINGS
WHERE YOU THROW A WHOLE BUNCH OF STUFF
IN A BAG WITH SOME GRAVEYARD DIRT
AND THEN HANG IT FROM A NORTH FACING TREE?
ONLY IF YOU HAVE THE HICCUPS, TOO.
YEAH, THE PICTURES ARE FOR YOU.
THE CHOCOLATE
AND THE WATER'S FOR ME.
I JUST DIDN'T FEEL LIKE GETTING UP.
OKAY, I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU A PICTURE OF ROSS, OKAY?
AND YOU'RE GOING TO REMEMBER ALL THE BAD THINGS ABOUT HIM.
ALL RIGHT? REALLY FOCUS ON HIS FLAWS.
I CAN DO THAT.
I CERTAINLY DID THAT WHILE WE WERE GOING OUT.
OKAY. HMM, BEFORE WE GET STARTED
I JUST WANT TO SAY FOR THE RECORD
THAT I LOVE ROSS.
I THINK HE'S SUCH A GREAT GUY.
OKAY, NOW
CLOSE YOUR EYES
AND IMAGINE THAT YOU'RE WITH ROSS.
OKAY, AND IMAGINE THAT YOU'RE KISSING HIM
AND YOU'RE RUNNING YOUR HANDS ALL OVER HIS BODY
AND THEN YOU RUN YOUR HANDS THROUGH HIS HAIR
BUT, OH! EW! GROSS!
IT'S SOME KIND OF GREASE.
IT'S GROSS!
HUH?
WELL, I DON'T KNOW.
HIS HAIR NEVER BOTHERED ME THAT MUCH.
AND, YOU KNOW, IT WAS ALWAYS MORE CRUNCHY THAN IT WAS GREASY.
OKAY.
THIS'LL BE HARDER THAN I THOUGHT.
UM, LET'S TRY SOME AVERSION THERAPY.
OKAY. OKAY?
SO LOOK AT THE PICTURE.
OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
AND, UM...
OW!
OKAY. HOW DO YOU FEEL NOW?
WELL, I LIKE YOU LESS.
WOW. THIS IS JUST AS BORING IN ENGLAND.
HEY.
OH. SORRY.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M SORRY.
I REALLY SHOULDN'T HAVE SAID
THAT YOU WERE EMBARRASSING ME.
THAT REALLY WASN'T COOL.
IF IT MAKES YOU FEEL ANY BETTER
I'VE HAD A REALLY LOUSY DAY.
ME, TOO.
YEAH?
NO!
I HAD THE BEST DAY EVER.
DUDE, CHECK THIS OUT.
ALL RIGHT, NOW
I'M GOING TO FAST FORWARD PAST THE PART WITH YOU
BECAUSE IT IS BORING.
HEY!
SHH, SHH.
Say hi to my friend and tell him you like my hat.
So what's your friend's name?
Chandler.
Okay. So, hi, Chandler.
THAT... THAT WAS...
THAT'S FERGIE, BABY!
Joey says you don't really like his hat
but I think it's kind of dashing.
So I hear you're single now.
Yeah, um...
I don't like the hat that much.
HOW DID YOU...? WHEN DID YOU...?
I WAS TRYING TO FIGURE OUT HOW TO GET TO BUCKINGHAM PALACE
SO I'M IN MY MAP, AND...
HEY.
I UNDERSTAND YOU HAD A LITTLE TALK WITH EMILY.
YES, I DID.
AND YOU ARE WELCOME.
AM I?
AND WAS IT YOUR IDEA TO POSTPONE THE WEDDING?
UM...
I'M GOING TO GO TO THE BATHROOM.
WAIT UP.
HEY, HEY.
SINCE YOU'RE THE FIX IT LADY
HERE'S A PICKLE.
WHAT DO YOU DO WHEN THE BRIDE SAYS
SHE DOESN'T WANT TO HAVE THE WEDDING AT ALL?
SHE SAID THAT?
YEAH.
WHY?
I DON'T KNOW.
I TOLD HER IT WAS STUPID
TO PUT OFF THE WEDDING JUST BECAUSE THE HALL WAS GONE
AND SHE, LIKE, FLIPPED OUT.
OH, MY GOD.
YOU'RE EVEN DUMB ER THAN I AM.
EXCUSE ME?
ROSS, HOW LONG HAVE YOU BEEN PLANNING THIS WEDDING?
I DON'T KNOW. A MONTH.
EMILY HAS PROBABLY BEEN PLANNING IT SINCE SHE WAS FIVE--
EVER SINCE THE FIRST TIME SHE TOOK A PILLOWCASE
AND HUNG IT OFF THE BACK OF HER HEAD.
THAT'S WHAT WE DID.
WE DREAMED ABOUT THE PERFECT WEDDING...
AND THE PERFECT PLACE...
WITH THE PERFECT FOUR TIERED WEDDING CAKE...
WITH THE LITTLE PEOPLE ON TOP.
BUT THE MOST IMPORTANT PART
IS THAT WE HAD THE PERFECT GUY
WHO UNDERSTOOD JUST HOW IMPORTANT
ALL THAT OTHER STUFF WAS.
I HAD NO IDEA.
THAT PILLOWCASE THING?
I THOUGHT YOU GUYS WERE JUST DOING THE FLYING NUN.
SOMETIMES WE WERE.
COME ON.
YOU'RE GOING TO HELP ME FIGURE OUT WHAT TO DO, OKAY?
OKAY.
COME ON.
WHOA, PRETTY INTENSE, HUH?
YEAH.
HEY, I HOPE ROSS DIDN'T THINK WE JUST WENT IN THERE
BECAUSE WE WERE UNCOMFORTABLE BEING OUT HERE.
I HOPE HE DID.
OOH. I THOUGHT OF A GOOD FLAW.
ROSS POPS HIS GUM.
OH, RIGHT.
WAIT A MINUTE.
I DO THAT, TOO.
YEAH, I KNOW. IT DRIVES ME CRAZY.
I'LL GET IT.
HELLO.
HEY, PHEEBS. IT'S JOEY.
HEY, JOEY. HEY, OH.
OH, I JUST SAW SOMEONE
THAT LOOKS JUST LIKE YOU ON THE SUBWAY
AND I WAS GOING TO GO OVER AND SAY HI
BUT THEN I FIGURED, HE DOESN'T CARE HE LOOKS LIKE YOU.
THAT JUST COST ME FOUR BUCKS.
BUT, LISTEN, I JUST CALLED
TO SEE HOW THE CHICK AND THE DUCK ARE DOING.
THEY'RE HAVING A GREAT TIME WITH THEIR AUNT PHOEBE.
AUNT RACHEL
HASN'T BEEN HELPFUL AT ALL.
SO DO YOU MISS ME?
KIND OF, BUT I'VE JUST BEEN HAVING WAY TOO MUCH FUN.
OH, SO YOU'RE NOT HOMESICK YET?
NO. I DON'T THINK SO.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, THE SEVEN OF US MISS YOU.
WHO'S SEVEN?
WELL, YOU KNOW, ME, RACHEL
THE BIRDS, THE BABIES.
AW, THE BABIES MISS ME?
OF COURSE THEY DO.
OR I'M JUST REALLY HUNGRY.
THE PIZZA GUY'S HERE.
YOU ORDERED PIZZA WITHOUT ME?
YEAH, BUT, YOU KNOW, WE WERE THINKING ABOUT YOU.
YOU KNOW, WE ORDERED THE JOEY SPECIAL.
TWO PIZZAS?
YEP.
OKAY, GOT TO GO.
TALK TO YOU LATER.
WAIT. WHERE DID YOU GET IT FROM?
?? ...Where everybody knows your name ??
?? And they're always glad you came ??
?? You want to be where you can see ??
?? Troubles are all the same ??
?? You want to be where everybody knows your name. ??
MONICA, WHY HAVE YOU
BROUGHT ME HERE OF ALL PLACES?
YOU'LL SEE.
I TELL YOU, THIS WEDDING
IS NOT GOING TO HAPPEN.
OH, GOD.
OKAY, BUT IMAGINE A LOT MORE LIGHTS, OKAY?
AND... AND, YOU KNOW, FEWER BRICKS, AND...
AND FLOWERS AND CANDLES.
AND THE MUSICIANS-- THEY CAN GO OVER HERE
AND THE CHAIRS-- THEY CAN FACE THIS WAY
AND...
YOU GO.
BUT... BUT IF  YOU DON'T LOVE THIS
THEN WE'LL DO IT ANY OTHER PLACE, ANY OTHER TIME.
REALLY, IT'S FINE. WHATEVER YOU WANT.
IT'S PERFECT.
AND, I DON'T KNOW,  IF IT STARTS TO RAIN...
WELL, THEN WE'LL GET WET.
OH...
I DON'T EVEN HAVE A DATE.
PHEEBS?
YEAH?
DO YOU REMEMBER WHERE THE DUCK FOOD IS?
YEAH, IT'S IN THE GUYS' APARTMENT UNDER THE SINK. WHY?
BECAUSE I'M GOING TO LONDON.
WHAT?!
WHAT DO YOU MEAN YOU'RE GOING TO LONDON?
YEAH, I HAVE TO TELL ROSS THAT I LOVE HIM.
NOW, HONEY, YOU TAKE CARE
AND YOU DON'T HAVE THOSE BABIES TILL I GET BACK.
WHAT ABOUT ALL THE FINDING HIS FLAWS STUFF
WE'VE BEEN DOING?
YEAH. THAT DIDN'T WORK.
RACHEL, YOU CAN'T GO.
ROSS LOVES EMILY.
I KNOW. I KNOW HE DOES
BUT I HAVE TO TELL HIM HOW I FEEL.
HE DESERVES TO HAVE ALL OF THE INFORMATION
AND THEN HE CAN MAKE AN INFORMED DECISION.
THAT'S NOT WHY YOU'RE GOING.
YOU'RE GOING BECAUSE YOU HOPE HE'S GOING TO SAY
"YEAH, I LOVE YOU, TOO, RACH.
FORGET ABOUT THAT BRITISH CHIPPY."
DO YOU THINK HE WILL?
NO, BECAUSE HE'S IN LOVE WITH THE BRITISH CHIPPY.
RACHEL, IF YOU GO
YOU'RE JUST GOING TO MESS WITH HIS HEAD
AND RUIN HIS WEDDING.
YOU KNOW, IT'S TOO LATE.
YOU MISSED YOUR CHANCE.
I'M SORRY.
I KNOW THIS MUST BE REALLY HARD.
IT'S OVER.
YOU KNOW WHAT? NO.
IT'S NOT OVER UNTIL SOMEONE SAYS, "I DO."
I DO.
I DO. I DO.
I DO! I DO!
YEAH, LIKE I CAN REALLY CHASE YOU.
I'M CARRYING A LITTER.