THANK YOU FOR THE DELICIOUS DINNER.
YOU'RE WELCOME FOR THE DELICIOUS DINNER.
HEY! WHAT ARE YOU GUYS LOOKING AT?
ROSS AND THE MOST BEAUTIFUL GIRL IN THE WORLD.
YEAH, COME TO PAPA!
I KNOW!
PROBABLY THE ONLY TIME I'LL EVER SAY THIS
BUT DID YOU SEE THE ASS ON HER?
WHERE DID YOU...?
WHEN DID YOU...?
HOW DID YOU...?
HOW DID YOU GET A GIRL LIKE THAT?
YEAH, SO, WHAT IS SHE...
LIKE, A SPOKES MODEL?
AEROBICS INSTRUCTOR? WHAT?
ACTUALLY, SHE'S A PALEONTOLOGY DOCTORAL CANDIDATE
SPECIALIZING IN THE CENOZOIC ERA.
OKAY, BUT THAT'S, LIKE, THE EASIEST ERA.
I'VE SEEN HER AT WORK
BUT I ALWAYS FIGURED...
BUT, UH, I MADE HER DINNER
WE HAD A GREAT TIME
AND WE'RE GOING OUT AGAIN TOMORROW.
MAYBE SHE AND HER FRIENDS ARE HAVING A CONTEST
TO SEE WHO BRINGS HOME THE BIGGEST GEEK.
FINE BY ME.
HOPE SHE WINS.
HEY, WE SHOULD HAVE A CONTEST.
CAN YEAH. SEE WHO
BRING HOME THE MOST BEAUTIFUL WOMAN.
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA, JOE.
WE COULD CALL IT "LIFE."
YOU GUYS HAVE ANY WRAPPING PAPER?
OH! IS IT FOR MY BIRTHDAY PRESENT?
PHEEBS, IT WAS YOUR BIRTHDAY, LIKE, MONTHS AGO.
YEAH, BUT REMEMBER YOU SAID YOU ORDERED SOMETHING SPECIAL
AND IT JUST HADN'T COME YET?
WELL, I HAVE A CALL IN ABOUT THAT.
OH, OKAY.
ACTUALLY, THIS IS FOR KATHY'S BIRTHDAY.
IT'S AN EARLY EDITION OF HER FAVORITE BOOK.
OH!
THE VELVETEEN RABBIT.
OH, MY GOD. WHEN THE BOY'S LOVE MAKES THE RABBIT REAL...
OKAY, BUT DON'T TOUCH IT
BECAUSE YOUR FINGERS HAVE DESTRUCTIVE OILS.
OH.
WELL, THEN YOU BETTER KEEP IT AWAY
FROM ROSS'S HAIR.
THIS IS PRETTY RARE.
HOW DID YOU GET THAT?
OH, IT WASN'T A BIG DEAL.
I JUST WENT TO A COUPLE OF BOOKSTORES
TALKED TO A COUPLE OF DEALERS
CALLED A COUPLE OF THE AUTHOR'S GRANDCHILDREN.
AW, HONEY, THAT'S SO SWEET.
YEAH, AND WHAT A GREAT WAY
TO SAY, "I SECRETLY LOVE YOU
ROOMMATE'S GIRLFRIEND."
IT DOESN'T SAY THAT.
DOES IT?
HOW DO YOU THINK IT WILL LOOK WHEN YOU GET HER
SOMETHING INCREDIBLY MEANINGFUL AND EXPENSIVE
AND HER BOYFRIEND JOEY
GIVES HER AN ORANGE?
OKAY, I'LL JUST MAKE SURE
JOEY GETS HER SOMETHING REALLY GREAT.
IT'S GOT TO BE BETTER THAN THAT BOOK.
OOH! LIKE A CROSSBOW!
YEAH.
ONCE AGAIN, I AM SORRY.
THANK YOU.
BYE.
I JUST HAD TO TURN DOWN A JOB
CATERING A FUNERAL FOR 60 PEOPLE.
OH, MY GOD!
WHAT HAPPENED?
60 GUESTS.
SO, UH, WHY'D YOU HAVE TO TURN IT DOWN?
BECAUSE  I DON'T HAVE
THE MONEY OR EQUIPMENT
TO HANDLE SOMETHING THAT BIG
ON SUCH SHORT NOTICE.
THERE'S NO WAY.
WHAT IS WITH ALL THE NEGATIVITY?
YOU SOUND LIKE "MONICAN'T", NOT "MONICAN."
"MONICA."
YOU HAVE BEEN PLAYING AROUND WITH CATERING
FOR OVER THREE YEARS.
DO YOU WANT TO BE A CATERER OR NOT?
I DON'T KNOW.
THERE YOU GO! THAT'S THE SPIRIT!
NOW, IF YOU NEED MONEY
I WILL LEND YOU MONEY
BUT JUST GET MOVING!
REALLY? I NEED $500 FOR FOOD AND SUPPLIES AND STUFF.
IT'S WORTH IT IF IT'LL GET YOU MOVING.
YOU HAVEN'T WORKED IN MONTHS.
YOU'RE NOT WORKING EITHER.
YES, BUT I'M DOING THIS.
THAT'D BE GREAT.
THANK YOU.
HEY.
HEY! HEY.
CAN I BORROW THE KEYS TO YOUR APARTMENT?
WHY?
YOU CAN PEE HERE!
YES, I CAN.
OF COURSE.
IF YOU'LL EXCUSE ME.
IT'S OKAY.
THE DUCK'S USING OUR BATHROOM ANYWAY.
HEY, JOE
WHAT ARE YOU GETTING KATHY FOR HER BIRTHDAY?
WE'VE ONLY GONE OUT A COUPLE OF WEEKS.
YOU THINK I GOT TO GET HER SOMETHING?
YES. YOU HAVE TO GET HER SOMETHING REALLY NICE.
OH! I KNOW.
AND NOT ONE OF YOUR COUPONS
FOR AN HOUR OF "JOEY LOVE."
OOH! A CROSSWORD! CAN I HELP?
NO!
I'M SORRY, HONEY.
LAST WEEK, I GOT ALL BUT THREE ANSWERS.
I WANT TO FINISH ONE WITHOUT HELP.
FINE.
BUT YOU CAN'T HELP ME DEVELOP
MY NEW UNIVERSAL LANGUAGE.
HEY.
HOW'D IT GO?
OH, MY GOD!
IT WAS THE BEST FUNERAL EVER!
EVERYONE LOVED THE FOOD
AND GUESS WHAT?
I GOT ANOTHER FUNERAL TOMORROW--
THE DEAD GUY FROM TODAY'S BEST FRIEND.
IT IS LIKE I AM THE OFFICIAL CATERER
FOR THAT ACCIDENT.
GOD, I'M SO HAPPY FOR YOU!
OH, THANKS.
CHECK OUT MY NEW CATERING STUFF.
LOOK! I'M AN OMELET STATION!
"OMELET, MADE TO ORDER."
I'LL HAVE ONE, PLEASE.
PLUS MY MONEY.
OH.
I DIDN'T REALIZE YOU NEEDED IT BACK RIGHT AWAY.
YOU TOLD ME TO GO BE A CATERER.
SO I WENT, I BE'D.
I USED IT TO BUY
ALL THIS STUFF.
"ABORIGINE!"
OH... NO.
I GOT ANOTHER JOB TOMORROW.
I'LL PAY YOU BACK WITH THE MONEY FROM THAT.
OH! OKAY.
OOH, SORRY I ACTED LIKE A BANK.
"ABORIGINE!"
OH, NO, I TRIED THAT ALREADY.
HMM...
UM...
WOULD YOU LIKE TO COME IN?
DID HOMO ERECTUSHUNT WITH WOODEN TOOLS?
ACCORDING TO RECENT FINDINGS.
HERE, MITZI!
HERE, MITZI.
UH...
MITZI IS...?
MY HAMSTER.
I HOPE SHE'S OKAY.
I HAVEN'T SEEN HER IN A WHILE.
HAVE A SEAT.
UH...
OH, HEY!
DO YOU, UH...
DO YOU HAVE ANY, UM...
CINNAMON FRUIT TOASTIES?
WHAT?
WELL, I DO.
WHY DON'T WE GO BACK TO MY PLACE
LIGHT A COUPLE OF CANDLES
BREAK OPEN A BOX OF CINNAMON FRUIT TOASTIES.
I'D RATHER NOT.
OH, YEAH?
WHY NOT?
OKAY, UM...
DON'T TAKE THIS THE WRONG WAY
BUT YOUR PLACE KIND OF HAS A WEIRD SMELL.
IS EVERYTHING IN THE CAR?
YEP. DID YOU SETTLE THE BILL?
NO.
I HATE THIS PART.
OH! LOOK WHAT WE ALMOST LEFT!
THAT'S NOT MINE.
OH, ALL RIGHT.
OOH! LOOK WHAT WE ALMOST TOOK!
EXCUSE ME, MS. BURKART.
WELL, WE'RE ALL CLEANED UP IN THE KITCHEN.
OH, GOOD.
THANK YOU.
UM...
AND, WELL, THERE'S JUST...
THE SMALL MATTER OF THE, UM...
DEAR?
JUST THE MATTER OF...
THE PAYMENT?
JACK USED TO HANDLE THE FINANCES.
DID YOU GET IT?
NO, BUT I MADE A WIDOW CRY.
SEE YOU IN HELL.
YOU KNOW WHAT WE SHOULD ALL DO?
GO SEE A MUSICAL.
SURE.
AND YOU KNOW
WHICH ONE WE SHOULD SEE?
THE 1996 TONY AWARD WINNER.
I MEAN, THAT ONE'S GOT TO BE GOOD.
DO YOU HAPPEN TO KNOW
THE NAME OF THAT ONE?
I DON'T KNOW, UH...
GREASE?
NO.
RENT?
YES!
RENT.
OKAY, SO WHEN DO YOU WANT TO GO?
WHAT?
OH, I'M SORRY, I CAN'T.
I'M BUSY.
HEY.
MAN, IT IS SO HARD TO SHOP FOR GIRLS.
YES, IT IS-- AT "OFFICE MAX."
WHAT DID YOU GET HER?
A PEN.
IT'S TWO GIFTS IN ONE.
IT'S A PEN THAT'S ALSO A CLOCK, HUH?
HA HA!
YOU CAN'T GIVE HER THAT.
WHY NOT?
BECAUSE SHE'S NOT 11!
AND IT'S NOT
THE SEVENTH NIGHT OF HANUKKAH!
HONEY, WHAT HE MEANS IS, WHILE THIS IS A VERY NICE GIFT
MAYBE IT'S JUST NOT SOMETHING A BOYFRIEND GIVES?
SURE, IT IS.
SHE NEEDS A PEN FOR WORK
SHE'S WRITING, SHE TURNS IT OVER--
"WHOA! IT'S TIME FOR MY DATE WITH JOEY!"
LOOK, WHAT DID YOU GET FOR ANGELA DELVECCHIO
FOR HER BIRTHDAY?
SHE DIDN'T HAVE A BIRTHDAY WHILE
WE WERE GOING OUT.
FOR THREE YEARS?
WELL, LOOK, IT'S TOO LATE, AND I GOT AN AUDITION.
I CAN'T SHOP ANYMORE!
ALL RIGHT, I WILL GO OUT
AND I WILL TRY TO FIND SOMETHING FOR HER, OKAY?
THANKS, MAN.
OH, WHILE YOU'RE AT IT, COULD YOU GET HER A CARD?
WOULD YOU LIKE ME TO WRITE HER A LITTLE POEM, AS WELL?
OR JUST GET A CARD  THAT HAS A POEM
ALREADY IN IT.
OH, SO IT'S A CARD
BUT IT'S ALSO A POEM HOLDER.
YOU HAVE TO GET OUR MONEY!
PHEEBS, SHE COULDN'T STOP CRYING.
WITH THOSE THICK GLASSES, HER TEARS LOOKED GIANT.
I KNOW IT'S TOUGH.
YOU KNOW THE FIRST THING I DID AFTER MY MOTHER'S FUNERAL?
WHAT?
PAID THE CATERER.
LOOK, I'VE HAD A LOT OF JOBS
AND THERE ARE SOME PEOPLE
WHO JUST ALWAYS TRY TO GET OUT OF PAYING.
IT'S EITHER, "THAT MASSAGE WASN'T LONG ENOUGH"
OR, "I DON'T RECOGNIZE ANY OF THOSE SONGS"
OR, "THESE SOMBREROS AREN'T BIG ENOUGH.
BAD LITTLE WHITE GIRL."
OKAY.
SO YOU... YOU THINK SHE'S FAKING?
IT SEEMS LIKE THERE WEREN'T ANY TEARS
TILL YOU SHOWED HER THE BILL.
PHOEBE, SHE SOUNDED PRETTY UPSET TO ME.
?? YOU'RE A GRAND OLD FLAG ??
?? YOU'RE A HIGH FLYIN' FLAG ??
?? AND FOREVER IN PEACE MAY YOU WAVE... ??
SHE SEEMS FINE NOW.
?? THE LAND I LOVE  ??
?? THE HOME OF  ??
??THE FREE AND THE BRAVE.??
SO YOU JUST LEFT?
HER PLACE WAS REALLY THAT BAD?
YOU KNOW HOW YOU THROW YOUR JACKET ON A CHAIR
AT THE END OF THE DAY?
LIKE THAT, ONLY INSTEAD OF A CHAIR
IT'S A PILE OF GARBAGE.
AND INSTEAD OF A JACKET, IT'S A PILE OF GARBAGE.
AND INSTEAD OF
THE END OF THE DAY
IT'S THE END OF TIME
AND GARBAGE IS ALL THAT HAS SURVIVED.
HERE.
WOW. THANKS.
SO, UH, WHAT HAPPENED?
NOTHING HAPPENED.
I HAD TO GET OUT OF THERE.
ALL RIGHT. NEXT TIME, YOU TAKE HER TO YOUR PLACE.
NO. I TRIED THAT.
SHE SAYS IT HAS A WEIRD SMELL.
WHAT KIND OF SMELL?
I DON'T KNOW-- SOAP?!
ALL RIGHT. LISTEN, ROSS.
YOU LIKE THIS GIRL, RIGHT?
YOU WANT TO SEE HER AGAIN? YEAH.
SO YOU'LL HAVE TO DO IT
IN THE MESS!
YEAH, OKAY. YOU'RE RIGHT.
YEAH.
I MEAN, UH, WHO CARES ABOUT A LITTLE SLOPPINESS?
YEAH. IT'S, UH...
IT'S ENDEARING, REALLY.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW, YOU GO GET THAT BEAUTIFUL PIG.
OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
I JUST SPENT THE ENTIRE AFTERNOON
LOOKING FOR A PRESENT FOR KATHY
THAT WOULD BE BETTER THAN THE RABBIT.
ANY LUCK?
OH, YEAH.
I FOUND THIS GREAT PLACE CALLED
"INVISIBLE THINGS FOR KATHY."
CAN YOU GIVE ME A HAND WITH ALL THIS STUFF?
ALL RIGHT, LOOK.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST RETURN THE BOOK
LET JOEY GIVE HER THE CLOCK PEN AND YOU GET HER SOMETHING
WORSE THAN THAT... LIKE A REGULAR PEN.
SHE'S REALLY GOING TO LOVE THIS, YOU KNOW?
THE BOTTOM LINE IS I WANT HER TO HAVE IT
EVEN IF I DON'T GET TO BE THE ONE
WHO GIVES IT TO HER.
OH, HONEY, THAT'S SO SWEET.
YEAH? YOU DON'T THINK IT'S JUST PATHETIC?
OOH! "PATHETIC."
HEY! I'M MEETING KATHY IN TEN MINUTES.
I BEEN LOOKING ALL OVER FOR YOU.
WHERE?
OUR PLACE, THE HALL!
I... WE...
I GOT SOMETHING FOR HER.
IT'S A BOOK.
A BOOK?
IS IT, LIKE, A BOOK THAT'S ALSO A SAFE?
IT'S A BOOK THAT'S JUST A BOOK.
IT'S AN EARLY EDITION OF THE VELVETEEN RABBIT.
IT WAS HER FAVORITE BOOK AS A KID.
SO, UH, JUST LET ME KNOW IF SHE LIKES IT, OKAY?
OH, YOU GOT IT. THANKS, MAN.
THANKS FOR DOING THIS. I OWE YOU ONE.
HEY! THERE WASN'T CHANGE FROM THAT 20, WAS THERE?
NO. IT CAME OUT TO AN EVEN 20.
WOW.
THAT'S ALMOST AS MUCH AS A NEW BOOK.
?? JEEPERS, CREEPERS ??
?? WHERE'D YOU GET THOSE PEEPERS? ??
?? JEEPERS, CREEPERS...??
YOU DIDN'T GET THE MONEY, DID YOU?
MAYBE I CAN TRY AT INTERMISSION?
OH, PHOEBE, COME ON.
LET'S JUST GO.
NO! HEY, WE'RE NOT LEAVING TILL WE GET PAID.
WHO DOES SHE THINK SHE IS?
I WAS TALKING TO THE FLORIST.
SHE DIDN'T GET PAID EITHER.
OR THE LIMO DRIVER, OR THE PRIEST--
AND HE CAN GET THE DEAD GUY DAMNED FOR ALL ETERNITY.
WELL, I... I'M NOT GOING BACK OUT THERE.
FINE. ENOUGH IS ENOUGH.
HEY, WIDOW.
?? COME ON ALONG AND LISTEN TO ?? WIDOW?
?? THE LULLABY OF... ?? EXCUSE ME. EXCUSE ME!
THANKS.
UM, CLEARLY, THIS IS A VERY, VERY HARD TIME FOR YOU
UM, BUT WE PROVIDED A SERVICE AND WE DESERVE TO BE PAID
BECAUSE YOU ATE THAT SERVICE
AND, UM, WE ARE NOT LEAVING HERE
UNTIL WE ARE PAID EVERY PENNY, BECAUSE YOU KNOW WHAT, LADY?
WE'RE PART TIME CATERERS AND WE HAVE NO PLACE ELSE TO GO.
OH, ALL RIGHT.
I'LL GET MY BAG.
GOOD.
I'M GOING TO LEAVE SOME CARDS HERE.
PLEASE THINK OF US  FOR YOUR NEXT EVENT.
SO, YOU WANT TO COME INSIDE?
YES.
YES, I DO.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
MAKE YOURSELF COMFORTABLE.
GUESS WHO.
UH... DEPARTMENT OF SANITATION?
IT'S ME.
OH.
OH!
WHAT?
OH, CHERYL!
OH, ROSS!
OH! OH!
OH... GOD.
ROSS, NO!
NO, NO, NO!
IT'S MITZI. IT'S MY...
IT'S MY HAMSTER! IT'S MITZI!
OH, MY GOD.
I'M SO SORRY. I MUST HAVE FREAKED OUT.
OH, THANK GOD, IT'S NOT MITZI.
IT'S JUST A RAT.
I DID IT.
OH! I FINISHED IT!
I DID IT ALL BY MYSELF!
AND THERE'S NOBODY TO HUG.
MOVE!
HEY.
HEY, YOU GUYS!
I FINISHED THE CROSSWORD BY MYSELF. HUG ME.
YAY! THAT'S SO GOOD.
CONGRATULATIONS.
THANK YOU.
HOW'D THE CATERING GO?
OH, IT WAS GREAT.
THE WIDOW WOULDN'T PAY
SO PHOEBE YELLED AT HER TILL SHE DID.
YEAH. I'M A HARD ASS.
AND I'M A WUSS.
AND WE SHOULD BE PARTNERS.
YEAH-- HARD ASS AND WUSS.
WE COULD FIGHT CRIME.
WAIT A MINUTE, PHOEBE.
WE SHOULD BE PARTNERS.
WE SHOULD BE CATERING PARTNERS.
THINK ABOUT IT.
YOU'RE NOT WORKING RIGHT NOW
AND WE HAVE SUCH A GREAT TIME TOGETHER.
OKAY.
I COOK, YOU TAKE CARE OF THE MONEY.
OH! IT'LL BE LIKE I HAVE A WIFE IN THE '50s.
HEY.
HEY. HOW'D IT GO?
HOW'D SHE LIKE THE GIFT?
MAN, SHE LOVED IT.
SHE'S SHOWING MONICA AND RACHEL NOW.
OH, YEAH? THAT'S GREAT.
LISTEN. I GOT TO TELL YOU.
I FEEL KIND OF BAD TAKING CREDIT FOR THIS
BECAUSE, MAN, AM I GOING TO GET
A LOT OF CREDIT FOR THIS.
HEY.
HEY. HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
THANK YOU.
YOU KNOW, UH, CHANDLER GOT YOU A GIFT, TOO.
NO, HE DIDN'T.
YEAH, HE DID.
LOOK. IT'S RIGHT THERE ON THE COUNTER. HO HO HO!
HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
I'M SORRY.
YOU REALLY DIDN'T HAVE TO.
WOW.
SEE, YOU THINK IT'S JUST A PEN
BUT THEN YOU TURN IT OVER AND IT'S ALSO A CLOCK.
YEAH.
NO. THIS IS GREAT.
THANK YOU, CHANDLER.
OH. Y YEAH.
AH.
WANT TO GO TO BED?
I'LL BE IN IN A MINUTE.
OH, UH, DON'T FORGET YOUR COUPON.
GOOD NIGHT.
UM, THANK YOU FOR THE GIFT.
OH, UH, YEAH.
I JUST KNEW THAT SOMETIMES WHEN YOU'RE WRITING
YOU YOU DON'T ALWAYS KNOW THE EXACT TIME.
NO. I DIDN'T MEAN THE PEN.
THANK YOU FOR THE BOOK.
UH, THE BOOK?
THE VELVETEEN RABBIT?
I HAVE A FEELING YOU HAD SOMETHING TO DO WITH IT.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WELL, WHEN JOEY GAVE IT TO ME
HE SAID, "THIS IS BECAUSE I KNOW YOU LIKE RABBITS
AND I KNOW YOU LIKE CHEESE."
THANKS. I LOVE IT.
AND I KNOW HOW HARD IT MUST HAVE BEEN
FOR YOU TO FIND.
OH, WELL.
BY THE WAY, IN CASE YOU MISSED THAT, THAT SOUND WAS:
YOU MUST REALLY LIKE JOEY
TO GO TO ALL THAT TROUBLE FOR HIM.
OH, YEAH! HE'S MY...
HE'S MY BEST FRIEND.
WELL...
GOOD NIGHT.
HEY, THAT COUPON EXPIRES, YOU KNOW.
HI.
UH, YOU DON'T KNOW ME.
I'M MONICA GELLER, ROSS'S SISTER.
OH, YEAH. YOU KNOW, IT'S TOO BAD
THAT DIDN'T WORK OUT.
YEAH.
ANYWAY, HE TOLD ME ABOUT YOUR APARTMENT
AND, UM, WELL...
I COULDN'T SLEEP THINKING ABOUT IT.
SO, UH...
WOULD IT BE OKAY IF I CLEANED IT?
NO?
I WON'T BE ABLE TO SLEEP.