WOW, THAT RIPPED.
THAT RIPPED REAL NICE.
HOW MANY TIMES DO I HAVE TO TELL YOU--
YOU TURN AND SLIDE?
YOU KNOW? TURN AND SLIDE.
YOU DON'T TURN AND SLIDE.
YOU THROW IT OUT.
I'M TIRED OF HAVING
TO GET A TETANUS SHOT EVERY TIME I GET DRESSED.
WELL, WE'RE NOT THROWING IT OUT.
I BUILT THIS THING WITH MY OWN HANDS.
ALL RIGHT. HOW ABOUT WE...
HOW ABOUT WE SELL IT?
ALL RIGHT.
BUT WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO TELL THEM.
YOU MIND IF WE STICK YOU IN A DIFFERENT CABINET?
THEY SEEM ALL RIGHT WITH IT.
WHY DID THE CHICKEN FALL OUT OF THE TREE?
WHY?
BECAUSE YOU HAVE DOODY ON YOUR HEAD.
IT WAS FUNNIER WHEN BEN TOLD IT.
Hey, Monica. It's Chip.
YES!
WHO'S CHIP?
SHH!
It was good running into you
at the bank today, so here's my number-- 555-9323.
Give me a call. Later.
"CHIP" IS CHIP MATTHEWS.
THE GUY WHO TOOK RACHEL TO THE PROM?
WHY IS HE CALLING YOU?
BECAUSE I RAN INTO HIM AT THE BANK.
HE IS STILL SO CUTE.
MONICA, YOU'RE SO LUCKY.
HE'S, LIKE, THE MOST POPULAR GUY
IN SCHOOL.
YEAH, I KNOW.
CHIP?
HI. IT'S MONICA.
OKAY.
OKAY. GOOD BYE.
OH, MY GOD, WE JUST HAD THE BEST CONVERSATION.
I WAS JUST LEAVING.
GOOD, BECAUSE I'VE GOT
A PRODUCT REPORT TO READ.
IT'S, LIKE, EIGHT PAGES.
I HOPE I DON'T FALL ASLEEP.
WHY? DID YOU WRITE IT?
WELL, HELLO.
LOOK AT THAT.
CHIP MATTHEWS CALLED.
WONDER WHAT HE WANTS.
WELL, UH, ACTUALLY...
I BET HE SENSED THAT I WAS READY TO HAVE SEX WITH ANOTHER GUY.
WELL, UM...
WHY DON'T YOU GIVE HIM A CALL?
OKAY.
ARE YOU SURE YOU WANT TO HEAR THIS?
OH, I'M SURE.
CHIP.
HI. IT'S RACHEL.
RACHEL GREEN.
YEAH. UM, YOU LEFT ME A MESSAGE?
YES, YOU DID.
MY ROOMMATE WROTE IT DOWN.
MONICA GELLER.
OH.
OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
HE CALLED TO ASK OUT MONICA.
OHH. THAT'S-- THAT'S GOT TO BE EMBARRASSING.
?
?? ...DUMB, DRUNKEN BITCH! ?
THANK YOU.
THANKS.
NOW, HERE'S A QUESTION.
WHERE'D YOU GUYS GET "THE FINEST OAK
EAST OF THE MISSISSIPPI"?
FIRST YOU TELL US WHERE YOU GOT
THE PRETTIEST LACE IN ALL THE LAND.
I'M READING YOUR AD.
LOOKS GOOD, HUH?
YEAH.
"STUNNING ENTERTAINMENT CENTER. FINE..."
"FINE ITALIAN CRAFTSMANSHIP."
OH, MY GOD.
YOU GUYS ARE SELLING THE ENTERTAINMENT CENTER?
WHY? I LOVE THAT THING.
YOU WANT IT?
EWW! NO!
UH, GEPPETTO?
5,000 DOLLAR?
ARE YOU INSANE?
HEY, THE AD ALONE COST 300 BUCKS.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK.
I'M CHANGING IT TO "$50 DOLLAR OR YOUR BEST OFFER."
WHAT KIND OF PROFIT IS THAT?
AND YOU CALL YOURSELF AN ACCOUNTANT?
NO.
OH.
WHAT DO YOU DO?
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT I DO FOR A LIVING.
I DON'T. SOMETHING TO DO WITH...?
OH, MY GOD! NO!
SHOO! KITTY? NO!
NO! GUNTHER...
GUNTHER, THERE'S A KITTY IN MY GUITAR CASE.
SHH! EVERYONE'S GOING TO WANT ONE.
COME ON, YOU.
COME ON.
YOU'RE CRAZY.
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT?
NOTHING. NOTHING.
WHAT? WHAT'S WRONG?
I JUST...
I JUST HAVE THIS REALLY STRONG FEELING THAT...
THIS CAT IS MY MOTHER.
YOU MEAN THE MOM YOU MET IN MONTAUK?
SHE WAS A CAT?
THAT MAKES THE FACT
THAT SHE OWNS BEACH FRONT PROPERTY
ALL THE MORE IMPRESSIVE.
NO, NO, NO.
SHE WAS A HUMAN LADY.
THIS IS THE SPIRIT  OF MY MOM, LILY--
THE ONE THAT KILLED HERSELF.
ARE YOU SURE SHE'S IN THE CAT, OR HAVE YOU BEEN TAKING
YOUR GRANDMA'S GLAUCOMA MEDICINE AGAIN?
NO, DR. SKEPTISMO.
I'M SURE.
FIRST OF ALL, OKAY, THERE'S THE FEELING.
OKAY, AND FOR ANOTHER
HOW ABOUT THE FACT THAT SHE WENT INTO MY GUITAR CASE?
WHICH IS LINED WITH ORANGE FELT.
MY MOTHER'S FAVORITE FISH WAS ORANGEROUGHY.
CATS LIKE FISH.
YOU HAD ME WITH ORANGE FELT.
HI, MOMMY.
OH! I HAVEN'T SEEN
THIS SMILE IN 17 YEARS.
DUDE, PHOEBE'S MOM'S GOT A HUGE PAIR...
LET IT GO!
HEY.
UM, WHEN WERE YOU GOING TO TELL ME
THAT YOU'RE GOING OUT WITH CHIP MATTHEWS?
NOW.
IS IT OKAY IF I GO OUT WITH CHIP MATTHEWS?
NO, IT'S NOT OKAY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU WOULD WANT TO
AFTER WHAT HE DID TO ME.
WHAT? THAT LITTLE THING AT THE PROM?
MONICA, I COULDN'T FIND HIM FOR TWO HOURS.
HE WAS HAVING SEX WITH AMY WELSH.
OH, COME ON, THAT WAS BACK IN HIGH SCHOOL.
HOW COULD THAT STILL BOTHER YOU?
OH, YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT, MONI COW.
OKAY, I HEAR YOU.
WHY, OF ALL PEOPLE, DO YOU HAVE TO GO OUT WITH CHIP?
YOU AND I WENT TO DIFFERENT HIGH SCHOOLS.
THAT DOESN'T HELP ME, BECAUSE WE WENT TO THE SAME HIGH SCHOOL.
YOU WENT TO ONE WHERE YOU WERE POPULAR
AND YOU GOT TO RIDE OFF ON CHIP'S MOTORCYCLE
AND WEAR HIS LETTERMAN JACKET.
I WENT TO ONE WHERE I WORE A BAND UNIFORM
THEY HAD TO HAVE SPECIALLY MADE.
THEY HAD TO HAVE THAT SPECIALLY MADE?
IT WAS A PROJECT FOR ONE OF THE HOME EC CLASSES.
OH, MY GOD.
THEY TOLD US THAT WAS FOR THE MASCOT.
BACK THEN, I THOUGHT
THAT I WOULD NEVER, EVER GET THE CHANCE
TO GO OUT WITH A CHIP MATTHEWS
AND NOW HE'S... HE'S CALLED ME UP AND ASKED ME OUT
AND THE FAT GIRL INSIDE ME REALLY WANTS TO GO.
I OWE HER THIS.
I NEVER LET HER EAT.
OH, YOU GO OUT WITH HIM.
OH, REALLY?
YEAH.
JUST, IF IT'S POSSIBLE
COULD YOU LEAVE HIM SOMEWHERE
AND GO HAVE SEX WITH ANOTHER GUY?
I'LL TRY.
YOU GUYS HAVING ANY LUCK GETTING RID
OF THE ENTERTAINMENT CENTER?
THERE WERE A COUPLE CALLS LAST NIGHT
BUT I DON'T THINK ANY OF THEM
ARE GOING TO WORK OUT.
YES, JOEY HAS A VERY CAREFUL SCREENING PROCESS.
APPARENTLY, NOT EVERYONE IS QUALIFIED TO OWN
WOOD AND NAILS.
STOP IT. STOP IT.
SHE KEEPS SQUIRMING AND TRYING TO GET AWAY--
JUST LIKE WHEN SHE WAS ALIVE.
SO, PHEEBS, HOW LONG
IS YOUR MOM GOING TO BE WITH US?
WELL, I'M NOT SURE.
I MEAN, I GUESS UNTIL SHE, YOU KNOW, GETS USED TO THE FACT
THAT THERE'S, YOU KNOW, A NEW MOM.
YOU KNOW, I THINK SHE'S WORRIED
THAT SHE'S GOING TO...
SHE'S GOING TO BE REPLACED.
WELL, THAT'S NOT GOING TO HAPPEN, IS IT? NO.
OKAY, I HAVE TO RETURN
A CALL IN THE OTHER ROOM.
WHY CAN'T YOU USE THE PHONE IN HERE?
WELL, I'M RETURNING A CALL FROM A CERTAIN MOM
AT THE B E A C H.
I JUST SPELLED THE WRONG WORD.
ANYWAY, I DON'T WANT TO DO IT
IN FRONT OF SOMEONE WITH A TAIL.
HEY, YOU SWORE YOU WOULD NEVER TELL.
SO, GUYS, AM I CRAZY, OR DOES PHOEBE'S MOM
REMIND ANYONE ELSE OF A CAT?
ROSS, DON'T START.
COME ON.
YOU CAN'T TELL ME YOU ACTUALLY BELIEVE
THAT THERE'S A WOMAN INSIDE THAT CAT.
I BELIEVE IT.
NO, YOU DON'T.
YES, I DO.
NO, YOU D...
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO SUCK ME INTO THIS.
OH, SURE, I AM--
BECAUSE YOU ALWAYS HAVE TO BE RIGHT.
I DO NOT ALWAYS HAVE... OKAY, OKAY.
JURASSIC PARK  COULD HAPPEN.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
ACTUALLY, I DO THINK KIRK WAS SMARTER THAN SPOCK.
YOU WERE KIDDING
ABOUT THE KIRK SPOCK THING, THOUGH, RIGHT?
WOW. THAT'S, UH... THAT'S PRETTY NICE.
PRETTY NICE?
YOU'LL HAVE TO PARDON MY ROOMMATE.
HE WANTED TO MARRY THIS.
WE DON'T HAVE 50 BUCKS.
BUT WOULD YOU BE WILLING TO TRADE FOR IT?
WE GOT A CANOE.
YOU KNOW, I... I REALLY DON'T THINK WE NEED A CANOE.
YOU GOT TO TAKE
THE CANOE.
ALL RIGHT, JUST...
JUST TAKE THE ENTERTAINMENT CENTER
AND THEN, WHEN YOU GET HOME
THROW THE CANOE AWAY.
WE'RE NOT THROWING IT AWAY.
I BUILT THAT CANOE.
GOOD FOR YOU!
GUYS, YOU'RE NEVER GOING TO BELIEVE
WHAT I JUST FOUND TACKED UP ON A TELEPHONE POLE.
LOOKS KIND OF FAMILIAR.
APPARENTLY, PHOEBE'S MOTHER ALSO GOES BY THE NAME JULIO.
WAIT A MINUTE.
THIS IS NOT THE SAME CAT.
THIS CAT'S ONLY THIS BIG.
YOU GUYS, THERE'S A LITTLE GIRL IN SOHO
LOOKING FOR THIS CAT.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS?
YEAH. A $200 REWARD SPLIT FIVE WAYS.
DO WE HAVE TO TELL HER?
YES, WE HAVE
TO TELL HER.
OH, BUT IT'S MADE HER SO HAPPY.
LITTLE GIRL MISSES HER CAT.
CRAZY LADY THINKS HER MOTHER IS IN A CAT.
OKAY. YOU KNOW WHAT?
I HAVE TO GO HAVE DINNER WITH MY SON.
CAN I TRUST THAT, WHEN YOU SEE PHOEBE, YOU WILL TELL HER?
YES. YEAH.
THANK YOU.
I HATE WHEN ROSS IS RIGHT.
HE IS RIGHT, ISN'T HE?
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
THIS MIGHT BE ONE OF THE TIMES WHEN HE'S WRONG.
YOU THINK? YOU THINK?
OH, NO. HE'S RIGHT.
HI.
HI. HI.
HEY.
UH, PHEEBS
ABOUT YOUR MOM...
YEAH?
HOW'S THAT GOING?
SO GREAT.
OH, WE TOOK A NAP TOGETHER TODAY.
MY MOM FELL ASLEEP ON MY TUMMY AND PURRED.
THAT'S SO SWEET.
I'M GOING TO GET SOME COFFEE.
OKAY.
HUH? WHAT'D YOU SAY, JOE?
I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
PHEEBS...
I JUST FEEL SO... OH...
I'M COMING ALREADY. GEEZ!
NOT YET, NOT YET, NOT YET, NOT YET
NOT YET, NOT YET, NOT YET!
HELLO, CHIP.
HEY, RACH, HOW YOU DOING?
I'M GREAT. I'M GREAT.
GOT A GREAT JOB AT BLOOMINGDALE'S
I HAVE WONDERFUL FRIENDS
AND EVEN THOUGH I'M NOT SEEING ANYONE RIGHT NOW
I'VE NEVER REALLY FELT BETTER ABOUT MYSELF.
SO, UH, MONICA READY YET?
SHE'LL BE OUT IN A SECOND.
SO, CHIP, HOW'S, UM, AMY WELSH?
AMY WELSH?
WOW. I HAVEN'T SEEN HER SINCE...
SO... MONICA ABOUT READY?
HI.
HEY. WOW. YOU LOOK GREAT.
THANKS.
WELL, YOU GUYS HAVE FUN.
CATCH YOU LATER.
GOOD BYE, CHIP.
ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE OKAY ABOUT THIS?
ACTUALLY...
OKAY, GREAT!
THIS IS THE UNIT FOR YOU, MY FRIEND--
STURDY CONSTRUCTION, TONS OF STORAGE COMPARTMENTS
SOME BIG ENOUGH TO FIT A GROWN MAN.
WHAT?
OH, YEAH.
I GOT IN THERE MYSELF ONCE.
MY ROOMMATE BET ME FIVE BUCKS THAT I COULDN'T
AND THEN HE STUCK A BOARD THROUGH THE HANDLES
AND LOCKED ME IN-- YEAH.
IT WAS FUNNY TILL I STARTED FEELING LIKE I WAS IN A COFFIN.
NO, YOU...
YOU CAN'T FIT IN THAT THING.
THAT'S NOT DEEP ENOUGH.
OH, YEAH?
IF I CAN'T
I'LL KNOCK FIVE BUCKS OFF THE PRICE OF THE UNIT.
YOU HAVE YOURSELF A DEAL.
OKAY.
SEE? I TOLD YOU.
SOMETIMES I COME IN HERE JUST TO GET AWAY FROM IT.
HEY, A NICKEL!
HERE WE ARE.
OH, MY GOD, YOU STILL HAVE THE CHIPPER.
THE WHAT?
THAT'S WHAT WE USED TO CALL YOUR MOTORCYCLE
IN HIGH SCHOOL.
YOU KNOW, A MOTORCYCLE'S A CHOPPER
AND YOU'RE CHIP.
NEVER MIND.
NO. I THINK IT'S CUTE.
WOW.
A LIPPER FROM THE CHIPPER.
SO, YOU STILL IN TOUCH
WITH ANYONE FROM HIGH SCHOOL?
UM, THERE'S RACHEL, AND, UM...
I THINK THAT'S IT.
HOW ABOUT YOU?
OH, YEAH, I STILL HANG WITH SIMENS AND ZANA
AND I SEE SPINDLER A LOT, AND LEVINE, KELLY
AND I RUN INTO GOLDIE FROM TIME TO TIME.
STICK, BROWN, SULKOV, McGUIRE
J.T., BEARDSLEY...
IS THAT ALL?
YOU KNOW, AFTER HIGH SCHOOL
YOU JUST KIND OF LOSE TOUCH.
OH, YEAH, I RAN INTO RICHARD DORFMAN.
OH, HOW IS HE?
NOT SO GOOD. ME AND SIMENS
GAVE HIM A WEDGIE.
ISN'T HE AN ARCHITECT NOW?
YEAH. THEY STILL WEAR UNDERWEAR.
OH, MY GOD!
WHAT?!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH.
WHAT HAPPENED?
OH, MAN! HE PROMISED HE WOULDN'T TAKE THE CHAIRS.
WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED?
HOW WERE YOU LOCKED IN THERE?
WHERE THE HELL'S ALL OF OUR STUFF?
WELL, THIS GUY CAME BY TO LOOK AT THE UNIT
AND HE DIDN'T THINK IT WAS BIG ENOUGH TO FIT A GROWN MAN.
SO YOU GOT IN VOLUNTARILY?
I WAS TRYING TO MAKE A SALE.
IF I RUN INTO THAT GUY AGAIN, YOU KNOW
WHAT I'M GOING TO DO?
BEND OVER?!
AND THEN ZANA JUST LET ONE RIP!
NOT THAT I DON'T ENJOY TALKING ABOUT PEOPLE
WE WENT TO HIGH SCHOOL WITH, BECAUSE I DO
BUT MAYBE WE COULD TALK ABOUT SOMETHING ELSE.
LIKE YOU.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHERE YOU WORK.
YOU KNOW WHERE I WORK.
I DO?
THE MOVIE THEATER.
YOU USED TO COME IN
ALL THE TIME.
YOU STILL WORK AT THE MULTIPLEX?
LIKE I'D GIVE UP THAT JOB.
FREE POPCORN AND CANDY ANYTIME I WANT?
I CAN GET YOU FREE POSTERS FOR YOUR ROOM.
THANKS. I'M SET.
YOU KNOW WHO CAME IN THE OTHER NIGHT? PETERS.
HE JUST WENT OUT WITH LESLIE MASKIN.
GOT TO THIRD BASE!
DO YOU STILL LIVE WITH YOUR PARENTS?
YEAH, BUT I CAN STAY OUT
AS LATE AS I WANT.
YOU KNOW...
WITH ALL OUR STUFF GONE
THE UNIT DOESN'T SEEM THAT BIG.
WHY COULDN'T HE HAVE BEEN A KIDNAPPER?
WOW. THEY REALLY GOT YOU GUYS--
YOUR TV, THE CHAIRS.
YEAH, YOUR MICROWAVE, THE STEREO...
OH, MAN, HE TOOK THE FIVE OF SPADES!
OH, NO, NO. HERE IT IS.
OH, MY GOD. WHAT HAPPENED?
OH, UM, JOEY WAS BORN
AND THEN, 28 YEARS LATER, I WAS ROBBED.
SO HOW WAS YOUR DATE?
WELL, YOU KNOW HOW I ALWAYS WANTED TO GO OUT
WITH CHIP MATTHEWS IN HIGH SCHOOL?
WELL, TONIGHT, I ACTUALLY WENT OUT WITH CHIP MATTHEWS
IN HIGH SCHOOL.
OH, HONEY, I'M SORRY.
NO, IT'S OKAY.
NOT ONLY DID I GET TO GO OUT WITH CHIP MATTHEWS
I GOT TO DUMP CHIP MATTHEWS.
OH, THAT'S SO GREAT.
I KNOW.
HI.
SO, UH, WHAT DID THE INSURANCE COMPANY SAY?
OH, THEY SAID, "YOU DON'T HAVE INSURANCE HERE
SO STOP CALLING US."
YOU DIDN'T TELL HER?
OKAY, FINE.
PHEEBS.
YEAH, HI. HI.
LISTEN, UH...
THIS CAT BELONGS TO A LITTLE GIRL.
ALL RIGHT?
THERE ARE FLYERS ALL OVER THE PLACE.
I'M SORRY, SWEETIE.
HEY, WE CAN TAKE HER BACK
WITH YOU IF YOU WANT.
OH. HM MMM.
BUT YOU KNOW, SHE CHOSE TO FIND ME.
I MEAN, I HAVE TO RESPECT HER DECISION, RIGHT?
IT'S A GOOD CALL. RIGHT.
NO, NO! HEY! ENOUGH IS ENOUGH!
LOOK, I AM SORRY THAT YOU FEEL GUILTY
OR WHATEVER ABOUT SPENDING TIME WITH YOUR NEW MOM
BUT THIS IS NOT YOUR OLD MOM.
THIS IS A CAT, OKAY?
JULIO THE CAT.
NOT MOM. CAT.
OKAY.
ROSS, HOW MANY PARENTS HAVE YOU LOST?
NONE.
THEN YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT IT FEELS LIKE
WHEN ONE OF THEM COMES BACK
DO YOU?
I BELIEVE THIS IS MY MOTHER.
EVEN IF I'M WRONG, WHO CARES?
JUST BE A FRIEND, OKAY?
BE SUPPORTIVE.
I'M SORRY.
OKAY.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
YOU COULD SAY YOU'RE SORRY TO HER MOM.
I THINK SHE WOULD LIKE THAT.
COME HERE, HERE, COME HERE, COME HERE.
MRS. BUFFAY?
SORRY ABOUT WHAT I SAID.
UM, IT WAS-- IT WAS INSENSITIVE OF ME
TO SAY THAT YOU WERE JUST A CAT...
WHEN, CLEARLY, YOU ARE ALSO THE REINCARNATED SPIRIT...
OF MY FRIEND'S MOTHER.
THANK YOU.
WE BOTH FORGIVE YOU.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO ABOUT THE LITTLE GIRL?
YEAH. OKAY, LISTEN...
UM, MOM, I HOPE YOU KNOW
THAT YOU STILL MEAN A LOT TO ME
AND YOU'RE WELCOME TO COME BACK ANYTIME.
PHEEBS, IF SHE COULD COME BACK AS A COUCH
WE'D REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
COME ON, MOM.
I'M GOING TO TAKE YOU HOME.
I'LL GO WITH YOU. ME, TOO.
OH, YOU KNOW, I GOT AN EXTRA FUTON.
DUDE, YOU DON'T HAVE TO BRAG.
WE GOT NOTHING HERE.
YOU KNOW...
IT'S PEACEFUL OUT HERE.