I CAN'T BELIEVE
MY LITTLE BROTHER IS MARRIED.
I KNOW.
YOU GUYS, WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME
YOU WERE ELOPING?
WE WERE AT THE COURTHOUSE.
WE WERE HAVING LUNCH...
WAIT. WHY WERE YOU AT THE COURTHOUSE?
WE WERE HAVING LUNCH.
YEAH, AND THEN, ALL OF A SUDDEN, WE WERE, LIKE
"HEY, YOU KNOW, WE'RE HERE.
"WE'RE HAVING LUNCH.
LET'S GET MARRIED!" RIGHT?
WOW. A YEAR AND A HALF AGO
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW I HAD A BROTHER.
NOW I HAVE A SISTER, TOO.
OH, IT'S SO GREAT. OH...
OKAY.
STOP IT. DON'T.
OH.
SO, OOH, I'M GOING TO GET YOU A GIFT NOW.
IS THERE ANYTHING YOU NEED?
UH... YEAH.
WE'VE BEEN TRYING TO GET PREGNANT
UH, PRETTY MUCH EVER SINCE
WE GOT ENGAGED.
THOUGHT WE'D GET A JUMP ON THINGS.
YOU KNOW, NO ONE'S GETTING ANY YOUNGER.
BECAUSE THE THING IS
UM, WE'RE NOT ABLE TO, YOU KNOW
UH, CONCEIVE, YOU KNOW?
AND WE'VE TRIED EVERYTHING.
WE'VE SEEN A BUNCH OF DOCTORS.
YEAH, AND THEY... THEY SAY THAT...
THAT OUR ONLY CHANCE TO HAVE A BABY
IS IF THEY TAKE MY SPERM
HER EGG, AND PUT IT TOGETHER IN A DISH
AND THEN PUT IT INTO ANOTHER GIRL.
SO WE WERE WONDERING
IF YOU COULD BE THE GIRL THAT WE COULD PUT IT INTO.
THAT'S A REALLY NICE GIFT.
I WAS THINKING OF, LIKE, A GRAVY BOAT.
WE KNOW... WE KNOW IT'S A LOT TO ASK.
WE DON'T HAVE ANYONE ELSE TO GO TO.
WE COULD PAY SOMEONE TO DO IT
BUT WE DON'T HAVE THAT KIND OF MONEY.
PLUS, YOU KNOW , YOU'RE FAMILY.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST DON'T WANT MY BABY TO GROW
INTO SOME CHICK I DON'T KNOW, YOU KNOW?
DON'T GIVE US AN ANSWER YET.
THINK ABOUT IT.
AND, IF YOU SAY NO, WE WILL TOTALLY UNDERSTAND.
OKAY. OKAY.
OH, AND ALSO, WE WERE WONDERING
IF YOU COULD GIVE US A RIDE
DOWN TO THE TRAIN STATION.
WELL, ACTUALLY, WE KIND OF NEED AN ANSWER
TO THAT ONE RIGHT NOW.
HEY! YOU GUYS.
CHECK IT OUT, CHECK IT OUT.
GUESS WHAT JOB I JUST GOT.
I DON'T KNOW, BUT DONALD TRUMP WANTS HIS BLUE BLAZER BLACK.
WHAT?
BLUE BLAZER BACK.
HE HE WANTS IT BACK.
WELL, Y YOU SAID "BLACK."
WHY WOULD HE WANT HIS BLUE BLAZER BLACK?
WELL, YOU YOU KNOW WHAT I MEANT.
NO. YOU MESSED IT UP.
YOU'RE STUPID.
SO, WHAT JOB DID YOU GET, JOE?
OH. UH, TOUR GUIDE AT THE MUSEUM.
YEAH. ROSS GOT IT FOR ME.
DON'T YOU HAVE TO BE A DINOSAUR EXPERT OR SOMETHING?
NO, NOT REALLY.
THEY GIVE YOU ALL THE INFORMATION.
IT'S, UH, IT'S LIKE MEMORIZING A SCRIPT. YEAH.
"AND, ON YOUR LEFT, YOU HAVE TYRANNOSAURUS REX
A CARNIVORE FROM THE JURASSIC PERIOD."
UH, ACTUALLY, JOEY
IT'S THE CRETACEOUS PERIOD.
YEAH, BUT I CAN PRONOUNCE "JURASSIC."
HEY. HEY!
GUESS WHAT.
FRANK JR. AND ALICE GOT MARRIED.
AND THEY'RE HAVING A BABY.
AND, AND, THEY WANT ME TO GROW IT FOR THEM IN MY UTERUS.
OH, MY GOD.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
YEAH.
YOU'RE REALLY THINKING
OF HAVING SEX WITH YOUR BROTHER?
EWW! AND, OH, NO!
IT'S... THEY WANT ME TO BE THE SURROGATE.
IT'S HER EGG AND HIS SPERM, AND I'M I'M JUST THE OVEN.
IT'S TOTALLY THEIR BUN.
OH.
WHAT DID YOU TELL THEM?
WELL, THEY SAID
I HAD TO THINK ABOUT IT FIRST
BUT WHAT IS THERE TO THINK OF?
I'M GOING TO BE GIVING SOMEONE
THE GREATEST GIFT YOU CAN POSSIBLY GIVE.
YOU'RE GOING TO CARRY THEIR CHILD AND GET THEM
A SONY PLAYSTATION?
HONEY, THIS REALLY IS AN INCREDIBLE THING TO DO FOR THEM
BUT THERE ARE THINGS TO THINK ABOUT.
YEAH. I MEAN, YOU'D BE PREGNANT.
I MEAN, PREGNANT.
I KNOW.
PHEEBS, YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT PUTTING YOUR BODY THROUGH AN AWFUL LOT.
I MEAN, MORNING SICKNESS, UH... LABOR
AND IT'S ALL FOR SOMEBODY ELSE.
YEAH. WHAT'S YOUR POINT?
WELL, THE STUFF I JUST MENTIONED.
WOW. I DON'T KNOW IF I COULD EVER DO THAT.
YOU KNOW, I ALWAYS FIGURED THE FIRST TIME I HAD A BABY
IT WOULD BE WITH SOMEONE I LOVE, AND THAT BABY WAS, YOU KNOW...
A KEEPER.
YOU KNOW, YOU GUYS WERE A LOT MORE SUPPORTIVE
WHEN I WANTED TO MAKE DENIM FURNITURE.
PHEEBS, LISTEN, IF YOU DECIDE TO DO THIS
WE'LL BE SUPPORTIVE LIKE CRAZY.
YEAH. YEAH.
JUST THINK IT THROUGH.
TALK TO SOMEBODY WHO'S HAD A BABY.
LIKE YOUR MOM.
MY MOM NEVER GAVE BIRTH.
OH, BUT MY BIRTH MOM DID.
MMM, I LOVE THIS TUSHIE.
CAN I TAKE IT TO WORK WITH ME?
OH, YEAH, SURE. IT'S NOT MINE ANYWAY.
IT CAME WITH THE PANTS.
OH.
I AM SO SJEALOUS.
YOU GUYS ARE REALLY JUST RIGHT STHERE, AREN'T YOU?
YES.
RIGHT WHERE?
THE BEGINNING, WHERE... YOU KNOW, IT'S ALL SEX
AND TALKING AND SEX AND TALKING AND...
YEAH. YOU YOU GOT TO LOVE THE TALKING.
AND THE SEX?
WE HAVEN'T HAD SEX YET.
OKAY, BUT WHAT'S
THE BIG DEAL, YOU KNOW?
THIS IS SPECIAL, AND I WANT OUR LOVE TO GROW
BEFORE WE MOVE ON TO THE NEXT LEVEL.
OH, CHANDLER, THAT IS SO NICE.
THAT IS REALLY NICE...
LYING.
NO WAY IS THAT THE REASON.
WHY?
JUST BECAUSE YOU'RE NOT MATURE ENOUGH TO UNDERSTAND?
NO, HE'S RIGHT.
I'M TOTALLY LYING.
THEN WHAT IS IT?
WELL, KATHY'S LAST BOYFRIEND WAS JOEY.
AND YOU'RE AFRAID YOU WON'T BE ABLE TO...
"FILL HIS SHOES."
NO, I'M AFRAID I WON'T BE ABLE TO MAKE LOVE AS WELL AS HIM.
YEAH. I WAS GOING FOR THE METAPHOR.
YES, AND I WAS SAYING THE ACTUAL WORDS.
WELL, BIG DEAL.
SO JOEY'S HAD A LOT OF GIRLFRIENDS.
THAT DOESN'T MEAN HE'S GREAT IN BED.
WE SHARE A WALL.
SO EITHER HE'S GREAT IN BED
OR SHE JUST LIKED TO AGREE WITH HIM A LOT.
LOUDLY AND A LOT.
ALL NIGHT LONG, SHE'D AGREE.
SWEETIE, WITH YOU, IT'S GOING TO BE DIFFERENT.
THE SEX IS GOING TO BE GREAT
BECAUSE YOU YOU GUYS ARE IN LOVE.
YEAH?
YEAH.
JUST GO FOR IT, CHANDLER.
YEAH. YOU SHOULD. YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT. I'LL SLEEP WITH MY GIRLFRIEND
BUT I'M JUST DOING IT FOR YOU GUYS.
OKAY. NOW, THE MASTODON IS FROM THE SEMI LATE JURASSIC PERIOD.
ISN'T THE MASTODON FROM THE PLIOCENE EPOCH?
SHH! THIS IS A MUSEUM.
NO TALKING.
OKAY. RIGHT DOWN HERE, WE HAVE...
A LARGE FOOT.
UH... AND, OVER HERE, WE HAVE ROSS GELLER.
EVERYONE WAVE HI TO ROSS.
ROSS IS ONE OF OUR MOST IMPORTANT SCIENTISTS.
LOOK AT HIM HARD AT WORK.
OKAY. MOVING RIGHT ALONG.
COME ON.
IT'S OPEN. COME IN.
HI. HI.
I'M SORRY I'M LATE.
OH, THAT'S OKAY.
IT GAVE ME TIME TO FINISH, UH, GLAZING MY NIPPLES.
WOW. YOU REALLY GO ALL OUT WHEN YOU'RE EXPECTING COMPANY.
NO, I WAS WORKING ON MY POTTERY.
OH.OH!OH, I DIDN'T KNOW THAT YOU DID...
POT.
WELL, YEAH, UH, MOSTLY NUDES.
IT COMBINES MY TWO PASSIONS: POTTERY AND EROTICA.
OH. OOH! "ERROTERY."
HEY! OKAY.
WELL, THANKS FOR COMING OUT TO SEE ME.
I JUST THOUGHT IT WOULD BE A VERY GOOD IDEA
TO TALK ABOUT THIS BABY STUFF IN PERSON.
OKAY.
I DON'T THINK IT'S A VERY GOOD IDEA.
WHY NOT?
WELL, BECAUSE YOU'D BE GIVING UP A BABY
AND I I REALLY DON'T...
I DON'T KNOW IF THERE'S ANYTHING THAT I COULD SAY
THAT COULD MAKE YOU UNDERSTAND THE PAIN
OF GIVING UP A BABY, SO...
UM...
OH, NO, NO, NO. I UNDERSTAND THE PAIN.
DON'T DON'T HURT THE PUPPY.
NO, NO, NO. THE PUPPY IS YOURS.
OH, I GET A PUPPY?
WELL, YEAH.
I MEAN, BUT FOR ONLY THREE DAYS.
WHY?
WELL, YOU KNOW
I I REALIZE THAT I DON'T HAVE ANY RIGHT
TO START GETTING ALL PARENTY ON YOU AND EVERYTHING NOW
BUT, UM... UH...
PHOEBE, WOULD YOU PLEASE LOOK AT ME
AND NOT THE PUPPY?
IT'S VERY IMPORTANT.
OKAY.
I MEAN, I KNOW WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
I GAVE UP TWO BABIES
AND I ONLY WISH THAT I HAD SOMEONE THERE
WHO HAD GIVEN UP BABIES THAT COULD HAVE TOLD ME
HOW TERRIBLE IT IS TO GIVE UP BABIES.
I REALLY SHOULDN'T HAVE GIVEN YOU THE PUPPY FIRST.
I'M SORRY.
THAT'S OKAY.
WE'RE LISTENING.
I JUST THINK THAT IT WOULD BE SOMETHING
THAT YOU WOULD REGRET EVERY SINGLE DAY
FOR THE REST OF YOUR LIFE.
SO, HOWEVER HARD IT IS
FOR YOU TO GIVE UP THIS PUPPY
IT WOULD BE, LIKE, A MILLION TIMES HARDER
TO GIVE UP A CHILD.
OKAY. FAIR ENOUGH.
THREE DAYS.
OH, IT'S TIME TO TAKE MY ASS OUT OF THE KILN.
OH, UH, WOULD YOU MIND SITTING THERE?
I'M SAVING THIS SEAT FOR MY FRIEND ROSS.
YOU MEAN DR. GELLER?
"DOCTOR"? OH, I DIDN'T KNOW HE HAD A NICKNAME.
OH, HE WON'T SIT HERE.
ONLY THE PEOPLE IN THE WHITE COATS SIT OVER THERE
AND ONLY THE PEOPLE IN THE BLUE BLAZERS SIT OVER HERE.
WELL, UH, H HOW COME?
THAT'S THE WAY IT IS.
THAT'S CRAZY.
MAYBE IT'S CRAZY IN A PERFECT WORLD--
A WORLD WITHOUT LAB COATS AND BLAZERS--
BUT YOU NOT IN A PERFECT WORLD.
YOU IN A MUSEUM NOW.
SEE THAT SCIENTIST WITH THE GLASSES?
HE AND I USED TO PLAY TOGETHER ALL THE TIME
IN GRADE SCHOOL.
HMM, BUT NOW...
PETER!
HEY, PETER!
IT'S ME, RHONDA
FROM P.S. 129!
I SHARED MY PUDDING WITH YOU, MAN.
I GAVE YOU MY SNACK PACK!
SEE? HE PRETEND HE DON'T EVEN HEAR ME!
I I THINK EVERYBODY'S PRETENDING
THEY DON'T HEAR YOU.
ANYWAY, LOOK.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU AND YOUR JACKETS
AND YOUR SEPARATE TABLES
BUT ROSS IS ONE OF MY BEST FRIENDS
AND IF I SAVE HIM A SEAT
I'M TELLING YOU, HE WILL SIT IN IT.
ROSS, ROSS, OVER HERE, MAN.
I SAVED YOU A SEAT.
THAT'S OKAY.
I'M COOL OVER HERE.
I'LL CATCH UP WITH YOU LATER, JOEY.
OOP! THIS IS SAVED.
GIFT SHOP.
HEY, UH...
I'M REALLY, REALLY SORRY
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED IN THE CAFETERIA TODAY.
IT'S NO BIG DEAL, YOU KNOW.
YOU YOU DO WHAT YOU GOT TO DO, RIGHT?
IT'S NOT JUST ME.
I MEAN, THE SCIENTISTS AND THE TOUR GUIDES
NEVER SIT TOGETHER.
WHATEVER.
IT'S LIKE THAT EVERYWHERE, JOEY.
OKAY, MON, BACK ME UP HERE.
WHERE YOU WORK
THE, UH, THE WAITERS EAT WITH THE WAITERS, RIGHT?
AND THE CHEFS EAT WITH THE OTHER CHEFS, RIGHT?
I EAT BY MYSELF IN THE ALLEY
BECAUSE EVERYBODY HATES ME.
OKAY, RACH, WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME
YOU HAD LUNCH WITH THE SHIPPING CLERKS?
OKAY, WELL, I'VE NEVER ACTUALLY EATEN LUNCH
WITH THE SHIPPING CLERKS
BUT IT'S TOTALLY DIFFERENT.
THEY'RE NOT ALLOWED IN THE EXECUTIVE CAFETERIA.
OH, I SEE... I SEE WHAT YOU'RE SAYING.
LOOK, ROSS...
REALLY, IT'S IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
YOU KNOW, YOU WEAR A WHITE COAT.
I WEAR A BLUE BLAZER.
IF THAT MEANS WE CAN'T BE FRIENDS AT WORK
THEN SO BE IT, YOU KNOW.
AND I UNDERSTAND, YOU KNOW?
WHEN I'M IN A PLAY
AND YOU'RE IN THE AUDIENCE
I DON'T TALK TO YOU, RIGHT?
SO, IT'S... YOU KNOW, IT'S, UH, IT'S IT'S COOL.
I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW.
YEAH. WHEN WE'RE IN THE AUDIENCE
HE DOESN'T TALK TO US, BUT HE DOES WAVE.
WHO'S MY PUPPY? WHO'S MY PUPPY?
WHO'S MY PUPPY?
HAVE YOU NAMED HIM YET?
NO. I DON'T WANT TO GET ATTACHED.
CAN I HOLD HIM?
SURE. HERE.
COME HERE, SQUIRMY. HELLO.
NOT LIKE THAT! NO!
HI.
WHY'S PHOEBE SINGING TO KARL MALDEN?
OOH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK IT'S TIME
FOR PUPPY TO GO OUT AGAIN.
COME ON. LET'S GO TO THE BALCONY.
WHAT?
UH... THE STREET.
COME ON. LET'S GO TO THE STREET.
OH, LISTEN, DON'T GO ON THE BALCONY
UNTIL AFTER I GET BACK.
SO... DID YOU DO IT?
YES, YES, WE HAD THE SEX.
UH OH. IT WAS BAD?
IT WAS FINE, YOU KNOW, BUT SHE DIDN'T AGREE WITH ME
AS STRONGLY AS SHE AGREED WITH JOEY.
SHE WAS MORE, LIKE, UH
"OH, I SEE YOUR POINT.
I'M ALL RIGHT WITH IT."
WELL, I MEAN, IT WAS THE FIRST TIME.
YOU KNOW, THERE'S NOT ALWAYS
A LOT OF AGREEMENT THE FIRST TIME.
YEAH. NOT FOR GIRLS, ANYWAY.
GUYS AGREE... LIKE THAT.
LOOK, YOU HAVE TO HELP ME, OKAY?
I MEAN, I KNOW WHAT TO DO WITH A WOMAN.
YOU KNOW, I KNOW WHERE EVERYTHING GOES.
IT'S ALWAYS... NICE, BUT I NEED TO KNOW
WHAT MAKES IT GO FROM NICE
TO "MY GOD, SOMEBODY'S KILLING HER IN THERE!"
ALL RIGHT. I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU SOMETHING
A LOT OF GUYS DON'T KNOW.
RACH, HAND ME THAT PAD, PLEASE.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW...
WELL, YOU DON'T HAVE TO DRAW
AN ACTUAL WO... WHOA, SHE'S HOT.
NOW, EVERYBODY KNOWS THE BASIC EROGENOUS ZONES.
YOU GOT ONE, TWO, THREE...
FOUR...
FIVE...
SIX AND SEVEN.
THERE ARE SEVEN?
LET ME SEE THAT.
OH, YEAH.
THAT'S ONE?
KIND OF AN IMPORTANT ONE.
OH, YOU KNOW...
YOU KNOW WHAT? I WAS LOOKING AT IT UPSIDE DOWN.
WELL, YOU KNOW, SOMETIMES THAT HELPS.
OKAY. NOW, MOST GUYS WILL HIT, UH, ONE, TWO, THREE
AND THEN GO TO SEVEN AND SET UP CAMP.
TH THAT'S BAD?
WELL, IF YOU GO TO DISNEYLAND
YOU DON'T SPEND THE WHOLE DAY ON THE MATTERHORN.
WELL, YOU MIGHT, IF IT WERE ANYTHING LIKE SEVEN.
ALL RIGHT.
UH, THE IMPORTANT THING
IS TO TAKE YOUR TIME.
YOU WANT TO HIT THEM ALL
AND YOU WANT TO MIX THEM UP.
YOU GOT TO KEEP THEM ON THEIR TOES.
OH, TOES!
YEAH...
FOR SOME PEOPLE.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU COULD, UH
START OUT WITH A A LITTLE ONE...
A TWO...
A ONE, TWO, THREE...
A THREE...
A FIVE...
A FOUR...
A THREE, TWO...
TWO...
A TWO, FOUR, SIX...
TWO, FOUR, SIX...
FOUR...
TWO...
FOUR, SEVEN...
FIVE, SEVEN...
SIX, SEVEN...
SEVEN...
SEVEN, SEVEN, SEVEN...
SEVEN!
SEVEN.
AND THERE YOU ARE.
YEAH, THAT WILL WORK.
DR. GELLER, THERE'S A SEAT OVER HERE.
THANK YOU, DR. PHILLIPS...
BUT I'M HAVING MY LUNCH
AT THIS TABLE, HERE IN THE MIDDLE.
I'M HAVING MY LUNCH
RIGHT HERE WITH MY GOOD FRIEND JOEY...
IF HE'LL SIT WITH ME.
I WILL SIT WITH YOU, DR. GELLER.
YOU KNOW, WE WORK IN A MUSEUM OF NATURAL HISTORY
AND YET, THERE IS SOMETHING... UNNATURAL
ABOUT THE WAY WE EAT LUNCH.
I WANT YOU TO KNOW
IT TOOK A TOUR GUIDE
TO SHOW THIS SCIENTIST THE ERROR OF HIS WAYS.
YOU MIGHT EVEN SAY HE TOOK ME ON A TOUR OF MYSELF.
YEAH, THAT WAS... THAT WAS ME.
NOW...
I LOOK AROUND THIS CAFETERIA, AND YOU KNOW WHAT I SEE?
I SEE I SEE DIVISION--
DIVISION BETWEEN PEOPLE IN WHITE COATS
AND PEOPLE IN BLUE BLAZERS
AND I ASK MYSELF, "MY GOD, WHY?!"
NOW, I SAY WE SHED THESE THESE COATS
THAT SEPARATE US
AND WE GET TO KNOW THE PEOPLE UNDERNEATH.
I'M ROSS.
I'M DIVORCED, AND I HAVE A KID.
I'M JOEY.
I'M AN ACTOR.
I DON'T KNOW SQUAT ABOUT DINOSAURS.
I'M TED, AND I JUST MOVED HERE A MONTH AGO
AND NEW YORK REALLY SCARES ME.
ALL RIGHT. THERE YOU GO!
YEAH. YOU HANG IN THERE, TEDDY.
I'M ANDREW...
AND I DIDN'T PAY FOR THIS PEAR.
OKAY. GOOD GOOD FOR YOU.
I'M RHONDA...
AND THESE AREN'T REAL!
WOW, RHONDA.
UH...
I'M SCOTT...
YEAH. OKAY, SCOTT!
AND I NEED TO FLIP THE LIGHT SWITCH
ON AND OFF 17 TIMES BEFORE I LEAVE A ROOM
OR MY FAMILY WILL DIE.
MY MOM'S GOING TO BE HERE ANY MINUTE.
I CAN'T DO THIS.
I CAN'T GIVE HIM UP.
YES. NO, I CAN.
I DON'T WANT TO...
BUT I CAN.
NO.
OH, I CAN'T WATCH THIS.
IT'S LIKE SOPHIE'S CHOICE.
YOU KNOW, I NEVER SAW THAT.
OH, IT WAS ONLY OKAY.
I CAN'T DO THIS.
MY MOM WAS RIGHT.
IF I CAN'T... IF I CAN'T GIVE HIM UP
THEN... THERE'S NO WAY I CAN GIVE UP A LITTLE BABY.
OH, GOD, FRANK AND ALICE ARE GOING TO BE SO CRUSHED.
WH WHAT ELSE, WHAT ELSE CAN I GIVE THEM?
A KIDNEY.
HI.
UM, WE WERE JUST IN THE NEIGHBORHOOD, SO...
SO WE JUST THOUGHT WE'D STOP BY
AND LET YOU KNOW THERE'S STILL NO PRESSURE.
NONE, BUT IF THERE WAS
SOMETHING YOU WANTED TO TELL US
WE'RE JUST GOING TO BE RIGHT OVER THERE HAVING COFFEE.
OKAY.
OH, WHO'S THIS LITTLE GUY?
OH. OH!
UM...
OH, HE'S SO CUTE.
HE REMINDS ME OF MY OLD DOG, TUMOR.
OH, OH.
YOU ARE SO PRECIOUS. I COULD JUST TAKE YOU HOME.
HEY, WHY DON'T YOU?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
UH HUH. YEAH.
OH...
OH, THANKS.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
NO. I'M REALLY OKAY WITH THIS.
YOU KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE LOOK AT THEM.
LOOK HOW HAPPY THEY ARE...
AND I MADE THAT, SO, YOU KNOW... I KNOW IT'S GOING TO BE, LIKE
A MILLION TIMES HARDER TO GIVE UP A BABY
BUT, OH, MY GOD
IT'S GOING TO FEEL, LIKE, A MILLION TIMES BETTER, RIGHT?
I WANT TO DO THIS.
I WANT TO CARRY YOUR BABY.
OH...
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT THIS MEANS TO US.
OH...
OH, MY GOD, I THINK I'M GOING TO CRY.
OH, MY GOD.
IT'S GOING TO BE SO GREAT.
UH HUH.
HI.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
OH! I I GAVE THEM THE PUPPY
AND IT MADE THEM SO HAPPY THAT I DECIDED I'M GOING
TO CARRY THEIR BABY.
UH, PHOEBE...
NO, NO, I KNOW.
YOU AND I ARE TOTALLY DIFFERENT PEOPLE, THOUGH
AND THIS IS A TOTALLY DIFFERENT SITUATION
AND I KNOW THAT I AM NOT GOING TO REGRET THIS.
OH, I I UNDERSTAND ALL THAT.
IT'S JUST... THAT WAS MY PUPPY.
OH...
WOULD YOU EVER BE A SURROGATE FOR ANYONE?
IT DEPENDS WHO ASKED.
WHAT IF I ASKED?
OH, MON...
SURE.
REALLY?
YES.
YOU'RE NOT ASKING ME, ARE YOU?
NO.
YES, TOTALLY.
THANK YOU.
YES! THANK YOU!