ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
JOEY. JOEY.
JOEY. JOEY, JOEY, JOEY, JOEY, JOEY...
JOEY... JOEY... JOEY.
JOEY. JOEY!
ALL RIGHT!
OH, OH, DID DID... DID I WAKE YOU?
GUNTHER, COULD I GET
ANOTHER CUP OF COFFEE, PLEASE?
SO, UH, WHAT DO YOU DO WHEN YOU' RE NOT WORKING HERE?
YOU DON'T NEED
TO FILL THESE SILENCES.
OH, OKAY, THANKS.
CHANDLER, THAT'S, LIKE
YOUR FOURTH CUP OF COFFEE.
OKAY, DO ME.
I'VE HAD A CERTAIN NUMBER OF JUICES.
WELL, I AM DRINKING LOTS OF CUPS OF COFFEE BECAUSE I AM EXHAUSTED
BECAUSE JOEY STARTED SNORING.
HE'S IN A DIFFERENT ROOM.
HE'S REALLY THAT LOUD?
OH, YOU SHOULD HEAR ME.
IT'S NOT SOMETHING TO BE PROUD OF, OKAY?
YOU HAVE TO GO TO A SLEEP CLINIC.
LOOK, I TOLD YOU I'M NOT GOING TO ANY CLINIC.
I DON'T HAVE A PROBLEM.
YOU'RE THE ONE WITH THE PROBLEM.
YOU SHOULD GO
TO A QUIT BEING A BABY- AND LEAVE ME ALONE CLINIC.
THEY DON'T HAVE THOSE.
YEAH, THEY DO.
QUIT BEING A BABY AND LEAVE ME ALONE.
THERE, YOU JUST HAD
YOUR FIRST CLASS.
YOU KNOW, I USED TO  GO OUT WITH THIS GUY
THAT WAS A REALLY LIGHT SLEEPER
AND WHENEVER I'D START TO SNORE
HE'D JUST ROLL ME OVER...
OH, YEAH...
HE WOULD JUST ROLL ME OVER
AND I WOULD STOP SNORING.
NEXT TIME YOU SNORE, I'M ROLLING YOU OVER.
I GOT TO DO WHAT I GOT TO DO.
YOU GOT TO DO WHAT YOU GOT TO DO.
HEY, GUYS.
HEY. HEY.
OH, THE OLYMPICS.
HAVE YOU GUYS PICKED A DATE YET?
HUH? OH, NO, NOT YET.
I STILL CANNOT BELIEVE YOU'RE ENGAGED.
JUST BECAUSE
IT'S HAPPENING SO FAST, NOT BECAUSE YOU'RE SUCH A LOSER.
THANKS. UH, HAS ANYONE SEEN RACH?
OH, SHE'S UPSTAIRS NOT DOING THE DISHES.
AND I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING.
YOU KNOW, I'M NOT DOING THEM THIS TIME.
I DON'T CARE IF THOSE DISHES JUST SIT IN THE SINK
UNTIL THEY'RE  ALL COVERED WITH...
I'LL DO THEM WHEN I GET HOME.
YEAH. OH, HEY, LISTEN
EMILY FOUND THIS WEDDING DRESS IN LONDON...
ALREADY?
YEAH, BUT IT DIDN'T FIT.
WELL, LUCKILY, THERE'S A STORE HERE HAS ONE LEFT IN HER SIZE
BUT I'M THE GROOM-- I'M NOT SUPPOSED TO SEE THE DRESS...
I'LL PICK IT UP FOR YOU.
THANK YOU. OKAY.
WHOA, SHE'S GOT YOU RUNNING ERRANDS
YOU KNOW, PICKING UP WEDDING DRESSES...
WAH PAH!
WHAT'S "WAH PAH"?
YOU KNOW-- WHIPPED.
WAH PAH!
THAT'S NOT "WHIPPED."
"WHIPPED" IS...
WA TSSH!
THAT'S WHAT I DID.
WAH PAH!
YOU CAN'T DO ANYTHING!
HEY, MON...
I WAS JUST DOING THESE DISHES...
HEY. OH.
HI. OH. IT'S YOU.
HEY, DO YOU, UH, YOU HAVE A MINUTE?
YEAH, YEAH. I WAS JUST ABOUT TO TAKE A BREAK ANYWAY SO...
WHEW!
SO, LISTEN, UH... I KNOW YOU AND I
HAVEN'T REALLY HAD A CHANCE TO TALK
SINCE, UH... EMILY AND I DECIDED TO GET MARRIED
AND I WAS JUST WONDERING HOW YOU WERE.
OH.
I MEAN, I KNOW IF YOU WERE GETTING MARRIED
UH, I MEAN, I WOULD FEEL, UM, KIND OF...
YOU KNOW? UH...
YEAH, YEAH. IT DEF...
IT DEFINITELY, UH, TOOK ME BY SURPRISE
BUT, YOU KNOW, UH... I'M OKAY.
YEAH?
YEAH, YOU KNOW. I'M OKAY.
ALL RIGHT. I JUST WANTED TO CHECK.
OH, THAT'S SWEET. THANK YOU.
YOU'RE GREAT.
AND I I KNOW SOMEDAY THIS WILL HAPPEN
FOR YOU, TOO.
YOU JUST HANG IN THERE.
UH...
"HANG IN THERE"?
OH, NO, I I DIDN'T MEAN, UH...
I MEAN, MAYBE YOU HAVE NOT HEARD OF A LITTLE
SERIOUS RELATIONSHIP CALLED "ME AND JOSHUA"?
OH. UH, I THOUGHT YOU GUYS
HAD JUST BEEN ON, LIKE, FOUR DATES.
I DIDN'T REALIZE THAT HAD...
BECOME ANYTHING.
OH, YEAH. NO, OH, NO; OH, NO, THAT HAS BECOME.
OH. IT HAS. YEAH.
OH, NO, THOSE WERE FOUR GREAT DATES.
OH. YEAH?
OH, YEAH. OH, I MEAN, AND THE CONNECTION?
I MEAN, YOU KNOW...
EMOTIONALLY, MENTALLY, YOU KNOW?
PHYSICALLY.
WOW, THAT'S THAT'S THAT'S INCREDIBLE.
I KNOW. ISN'T IT?
IT'S LIKE I'M RIGHT THERE WITH JOSHUA;
YOU ARE RIGHT THERE WITH EMILY;
AND IT'S, YOU KNOW, IT'S KIND OF LIKE...
IT'S A TIE.
YEAH, WELL , I GOT TO GET...
I GOT TO GET BACK TO MY DISHES.
OH, I GOT TO GET TO WORK.
OH, YEAH. OKAY.
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT WOULD MAKE ME REALLY HAPPY?
OH, YOU KNOW, WHAT'S THAT?
IF, LIKE, THE FOUR OF US
COULD ALL, YOU KNOW, HANG OUT TOGETHER.
IN FACT, EMILY'S COMING INTO TOWN THIS WEEKEND.
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE ALL HAVE DINNER, SAY, SUNDAY NIGHT?
THAT WOULD BE GREAT!
YEAH?
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT. IT'S A DATE.
YEAH.
"HANG IN THERE."
YOU HANG IN THERE.
YOU SAY SOMETHING?
NO, I WAS JUST SINGING.
?
?? LA LA LA, LA LA LA LA... ?
OH, MY GOD.
OH, LOOK AT THIS ONE.
WOW.
OH, IT'S SO BEAUTIFUL.
YEAH, OOH...
WELL, YOU KNOW, ABOUT HALF OF THESE
ARE GOING TO END UP GETTING DIVORCED.
MAY I HELP YOU, LADIES?
YES, I'M HERE TO PICK UP A DRESS
THAT YOU HAVE ON HOLD.
YES, WHAT'S THE NAME, PLEASE?
EMILY WALTHAM.
OH, YES, I HAVE IT RIGHT HERE.
OH, MY...
WOULD YOU LIKE TO TRY IT ON, MISS WALTHAM?
OKAY.
YOU'RE THE MOST BEAUTIFUL BRIDE I'VE EVER SEEN.
I AM, AREN'T I?
YEAH.
MISS WALTHAM.
YES?
WE'RE CLOSING.
ALL RIGHT.
AND COULD I GET MY RING BACK?
ALL RIGHT, BUDDY.
TIME TO ROLL OVER.
NO, NO! NO, NO, NO, NO, NO!
YOU ARE GOING TO A CLINIC.
YOU'RE GOING TO A CLINIC...
AND A PAJAMA STORE.
DOES SHE USE THE CUPS?
YES, I BELIEVE SHE DOES.
DOES SHE USE THE PLATES?
THANK YOU.
AW... THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
OH, WELL, THANK YOU FOR COMING.
UH, JUST A SECOND!
NO, NO, LET ME IN.
PHOEBE?
YEAH.
CAN YOU HOLD ON JUST ONE MINUTE?
NO, YOU HAVE TO LET ME IN RIGHT NOW!
ARE YOU ALONE?
YES.
ALL RIGHT.
THIS SUCKS.
I DIDN'T KNOW I HAD TO STAY UP ALL NIGHT
BEFORE I GO TO THIS STUPID SLEEP CLINIC.
I'M SO TIRED.
IT'S 6:00.
HI.
HEY, I HEAR THAT YOU AND JOSHUA
ARE GOING OUT TO DINNER WITH ROSS AND EMILY
AND I THINK THAT'S-- I THINK THAT'S REALLY COOL.
YEAH, RACHEL, I THINK YOU'RE HANDLING THAT
REALLY WELL.
WHAT DO YOU ME AN, "HANDLING" IT?
THERE'S NOTHING TO HANDLE.
YOU KNOW, MAYBE I WOULD HAVE A PROBLEM WITH THIS
IF IT WASN'T FOR ME AND JOSHUA.
YOU KNOW, THEY'RE NOT GOING TO GET MARRIED ANYWAY.
WHAT?
COME ON. THEY RUSHED INTO THIS THING SO FAST
IT'S RIDICULOUS.
I MEAN, THEY'RE GOING TO BE ENGAGED FOR, LIKE, WHAT, A YEAR?
AND SOMEWHERE ALONG THE WAY
ONE OF THEM IS GOING TO REALIZE WHAT THEY'VE DONE
AND THEY'RE GOING TO CALL THE WHOLE THING OFF.
I'M TELLING YOU, YOU'RE GOING TO BE DANCING AT MY WEDDING
BEFORE YOU'RE DANCING AT THEIRS.
YEAH, WELL, I DON'T DANCE AT WEDDINGS.
WHY NOT?
BECAUSE WEDDINGS ARE A GREAT PLACE TO MEET WOMEN
AND WHEN I DANCE, I LOOK LIKE THIS:
HEY, MAN.
HEY.
SO, WHAT'RE YOU GUYS DOING FOUR WEEKS FROM TODAY?
NOTHING.
I AM...
FREE.
GREAT, BECAUSE EMILY AND I ARE GETTING MARRIED IN A MONTH.
WHAT? WHAT?
YEP.
IN A MONTH? YEAH.
YOU MEAN, 30 DAYS?
YEAH.
FROM NOW.
OH, THAT'S GREAT! YEAH.
YEAH, EMILY ALWAYS WANTED
TO GET MARRIED IN THIS BEAUTIFUL PLACE
THAT HER PARENTS GOT MARRIED
BUT IT'S GOING TO BE TORN DOWN, SO...
I MEAN, I I KNOW IT'S CRAZY
BUT EVERYTHING UP TILL NOW HAS BEEN SO CRAZY
AND, I DON'T KNOW-- IT JUST FEELS RIGHT, YOU KNOW?
HEY...
THAT'S THE DAY AFTER I START MENSTRUATING.
THIS ISN'T MINE.
HEY, RACHEL.
HI.
WHAT'S UP?
OH...
YOUR VOICE SOUNDED ALL SQUEAKY ON THE PHONE.
OH... NOTHING.
I JUST WANTED TO SEE YOU.
SEE YOU AND HUG YOU.
S SEE YOU...
GREAT.
YEAH, SO...
SIT.
YOU OKAY?
I'M MORE THAN OKAY.
I AM REALLY, REALLY HAPPY.
WANT TO KNOW WHY?
DO I?
BECAUSE I AM REALLY HAPPY ABOUT US.
I THINK WE ARE...
I THINK WE ARE SO ON THE RIGHT TRACK.
YOU KNOW? I MEAN
I THINK WE ARE WORKING.
I THINK WE ARE CLICKING.
YOU KNOW?
YEAH, SURE, SURE.
YEAH, WE'RE WE'RE- WE'RE CLICKING.
YEAH, YEAH, YOU KNOW
IF IF THERE WAS JUST, LIKE, ONE LITTLE AREA WHERE...
THAT I THINK WE WE WOULD NEED TO WORK ON...
I I WOULD THINK IT WAS THAT WE'RE JUST NOT CRAZY ENOUGH.
I I GOT TO SAY I'M NOT TOO SURE I AGREE WITH THAT.
WELL, YEAH, RIGHT, YOU KNOW, YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I MEAN, WE... YOU KNOW, WE HAVE OUR FUN, YEAH...
BUT, IT'S... WE'RE JU...
I MEAN, I MEAN, I MEAN, LIKE, CRAZY, YOU KNOW?
ARE YOU GOING TO PUT ON THAT CHEERLEADER OUTFIT AGAIN?
OH, NO, NO...
YEAH, YOU WISH.
NO.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
THIS IS GOING TO... THIS IS GOING TO SOUND, YOU KNOW
A LITTLE, UM... HASTY, BUT, UH, JUST GO WITH ME.
WHAT IF WE GOT MARRIED?
WHAT?
OH, I KNOW, I KNOW. IT'S SO...
IT'S SO TOTALLY, LIKE
WHOA, CAN WE DO THIS?
YOU KNOW, I MEAN... BUT I MEAN, IT JUST FEELS RIGHT.
DON'T YOU THINK? IT DOES.
I MEAN, IT JUST FEELS RIGHT, DON'T...
WOW, UH...
RACHEL, UM, YOU'RE...
A REAL... SPECIAL LADY...
BUT...
MY DIVORCE ISN'T FINAL YET
AN AN AND WE'VE BEEN ON FOUR DATES.
SO...
I'M THINKING...
NO...
BUT...
THANKS.
YOU IDIOT!
YOUR NAME, PLEASE?
JOEY TRIBBIANI.
MM HMM. DID YOU STAY UP ALL NIGHT IN PREPARATION
FOR YOUR SLEEP STUDY?
UH, SIR?
YES, HE DID.
ALL RIGHT, WE'LL CALL YOU IN A FEW MINUTES.
OKAY.
WHOO.
CHECK OUT THAT GIRL.
SHE'S REALLY HOT.
YEAH, SHE IS.
WOW.
HOW YOU DOING?
YOU'RE LOOKING GOOD.
WHAT?!
YOU'RE COMING ON TO THE ENTIRE ROOM.
I'M CHANDLER.
MARJORIE. HI.
DO YOU MIND IF I SIT? NO. PLEASE.
SO, UH, WHAT ARE YOU IN FOR?
I I TALK IN MY SLEEP.
WHAT A COINCIDENCE ; I LISTEN IN MY SLEEP.
SO WHY DON'T YOU GIVE ME YOUR NUMBER?
YOU READY? YEAH.
OKAY.
I GOT IT! MINE!
CONGRATULATIONS!
OKAY...
MY TURN! MY TURN!
OKAY.
OKAY, READY?
YEAH.
OKAY.
THAT WAS A TERRIBLE THROW!
WELL, I'M NOT GOING TO THROW IT RIGHT TO YOU.
THAT'S NOT REAL.
LOOK AT ME.
MY BIG CONCERN IS WHAT'S REAL?
OH, MY GOD.
WE'RE REALLY SAD, AREN'T WE?
YEAH, I THINK WE ARE.
THIS ISN'T EVEN MY DRESS.
YEAH, WELL, AT LEAST YOU DIDN'T RENT YOURS
FROM A STORE CALLED "IT'S NOT TOO LATE."
I'M CHANGING OUT OF THIS.
ME, TOO.
IN, LIKE, A HALF AN HOUR?
OKAY. ALL RIGHT, NOW
THROW IT STRAIGHT THIS TIME.
OKAY. OKAY.
I'M GETTING MARRIED NEXT!
YAY!
I HATE MY REGULAR CLOTHES NOW, YOU KNOW?
IT'S LIKE I LOOK DOWN AND AND I KNOW
THIS ISN'T GOING TO BE THE MOST SPECIAL DAY
OF MY LIFE.
YEAH, I MEAN, IT WAS KIND OF FUN FOR A WHILE
BUT DIDN'T YOU START FEELING KIND OF SILLY?
I GUESS.
YEAH.
OH, MY GOD!
OH!
YOU'RE SUCH A CHEATER!
HELLO, LITTLE ONES.
HEY... HEY...
SO IS JOEY GOING TO STOP SNORING?
YEP, AND A BEAUTIFUL WOMAN AGREED TO GO OUT WITH ME.
JOEY WANTED TO ASK HER OUT
BUT, UH, YOU KNOW, SHE PICKED ME.
OH, HOW'D THAT HAPPEN?
BECAUSE I'M COOLER.
NO, SERIOUSLY.
WELL, SHE'S, YOU KNOW, SHE'S THE KIND OF GIRL...
JOEY WAS UNCONSCIOUS.
HEY, YOU GUYS, WHAT'S HAPPENING?
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT IS THAT?
OH... THEY GAVE IT TO ME AT THE SLEEP CLINIC
AND IT'S GOING TO HELP ME NOT TO SNORE.
WELL, ARE YOU ASLEEP RIGHT NOW, JOE?
BECAUSE I DON'T THINK YOU HAVE TO WEAR IT UNLESS YOU ARE.
I KNOW I DON'T HAVE TO.
IT TASTES GOOD.
PLUS, YOU LOOK COOL.
I HOPE I DIDN'T STRETCH OUT EMILY'S DRESS TOO MUCH.
NO, YOUR BUTT'S NOT THAT MUCH BIGGER THAN HERS.
WELL, I JUST CALLED JOSHUA.
OH, HOW'D IT GO?
WELL, I DID MY BEST TO CONVINCE HIM
THAT I'M NOT SOME CRAZY GIRL
WHO IS DYING TO GET MARRIED--
THAT I'M JUST GOING THROUGH A HARD TIME.
WHAT'D HE SAY?
WELL, UH, HIS ANSWERING MACHINE
WAS VERY UNDERSTANDING.
I FEEL BLUE.
AW, SWEETIE, OH...
HONEY, I'LL BET YOU ANYTHING
HE'S GOING TO CALL YOU AGAIN.
YEAH, MAYBE, BUT, YOU KNOW, I DON'T THINK I EVEN CARE.
I DON'T THINK... HE'S THE ONE I'M SAD ABOUT.
YOU KNOW, I KNOW THAT I SAID
I AM TOTALLY OKAY WITH ROSS GETTING MARRIED
BUT AS IT TURNS OUT
I DON'T THINK I AM HANDLING IT ALL THAT WELL.
YEAH, MAYBE.
AN AND I'M JUST TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHY.
ANY LUCK?
WELL, YEAH, I MEAN, YOU KNOW, HOW ROSS AND I
HAVE ALWAYS BEEN ON AGAIN, OFF AGAIN
ON AGAIN, OFF AGAIN.
I GUESS I JUST FIGURED THAT SOMEWHERE DOWN THE ROAD...
WE WOULD BE ON AGAIN... AGAIN.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK WE ALL DID.
YEAH.
HEY.
HEY. HEY.
SO, GOT US RESERVATIONS FOR SUNDAY NIGHT, OKAY?
HOW ABOUT ERNIE'S AT 9:00?
YEAH, WELL, YOU, UH, BETTER MAKE IT FOR THREE.
OH, SEE, I I DON'T KNOW
IF WE'RE GOING TO BE HUNGRY AT 3:00.
THREE PEOPLE.
JOSHUA'S NOT GOING TO BE THERE.
WHAT HAPPENED?
UM, WELL, I THINK- - I THINK HE BROKE UP WITH ME.
NO. WHY?
WELL... APPARENTLY, HE SCARES EASY.
OH, RACHEL, I'M SORRY.
WELL... THAT'S OKAY.
SOMETIMES... THINGS DON'T WORK OUT
THE WAY YOU THOUGHT THEY WOULD.
COME HERE.
OH...
WELL, HEY, DON'T YOU HAVE
TO GO PICK UP EMILY?
YEAH.
ARE YOU OKAY?
I GOT MY GIRLS.
OKAY.
UGH.
OH...
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT MIGHT CHEER YOU UP?
WHAT?
YOU KNOW, I GOT TO TELL YOU
THIS REALLY DOES PUT ME IN A BETTER MOOD.
MM HMM.
OH. I WISH THERE WAS A JOB
WHERE I COULD WEAR THIS ALL THE TIME.
MAYBE SOMEDAY THERE WILL BE.
OH, GOD, THAT'S CHANDLER.
HE WAS GOING TO COME BY
AND BORROW SOME CANDLES FOR HIS BIG DATE.
OH, OKAY.
RACHEL, DON'T GET  IT; HE'LL SEE US.
THE GROOM CANNOT SEE THE BRIDE.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO MARRY CHANDLER.
NOT AFTER THIS.
OKAY, GUYS... JUST RELAX.
IDO...
I GOT TO GO.
OH, NO, JOSHUA...
JOSHUA...
OH...
YEAH, WELL, THAT OUGHT TO DO IT.
FOOD'S HERE.
FAIR ENOUGH.
15 MINUTE WARNING!
LATER...
DUDE, I AM TRYING TO SLEEP.