HELLO.
Hey, it's me.
You can't stand to be in the same room as me
so I thought I'd apologize
over the phone. All...
HELLO.
Look, I just want to say
I'm really...
STOP CALLING!
Hey, hey, hey!
This is 92.3 WXRK, K Rock
calling with our $1,000 daily challenge.
ALL RIGHT.
What is the name of your roommate
who is very, very sorry and would do anything...?
DAMN IT, CHANDLER, STOP CALLING!
Joey Joey, it's Ross.
OH. SORRY, MAN.
That's all right.
WHAT'S UP?
Not much.
Uh, I got Chandler here and he's really, really sorry...
UGH... TURKEY.
UGH, GIVING THANKS.
UGH!
LOOK, EVERYONE.
IT'S THE SPIRIT OF THANKSGIVING.
SO, ARE THINGS WITH YOU AND JOEY ANY BETTER?
THEY COULDN'T BE WORSE.
I SPENT EIGHT HOURS CALLING HIM LAST NIGHT
TRYING TO GET HIM TO TALK TO ME.
OH, WOW.
EIGHT HOURS-- SO, YOU COULD PROBABLY REALLY USE
ONE OF THOSE PLUG IN TELEPHONE HEADSETS, HUH?
SHOULD WE ALL EXPECT CHRISTMAS GIFTS
THAT CAN BE STOLEN FROM YOUR OFFICE?
YOU SHOULDN'T.
SPEAKING OF CHRISTMAS
SINCE MONICA AND I ARE STARTING A NEW BUSINESS
AND HAVE, LIKE, NO MONEY
UM, THIS YEAR MAYBE WE COULD DO SECRET SANTA
AND THEN WE EACH ONLY BUY ONE GIFT
AND AND THERE'S THE ADDED MYSTERY
OF, YOU KNOW, WHO GETS WHO.
WHO GETS WHOM.
I DON'T KNOW WHY I DO THAT.
BUT IT IS CORRECT.
HEY, WHAT'S THIS?
IT'S ALL OF YOUR NAMES!
LET'S PICK.
HEY, WHAT'S GOING...
COME ON! NO, JOEY...!
JOEY, COME ON. WE'RE PICKING NAMES FOR SECRET SANTA.
OKAY.
I INVENTED SECRET SANTA, YOU KNOW.
WHAT ARE YOU LAUGHING AT?
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO SAID DIE HARDWAS YOUR IDEA.
IT WAS!
DON'T MAKE ME SHOW YOU THE NAPKIN.
OH, I'M GOING TO TAKE A NAP.
TURKEY MAKES ME SLEEPY.
WE HAVEN'T EATEN YET.
I KNOW, BUT ALL THAT WORK YOU'RE DOING
TO GET IT READY AND I JUST...
HEY, BY ANY CHANCE
DID EITHER OF YOU PICK RACHEL
FOR YOUR SECRET SANTA?
BECAUSE I WANT TO TRADE FOR HER.
I PICKED HER.
OOH, THANK GOD, YOU WANT HER.
OOH!
WOW. WHY DO YOU WANT TO GET RID OF HER SO BADLY?
BECAUSE SHE EXCHANGES EVERY GIFT SHE EVER GETS.
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE TO GET HER SOMETHING SHE LIKES.
COME ON, LET'S TRADE!
OH, THAT'S NOT TRUE.
I GOT HER THAT BACKPACK, AND SHE LOVED IT.
I REMEMBER HOW MUCH SHE WAS CRYING THE DAY
THAT BIG DOG RAN OFF WITH...
WELL, THERE WAS NO BIG DOG.
ALL RIGHT, THIS SUCKS
BECAUSE I ALREADY GOT HER THIS BRIEFCASE, AND I HAD
"R.G." PUT ON IT.
HER INITIALS.
OH. OKAY. I'M REALLY BAD AT INITIALS.
WOW. YOU GOT YOUR SHOPPING DONE EARLY THIS YEAR.
YEAH, WELL, MY CAMEL CASH WAS ABOUT TO EXPIRE, SO...
WELL, MAYBE YOU CAN GIVE IT TO SOMEBODY ELSE.
OH, LIKE ROSS GELLER.
OH, YOU KNOW WHAT, THOUGH?
IT'S KIND OF A GIRLY BRIEFCASE.
WHO CARES? HE WORKS IN A MUSEUM.
HEY, WHAT TIME IS IT?
THE BIG GAME IS ABOUT TO START.
ROSS AND JOEY AREN'T HERE.
YOU CAN WATCH THE PARADE IF YOU WANT.
THANKS.
WHAT IS WRONG WITH THIS FREEZER?
OW! OW!
GOD, WHAT HAPPENED?
OH, MY GOD, ICE JUST GOT
IN MY EYE!
PEOPLE ARE TRYING TO SLEEP IN HERE.
MONICA GOT ICE IN HER EYE, AND IT HURTS.
OPEN IT UP. LET ME SEE.
OH, I CAN'T. IT REALLY KILLS.
WELL, MAYBE YOU SHOULD
PUT SOME ICE ON IT.
OOH, IT LOOKS BAD.
HONEY, MAYBE WE SHOULD TAKE YOU TO A DOCTOR.
NO. MY EYE DOCTOR IS RICHARD.
I CAN'T GO TO HIM WHEN I DON'T HAVE A BOYFRIEND.
HE'S REALLY PICKY ABOUT HIS PATIENTS.
OKAY, YOU'VE GOT TO GO.
WHAT'S HIS OFFICE NUMBER?
LIKE, I REMEMBER HIS OFFICE NUMBER.
SPEED DIAL SEVEN.
HI. YEAH, I'M CALLING ON BEHALF OF MONICA GELLER'S EYE, AND...
IS, UM... IS RICHARD BURKE IN TODAY?
HE'S OUT OF TOWN, BUT DOES SHE WANT TO SEE THE ON CALL DOCTOR?
YES!
YES! SHE'S VERY EXCITED ABOUT THAT.
OKAY. WE'LL BE RIGHT IN.
OKAY, SO, UH, WHO'S GOING TO TAKE HER IN?
I'LL GO. YOU CAN WATCH YOUR PARADE.
THIS IS SO COOL.
TILL MONICA GETS BACK
IT'S, LIKE, I'M HEAD CHEF
AND I GET TO MAKE ALL THE DECISIONS.
HEY, HEY, I THOUGHT SHE TOLD YOU
TO FOLLOW THE RECIPE EXACTLY.
OKAY, GET OUT OF MY KITCHEN.
ALL RIGHT, I THINK I AM MAKING SOME PROGRESS WITH JOEY.
WHEN I WENT INTO THE APARTMENT
HE WENT STRAIGHT INTO HIS BEDROOM
BUT HE ONLY SLAMMED THE DOOR ONCE.
WOW.
I MEAN, YEAH, HE GAVE ME
THE FINGER WHILE DOING IT.
ALL RIGHT, I'VE... I GOT TO CALL MY MOM
AND ASK HER A LEFT HANDED COOKING QUESTION.
I'M GOING TO BE IN THERE.
WHILE I'M GONE...
CHANDLER, YOU'RE IN CHARGE.
SO, LISTEN, UH , I PICKED MONICA
FOR SECRET SANTA, BUT I'M ALREADY
GETTING HER SOMETHING FOR HANUKAH.
I WAS WONDERING IF YOU WANT TO SWITCH.
OH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I WAS TRYING TO TRADE FOR, UH... WELL, YOU.
REALLY?
WOW, THAT'S... THAT'S SO NICE.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO GET ME?
I DON'T KNOW, R.G.
I THOUGHT SOMETHING GIRLY FOR YOUR OFFICE.
YEAH.
WELL, MAYBE PHOEBE WILL SWITCH WITH ME.
YOU DON'T WANT TO DO THAT.
YOU'LL GET STUCK WITH RACHEL.
SHE EXCHANGES EVERY GIFT SHE GETS.
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
I GOT HER LOTS OF STUFF SHE NEVER TOOK BACK.
LIKE?
LIKE THAT GOLD NECKLACE
I GOT HER LAST YEAR.
WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME SHE WORE IT?
WELL, SHE WORE IT ALL CHRISTMAS DAY, AND THEN, UH...
BIG DOG?
HI.
HEY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
SENDING BACK THIS STUFF CHANDLER BOUGHT OUT OF GUILT.
EVERYTHING? EVEN THE TV?
NO. I'M GOING TO PUT THAT IN MY ROOM.
LISTEN, JOEY...
I KNOW WHAT HE DID WAS WRONG
BUT DON'T YOU THINK
YOU COULD AT LEAST HEAR THE GUY OUT?
BACK WHEN YOU AND RACHEL WERE TOGETHER
IF CHANDLER HAD KISSED HER
WOULD YOU HEAR HIM OUT?
GOOD POINT.
SO, UH, HOW LONG ARE YOU GOING TO PUNISH HIM?
FIVE YEARS.
YOU'VE SENTENCED HIM?
HEY, DON'T DO THE CRIME IF YOU CAN'T DO THE TIME.
JOEY, THE GUY IS YOUR BEST FRIEND.
WAS MY BEST FRIEND.
ANYWAY, I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU'RE PUSHING FOR HIM SO HARD.
WITH HIM OUT OF THE WAY AS MY BEST FRIEND
THERE'S A SPOT OPEN.
WELL, WHO, ME?
YEAH.
WOW. I'M HONORED.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'LL DO
AS MY FIRST ACT AS YOUR BEST FRIEND?
WHAT?
I'M GOING TO GET YOU
TO TALK TO CHANDLER.
ALL RIGHT.
OH, BUT IF YOU WEREN'T MY BEST FRIEND...
YEAH...
OH, MY GOD. IS IT REALLY THAT BAD?
I WALK INTO THE ROOM, AND HE WON'T EVEN TALK TO ME.
HE'LL JUST MUMBLE SOMETHING IN ITALIAN...
AND I KNOW HE ONLY KNOWS THE BAD WORDS.
OH, I'M SO, SO SORRY.
I FEEL RESPONSIBLE.
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
HEY, GUNTHER, HAVE YOU, UH...
HAVE YOU SEEN CHANDLER?
I THOUGHT YOU WERE CHANDLER.
BUT, UM, ONE OF YOU IS OVER THERE.
OH.
HEY, JOE.
VA FA A NAPOLI, HUH?!
I'LL BE RIGHT WITH YOU, OKAY?
THANKS FOR COMING IN.
SURE.
OH, MY GOD.
HOW CUTE IS THE ON CALL DOCTOR?
OH, SO CUTE THAT I'M THINKING
ABOUT JAMMING THIS PEN IN MY EYE.
YOU HAVE THE BEST LUCK WITH EYE DOCTORS.
I KNOW.
DR. BURKE WILL SEE YOU NOW.
OH, NO, NOT DR. BURKE.
DR. BURKE'S OUT OF TOWN.
THE ON CALL DOCTOR WILL SEE ME NOW.
DR. RICHARD BURKE IS OUT OF TOWN.
DR. TIMOTHY BURKE, HIS SON, WILL SEE YOU NOW.
READY?
HEY, I'M SORRY.
THAT...
WHERE YOU GOING?
MY FOLKS'.
OH. UH... WHEN YOU, WHEN YOU COMING BACK?
I DON'T KNOW.
I MIGHT STAY THERE FOR A FEW DAYS
WHILE I LOOK FOR AN APARTMENT.
WHAT?
AT FIRST I THOUGHT WE COULD TALK ABOUT THIS
YOU KNOW, WORK IT OUT
BUT SEEING YOU TWO TOGETHER AND ALL...
HEY, LOOK, WHAT DO YOU
WANT ME TO SAY?
DO YOU WANT ME
TO SAY I'LL STOP SEEING HER?
IT'S NOT ABOUT HER, OKAY?
BUT SEEING YOU TWO TOGETHER JUST REMINDS ME OF WHAT YOU DID
AND I DON'T WANT TO LIVE WITH SOMEONE WHO DOESN'T KNOW
WHAT IT IS TO BE A FRIEND, SO I'LL SEE YOU.
LOOK, I KNOW WHAT IT IS TO BE A FRIEND.
I JUST... I SCREWED UP.
YEAH, YOU DID...
AND THAT'S WHY I'M LEAVING.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK.
IF YOU'RE NOT GOING TO STAY FOR ME
THEN AT LEAST STAY FOR THEM.
OKAY, THEY HAVE HAD A VERY DIFFICULT YEAR
WHAT WITH THE ROBBERY AND ALL.
AND THAT CHICK USED TO BE VERY CUTE.
WHEN THAT GUY WAS ROBBING US
AND I WAS LOCKED IN THE ENTERTAINMENT UNIT
FOR SIX HOURS, DO YOU KNOW
WHAT I WAS DOING IN THERE ALL THAT TIME?
I WAS THINKING ABOUT HOW I LET YOU DOWN.
WOW.
YEAH, BUT IF I'D KNOWN
WHAT KIND OF FRIEND YOU WOULD TURN OUT TO BE
I WOULDN'T HAVE WORRIED ABOUT IT SO MUCH.
SEE YOU AROUND.
JUST WAIT ONE SECOND NOW.
THERE HAS TO BE SOMETHING THAT I CAN DO, SOMETHING.
IF WE STILL HAD THAT ENTERTAINMENT UNIT
I WOULD GET IN THERE FOR SIX HOURS AND THINK
ABOUT HOW I LET YOU DOWN.
WHAT?
WE GOT A BOX.
I REMEMBER THE LAST TIME I SAW YOU.
IT WAS THE MORNING I LEFT FOR COLLEGE
AND YOU WERE JUST STANDING OUTSIDE THE DAIRY QUEEN.
I WAS JUST PROBABLY WAITING FOR IT TO OPEN.
GOT TO TELL YOU, YOU LOOK GREAT NOW.
YOU LOOK GREAT, TOO.
YOU'RE AN EXCELLENT PATIENT.
SO HOW DOES IT LOOK?
YOU'VE GOT A LITTLE SCRATCH ON YOUR CORNEA.
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO WEAR A PATCH FOR A COUPLE OF DAYS.
LIKE A PIRATE?
IF THAT HELPS YOU.
OOH.
SO HOW LONG YOU BEEN WORKING WITH YOUR DAD?
COME ON. ONE OF US HAD TO MENTION HIM.
I MOVED BACK HERE A COUPLE MONTHS AGO.
BIG FAMILY DINNER TONIGHT?
UH, HERE.
OH, NO WAY.
I WAS GOING TO HAVE THANKSGIVING
AT MY GIRLFRIEND'S...
OH.
BUT WE BROKE UP.
OH?
SHE SHE WASN'T READY FOR A SERIOUS COMMITMENT.
OH...
SO YOU MADE HER WALK THE PLANK, AYE, MATEY?
YOU'RE NOT WEARING THE PATCH YET.
I KNOW.
HE'S COMING HERE FOR THANKSGIVING?
I KNOW. IT'S SICK.
WHY IS IT SICK?
BECAUSE IT'S RICHARD'S SON.
IT'S LIKE INVITING A GREEK TRAGEDY OVER FOR DINNER.
OKAY, IF IT WERE GREEK, I'D BE BLIND IN BOTH EYES.
COME ON, I LIKE HIM BECAUSE HE'S HANDSOME AND HE'S NICE AND SMART
AND HANDSOME.
I MEAN, COME ON, PHOEBE.
YOU UNDERSTAND, DON'T YOU?
YEAH, I COULD SEE
WHERE I'D BE YOUR BEST SHOT, BUT NO.
NO, I'M SORRY, HONEY.
I THINK IT'S TWISTED.
WHAT'S TWISTED?
ME GOING OUT WITH RICHARD'S SON.
EWW!
EWW, EWW, EWW!
SOUNDS LIKE
A REALLY BAD IDEA TO ME.
IS HE OKAY IN THERE?
HE'S FINE.
HEY, YOU KNOW, MON
IF THINGS WORK OUT BETWEEN YOU AND RICHARD'S SON
YOU'D BE ABLE TO TELL YOUR KIDS
THAT YOU SLEPT WITH THEIR GRANDFATHER.
FINE. JUDGE ALL YOU WANT TO
BUT MARRIED A LESBIAN
LEFT A MAN AT THE ALTAR
FELL IN LOVE WITH A GAY ICE DANCER
THREW A GIRL'S WOODEN LEG IN THE FIRE
LIVE IN A BOX!
SO, NOW, WHAT EXACTLY IS THE POINT OF THE BOX?
CHANDLER?
THE MEANING OF THE BOX IS THREEFOLD.
ONE:
IT GIVES ME THE TIME TO THINK ABOUT WHAT I DID.
TWO:
IT PROVES HOW MUCH I CARE
ABOUT MY FRIENDSHIP WITH JOEY.
AND THREE:
IT HURTS.
AND IF HE STAYS IN THE BOX
YOU GUYS WILL BE FRIENDS AGAIN?
LET'S JUST SAY IT'S A START.
OH, HEY.
HEY, UH, DO YOU REMEMBER THAT NECKLACE
THAT I GAVE YOU LAST YEAR?
CAN I SEE IT?
WHY?
I WANT TO CHECK SOMETHING.
OKAY.
NOW WE'LL SEE.
AIR HOLE! AIR HOLE!
SORRY.
HERE IT IS. I LOVE IT.
I WEAR IT ALL THE TIME.
THE NECKLACE I GOT YOU WAS GOLD.
THIS IS SILVER.
HUH.
WELL, MAYBE IT, UH...
IT CHANGED.
OH, MY GOD.
YOU ACTUALLY EXCHANGED IT.
ISN'T IT BETTER THAT I EXCHANGE IT
FOR SOMETHING THAT I ENJOY
AND CAN GET A LOT OF USE OUT OF?
WHAT DID YOU GET? CREDIT.
I'LL GET IT. I'LL GET IT. I'LL GET IT. I'LL GET IT.
HI, TIM.
HI.
HI. THANK YOU.
MEET MY FRIENDS.
THIS IS, UH, PHOEBE.
HI. NICE TO MEET YOU.
AND JOEY.
HEY. MY BROTHER, ROSS.
HEY.
AND RACHEL.
THAT'S CHANDLER.
HOW DO YOU DO?
WHAT'S...?
WELL, HE'S, UM...
HE'S DOING SOME THINKING.
McCallister tries...
YEAH! YES!
WHAT HAPPENED? WHAT HAPPENED?
YOU KISSED MY GIRLFRIEND.
OOH, I LIKE THOSE SUNGLASSES.
"LIKE THEM" LIKE THEM
OR "I'D LIKE TO GET STORE CREDIT FOR THAT AMOUNT"
LIKE THEM?
VA FA A NAPOLI.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY; THIS TURKEY IS READY.
WHERE CAN I WASH UP?
HERE. LET ME SHOW YOU.
OKAY, THE TOWELS ARE HANGING NEXT TO THE SINK
AND YOU CAN USE THE FANCY SOAP.
THANK YOU.
"FANCY SOAP"?
I THOUGHT WE WERE SAVING THAT FOR THE POPE.
SEE? HE'S NICE, RIGHT?
BUT DO YOU REALLY WANT
TO BE IN A RELATIONSHIP WHERE YOU CAN USE THE PHRASE
"THAT'S NOT HOW YOUR DAD USED TO DO IT"?
WOW. EVERYTHING LOOKS GREAT.
WHERE SHOULD I SIT?
SAVED YOU A SEAT.
SICK, SICK, SICK, SICK, SICK.
OH, I'LL GET IT.
GOTCHA!
THAT DOESN'T SOUND LIKE THINKING TO ME.
SORRY.
I DON'T THINK YOU SHOULD BE TALKING AT ALL.
I THINK YOU GOT TOO MUCH THINKING TO DO
TO BE TALKING AND MAKING JOKES.
OKAY, OKAY. YOU GOT IT.
ROSS, COULD YOU PASS ME THE YAMS?
OH, AND JOEY'S GOT THE MASHED POTATOES
IF YOU WANT TO EXCHANGE THEM.
WILL YOU STOP? WHAT IS THE MATTER WITH YOU?
OH, WE'VE GOT COMPANY.
THERE'S NOTHING THE MATTER WITH ME.
SEE, I'M NOT COMPLETELY DEVOID OF SENTIMENT.
SEE, I HAVE FEELINGS.
OKAY, FINE.
YOU CAN'T TELL, BUT I'M TRYING TO BREAK THE TENSION
BY MOONING YOU GUYS.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK.
IF THIS IS JUST A BIG JOKE TO YOU, THEN FORGET ABOUT IT.
ALL RIGHT, THIS MEANS SOMETHING TO ME.
IF IT DOESN'T MEAN ANYTHING TO YOU
THEN YOU SHOULD GET OUT OF THERE.
OTHERWISE, YOU'RE JUST AN IDIOT IN A BOX.
YOU'RE RIGHT, AND I'M SORRY.
THIS MEANS A LOT TO ME.
I WANT YOU TO BE MY FRIEND AGAIN.
I SWEAR I WON'T SAY ANOTHER WORD TONIGHT.
SO YOU'RE GOING TO START TAKING THIS THING SERIOUSLY?
ABSOLUTELY.
THAT SOUNDS LIKE ANOTHER WORD TO ME.
ARE YOU GOING TO TAKE THIS SERIOUSLY?
OKAY.
DON'T SAY THAT I HAVE NO SENTIMENT.
THIS IS A MOVIE STUB FROM OUR FIRST DATE.
THIS IS AN EGGSHELL
FROM THE FIRST TIME YOU MADE ME BREAKFAST IN BED.
THIS IS FROM THE MUSEUM
THE FIRST TIME...
WE WERE TOGETHER.
OKAY, MAYBE
I EXCHANGE GIFTS SOMETIMES
BUT I KEEP THE THINGS THAT MATTER.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
I'M SORRY.
THOUGH...
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO TAKE THESE.
IT'S, LIKE, A MILLION YEARS OLD.
WE... WE ACTUALLY...
WE HAVE PEOPLE LOOKING FOR THAT.
HEY...
MIND IF I SMOKE?
CARE IF I DIE?
NO. I'M JUST KIDDING, I'M JUST KIDDING.
GO AHEAD, SMOKE.
OH, THIS ALWAYS HAPPENS.
HERE. LET ME, UM...
THANK YOU.
YOU HAVE VERY BEAUTIFUL...
EYE.
YOU KNOW, MY FRIENDS ALL THINK THIS IS WEIRD.
EVEN THE ONE IN THE BOX?
IT'S NOT WEIRD, IS IT?
YOU KNOW, I THOUGHT IT WAS GOING TO BE WEIRD.
I ALMOST CALLED TO CANCEL, BUT IT REALLY ISN'T.
I KNOW. IT'S LIKE YOU AND YOUR DAD--
THAT'S A TOTALLY SEPARATE THING.
OH, I TOTALLY AGREE.
WE'RE JUST TWO PEOPLE WHO FIND EACH OTHER...
VERY ATTRACTIVE.
RIGHT?
WHAT?
NOTHING. NOTHING.
NO. NO, REALLY-- WAS THAT NOT OKAY?
NO, NO, NO, NO. THAT WAS GOOD.
THAT WAS, UH...
THAT WAS A GOOD KISS.
OH, MY GOD, IT DIDN'T REMIND YOU OF MY...?
OH, DON'T SAY IT!
NO, BUT IT DID, DIDN'T IT?
YES! OH, MAN!
I KNOW!
MY GOD, I AM SORRY.
I AM... I AM SO SORRY.
IT'S OKAY.
I MEAN, WOULDN'T BE THANKSGIVING
WITHOUT A LITTLE EMOTIONAL SCARRING.
OH...
YOU KNOW WHAT'S EVEN WORSE?
MY FRIENDS WERE RIGHT.
YOU KNOW WHAT THE WORST THING IS FOR ME
IS THAT YOU ACTUALLY REMIND ME OF A YOUNGER VERSION OF...
MY MOM.
...that's 18 yards.
Is he having quite a day.
I GOT IT.
OH.
HEY.
LISTEN. I WANT YOU TO KNOW HOW SORRY I AM...
THAT'S OKAY.
CHANDLER'S THE ONE I'M MAD AT, SO...
WELL, I'M STILL SORRY.
IS HE HERE?
IN THE BOX.
HI.
CHANDLER?
OH, HE CAN'T TALK RIGHT NOW.
WHY NOT?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
HE'S TRYING TO SHOW JOEY
HOW MUCH HE MEANS TO HIM.
BY BEING IN A BOX.
JOEY HAD REASONS.
THEY WERE THREE FOLD.
OH. WELL, UH...
YOU NOT BEING ABLE TO TALK
MIGHT ACTUALLY MAKE THIS EASIER.
LISTEN, UM...
LISTEN.
I DON'T WANT TO BE SOMEONE
WHO COMES BETWEEN TWO BEST FRIENDS.
I JUST... I CAN'T STAND SEEING WHAT THIS IS DOING TO YOU GUYS
AND I DON'T WANT TO BE THE CAUSE OF THAT.
SO... I DON'T THINK WE CAN SEE EACH OTHER ANYMORE.
I'M GOING TO GO
TO MY MOM'S IN CHICAGO.
I'M GOING TO STAY THERE FOR A WHILE.
I THINK THIS COULD HAVE BEEN SOMETHING REALLY AMAZING.
BUT, YOU KNOW, THIS IS PROBABLY FOR THE BEST.
YOU KNOW?
I'M GOING TO MISS YOU.
GOOD BYE, CHANDLER.
OPEN THE BOX!
WHAT?
HE CAN STILL CATCH HER!
HEY, COME ON. GET OUT OF THERE!
GET OUT OF THERE!
SO...?
YEAH, WE'RE GOING TO BE FINE. GET OUT.
YEAH?
YEAH. YOU DID SOME REAL GOOD THINKING IN THERE.
I MEAN, THIS IS...
NOW, GO BECAUSE YOU CAN STILL CATCH HER
AND MERRY CHRISTMAS FROM YOUR SECRET SANTA!
ALL RIGHT, WHO GOT CHANDLER? BECAUSE I NEED TO TRADE.
OH, HE SEES HER.
OH, HE'S CATCHING UP TO HER.
OH, SHE SEES HIM.
OH, THEY'RE HUGGING.
OHH.
HE'S TAKING HER PURSE.
UH, THAT'S NOT THEM.
I'M GOING TO GO CALL THE POLICE.
OH, THERE THEY ARE!
WHERE? OH...
ALL RIGHT, GET A ROOM.