WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
IS THAT YOU?
OH!
BOY, YOU ARE REALLY NOT A MORNING PERSON.
BACK OFF!
GET UP! GET UP! GET UP!
GET UP! GET UP!
WHAT IS THAT NOISE?
YOU.
IT'S THE CHICK.
SHE'S GOING THROUGH SOME CHANGES.
WHAT KIND OF CHANGES?
THE VET SEEMS TO THINK
THAT SHE'S BECOMING A ROOSTER.
WE'RE GETTING A SECOND OPINION.
HEY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING SHOPPING
AT 8:00 IN THE MORNING?
WELL, I'VE BEEN UP SINCE 6:00
THANKS TO SOMEBODY'S DUMB ASS ROOSTER.
GUYS, YOU REALLY SHOULD GET RID
OF THOSE ANIMALS.
THEY SHOULDN'T BE LIVING IN AN APARTMENT.
ESPECIALLY NOT WITH ALL THESE KNIVES AND COOKBOOKS AROUND.
ALL RIGHT, I'M GOING TO GO TO THE FERTILITY DOCTOR
AND SEE IF I'M READY TO HAVE FRANK AND ALICE'S EMBRYO
TRANSFERRED INTO MY UTERUS.
NOW, HOW WILL THEY KNOW IF YOU'RE READY?
THEY'RE GOING TO SEE
IF MY ENDOMETRIAL LAYER IS THICK.
WELL, I CAN, UH, CHECK THAT FOR YOU.
OKAY, EVERYONE, THINK THICK.
GOOD LUCK. GOOD LUCK.
HEY! HEY!
WISH ME LUCK.
OH... GOOD LUCK.
AND I'M STILL RIGHT.
THAT IS SO NOT TRUE.
WHAT?
SHE'S MAD BECAUSE I KNOW TODAY'S HER LAUNDRY DAY
AND THAT MEANS SHE'S WEARING HER OLD LADY UNDERPANTS.
WELL, I CAN CHECK THAT FOR YOU.
I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE THAT YOU THINK
THAT YOU AND CHANDLER KNOW ME AND RACHEL BETTER
THAN WE KNOW YOU.
WELL, WE DO.
YOU CAN ONLY EAT TIC TACS IN EVEN NUMBERS.
YEAH, WHAT'S THAT ABOUT?
AND YOU...
ROSS, I BELIEVE IF YOU CHECK RACHEL'S BAG
YOU WILL FIND A HALF EATEN BOX OF COOKIES IN THERE.
YOU'RE GOOD.
THESE ARE NOT.
SO NOT IMPRESSED.
EVERYBODY SNACKS WHEN THEY SHOP.
OH, YEAH?
ROSS, HOW MANY ITEMS LEFT IN THAT BAG?
FIVE.
OKAY, TEN BUCKS SAYS
THAT WE CAN NAME EVERY ITEM IN THAT BAG.
HOW MANY GUESSES DO YOU GET?
SIX.
CHALLENGE EXTENDED.
DEAL.
CHALLENGE ACCEPTED.
ALL RIGHT.
WE'LL START WITH...
APPLES.
WE'LL BE STARTING WITH APPLES.
STOP THAT NOW.
YES.
OKAY, UH, TORTILLA CHIPS, YOGURT...
DIET SODA...
YES, YES...
YES.
ORANGE JUICE.
THERE'S NO ORANGE JUICE IN THERE.
WE WIN!
THEY HAVE ANOTHER GUESS.
OKAY, WELL, WE WON THAT ONE.
OKAY, THE LAST THING IS...
OOH, OOH! OOH! OOH, OOH!
NO. NO. NOT FOR LIKE ANOTHER TWO WEEKS.
I GOT IT.
SCOTCH...
TAPE.
HA!
HOW DID YOU KNOW SHE WOULD BUY SCOTCH TAPE?
WELL, WE USED UP THEIRS LAST NIGHT MAKING SCARY FACES.
OH, MAN.
ALL RIGHT, TEN BUCKS.
FORK IT OVER.
COUGH IT UP.
PAY THE PIPER.
GIVE ME IT.
THAT DOES NOT MEAN YOU KNOW US BETTER.
I WANT A REMATCH.
AND NONE OF THESE STUPID GROCERY QUESTIONS.
REAL PERSONAL QUESTIONS.
YEAH, AND THE WINNER GETS A HUNDRED BUCKS.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
ARE YOU SCARED?
NO.
OKAY, WHO MAKES UP THE QUESTIONS?
ROSS'LL DO IT.
OH, SURE, ROSS'LL DO IT.
IT'S NOT LIKE HE HAS A JOB OR A CHILD
OR A LIFE OF HIS OWN.
WELL, FINE. WE'LL ASK PHOEBE.
NO. I WANT TO PLAY.
LOOKS LIKE YOUR UTERUS
IS READY FOR IMPLANTATION.
OH, I KNEW IT.
I FELT REALLY THICK THIS MORNING.
WELL, OKAY, SO, WHAT'S NOW?
GO GO GET THE EGGS.
PUT THEM IN THERE.
OKAY. IT'LL TAKE JUST A LITTLE WHILE
TO PREPARE THE EMBRYOS.
EMBRYOS?
AS IN MORE THAN ONE.
FIVE, ACTUALLY.
FIVE? OKAY, WHERE AM I GIVING BIRTH?
IN A HOSPITAL OR A BIG BOX UNDER THE STAIRS?
WE DO FIVE
BECAUSE THAT GIVES YOU A 25% CHANCE
THAT AT LEAST ONE WILL ATTACH.
THAT'S IT? 25 PERCENT?
THAT MEANS THAT IT'S
LIKE 75 PERCENT CHANCE OF NO BABY AT ALL?
YEAH, YOU KNOW , I WAS THINKING.
WHAT ARE THE ODDS IF YOU STUFF 200 OF THEM IN THERE?
SWEETIE, NOW, SHE'S A WOMAN
NOT A GUM BALL MACHINE.
OKAY, WELL, DO N'T WORRY, YOU GUYS
BECAUSE I'M GOING TO DO THIS AS MANY TIMES AS IT TAKES
TO GET IT RIGHT.
WELL, SEE, THE THING IS
WE KIND OF ONLY HAVE ONE SHOT.
IT COSTS $16,000 EACH TIME YOU DO THIS.
$16,000 DOLLAR?!
I IT'S 20 IN CALIFORNIA.
UM, WE'RE...
WE'RE KIND OF USING ALL THE MONEY WE HAVE
JUST TO DO IT THIS ONE TIME.
WHOA!
THAT'S... OKAY, THAT'S A LOT OF PRESSURE
ON ME AND MY UTERUS.
SO, WELL, OKAY.. . SO, MAYBE THERE'S SOMETHING I CAN DO
YOU KNOW, JUST TO, LIKE, HELP MAKE SURE I GET PREGNANT.
NO. I'M SORRY.
WOW. YOU GUYS REALLY DON'T KNOW ANYTHING.
WHY DON'T YOU GET DRUNK?
THAT WORKED FOR A BUNCH OF GIRLS
IN MY HIGH SCHOOL.
SO, HOW'S THE TEST COMING?
HEY, HEY, HEY, YOU'RE TOUCHING THE GAME BOARD.
SORRY.
YOU FREAK.
HEY, GUYS, DO YOU REALIZE
THAT ANY MINUTE NOW, PHOEBE COULD BE PREGNANT.
I KNOW. I KNOW.
IT'S SUCH A HUGE, LIFE ALTERING THING.
I KNOW. IT IS.
THE TEST IS READY.
OKAY, EACH TEAM WILL ANSWER TEN QUESTIONS.
THE FIRST TEAM TO ANSWER THE MOST QUESTIONS WINS.
THE CATEGORIES ARE "FEARS AND PET PEEVES"
"ANCIENT HISTORY"
"LITERATURE"
AND "IT'S ALL RELATIVE."
NOW...
THE COIN TOSS, TO SEE WHO GOES FIRST.
OKAY...
SOMEBODY CALL IT THIS TIME.
YEAH. OKAY.
TAILS!
IT'S HEADS.
YES, IT IS!
GENTLEMEN, PICK YOUR CATEGORY.
"FEARS AND PET PEEVES."
"WHAT IS MONICA'S BIGGEST PET PEEVE?"
ANIMALS DRESSED AS HUMANS.
THAT'S CORRECT.
LADIES?
SAME CATEGORY.
"ACCORDING TO CHANDLER
WHAT PHENOMENON SCARES THE BEJEEZUS OUT OF HIM?"
MICHAEL FLATLEY, LORD OF THE DANCE.
THAT IS CORRECT.
AH! WHOO!
THE IRISH JIG GUY?
HIS LEGS FLAIL ABOUT
AS IF INDEPEND ENT FROM HIS BODY.
AW!
GENTLEMEN, YOUR PICK.
"IT'S ALL RELATIVE."
"MONICA AND I HAD A GRANDMOTHER WHO DIED.
"YOU BOTH WENT TO HER FUNERAL.
NAME THAT GRANDMOTHER."
NANA?
SHE HAS A REAL NAME.
ALTHEA!
ALTHEA? WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I TOOK A SHOT.
WITH ALTHEA?
ALTHEA IS CORRECT.
NICE SHOOTING!
WE'LL TAKE "LITERATURE!"
"EVERY WEEK THE TV GUIDE
"COMES TO CHANDLER AND JOEY'S APARTMENT.
WHAT NAME APPEARS ON THE ADDRESS LABEL?"
CHANDLER GETS IT!
IT'S CHANDLER BING!
NO!
I'M AFRAID THETV GUIDE COMES TO "CHANANDLER BONG."
I KNEW THAT.
RACHEL, USE YOUR HEAD.
ACTUALLY, IT'S "MISS CHANANDLER BONG."
HELLO, TEENY EMBRYOS.
WELL, I'M PHOEBE BUFFAY. HI.
I'M I'M HOPING TO BE YOUR UTERUS FOR THE NEXT NINE MONTHS, SO...
YOU SHOULD KNOW THAT WE'RE DOING THIS FOR FRANK AND ALICE
WHO YOU KNOW-- YOU'VE BEEN THERE.
UM...
YOU KNOW, THEY WANT YOU SO MUCH.
SO WHEN YOU GUYS GET IN THERE, REALLY GRAB ON.
OKAY, AND... AND I PROMISE
THAT I'LL KEEP YOU SAFE AND WARM
UNTIL, YOU KNOW, YOU'RE READY TO HAVE THEM TAKE YOU HOME.
SO...
OKAY.
OH, AND ALSO, NEXT TIME YOU SEE ME
IF I'M SCREAMING, DON'T WORRY.
THAT'S WHAT'S SUPPOSED TO HAPPEN.
READY?
UH HUH.
GOOD LUCK.
ALL RIGHT.
THE SCORE IS NINE TO EIGHT IN FAVOR OF THE GUYS.
LADIES, IF YOU MISS THIS, THE GAME IS THEIRS.
PICK YOUR CATEGORY.
"IT'S ALL RELATIVE!"
YOU DON'T HAVE TO SHOUT EVERYTHING.
I'M SORRY!
OOH.
"WHAT IS THE NAME
OF CHANDLER'S FATHER'S LAS VEGAS ALL MALE BURLESQUE?"
VIVA LAS GAYGAS!
UNFORTUNATELY, THAT IS CORRECT.
YES! YES!
ALL RIGHT.
WE HAVE A TIE.
LUCKILY, I'VE PREPARED FOR SUCH AN EVENT.
THE LIGHTNING ROUND!
OH! OH!
3O SECONDS.
ALL THE QUESTIONS YOU CAN ANSWER.
YOU GUYS ARE DEAD.
I AM SO GOOD AT LIGHTNING ROUNDS.
I MAJORED IN LIGHTNING ROUNDS, ALL RIGHT?
WE'RE GOING TO DESTROY YOU.
WANT TO BET?
I'M SO CONFUSED
AS TO WHAT WE'VE BEEN DOING SO FAR.
HOW ABOUT WE PLAY FOR MORE MONEY?
SAY, 150?
ONE HUNDRED AND FIFTY DOLLARS.
SAY, 200?
TWO HUNDRED DOLLARS.
YOU'RE DOING IT AGAIN.
EXCUSE ME.
MONICA, I DON'T WANT TO LOSE $200 DOLLAR.
WE WON'T.
300?
MONICA!
I'M JUST TRYIN G TO SPICE IT UP.
OKAY, SO THEN PLAY FOR SOME PEPPER.
STOP SPENDING MY MONEY.
I GOT IT.
HOW ABOUT IF WE WIN
THEY HAVE TO GET RID OF THE ROOSTER?
OOH, THAT'S INTERESTING.
HEY, NO WAY. THAT ROOSTER'S FAMILY.
THROW IN THE DUCK.
THE DUCK DOESN'T MAKE ANY NOISE.
WELL, HE GETS THE OTHER ONE ALL RILED UP.
LOOK, WE ARE NOT...
ALL RIGHT, HOLD ON.
IF YOU WIN, WE'LL GIVE UP THE BIRDS.
GAH!
BUT IF WE WIN...
WE GET YOUR APARTMENT.
OOH.
DEAL!
NO, THAT'S CRAZY.
THERE'S NO WAY WE ARE BETTING THE APARTMENT.
ALL RIGHT, I'M IN
BECAUSE EITHER HE GOES, OR I'M BUYING A COYOTE.
MONICA, BETTING THE APARTMENT?
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THIS.
I HAVE NOT MISSED ONE QUESTION THE WHOLE GAME.
I OWN THIS GAME!
LOOK AT MY HAND.
ARE THE ANSWERS
WRITTEN ON THERE?
NO! STEADY AS A ROCK.
NOW, ARE YOU WITH ME?
HUH! LET'S DO IT!
COME ON! OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, GENTLEMEN, YOU'RE UP FIRST.
OKAY. OKAY.
YOU HAVE 30 SECONDS.
THE LIGHTNING ROUND
BEGINS... STOP IT.
NOW. WHAT WAS MONICA'S NICKNAME
WHEN SHE WAS A FIELD HOCKEY GOALIE?
"BIG FAT GOALIE." CORRECT.
RACHEL CLAIMS THIS IS HER FAVORITE MOVIE.
DANGEROUS LIAISONS.
HER ACTUAL FAVORITE MOVIE IS?
WEEKEND AT BERNIE'S.
CORRECT.
IN WHAT PART OF HER BODY
DID MONICA GET A PENCIL STUCK AT AGE 14?
OH!
EW! NO!
HER EAR!
ALL RIGHT.
MONICA CATEGORIZES HER TOWELS.
HOW MANY CATEGORIES ARE THERE?
"EVERYDAY USE."
"GUEST." "FANCY."
"FANCY GUEST."
TWO SECONDS.
D'UH, 11?!
11. UNBELIEVABLE.
11 IS CORRECT.
YES!
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S FOUR FOR THE GUYS.
LADIES, YOU'RE UP.
ALL RIGHT, COME ON!
30 SECONDS ON THE CLOCK.
FIVE CORRECT QUESTIONS WINS THE GAME.
THE LIGHTNING ROUND BEGINS...
NOW. WHAT IS JOEY'S FAVORITE FOOD?
SANDWICHES. CORRECT.
CHANDLER WAS HOW OLD
WHEN HE FIRST TOUCHED A GIRL'S BREAST?
FOURTEEN? NO, 19.
THANKS, MAN.
JOEY HAD AN IMAGINARY CHILDHOOD FRIEND.
HIS NAME WAS...?
MAURICE.
HIS PROFESSION WAS...?
SPACE COWBOY! CORRECT!
WHAT IS CHANDLER BING'S JOB?
OH...!
OH, GOSH! DOES IT HAVE SOMETHING
TO DO WITH NUMBERS?
AND PROCESSING.
AND HE CARRIES A BRIEFCASE.
YOU NEED THIS, OR YOU LOSE THE GAME.
IT HAS SOMETHING TO DO WITH TRANSPONDING.
OH, OH, HE'S A TRANSPONDS- TRANSPONSTER!
THAT'S NOT EVEN A WORD!
OH!
I CAN GET THIS! I CAN...
NO!!!
YES! YES!
I CALL MONICA'S ROOM.
YOU CAN'T JUST CALL MONICA'S ROOM.
SURE, I CAN.
STANDARD SHOTGUN RULES.
I'M IN SIGHT OF THE ROOM
AND I CALLED IT.
MAN, I FEEL LIKE I'M COMING DOWN WITH SOMETHING.
OOH. YEAH.
BET YOU CAN'T GUESS
WHAT COLOR  MY TONSILS ARE.
I'LL BET THE APARTMENT.
I WOULD NEVER BET THIS APARTMENT.
IT'S TOO NICE.
HEY.
OOH, PHEEBS, ARE THEY IN THERE?
UM, YEAH, UH HUH, I'M IMPLANTED.
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
WELL, FREAKED.
IT TURNS OUT THE ODDS ARE, LIKE, REALLY SUCKY
AND THIS IS FRANK AND ALICE'S, LIKE, ONLY SHOT.
THEY ARE, LIKE, LITERALLY
PUTTING ALL THEIR EGGS IN MY BASKET.
YEAH, BUT I BET IT WORKS.
REALLY? HOW MUCH?
ALL RIGHT, I'M GOING TO GO
TAKE A PREGNANCY TEST RIGHT NOW.
OH, WOW. YOU CAN TELL THIS SOON?
WELL, THE DOCTOR SAYS IT TAKES A COUPLE DAYS
BUT MY BODY'S ALWAYS BEEN A LITTLE FASTER
THAN WESTERN MEDICINE, SO...
OH, MY GOD.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU GUYS
ACTUALLY THINK YOU'RE MOVING IN HERE.
WELL, BELIEVE IT, BABY.
WELL, I I, I'M NOT MOVING.
WHAT?!
NO. IT WAS A STUPID BET.
WE WERE JUST PLAYING A GAME.
YOU CAN'T JUST IGNORE THE BET.
IT'S A BET.
YOU BET ON A BET, AND IF YOU LOSE
YOU LOSE THE BET.
RACH, WE HAVE TO MOVE.
IF WE HAD LOST, WE WOULD HAVE MADE THEM
GET RID OF THE BIRDS, RIGHT?
NO.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, I HATE THIS
AS MUCH AS YOU, BUT... IF IT MAKES YOU FEEL ANY BETTER
THIS IS ALL YOUR FAULT.
WHAT?!
"CHANANDLER BONG."
COME ON, WE STEAL THATTV GUIDEEVERY WEEK.
I KNEW IT!
I DON'T CARE.
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
COOL. GIRL ROOMMATE.
WELL?
NOPE, NOT KNOCKED UP YET.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, IT'S ONLY BEEN A COUPLE HOURS
SO, JUST GIVE IT SOME TIME.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT. MEANWHILE
I'M GOING TO DO WHATEVER I CAN
TO HELP THIS, SO, I'M JUST GOING TO, YOU KNOW
LIE IN YOUR CHAIR, OKAY?
YOU KNOW, JUST... YEAH, GOOD.
I'M GOING TO LET GRAVITY, YOU KNOW, DO ITS JOB.
I WON'T GET IN THE WAY.
IT'LL BE JUST LIKE THAT TIME
I TRIED TO COUNT ALL THE BUMPS ON YOUR CEILING.
YOU KNOW, PHEEBS, IF YOU SIT THERE LONG ENOUGH
YOU'LL BE SITT ING IN OUR APARTMENT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
OH, RACH, F.Y.I., YOUR NEW APARTMENT
HASN'T HAD HOT WATER SINCE CHRISTMAS.
HEY, RACH, CAN YOU GIVE ME A HAND WITH THIS BOX?
NO! PUT THAT BOX DOWN!
WE ARE NOT GOING ANYWHERE!
THIS IS MY APARTMENT, AND I LIKE IT!
THIS IS A "GIRLS'" APARTMENT!
THAT IS A "BOYS'" APARTMENT!
IT'S DIRTY AND IT SMELLS!
THIS IS PRETTY!
IT'S SO PRETTY!
AND LOOK, AND IT'S PURPLE!
AND I'M TELLING YOU-- YOU WITH YOUR STEADY HAND--
I AM NOT MOVING, AND NOW I HAVE GOT THE STEADY HAND.
OKAY. OKAY. SHH.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF IT.
THAT'S RIGHT!
YOU DO WHAT THE HAND SAYS!
HOW'D IT GO?
I LOST OUR MATTRESSES.
?? ARE YOU IN THERE, LITTLE FETUS? ??
?
?? IN NINE MONTHS, WILL YOU COME GREET US...? ?
?? I WILL BUY YOU SOME ADIDAS... ??
HI. HEY.
OH, HI. PHOEBE, UM...
WE WERE JUST AT THE DRUGSTORE
UM, SO WE GOT YOU A LITTLE PRESENT.
OH, WHOA, THAT'S WHERE ALL MY BLOOD WAS.
UM, IT'S A LOLLIPOP AND, UH, A HOME PREGNANCY TEST.
DON'T MIX THOSE UP.
YOU COULD REALLY RUIN THAT LOLLIPOP.
SO, UM... YOU FEEL LIKE TAKING A TEST?
THERE'S ONLY ONE QUESTION.
A ALL RIGHT, I WILL.
I WILL, BUT, UM, YOU KNOW, JUST REMEMBER
THAT IT'S STILL REALLY EARLY
SO, IF IT SAYS THAT I'M NOT PREGNANT
THAT DOESN'T MEAN I'M NOT GOING TO GET PREGNANT
OKAY? AND, AND JUST PLEASE
JUST SO I DON'T  GO COMPLETELY NUTS
JUST TRY NOT TO PUT ALL YOUR HOPES ON THIS
OKAY?
OKAY. OKAY.
GREAT.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU ARE MEAN BOYS WHO ARE JUST BEING MEAN.
HEY, DON'T GET MAD AT US.
NO ONE FORCED YOU TO RAISE THE STAKES.
THAT IS NOT TRUE!
SHE DID! SHE FORCED ME!
WE'D STILL BE HERE, BUT YOU GOT THE QUESTION WRONG.
WELL, IT WAS A STUPID, UNFAIR QUESTION.
DON'T BLAME THE QUESTIONS.
WOULD YOU ALL STOP YELLING IN OUR APARTMENT?!
YOU ARE RUINING MOVING DAY FOR US!
STOP CALLING IT YOUR APARTMENT!
IT IS OUR APARTMENT!
YOU GUYS, YOU GUYS, YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE A BABY.
THEY'RE GOING TO HAVE A BABY!
MY SISTER'S GOING TO HAVE MY BABY!
OKAY, BUT THIS CAN'T BE GOOD FOR THE BABY.
I CAN'T FIND GARBAGE BAGS.
OH, WELL, I THINK I SAW SOME IN HERE.
WHAT IS IT?
I DON'T KNOW
BUT MAYBE IF WE KEEP THAT DRAWER SHUT
IT'LL DIE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE WE'RE LIVING HERE!
WHA...? WH WHAT IS IT?!
DID YOU SEE THE SIZE OF THE CLOSETS?!
I CAN'T BELIEVE WE LIVE HERE!
OH...! OH...!
OH!!! OH!!!