THAT'S, LIKE, THE TENTH TIME I'VE PEED
SINCE I'VE BEEN HERE.
IT'S ALSO, LIKE, THE TENTH TIME YOU'VE TOLD US.
YEAH, OH, I'M SORRY.
IT MUST BE REALLY HARD TO HEAR.
I TELL YOU, IT'S A LOT EASIER HAVING THREE BABIES PLAYING
BRINGIN' IN DA' NOISE, BRINGIN' IN DA' FUNK
ON YOUR BLADDER.
OH, I AM SO TIRED OF BEING PREGNANT.
I CAN'T SLEEP EXCEPT ON MY BACK, WHICH HURTS, SO I CAN'T SLEEP.
THE ONLY HAPPINESS I GET IS FROM A CUP OF COFFEE
WHICH, OF COURSE, IS DECAF BECAUSE, OH, I'M PREGNANT.
PHEEBS, YOU... YOU WANT A COOKIE?
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
SO, UH, PHEEBS, HONEY
HOW ARE THOSE MOOD SWINGS COMING?
I HAVEN'T REALLY HAD ANY YET.
HEY, GUYS.
HEY. HEY.
ALL RIGHT. HERE'S THE RING.
YES, YES. A THOUSAND TIMES, YES.
SO, UH, ANY IDEAS FOR THE BACHELOR PARTY YET?
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
BEFORE YOU START HANDING OUT WEDDING RINGS
AND PLANNING BACHELOR PARTIES
DON'T YOU HAVE TO DECIDE WHO YOUR BEST MAN'S GOING TO BE?
OH, IT'S AWKWARD.
IT'S AWKWARD, IT'S AWKWARD.
I SORT OF ALREADY ASKED CHANDLER.
WHAT?!
HE GOT TO DO IT AT YOUR FIRST WEDDING.
JOEY, I FIGURED YOU'D UNDERSTAND.
I MEAN, I'VE KNOWN HIM A LOT LONGER.
COME ON, ROSS. I DON'T HAVE ANY BROTHERS.
I'M NEVER GOING TO GET TO BE A BEST MAN.
YOU CAN BE THE BEST MAN
WHEN I GET MARRIED.
I'M NEVER GOING TO GET TO BE A BEST MAN!
WAIT, WAIT.
SO YOU GET TO BE
MY BEST MAN TWICE
AND I DON'T GET TO BE YOURS AT ALL?
OH, NO.
YOU... OF COURSE YOU CAN BE MY BEST MAN.
WHAT ABOUT ME?
YOU JUST SAID I COULD.
I'M NOT EVEN GETTING MARRIED, OKAY?
THIS IS A QUESTION FOR SCIENCE FICTION WRITERS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE NOT PICKING ME.
HEY, HOW COULD IT NOT BE ME?
I'M NOT EVEN...
I DON'T EVEN...
ALL RIGHT. YOU KNOW WHAT?
THAT'S IT.
FROM NOW ON, JOEY, I WANT YOU TO BE MY BEST MAN.
YES!
SHAME ABOUT YOU, THOUGH.
STOP IT.
WHAT?
ONE OF THE BABIES IS KICKING.
I THOUGHT THAT WAS A GOOD THING.
IT'S NOT KICKING ME.
IT'S KICKING ONE OF THE OTHER BABIES.
OH, DON'T MAKE ME COME IN THERE.
HEY. HEY.
DO YOU GUYS HAVE, LIKE, A BIG BOWL I CAN BORROW?
YEAH. THERE'S ONE RIGHT UNDER THE CABINET.
THANKS.
WHY DO YOU NEED IT?
OH, WE'RE HAVING A BIG PARTY TOMORROW NIGHT. LATER.
WHOA, HEY.
WERE YOU PLANNING ON INVITING US?
NO, NO.
LATER.
HEY, GET YOUR ASS BACK HERE, TRIBBIANI!
HORMONES.
WHAT PHOEBE MEANT TO SAY
WAS HOW COME YOU'RE
HAVING A PARTY A ND WE'RE NOT INVITED?
OH. IT'S ROSS'S BACHELOR PARTY.
SO?
ARE YOU BACHELORS?
NO.
ARE YOU STRIPPERS?
THEN YOU'RE NOT INVITED.
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
YOU'RE NOT INVITED TO THE PARTY
THAT WE'RE GOING TO HAVE EITHER.
OH, WELL, WHAT PARTY?
WELL, UM...
THE BABY SHOWER FOR PHOEBE.
BABY SHOWER?
WOW... THAT SO DOESN'T SOUND LIKE SOMETHING I WANT TO DO.
LATER.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I'M GOING TO HAVE A PARTY.
THAT'S SO GREAT!
A PARTY! YAY!
MY GOD!
OH, HONEY...
I DON'T KNOW WHY.
THIS IS WHAT I GOT GOING FOR THE PARTY SO FAR LIQUOR WISE:
"GET A LOT OF LIQUOR."
GREAT, GREAT.
OKAY. NOW, IN TERMS OF THE INVITE LIST
OBVIOUSLY, I GOT YOU, ME AND CHANDLER
AND I'M GOING TO INVITE GUNTHER
BECAUSE WE'VE BEEN TALKING ABOUT THIS PRETTY LOUDLY.
I'LL BE THERE.
ALL RIGHT, AND...
OH, LISTEN-- I KNOW IT'S YOUR PARTY
BUT I'D REALLY LIKE TO LIMIT THE NUMBER
OF MUSEUM GEEKS THAT ARE GOING TO BE THERE.
YEAH, TELL YOU WHAT.
LET'S NOT INVITE ANY OF THE ANTHROPOLOGISTS, OKAY?
JUST THE DINOSAUR DUDES.
OKAY. WE'LL NEED A SIX PACK OF ZIMA.
HEY, GUYS, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
OH, JUST PLANNING
MY BACHELOR PARTY WITH MY BEST MAN.
YEAH, WELL, GOOD LUCK TRYING TO TOP THE LAST ONE.
YEAH, SEE, I DON'T THINK
IT'S GOING TO BE THAT DIFFICULT
CONSIDERING THIS ONE WON'T TAKE PLACE
IN THE BASEMENT OF A PIZZA HUT.
OH, I'M ROSS, I'M ROSS.
I'M TOO GOOD FOR THE HUT.
LOOK. I GOT TO GO PICK UP BEN.
EVERYTHING SO FAR SOUNDS GREAT, JOEY.
JUST REMEMBER TO KEEP IT
ON THE MELLOW SIDE, OKAY?
JUST A COUPLE OF GUYS HANGING OUT PLAYING POKER.
NO NO STRIPPERS OR ANYTHING, OKAY?
YOU GOT IT.
OKAY. SEE YOU LATER.
SEE YA.
HAVE FUN PLANNING
YOUR MELLOW BACHELOR PARTY.
THERE'S GOING TO BE STRIPPERS THERE.
HE DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING ABOUT NO STRIPPERS.
HE JUST SAID, "NO STRIPPERS."
OH. I CHOSE NOT TO HEAR THAT.
LOOK WHAT I GOT!
OH...
CAN YOU BELIEVE
THEY MAKE THESE FOR LITTLE PEOPLE?
AW, LITTLE VILLAGE PEOPLE.
OKAY. LOOK AT THIS ONE.
THIS IS MY FAVORITE.
OH, THAT IS SO SWEET.
I KNOW.
PHOEBE'S GOING TO LOVE DRESSING THEM IN THESE.
HUH. EXCEPT, UH...
PHOEBE'S NOT GOING TO BE THE ONE WHO GETS TO DRESS THEM.
BECAUSE SHE'S NOT GOING TO GET TO KEEP THE BABIES.
OH, MY GOD.
WE ARE THROWING THE MOST DEPRESSING BABY SHOWER EVER.
NO... WAIT A MINUTE.
UNLESS WE GIVE HER
ALL GIFTS THAT SHE CAN USE
AFTER SHE'S DONE BEING PREGNANT--
LIKE REGULAR COFFEE
TEQUILA.
A CARTON OF CIGARETTES.
SHE DOESN'T SMOKE.
IT'S THE THOUGHT THAT COUNTS.
OH, NO, IT'S A GREAT IDEA. IT'S A GREAT...
OH, AND SOMEBODY CAN GET HER THOSE, THOSE LEATHER PANTS THAT SHE'S ALWAYS WANTED.
OH, SHE'S GOING TO LOVE THAT.
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
YOU ACTUALLY THOUGHT
IT WOULD MAKE ME FEEL BETTER
TO GIVE ME SOMETHING
I CAN'T EVEN USE FOR ANOTHER TWO MONTHS?!
THIS SUCKS! OOH!
WHO GAVE ME THIS?
WELL, UM... I... I...
THEY TOLD ME YOU'D LIKE THEM.
OH!
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
THEN I'M WRONG. IT'S A GREAT GIFT--
THE BEST PRESENT I EVER GOT! OH!
ALL RIGHT, WHAT'S MY NEXT PRESENT?!
I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING.
NO, NO.
ALL RIGHT, FINE. THEN THIS IS OVER.
GOD!
BALLOONS!
HEY, LISTEN, MAN, ABOUT THE STRIPPER...
YEAH?
GOOD CALL!
SO YOU KNOW WHO TO ASK TO HOST YOUR NEXT BACHELOR PARTY, HUH?
JOEY, I'M KIND OF HOPING THIS WILL BE MY LAST ONE.
OKAY. A LITTLE ANNOUNCEMENT.
A LITTLE ANNOUNCEMENT.
I'VE DECIDED THAT MY BEST MAN IS MY BEST FRIEND, GUNTHER.
WHAT'S MY LAST NAME?
CENTRAL PERK?
THANKS FOR NOT MARRYING RACHEL.
OH, HEY, GUNTHER, DON'T FORGET YOUR SHIRT.
HEY, HEY, WHAT ARE THOSE?
THEY'RE LITTLE PARTY FAVORS.
CHECK IT OUT.
WOW, YEAH.
OH, OH, OH...
AW.
OKAY. A LITTLE ANNOUNCEMENT.
I JUST WANT EVERYBODY TO KNOW
THE POSITION OF MY BEST MAN IS STILL OPEN
AND, UH, YOU KNOW
SO IS THE POSITION OF THE BRIDE.
GREAT.
OKAY.
SMOOTH, MAN.
YOU GOT SOME CHILI ON YOUR NECK.
WELL, I JUST WANT TO SAY, THANKS, EVERYONE.
THIS WAS GREAT, OKAY?
AND HEY, I'LL SEE  YOU GUYS MONDAY MORNING.
THANKS, JOE.
OH, HEY, DON'T FORGET YOUR SHIRT.
THANKS.
OKAY. HEY, MUSEUM GEEKS, PARTY'S OVER.
OKAY. WAVE BYE BYE TO THE NICE LADY. THERE YOU GO.
BACK TO YOUR PARENTS' BASEMENT.
ALL RIGHT.
COME ON, BOYS, COME ON OUT.
THERE YOU GO.
OH!
LOOK AT THE LITTLE BIRDIES.
ARE THOSE YOURS?
YEAH.
WELL, I DIDN'T KNOW THEY LET YOU KEEP CHICKENS AND DUCKS AS PETS.
AND I GOT THE DUCK TOTALLY TRAINED, TOO.
WATCH THIS.
STARE AT THE WALL.
HARDLY MOVE.
BE WHITE.
YOU ARE
REALLY GOOD AT THAT.
SO, I HAD FUN TONIGHT.
YOU THROW ONE HELL OF A PARTY.
WELL, THANKS, THANKS.
IT WAS GREAT MEETING YOU.
AND LISTEN, IF ANY OF MY FRIENDS EVER GET MARRIED
OR HAVE A BIRTHDAY OR A TUESDAY...
YEAH, THAT'D BE GREAT.
SO, I GUESS, UM, GOOD NIGHT.
OH, UNLESS YOU, UH...
UNLESS YOU WANT TO HANG AROUND.
YEAH?
YEAH. I'LL LET YOU PLAY
WITH MY DUCK.
HEY...
STRIPPER?
THE STRIPPER STOLE THE RING!
CHANDLER, GET UP! GET UP!
WHAT?
THE RING IS GONE!
OH.
OKAY. JUST, LIKE, GIVE ME...
A MINUTE TO WAKE UP FOR THIS.
YOU LOST THE RING.
YOU'RE THE WORST BEST MAN EVER.
DUDE, THIS ISN'T FUNNY.
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?
I GO TO SLEEP LAST NIGHT, EVERYTHING'S COOL.
I WAKE UP THIS MORNING
THE STRIPPER'S GONE AND THE RING IS GONE.
YOU SLEPT WITH THE STRIPPER?!
OF COURSE.
HI, GUYS.
HI, PHOEBE.
I I WANTED
TO APOLOGIZE IF I, YOU KNOW
SEEMED A TAD EDGY YESTERDAY AT MY SHOWER
YOU KNOW.
IT'S JUST THE HORMONES, YOU KNOW.
NO. WE...
HORMONES. HORMONES, YEAH.
ANYWAY, I JUST WANTED TO SAY THANK YOU.
IT WAS SO SWEET.
OKAY.
YOU'RE SO SWEET.
THANKS.
YEAH.
WOW, YOU SEEM TO BE DOING SO MUCH BETTER. THAT'S GREAT.
HOW ARE THINGS GOING?
GOOD.
OKAY. IT FEELS LIKE IT'S...
EVERYTHING'S BEEN ABOUT ME LATELY.
SO WHAT'S HAPPENING WITH YOU?
OH. WELL, ACTUALLY, WE WERE JUST TALKING
ABOUT ME NOT GOING TO ROSS' WEDDING.
OH.
IT JUST MIGHT BE TOO HARD
GIVEN THE HISTORY AND ALL THAT.
WOW, THIS REMINDS ME OF THE TIME
WHEN I WAS, UM, LIVING ON THE STREET
AND THIS GUY OFFERED TO BUY ME FOOD
IF I SLEPT WITH HIM.
BUT... H HOW IS THIS LIKE THAT?
WELL, LET'S SEE...
IT'S NOT REALLY... LIKE THAT
BECAUSE, YOU SEE, THAT WAS AN ACTUAL PROBLEM
AND, UM, YOURS IS JUST LIKE, YOU KNOW
A BUNCH OF, YOU KNOW, HIGH SCHOOL CRAP
THAT NOBODY REALLY GIVES... YOU KNOW.
WELL, I'M, I'M SORRY.
I GUESS I JUST THOUGHT...
ALL RIGHT, HERE COME THE WATERWORKS.
OH! I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M GOING TO DO.
I CALLED THE COMPANY THAT SENT HER
AND THEY DON'T CARE.
THEN I CALLED 911, AND THEY YELLED AT ME.
IF THIS ISN'T AN EMERGENCY, THEN WHAT IS?
I'LL TELL YOU, JOE, I REALLY WANT TO HELP YOU OUT
BUT I GOT PLANS TO GO SEE TITANIC
SO I'VE GOT TO CALL 911 TO FIND OUT WHAT TIME IT STARTS.
HEY, GUYS.
HEY. HEY.
I JUST WANTED TO THANK YOU AGAIN FOR LAST NIGHT.
WHAT A GREAT PARTY.
AND THE GUYS FROM WORK HAD A BLAST.
YOU KNOW, ONE OF THEM HAD NEVER BEEN TO A BACHELOR PARTY BEFORE.
YEAH, AND ANOTHER ONE HAD NEVER BEEN TO A PARTY BEFORE.
SO, UH, HEY, THAT, THAT WEDDING RING
HUH?
MAN, THAT IS NICE.
YEAH, RIGHT?
I WAS, UH, I WAS THINKING
I MIGHT PICK ONE OF THOSE BABIES UP FOR MYSELF.
WHERE MIGHT ONE GET ONE OF THOSE?
THAT RING?
WHEN MY GRANDMOTHER FIRST CAME TO THIS COUNTRY
THAT RING AND THE CLOTHES ON HER BACK
WERE ALL SHE HAD WITH HER.
SO YOU MIGHT SAY THAT THE RING IS IRREPLACEABLE.
MMM!
OH, ABSOLUTELY.
IT'S BEEN IN MY FAMILY FOR GENERATIONS
AND EVERY BRIDE WHO'S WORN IT
HAS LIVED A LONG AND HAPPY LIFE.
SO YOU MIGHT SAY IT'S A MAGIC RING.
THE STRIPPER STOLE IT.
HUH?
WHAT?
WHAT WHAT DID YOU JUST...?
I THINK I HEARD WHAT HE SAID.
I BELIEVE IT WAS...
OH, YES: "THE STRIPPER STOLE THE RING."
MY... MY RING?
MY MY WEDDING RING?
THE THE STRIPPER STOLE MY WEDDING RING?
H HOW? HOW HOW COULD THIS HAPPEN?
WELL, I THINK IT ALL STARTED WHEN YOU SAID
"HEY, JOEY, WHY DON'T YOU BE MY BEST MAN?"
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT, FINE.
I'M GOING TO CALL THE COPS.
DUDE, I I SCREWED UP.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO TURN ME IN.
NOT ON YOU.
ON THE STRIPPER.
OH, YEAH, WELL, I ALREADY DID THAT.
THEY SAID THEY'RE GOING TO LOOK INTO IT
RIGHT AFTER THEY SOLVE ALL THE MURDERS.
OKAY. WELL, THEN
WE'LL WE'LL CALL THE COMPANY THAT SENT HER.
I DID THAT, TOO. THEY WOULDN'T
GIVE ME HER REAL NAME OR HER NUMBER.
THEY SAID IF I BOTHERED THEM AGAIN
THEY'D CALL THE POLICE.
I SAID, "YOU TALK TO THE POLICE
YOU TELL THEM I'M MISSING A RING."
SO WHAT, JOEY?
W WHAT, WHAT ARE YOU TELLING ME?
THAT THERE'S NOTHING WE CAN DO?
HOW COULD THIS HAPPEN?!
LOOK, ROSS, I AM SO, SO SORRY.
I I...
WELL, WHAT IF WE JUST, UH, CALLED HER, USED A FAKE NAME
AND HAD HER COME TO MY OFFICE?
THAT SOUNDS LIKE FUN, BUT WE GOT A RING TO FIND!
HERE'S YOUR TEA, PHOEBE.
MMM. IT'S SO GOOD.
OH, THANKS . THAT'S SWEET.
SO GLAD YOU LIKE IT.
WHAT? WHAT? SHE MADE THE TEA.
NO. I... I THINK I JUST HAD A CONTRACTION.
YOU WHAT? OH, MY GOD.
YEAH, I THOUGHT I FELT O NE A COUPLE MINUTES AGO
AND NOW I KNOW THAT DEFINITELY WAS ONE.
OH, YOU CAN'T HAVE THE BABY HERE.
I HAVEN'T STERILIZED THE APARTMENT
SINCE THE GUYS MOVED OUT.
OKAY, IT'S OKAY WE'RE GOING TO BE OKAY.
YOU KNOW WHAT? IT'S OKAY.
I'M GOING TO BOIL SOME WATER AND JUST RIP UP SOME SHEETS.
OH. IT'S ALL RIGHT.
IT'S PROBABLY FALSE LABOR.
THEY SAID THAT COULD HAPPEN NEAR THE END
SO JUST... SOMEBODY GET THE BOOK.
RACHEL, GET THE BOOK.
THE BOOK.
OKAY, OKAY.
HERE.
THE BIBLE?
I DON'T KNOW!
ALL RIGHT. OKAY.
OKAY. THIS IS GREAT.
UH, CHANDLER, YOU GET BEHIND THE DESK
AND AND WHEN SHE COMES IN, HOPEFULLY
SHE WON'T RECOGNIZE YOU
BECAUSE... WELL, WHY WOULD SHE?
UH, OKAY
AND THEN YOU BUZZ ROSS AND I.
AND YOU BE MR. GONZALES AND I'LL BE MR. WONG.
DIVERSE.
ANYBODY CALL FOR SECURITY?
OKAY, OKAY.
YOU BE COOL.
OKAY.
WHICH ONE OF YOU GUYS IS GUNTHER CENTRAL PERK?
HEY, JOEY.
G?! WHERE'S MY RIN
MY DEAD GRANDMOTHER'S WEDDING RING--
WHERE IS IT?! WHERE IS IT?!
WAY TO BE COOL, MAN.
HEY, WHAT'S HE TALKING ABOUT?
THERE WAS A RING IN A BOX ON MY NIGHTSTAND.
AFTER YOU LEFT, IT WAS GONE.
YOU GUYS THINK I STOLE SOME RING?
WE KNOW YOU TOOK IT
SO JUST SAVE YOURS ELF THE TIME AND CONFESS.
OKAY. WHO ARE YOU, THE HARDY BOYS?
LOOK, I DON'T NEED
TO STEAL SOME STUPID RING, ALL RIGHT?
I MAKE $1,600 DOLLAR A WEEK DOING WHAT I DO.
ANY OF YOU GUYS MAKE THAT?
MARRY ME.
I DON'T GET IT.
IT WAS IN MY ROOM ALL NIGHT.
IF SHE DIDN'T TAKE  IT AND I DIDN'T TAKE IT
AND YOU DIDN'T TAKE IT
THEN WHO DID?
SHH! WE'RE TRYING TO THINK.
HERE.
I STILL DON'T GET HOW YOU KNOW WHEN IT'S FALSE LABOR.
WELL, DO YOU SEE ANY BABIES?
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
OKAY, I GUESS. I MEAN...
I DON'T KNOW. IT'S...
I GUESS I KNOW IT'S GOING TO BE OVER SOON, SO...
BUT ISN'T THAT A GOOD THING?
I MEAN, YOU SAID YOU WERE SICK OF THIS.
I KNOW.
IT'S JUST, YOU KNOW, USUALLY
WHEN YOU'RE DONE WITH THE PREGNANT THING
THEN, YOU KNOW, YOU GET TO DO THE MOM THING.
I'M GOING TO BE, YOU KNOW, SITTING AROUND
IN MY LEATHER PANTS DRINKING TEQUILA.
SOME MOMS DO THAT.
OKAY, THAT'S EVEN SADDER.
LOOK, I I KNOW
I KNOW WHAT I GOT MYSELF INTO, YOU KNOW.
IT'S JUST THAT NOW THAT THEY'RE IN ME, IT'S LIKE...
IT'S LIKE I KNOW THEM, YOU KNOW, AND AND...
IT'S JUST NOT... IT'S NOT GOING TO BE EASY
WHEN, YOU KNOW, THESE LITTLE BABIES HAVE TO GO AWAY.
OH, I KNOW, SWEETIE, BUT IT'S NOT LIKE
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO HAVE ANYTHING.
I MEAN, YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE NIECES AND NEPHEWS.
IN SOME WAYS, THAT'S EVEN BETTER.
YEAH. OKAY.
NO, REALLY. REALLY, PHEEBS.
I MEAN, YOU'RE NOT GOING TO BE THE ONE WORRYING
ABOUT SAVING FOR COLLEGE
OR YELLING AT THEM WHEN THEY'RE BAD, YOU KNOW
OR DECIDING TO PUT THEM ON RITALIN
WHEN THEY JUST WON'T CALM DOWN.
YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, YOU'RE GOING TO BE THE ONE THAT THEY COME TO
WHEN THEY WANT TO RUN AWAY FROM HOME
AND THE ONE THEY TALK TO ABOUT SEX.
YOU JUST GET TO  BE COOL AUNT PHOEBE.
"COOL AUNT PHOEBE."
I AM PRETTY COOL.
OH.
YEAH, AND YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE?
OH, MY GOD, ARE THEY GOING TO LOVE YOU.
THEY ARE GOING TO LOVE ME.
OH.
THANKS, YOU GUYS.
HONEY. AWW.
AGAIN.
OH, SWEETIE.
MMM...
THANKS. OH!
WHAT? OH, GOD. WHAT?
JUST KIDDING.
OH.
WHAT?  OH, MY GOD.
GOTCHA AGAIN. YOU'RE SO EASY.
IF ANYTHING SHOULD HAPPEN TO HIM...
JOEY, THE VET SAID IT'S A SIMPLE PROCEDURE.
SO?
THINGS COULD GO WRONG. YOU DON'T KNOW.
WHAT IF HE DOESN'T MAKE IT?
HE WILL,JOE.
YEAH, BUT WHAT IF HE DOESN'T?
K. HE'S SUCH A GOOD DUC
?? ...AND TELL ME ??
?? WHEN WILL OUR EYES MEET???
?? WHEN CAN I TOUCH YOU? ??
?? WHEN WILL THIS STRONG YEARNING END? ??
?? AND WHEN WILL I HOLD YOU??
?? AGAIN? ??
I'M JUST SO WORRIED ABOUT HIM, YOU KNOW.
SOMEBODY LOSE A RING?
OH!
OH, MY GOD!
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
HOW'S THE DUCK? HE'S DOING JUST FINE.
HE'S RESTING NOW, BUT YOU CAN SEE HIM IN A LITTLE BIT.
OH, GREAT.
HEY, LISTEN, ROSS, THANKS FOR BEING SO COOL ABOUT THIS.
NO, THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
NO, IT'S NOT.
YOU MADE ME YOUR BEST MAN
AND I TOTALLY LET YOU DOWN.
HEY, COME ON. IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
YEAH, IT IS.
YOU WOULDN'T HAVE LOST THE RING, RIGHT?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
ROSS, YOU WERE RIGHT FROM THE START.
HE SHOULD BE YOUR BEST MAN.
NO. YOU SHOULD.
LOOK, DON'T ARGUE WITH ME.
HEY, HEY, I GET TO CHOOSE MY BEST MAN.
AND I WANT BOTH YOU GUYS.
REALLY?
HEY, BOTH YOU GUYS SHOULD BE UP THERE WITH ME.
I MEAN, YOU TWO ARE... ARE MY...
I MEAN, I'M LUCKY TO HAVE JUST ONE GOOD...
TH THANKS, MAN.
I GOT TO GO CHECK SOMETHING OVER HERE.
WHAT A BABY.
TOTAL WUSS.
HEY, HOW COME YOU'RE GETTING NANA'S RING?
WELL, MOM GAVE IT TO ME.
SHE SAID SOMETHING ABOUT IT BEING A WEDDING RING
AND THAT YOU MAY NOT NEED...
ONE.
HMM.
I REALLY DIDN'T NEED TO TELL YOU ALL THAT.
YEAH, I DON'T REALLY THINK IT'S FAIR.
I MEAN, I ALWAYS LOVED THAT RING.
OH, MON, I'M SORRY. I'D LET YOU HAVE IT
BUT EMILY'S GOTTEN REALLY ATTACHED TO IT.
ALL RIGHT.
THANKS.
HERE YOU GO.
HEY, EMILY, DID YOU KNOW THAT
THAT RING SPENT TWO DAYS IN A DUCK'S COLON?