IT SEEMS LIKE ALL OF A SUDDEN
SO MUCH IS HAPPENING.
I KNOW. ROSS IS GETTING MARRIED...
PHOEBE'S... MAKING PEOPLE.
EVERYBODY'S DOING STUFF.
AND WE JUST SIT HERE.
IF I DIED, THE ONLY WAY
PEOPLE WOULD EVEN KNOW THAT I WAS HERE
WOULD BE BY THE ASS PRINT ON THIS CHAIR.
WHAT ARE WE DOING?
WASTING... OUR LIVES.
I MEANT FOR LUNCH.
LOOK, WE HAVE TO DO SOMETHING, OKAY?
SOMETHING HUGE.
WE COULD CLIMB MT. EVEREST.
NO. NOT SOMETHING STUPID-- SOMETHING HUGE.
NO, NO, I SAW AN AD FOR THIS VIDEO.
PEOPLE CLIMB THAT THING EVERY DAY.
WE COULD TOTALLY DO THAT.
WHY NOT? I MEAN, IT'S JUST... IT'S JUST CLIMBING.
IT'S JUST... IT'S JUST STEEP.
YEAH.
WE'RE GOING TO EVEREST, OKAY?
IT'D BE NICE TO LEAVE AN ASS PRINT ON EVEREST.
HEY. HEY.
HEY, WHAT'S UP?
WE'RE GOING TO CLIMB MT. EVEREST.
YEAH, BABY!
REALLY?
I LOOKED INTO THAT.
YEAH, BUT I MEAN, IT COSTS, LIKE, $60,000 DOLLAR
AND, YOU KNOW, YOU COULD DIE
AND... YOU WOULD DIE.
OH... WELL.
WE COULD GET THAT EVEREST VIDEO THOUGH.
YEAH, WE COULD DO THAT
WITHOUT, YOU KNOW, RISKING OUR LIVES AT ALL.
AND WHILE WE'RE DOWN AT THE VIDEO STORE
YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE WE COULD RENT?
DIE HARD.
OH, BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
I JUST REMEMBERED THAT EVEREST THING
IS ONLY AVAILABLE THROUGH MAIL ORDER.
OH, WELL.
SO YOU GUYS WILL STAY HERE AND HANG OUT WITH ME?
YEAH. YEAH.
BUT I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING.
ONE OF THESE DAYS, WE'RE GOING TO GET OFF OUR BUTTS
AND RENT DIE HARD AGAIN.
YEAH, WE ARE!
WOW.
THAT WAS FAST.
IT USUALLY TAKES ME TWO HOURS
TO GET BEN TO GO DOWN FOR HIS NAP.
HE'S SUCH A LITTLE SWEETHEART.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT HE JUST SAID?
WHAT? GOOD NIGHT, MOMMY.
OH... YEAH. THAT'S CAUSE HE'S GOT LOTS OF MOMMIES.
YEAH, IN FACT
IT'S KIND OF BECOME HIS WORD FOR WOMAN.
AH.
SO WHAT DID WE DECIDE?
DOES YOUR UNCLE NATHAN GET AN INVITE OR NOT?
OH, GOD, NOBODY LIKES HIM.
AND HE'S SO CHEAP.
I MEAN, HE'D NEVER FLY TO LONDON IN A MILLION YEARS.
YEAH, INVITE HIM.
HEY, DID I DO THESE NEAT ENOUGH?
YEAH. THEY'RE FINE.
YEAH?
IF ANYONE ASKS
WE'LL SAY THAT BEN ADDRESSED THEM.
OH. SO YOU INVITED RACHEL, THEN?
T? SURE. WHY NO
REALLY?
YEAH.
WELL, DON'T THINK I'D BE COMFORTABLE
HAVING ANY OF MY OLD LOVERS THERE.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
DO YOU THINK MAYBE  WE SHOULDN'T INVITE HER?
OH, NO, NO, ROSS.
YOU KNOW I ABSOLUTELY ADORE RACHEL.
IT'S JUST THAT...
WELL, I THOUGHT IT MIGHT BE A BIT AWKWARD FOR YOU.
BUT IT'S ABSOLUTELY YOUR DECISION.
MORE TEA?
YEAH. SURE.
EARL GREY?
HUH? FINE.
INVITE WHOEVER YOU WANT.
I DON'T WANT TO BE SINGLE, OKAY?
I JUST, I JUST , I JUST WANT
TO BE MARRIED AGAIN.
AND I JUST WANT A MILLION DOLLARS!
RACHEL?
OH, GOD, MONICA, HI.
THANK GOD.
OKAY, EVERYBODY...
THIS IS RACHEL , ANOTHER LINCOLN HIGH SURVIVOR.
THIS IS EVERYBODY.
THIS IS CHANDLER
AND PHOEBE
AND JOEY AND...
YOU REMEMBER MY BROTHER ROSS? SURE!
HEY. HI. OH!
OH, GOD!
YOU KNOW, YOU PROBABLY DIDN'T KNOW THIS
BUT BACK IN HIGH SCHOOL, I HAD A, UM...
MAJOR CRUSH ON YOU.
I KNEW.
YOU DID? OH.
I ALWAYS FIGURED YOU JUST THOUGHT
I WAS MONICA'S GEEKY OLDER BROTHER.
I DID.
OH!
LISTEN, DO YOU THINK--
AND TRY NOT TO LET MY INTENSE VULNERABILITY
BECOME ANY KIND OF A FACTOR HERE--
BUT DO YOU THINK
IT WOULD BE OKAY IF I ASKED YOU OUT SOMETIME, MAYBE?
YEAH.
MAYBE.
OKAY.
OKAY, MAYBE I WILL.
SEE, I SEE, UH...
BIG PASSION IN YOUR FUTURE.
REALLY?
I DO.
OH, ROSS, YOU'RE SO GREAT.
OH...
AH...
IT'S NEVER GOING TO HAPPEN.
YEAH, I'VE A QUESTION.
LOOK, UH, ACTUALLY, NOT SO MUCH A QUESTION
AS MORE OF A GENERAL WONDERING... MENT.
OKAY?
OKAY.
UM, WELL, FOR A WHILE NOW, I'VE BEEN WANTING TO, UM...
OH...
YES, YES.
THAT'S THAT'S RIGHT. LOOK AT
THAT LITTLE KITTY!
WHAT?
?? TOP OF THE WORLD LOOKIN' ??
?? DOWN ON CREATION ??
?? AND THE ONLY EXPLANATION I CAN FIND... ??
LISTEN, IF YOU WANT THIS CART
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO TAKE ME WITH IT!
YES!
DID YOU SEE THAT!?
YOU WERE INCREDIBLE!
A BRAND NEW WOMAN, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN.
I COULD NOT HAVE DONE THIS WITHOUT YOU.
NO, IT'S JUST...
OKAY, UM, UH...
MORE CLOTHES IN THE DRYER?
OH!
I'M FINE. I'M FINE.
YOU HAD NO RIGHT TO TELL ME
YOU EVER HAD FEELINGS FOR ME.
WHAT?
I WAS DOING GREAT WITH JULIE
BEFORE I FOUND OUT ABOUT YOU.
I WAS DOING GREAT BEFORE I FOUND OUT ABOUT YOU.
YOU THINK IT'S EASY FOR ME TO SEE YOU WITH JULIE?
THE POINT IS, I... I DON'T NEED THIS RIGHT NOW.
OKAY? IT'S IT'S TOO LATE.
I'M WITH SOMEBODY ELSE; I'M HAPPY.
THIS SHIP HAS SAILED.
FINE. GO AND DO THAT.
FINE. FINE.
I DON'T NEED YOUR STUPID SHIP!
GOOD.
OH!
ROSS, DO YOU REALIZE THIS IS THE FIRST TIME IN MY LIFE
I'M DOING SOMETHING I ACTUALLY CARE ABOUT?
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME IN MY LIFE
I'M DOING SOMETHING THAT I'M ACTUALLY GOOD AT?
IF YOU DON'T GET THAT...
HEY, I GET THAT.
I GET THAT BIG TIME, AND I'M HAPPY FOR YOU
BUT I'M TIRED OF HAVING A RELATIONSHIP
WITH YOUR ANSWERING MACHINE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO ANYMORE.
WELL, NEITHER DO I!
IS THIS ABOUT MARK?
OH, MY GOD!
OKAY, IT'S NOT.
I CANNOT KEEP HAVING
THIS SAME FIGHT OVER AND OVER AGAIN, ROSS.
NO, YOU'RE MAKING THIS TOO HARD!
I'M MAKING THIS TOO HARD?
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO?
I DON'T KNOW! I DON'T KNOW!
LOOK, MAYBE WE SHOULD JUST TAKE A BREAK.
YOU'RE RIGHT. LET'S TAKE A BREAK.
LET'S COOL OFF, OKAY?
LET'S GET SOME FROZEN YOGURT OR SOMETHING.
NO...
A BREAK FROM US.
DO I KNOW WHY WE'RE RUSHING?
YEAH. YOU KNOW THE GIRLFRIEND
I TOLD YOU ABOUT LAST NIGHT?
WELL, IT TURNS OUT
THAT SHE WANTS TO GET BACK TOGETHER WITH ME...
OH, I FOUND IT!
THAT'S SO GREAT FOR YOU GUYS!
YEAH.
GOOD LUCK WITH YOUR GIRLFRIEND.
OH, THANK YOU.
I... HEY!
RACHEL!
HI!
OH... YOU GOT MY MESSAGE, HUH?
YEAH. OH, YOU ARE RIGHT ON TIME!
SO, WHAT DO YOU SAY-- CAN I BE YOUR GIRLFRIEND AGAIN?
YES, YOU CAN, VERY MUCH.
AH...!
I WANT YOU TO LEAVE. JUST GET OUT!
I WANT TO STAY. I WANT TO TALK ABOUT THIS.
ALL RIGHT. HOW WAS SHE?
UH OH.
WH WHAT?
WAS SHE GOOD?
DON'T ANSWER THAT.
ROSS, YOU SAID
YOU WANTED TO TALK ABOUT IT.
LET'S TALK ABOUT IT! HOW WAS SHE?
SHE WAS...
AWFUL.
HORRIBLE. NOT GOOD.
NOTHING COMPARED TO YOU.
SHE WAS DIFFERENT.
UH OH! OOH!
GOOD DIFFERENT?
NOBODY LIKES CHANGE.
I...
JUST STOP THAT!
WHAT? OKAY! OKAY!
THE WAY YOU OWNED UP TO EVERYTHING
IT JUST SHOWED ME HOW MUCH YOU'VE GROWN, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, MY MOM NEVER THOUGHT THIS WOULD WORK OUT.
SHE WAS ALL, "ONCE A CHEATER, ALWAYS A CHEATER."
MM HMM.
OH... I JUST WISH
WE HADN'T LOST THOSE FOUR MONTHS.
BUT IF TIME WAS WHAT YOU NEEDED
JUST TO GAIN A LITTLE PERS PEC TIVE...
THAT'S...
WE WERE ON A BREAK!
YOU SEEM TO REALLY LIKE HER.
YEAH, BUT WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?
WE BOTH AGREED IT WAS GOING TO BE
A TWO WEEK THING, YOU KNOW-- NO COMMITMENT.
ROSS, THAT GIRL JUST SPENT THE ENTIRE EVENING
TALKING TO YOUR FRIENDS
YOU ASKING TO HEAR  STORIES ABOUT
LOOKING THROUGH MONICA'S PHOTO ALBUMS...
I MEAN, YOU DON'T DO THAT
IF YOU'RE JUST IN IT FOR TWO WEEKS.
YOU THINK? HUH.
YOU'VE GOT, LIKE, 14 HOURS
UNTIL SHE HAS TO BE AT THE AIRPORT
AND YOU'RE SITTING HERE IN A HALLWAY WITH A...
28 YEAR OLD CHEERLEADER WITH A FAT LIP.
HEY, YOU'RE RIGHT.
YEAH.
OH, THIS IS SO AMAZING.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
MY BROTHER'S GETTING MARRIED AND IN LONDON.
I MEAN, IT'S SO ROMANTIC.
HEY, PRETTY SMART.
TISSUE PAPER.
YOU'RE AT THE WEDDING, YOU HAVE TO CRY...
"HANDKERCHIEF?"
"NO. I GOT MY INVITATION."
OH, LOOK! ISN'T THIS ADORABLE?
ROSS LET BEN ADDRESS MINE.
HELLO.
HEY. HEY.
HEY, DID YOU GET YOUR INVITATION
TO ROSS'S WEDDING?
NO.
WELL, DON'T WORRY, MAN.
I GET TO BRING A GUEST.
WE'LL SHOW HIM.
SO JEALOUS YOU'RE ALL GOING.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I NEVER KNEW
THAT YOU CAN'T FLY IN YOUR THIRD TRIMESTER.
I DIDN'T KNOW EITHER.
I KNEW THAT.
SO DIDN'T KNOW THAT
BUT YOU SHOULD SEE YOUR FACES.
HI, GUYS. WHAT'S UP?
HEY. HEY.
WE'RE HANGING OUT.
WHAT'S THIS?
IS THIS ROSS'S WEDDING INVITATION?
SEE, MAYBE THAT'S THE ONE WE SHOULD HAVE ACTUALLY HIDDEN.
OH, NO, NO. GUYS, COME ON.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO THAT.
I'M HAPPY FOR HIM.
I AM. I REALLY... I'M... I...
I'LL WORK ON IT.
I'M SORRY, HONEY.
MMM.
RACHEL, YOU'RE GOING TO COME THOUGH, AREN'T YOU?
NEY OH, HO
I DON'T KNOW. I...
THIS ISN'T ONE OF THOSE, YOU KNOW
"SHE DOESN'T COME, WE DON'T COME," RIGHT?
BECAUSE I ALREADY BOUGHT MY TICKET...
DUDE, YOU'RE NOT EVEN INVITED.
YOU KNOW WHAT WOULD BE REAL WEIRD...
IS IF YOU WEREN'T THERE.
JUST SAY YOU'LL THINK ABOUT IT, OKAY?
NO, I'LL THINK ABOUT IT. YEAH.
WHO'S THIS FROM?
OH, THAT'S ROSS'S.
OH.
OH, MY GOD.
HE REMEMBERED!
REMEMBERED WHAT?
IT WAS LIKE MONTHS AGO.
WE WERE WALKING  BY THIS ANTIQUE STORE
AND I SAW THIS PIN IN THE WINDOW
AND I TOLD HIM THAT IT WAS JUST LIKE
ONE MY GRANDMOTHER HAD WHEN I WAS A LITTLE GIRL.
OH, I CAN'T BELIEVE HE REMEMBERED.
THIS MUST HAVE COST HIM A FORTUNE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HE DID THIS.
ROSS? REMEMBER BACK IN COLLEGE
WHEN HE FELL IN LOVE WITH CAROL
AND BOUGHT HER
THAT RIDICULOUSLY EXPENSIVE CRYSTAL DUCK?
WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY?
OH... MY GOD.
Flight 457
from Beijing now arriving.
OH, MY GOD.
ROSS AND I WERE IN GRAD SCHOOL.
WE HAVEN'T SEEN EACH OTHER
SINCE THEN.
WELL, I LAND IN CHINA.
GUESS WHO'S IN CHARGE OF THE DIG.
JULIE!
JULIE, ISN'T THAT GREAT?
I MEAN, ISN'T THAT JUST
KICK YOU IN THE CROTCH, SPIT ON YOUR NECK FANTASTIC?
OH, THAT IS SO SWEET.
NO...
NO, OKAY.
NO, YOU HANG UP.
NO, YOU... OKAY.
OKAY.
ONE, TWO, THREE.
WELL, YOU DIDN'T HANG UP EITHER.
SHE DIDN'T HANG UP. SHE DIDN'T HANG UP.
OKAY, NO.  NO, YOU HANG UP.
YOU, YOU, YOU...
ROSS?
HI. IT'S RACHEL.
I'M JUST CALLING TO SAY THAT, UM, EVERYTHING'S FINE
AND I'M REALLY HAPPY FOR YOU
AND YOUR CAT.
SO, OBVIOUSLY, I AM OVER YOU.
I AM OVER YOU
AND THAT, MY FRIEND, IS WHAT THEY CALL "CLOSURE."
RACHEL, GOT A MESSAGE FROM YOU.
OH, MY GOD, ROSS, NO.
HANG UP THE PHONE.
GIVE ME THE PHONE.
GIVE ME THE GOD DAMNED PHONE!
YOU'RE OVER ME?
OH, GOD.
WHAT, YOU'RE, UH...
Y YOU'RE OVER ME?
WHEN WERE YOU...
UNDER ME?
WELL... BASICALLY...
LATELY, I'VE, UH...
I'VE, UH, SORT OF HAD FEELINGS FOR YOU.
OKAY, I NEED TO LIE DOWN.
HE BROKE UP WITH JULIE.
WELL, GO HUG HER, FOR GOD'S SAKES!
REALLY?
REALLY.
IT'S ALWAYS BEEN YOU, RACH.
OH, GOD.
OH... OH...
LISTEN, I'M SORRY, I HAD TO WORK TONIGHT.
OH, THAT'S OKAY.
YOU WERE WORTH THE WAIT.
OH.
AND I DON'T JUST MEAN TONIGHT.
?? I NEVER DREAMED ??
?? THAT I'D MEET SOMEBODY LIKE YOU ??
?? I NEVER DREAMED THAT I... ??
WHAT... AH...
OH, GOD!
OH, HONEY...
OH, IT'S OKAY.
OH, NO, YOU JUST ROLLED OVER THE JUICE BOX.
GUNTHER, PLEASE TELL ME
YOU DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING TO RACHEL
ABOUT ME AND THE GIRL FROM THE COPY PLACE.
I'M SORRY.
WAS I NOT SUPPOSED TO?
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO ENDED IT, REMEMBER?
YEAH, BECAUSE I WAS MAD AT YOU
NOT BECAUSE I STOPPED LOVING YOU.
YOU STILL LOVE ME?
NO.
WHAT DOES THIS MEAN?
WHAT ARE YOU...?
DO YOU WANT TO... GET BACK TOGETHER?
NO... MAYBE.
I DON'T...
I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST... I FEEL...
I CAN'T BELIEVE I EVEN THOUGHT
OF GETTING BACK TOGETHER WITH YOU.
WE ARE SO OVER!
OH... OH... UH...
FINE BY ME!
NOW AND HEY, JUST SO YOU K
IT'S NOT THAT COMMON
IT DOESN'T HAPPEN TO EVERY GUY
AND IT IS A BIG DEAL!
I KNEW IT!
Rachel's coming out.
Doesn't she look pretty, Jack?
OH, MY GOD!
THIS IS US GETTING READY FOR THE PROM.
OH!
WE DON'T HAVE TO WATCH THIS.
YEAH, WE DO.
COME ON! COME ON!
Get a shot of Monica.
WAIT. HOW DO YOU ZOOM OUT?
THERE SHE IS.
WHOA!
SHUT UP!
THE CAMERA ADDS TEN POUNDS.
SO, HOW MANY CAMERAS ARE ACTUALLY ON YOU?
Dad, turn it off!
IT IS OFF.
IT'S NOT.
RIGHT, ROSS?
OH, COME ON.
LOOKING GOOD, MR. KOTTER.
I CAN'T GO TO MY OWN PROM WITHOUT A DATE.
I CAN'T. IT'S TOO LATE.
IF YOU'RE NOT GOING, I DON'T WANT TO GO EITHER.
I HAVE A WONDERFUL IDEA.
YOU SHOULD TAKE RACHEL TO THE PROM.
WE'VE SEEN ENOUGH. LET'S TURN IT OFF.
NO, NO, I WANT TO SEE.
WELL, I'M NOT GOING TO WATCH.
Come on, kid.
LET'S GO.
ARE YOU HANDSOME.
LET'S SHOW THEM!
OKAY, DAD.
RACHEL, READY OR NOT
HERE COMES YOUR KNIGHT IN SHINING...
OH, NO.
BYE! DON'T WAIT UP!
OKAY, CHIP!
LET'S  GO.
OH, DEAR.
JACK, HOW DO I TURN THIS OFF?
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU DID THAT.
YEAH, WELL...
SEE? HE'S HER LOBSTER.
NO!
YOU'RE REALLY NOT GOING?
YEAH.
IT'S JUST GOING TO BE TOO HARD.
YOU KNOW, I MEAN, IT'S ROSS.
HOW CAN I WATCH HIM GET MARRIED?
YOU KNOW, IT'S JUST...
IT'S FOR THE BEST, YOU KNOW?
IT IS. IT'S...
PLUS, SOMEBODY'S GOT TO STAY HERE WITH PHOEBE.
YOU KNOW, SHE'S GOING TO PRETTY BIG BY THEN
AND SHE'LL NEED SOMEONE TO HELP HER TIE HER SHOES.
DRIVE HER TO THE HOSPITAL
IN CASE SHE GOES INTO LABOR...
YOU DON'T HAVE A CAR, AND YOUR LICENSE EXPIRED.
I KNOW.
YEAH, SEE, THERE'S SO MUCH TO DO
AND I HAVE SO LITTLE TIME TO DO IT IN.
ALL RIGHT, CHECK THIS OUT--
SAYS HERE THERE'S A PLACE YOU CAN GO
TO RENT VIDEOS OF ALL THE MUSEUMS.
"IT'S ALMOST AS GOOD AS BEING THERE."
IT'S BETTER.
YOU CAN'T GO TO A MUSEUM IN YOUR UNDERWEAR.
WELL, YOU COULD, BUT PROBABLY JUST THE ONE TIME.
I BET WE COULD GET VIDEOS OF ALL THE SIGHTS.
GET A VCR IN OUR HOTEL ROOM
WE'D NEVER EVEN HAVE TO GO OUTSIDE.
IF WE DO THAT, WE'VE GOT TO RENT DIE HARD.
OH HO, I BET THE BRITISH VERSION IS GOOD.