I'M TELLING YOU, ROSS, SHE WANTS YOU.
SHE BARELY KNOWS ME.
WE JUST LIVE IN THE SAME BUILDING.
ANY CONTACT?
SHE LENT ME AN EGG ONCE.
YOU'RE IN.
OH, RIGHT.
HI, ROSS.
HI, K K K...
COME ON, ROSS.
YOU GOT TO GET BACK IN THE GAME HERE, OKAY?
THE RACHEL'S NOT HAPPENING
YOUR EX WIFE'S A LESBIAN...
I DON'T THINK WE NEED A THIRD.
EXCUSE ME, COULD WE GET AN EGG OVER HERE
STILL IN THE SHELL? THANKS.
AN EGG?
YEAH. YOU'RE GOING TO GO UP TO HER AND SAY
"HERE'S YOUR EGG BACK.
I'M RETURNING YOUR EGG."
I THINK IT'S WINNING.
COME ON. I THINK IT'S INSANE.
SHE'LL LOVE IT.
THANK YOU.
HERE.
GO WITH THE EGG, MY FRIEND.
GO, GO, GO, GO, GO, GO.
IS IT GOING TO WORK?
NO WAY. IT'S SUICIDE.
THE MAN'S GOT AN EGG.
YOU CANNOT DO THIS.
WHAT? DO WHAT?
ROGER WANTS TO TAKE HER OUT TOMORROW NIGHT.
NO, PHEEBS! DON'T YOU REMEMBER WHY YOU DUMPED THE GUY?
BECAUSE HE WAS CREEPY.
AND MEAN, AND A LITTLE FRIGHTENING.
STILL, IT'S NICE TO HAVE A DATE ON VALENTINE'S DAY.
HI. HI.
PHOEBE, YOU CAN GO OUT WITH A CREEPY GUY
ANY NIGHT OF THE YEAR.
I KNOW I DO.
HI.
HI. HI.
WH WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING TOMORROW NIGHT?
ACTUALLY, TOMORROW NIGHT
KIND OF DEPENDS ON HOW TONIGHT GOES.
OH, UH, LISTEN, ABOUT TONIGHT...
NO, NO, NO, DON'T YOU DARE BAIL ON ME.
THE ONLY REASON SHE'S GOING OUT WITH ME
IS BECAUSE I SAID I COULD BRING A FRIEND FOR HER FRIEND.
YES, I KNOW, BUT HER FRIEND SOUNDS LIKE SUCH A...
PATHETIC MESS.
I KNOW, BUT...
COME ON, MAN.
SHE'S NEEDY, SHE'S VULNERABLE.
I'M THINKING... CHA CHING.
THANKS.
LOOK, YOU HAVE NOT BEEN OUT
WITH A WOMAN SINCE JANICE.
YOU'RE DOING THIS.
HI.
HI. HI.
SHE SAID YES.
OH, YES!
WAY TO GO, MAN!
STILL GOT THE EGG, HUH?
YEAH.
HOW DO I LOOK?
OH, UM... I DON'T CARE.
THERE'S LORRAINE.
OKAY, NOW REMEMBER--
NO TRADING.
YOU GET THE PRETTY ONE, I GET THE MESS.
HI, JOEY.
HEY.
WELL, WELL, LOOK WHAT YOU BROUGHT.
VERY NICE.
AND WHAT DID YOU BRING?
SHE'S CHECKING HER COAT.
JOEY, I'M GOING TO GO WASH THE CAB SMELL OFF MY HANDS.
WILL YOU GET ME A WHITE ZINFANDEL
AND A GLASS OF RED FOR JANICE.
JANICE?
NO.
OH... MY... GOD.
HEY, IT'S JANICE.
OKAY, I'M MAKING A BREAK FOR IT.
I'M GOING OUT THE WINDOW.
NO, NO, DON'T.
PLEASE, I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR, LIKE, FOREVER
TO GO OUT WITH LORRAINE.
JUST CALM DOWN.
CALM DOWN? CALM DOWN?
YOU SET ME UP WITH A WOMAN I DUMPED TWICE
IN THE LAST FIVE MONTHS!
HEY, CAN YOU STOP YELLING?
YOU'RE MAKING ME NERVOUS AND...
I CAN'T GO WHEN I'M NERVOUS.
I'M SORRY, I'M SORRY. YOU'RE RIGHT.
COME ON! DO IT! DO IT!
GO! COME ON!
OKAY, OKAY, ROGER WAS CREEPY
BUT HE WAS NOTHING
COMPARED TO PETE CARNEY.
WHICH ONE WAS PETE CARNEY?
PETE THE WEEPER?
REMEMBER THE GUY THAT USED TO CRY
EVERY TIME WE HAD SEX?
"WAS IT GOOD FOR YOU?"
YEAH, WELL, I'D TAKE A LITTLE CRYING ANY DAY
OVER HOWARD THE "I WIN" GUY.
"I WIN! I WIN!"
I WENT OUT
WITH THE GUY FOR TWO MONTHS.
I DIDN'T GET TO WIN ONCE.
HOW DO WE END UP WITH THESE JERKS?
WE'RE GOOD PEOPLE.
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE WE'RE LIKE SOME KIND OF MAGNETS.
I KNOW I AM.
THAT'S WHY I CAN'T WEAR A DIGITAL WATCH.
THERE'S MORE BEER, RIGHT?
OH! YOU KNOW MY FRIEND ABBY WHO SHAVES HER HEAD?
NO.
OKAY, WELL, I HAVE THIS FRIEND ABBY WHO SHAVES HER HEAD
BUT SHE SAYS THAT IF YOU WANT TO BREAK
THE BAD BOYFRIEND CYCLE
YOU CAN DO, LIKE, A CLEANSING RITUAL.
PHEEBS, THIS WOMAN IS VOLUNTARILY BALD.
YEAH. SO...
WE CAN DO IT TOMORROW NIGHT, GUYS.
IT'S VALENTINE'S DAY.
IT'S PERFECT.
OKAY. WELL, WHAT KIND OF RITUAL?
OKAY. WE CAN BURN THE STUFF THEY GAVE US.
OR...
OR... OR WE CAN CHANT AND DANCE AROUND NAKED.
YOU KNOW, WITH STICKS.
BURNING'S GOOD. BURNING'S GOOD.
I GOT STUFF TO BURN.
YOU KNOW...
EVER SINCE I WAS LITTLE
I'VE BEEN ABLE TO PICK UP QUARTERS
WITH MY TOES.
YEAH?
GOOD FOR YOU.
UH... QUARTERS OR ROLLS OF QUARTERS?
BY THE WAY, CHANDLER...
I CUT YOU OUT OF ALL MY PICTURES
SO IF YOU WANT, I HAVE A BAG WITH JUST YOUR HEADS.
THAT'S OKAY.
ARE YOU SURE? REALLY?
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, YOU COULD MAKE LITTLE PUPPETS OUT OF THEM
AND YOU COULD USE THEM IN YOUR THEATER OF CRUELTY.
WE CAN'T DO THAT.
WHAT? WHAT CAN'T YOU DO?
UH... CAN I TALK TO YOU FOR A SECOND OVER THERE?
UH... WE MIGHT BE LEAVING NOW.
TELL ME IT'S "YOU AND ME" WE.
SHE SAID SHE WANTS TO SLATHER MY BODY WITH STUFF
AND THEN LICK IT OFF.
I'M NOT EVEN SURE WHAT SLATHERING IS.
BUT I DEFINITELY WANT TO BE A PART OF IT.
OKAY, YOU CANNOT DO THIS TO ME.
YOU'RE RIGHT. I'M SORRY.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
CAN WE HAVE THREE CHOCOLATE MOUSSES TO GO, PLEASE?
I'M OUT OF HERE.
LOOK...
HERE'S MY CREDIT CARD.
DINNER'S ON ME.
I'M SORRY, CHANDLER.
I HOPE SHE THROWS UP ON YOU.
THANKS.
SO...
JUST US.
OH, WHAT A CRAPPY NIGHT.
ALTHOUGH... I HAVE ENJOYED THE FACT
THAT YOUR SHIRT'S BEEN STICKING OUT
OF YOUR ZIPPER EVER SINCE YOU CAME BACK
FROM THE BATHROOM.
EXCUSE ME.
HOW YOU DOING?
SO...
DO WE HAVE THE BEST FRIENDS OR WHAT?
JOEY'S NOT A FRIEND.
HE'S...
A STUPID MAN WHO LEFT US HIS CREDIT CARD.
ANOTHER DRINK? SOME DESSERT? A BIG SCREEN TV?
I WILL GO FOR THAT DRINK.
YOU GOT IT.
GOOD WOMAN?
COULD WE GET A BOTTLE
OF YOUR MOST OVERPRICED CHAMPAGNE?
EACH.
THAT'S RIGHT, EACH.
OH, AND A ROB ROY.
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED TO KNOW.
HAPPY VALENTINE'S DAY.
OH, I MISS YOU ALREADY.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THIS HAPPENED?
NO... NO!
AND YET IT DID.
GOOD BYE, JANICE.
KISS ME.
OH, CHANDLER, SORRY.
OH, CHANDLER, SORRY...
HEY, JANICE.
HI, MONICA.
OKAY, WELL, THIS WAS VERY SPECIAL.
RACH, COME SEE WHO'S OUT HERE.
WHAT'S GOING...
OH, MY GOD.
JANICE, HI.
HI.
JANICE IS GOING TO GO AWAY NOW.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
OH...
JOEY, LOOK WHO IT IS.
WHOA.
OH, GOOD, JOEY'S HOME NOW.
THIS IS SO MUCH FUN.
THIS IS LIKE A REUNION IN THE HALL.
OH, HI, ROSS. YEAH.
THERE'S SOMEONE I WANT YOU TO SAY HI TO.
HE JUST HAPPENED TO CALL.
HELLO, ROSS.
YES, THAT'S RIGHT.
IT'S ME.
HOW DID YOU KNOW?
I'M JUST SAYING IF DOGS DO EXPERIENCE JET LAG
THEN BECAUSE OF THE WHOLE
"SEVEN DOG YEARS TO ONE HUMAN YEAR" THING
THAT WHEN A DOG FLIES FROM NEW YORK TO LOS ANGELES
HE DOESN'T JUST LOSE THREE HOURS
HE LOSES, LIKE, A WEEK AND A HALF.
THAT'S FUNNY.
YEAH.
YOU KNOW, THEY SHOULD BE COOKING THE FOOD SOON.
OH, GOOD.
WHAT?
WHO ARE THEY?
THE BLONDE IS MY EX WIFE
AND THE WOMAN
TOUCHING HER IS HER
CLOSE, PERSONAL FRIEND.
YOU MEAN THEY'RE LOVERS?
IF YOU WANT TO PUT A LABEL ON IT.
WOW...
UH, ANYTHING ELSE I SHOULD KNOW?
NOPE, NOPE. THAT'S IT.
OH, AND SHE'S PREGNANT WITH MY BABY.
I ALWAYS FORGET THAT PART.
HELLOOO...
OKAY, SO NOW WE NEED SAGE BRANCHES
AND THE SACRAMENTAL WINE.
ALL I HAD IS OREGANO AND A FRESCA.
UM... THAT'S OKAY.
OKAY.
OOH...
ALL RIGHT.
NOW WE NEED THE SEMEN OF A RIGHTEOUS MAN.
OKAY, PHEEBS, YOU KNOW WHAT?
IF WE HAD THAT, WE WOULDN'T BE DOING THE RITUAL
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
CAN WE JUST START THROWING THINGS IN?
YEAH, OKAY.
OH.
OKAY.
OKAY, BARRY'S LETTERS.
ADAM RITTER'S BOXER SHORTS.
OH, AND I HAVE
THE RECEIPT FROM MY DINNER WITH
NOKULULE OON  AH.
HERE'S A PICTURE OF SCOTTY JARED NAKED.
OH, LET ME SEE.
HE'S WEARING A SWEATER.
NO.
EWW! EWW!
OH, WAIT-- WHO'S M.C.I. CARD IS THAT?
MINE. OH, SHOOT.
OKAY, REMEMBER THIS NUMBER: 9743...
OH... OH, WELL.
OKAY, AND HERE WE HAVE THE LAST OF PAOLO'S GRAPPA.
WAIT, RACHEL.
ISN'T THAT ALMOST PURE--
HOW CAN I DUMP THIS WOMAN ON VALENTINE'S DAY?
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU DUMPED HER ON NEW YEAR'S.
OH, MAN.
IN MY NEXT LIFE, I'M COMING BACK AS A TOILET BRUSH.
HELLO, FUNNY VALENTINE.
HI, JUST JANICE.
HELLO, JOEY
OUR LITTLE MATCHMAKER.
I COULD JUST KISS YOU ALL OVER AND I'M GONNA.
IF YOU DON'T DO IT, I WILL.
SO, UH...
SO, ARE YOU ACTUALLY FROM NEW YORK?
NO, NOT ORIGINALLY. I'M FROM...
OH, GOD!
OH, NO. I THOUGHT YOU SAID
THEY COULD SHOOT THE SPOT WITHOUT YOU.
I THOUGHT THEY COULD.
I MEAN, THE MAXI PADS WERE A PIECE OF CAKE.
YOU'D THINK THE MINI PADS WOULD BE THAT MUCH EASIER.
BUT IT'S VALENTINE'S DAY.
I KNOW, I KNOW, BUT IT'S MY JOB. FINE.
LOOK, I'LL TRY TO GET BACK AS SOON AS I CAN.
I'M SORRY.
WELL, ACTUALLY
I'M SPENDING MOST OF MY TIME TEACHING SCIENCE
WHICH IS FUNNY
BECAUSE THAT WASN'T EVEN MY MAJOR.
NOW, THAT IS FUNNY.
HEY, DO YOU THINK...
WOULD IT BE TOO WEIRD
IF I INVITED CAROL OVER TO JOIN US?
BECAUSE SHE'S, SHE'S... SHE'S ALONE NOW
AND AND PREGNANT AND AND SAD.
I GUESS.
ARE YOU SURE?
THANKS.
CAROL, WANT TO COME OVER AND JOIN US?
OH, NO, NO. I'M FINE, I'M FINE.
COME ON. THESE PEOPLE WILL SCOOCH DOWN.
COME ON.
COME ON, WILL YOU?
YOU GUYS WILL SCOOCH, WON'T YOU?
LET'S TRY SCOOCHING.
COME ON.
THANK YOU.
UH, KRISTEN RIGGS, THIS... THIS IS CAROL WILLICK.
CAROL, KRISTEN.
HOW DO YOU DO?
UM, OH, UH, CAROL TEACHES SIXTH GRADE.
AND, UH, KRISTEN...
KRISTEN DOES SOMETHING THAT, FUNNILY ENOUGH
WASN'T EVEN HER MAJOR.
THANKS, YOU GUYS, FOR COMING OVER.
NOT AT ALL. IT'S PRETTY MUCH OUR JOB.
THAT'S WHY WE GET THE COOL HATS.
WHAT DO WE GOT THERE?
PIECE OF SILK... BOXER SHORTS...
SOME GREETING CARDS...
LOOKS LIKE A HALF CHARRED PICTURE...
WOW, THAT GUY'S HAIRIER THAN THE CHIEF.
YOU KNOW, IT'S A REALLY FUNNY STORY
HOW THIS HAPPENED.
WELL, YOU SEE, I WAS TAKING OUT THE TRASH
AND PHOEBE WAS LIGHTING INCENSE...
IT'S ALL RIGHT. IT'S ALL RIGHT.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO EXPLAIN.
THIS ISN'T THE FIRST BOYFRIEND BONFIRE
THAT WE'VE SEEN GET OUT OF CONTROL.
YOU'RE OUR THIRD CALL TONIGHT.
REALLY?
OH, SURE. VALENTINE'S OUR BUSIEST NIGHT
OF THE YEAR.
LOOK, LADIES, IN THE FUTURE
WHEN YOU'RE BURNING YOUR EX BOYFRIEND'S STUFF
NUMBER ONE: MAKE SURE
YOU'RE IN A WELL VENTILATED AREA.
NUMBER TWO: IF YOU'RE GOING TO BE BURNING HIS CLOTHING
YOU'RE GOING TO WANT TO STAY AWAY
FROM YOUR SYNTHETIC FABRICS.
NUMBER THREE: TRY TO LET GO
OF THE ANGER AND LEARN TO LOVE YOURSELF.
I BROUGHT YOU SOMETHING.
IS IT LOADED?
OH, LITTLE CANDY HEARTS.
"CHAN AND JAN FOREVER."
I HAD THEM MADE SPECIAL.
OKAY, JANICE.
JANICE...
HEY, JANICE.
LOOK, THERE'S NO WAY FOR ME TO TELL YOU THIS.
AT LEAST, THERE'S NO NEWWAY FOR ME
TO TELL YOU THIS.
I JUST DON'T THINK THINGS ARE GOING TO WORK OUT.
THAT'S FINE.
IT IS?
MM HMM.
BECAUSE I KNOW THAT THIS ISN'T THE END.
OH, NO, YOU SEE, ACTUALLY IT IS.
NO, IT ISN'T
BECAUSE YOU WON'T LET THAT HAPPEN.
DON'T YOU KNOW IT YET?
YOU LOVE ME, CHANDLER BING.
OH, NO, I DON'T.
WELL, THEN, ASK YOURSELF THIS:
WHY DO YOU THINK WE KEEP ENDING UP TOGETHER?
NEW YEAR'S-- WHO INVITED WHO?
VALENTINE'S-- WHO ASKED WHO INTO WHOSE BED?
I DID, BUT...
YOU SEEK ME OUT.
SOMETHING DEEP IN YOUR SOUL CALLS OUT TO ME LIKE A FOGHORN.
JAN ICE, JAN ICE.
AND THEN YOU PUSH ME AWAY, YOU PULL ME BACK.
JAN ICE.
YOU WANT ME.
YOU NEED ME.
YOU CAN'T LIVE WITHOUT ME
AND YOU KNOW IT.
YOU JUST DON'T KNOW YOU KNOW IT.
SEE YA.
CALL ME.
NOT TRUE. I NEVER CALLED YOUR MOTHER A WOLVERINE.
YOU DID SO.
I SWEAR, I SWEAR TO...
HOW LONG HAS SHE BEEN IN THE BATHROOM?
UH, I DON'T THINK SHE'S IN THE BATHROOM.
HER COAT IS GONE.
WELL, MAYBE IT'S COLD IN THERE.
OH...
MAYBE I SCREWED UP
THE FIRST DATE I HAD IN NINE YEARS.
THAT COULD BE IT.
OH, GOD.
YOU KNOW, THIS IS STILL PRETTY HOT.
MUSHROOM.
OH, SMILE.
THEY WON'T ALL BE LIKE THIS.
SOME WOMEN MIGHT EVEN STAY THROUGH DINNER.
I'M SORRY. THAT'S NOT FUNNY.
IT'S JUST...
WELL, YOU KNOW THE WHOLE
"GETTING ON WITH YOUR LIFE" THING?
WELL, DO I HAVE TO?
I MEAN, I'M SITTING HERE WITH THIS CUTE WOMAN
AND, AND, AND SHE'S PERFECTLY NICE, YOU KNOW?
AND, BUT THAT THERE'S...
THAT'S IT.
AND, UM, AND THEN I'M HERE TALKING TO YOU
AND IT'S EASY, AND IT'S FUN AND I DON'T HAVE TO...
I KNOW.
YOU KNOW?
HERE'S A WACKY THOUGHT:
WHAT SAY YOU AND I GIVE IT ANOTHER SHOT?
ROSS...
NO, NO, NO. I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE GOING TO SAY.
YOU'RE A LESBIAN.
BUT LET'S...
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE JUST PUT THAT ASIDE FOR NOW, YOU KNOW?
LET'S JUST STICK A PIN IN IT, OKAY?
BECAUSE WE'RE GREAT TOGETHER.
YOU KNOW, YOU CAN'T DENY IT.
AND BESIDES
I'VE GOT A RING AT HOME THAT FITS YOU.
UH... I'VE GOT, UH, LOTS OF PICTURES
WITH BOTH OF US IN THEM, OKAY?
AND AND, BEST OF ALL... HEY, HEY--
YOU'RE CARRYING MY BABY.
I MEAN, HOW PERFECT IS THAT?
ROSS...
NOW, SEE, YOU KNOW, YOU KEEP SAYING THAT
BUT THERE'S SOMETHING RIGHT HERE.
I LOVE YOU.
OH, I LOVE YOU, TOO.
BUT...
NO BUT, NO BUT.
YOU KNOW THAT THING WE PUT OVER HERE
WITH THE PIN IN IT?
IT'S TIME TO TAKE THE PIN OUT.
YEAH.
YOU'LL FIND SOMEONE, I KNOW YOU WILL.
THE RIGHT WOMAN IS JUST WAITING FOR YOU.
THAT'S EASY FOR YOU TO SAY.
YOU FOUND ONE ALREADY.
ALL YOU NEED IS A WOMAN WHO LIKES MEN
AND YOU'LL BE SET.
NOT HER.
SO YOU GUYS REALLY JUST SLIDE DOWN A POLE, HUH?
ABSOLUTELY.
THAT'S SO COOL.
AND HOW DO YOU GET BACK UP?
WELL, WE RARELY HAVE TO RETURN FROM A FIRE AS QUICKLY.
UM, SO, UH, WOULD YOU GUYS, UH...
WELL, WOULD YOU LIKE TO, UH...
SOMETIME MAYBE, UH, MAYBE YOU'D LIKE TO...?
GO FOR A DRINK SOMETIME?
SURE, DRINK SOUNDS GOOD.
YEAH. WE GOT TO GO NOW
BUT WE GET OFF AROUND MIDNIGHT.
WHY DON'T WE PICK YOU UP THEN.
OKAY, GREAT.
SO, UM, WILL YOU BRING THE TRUCK?
I'LL EVEN LET YOU RING THE BELL.
WHOO HOO!
WE'LL SEE YOU LATER. BYE.
BYE. I CAN'T WAIT.
SEE YOU LATER.
OKAY, SEE YOU.
OH, MY GOD.
SEE, THERE YOU GO.
THE CLEANSING WORKED.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
THEY'RE NICE GUYS.
THEY'RE FIREMEN GUYS.
YOU GUYS TELL THEM YOU WERE MARRIED?
NO WAY. YOU KIDDING?
MY GIRLFRIEND DOESN'T KNOW.
I'M NOT GOING TO TELL THEM.