OH, GOSH.
I LOVE YOU.
INSURANCE?
OH, YEAH. CHECK IT.
DEFINITELY GOING TO WANT SOME OF THAT.
YOU DON'T HAVE INSURANCE?
WHY? HOW MUCH IS THIS GOING TO COST?
X RAYS ALONE COULD BE A COUPLE HUNDRED DOLLARS.
WHAT WILL WE DO?
THERE'S NOT MUCH WE CAN DO.
UM... UNLESS, UNLESS I USE YOURS.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
NOW, WAIT A SECOND.
WHO DID I JUST PUT
AS MY "IN CASE OF EMERGENCY" PERSON?
THAT'S INSURANCE FRAUD.
WELL, ALL RIGHT.
THEN FORGET IT.
MIGHT AS WELL JUST GO HOME.
OW! OW! OW!
OKAY. COME HERE.
I HATE THIS.
THANK YOU.
I LOVE YOU.
HI.
UM, I'M GOING TO NEED A NEW SET OF THESE FORMS.
WHY?
I AM REALLY AN IDIOT.
YOU SEE
I WAS FILLING OUT MY FRIEND'S FORM
AND INSTEAD OF PUTTING HER INFORMATION
I PUT MINE.
YOU ARE AN IDIOT.
YEP. THAT'S ME.
I'M THAT STUPID.
I HAD A DREAM LAST NIGHT
WHERE I WAS PLAYING FOOTBALL WITH MY KID.
THAT'S NICE.
NO. WITH HIM.
I'M ON THIS FIELD, AND THEY HIKE ME THE BABY.
AND I KNOW
I'VE GOT TO DO SOMETHING
BECAUSE THE TAMPA BAY DEFENSE
IS COMING RIGHT AT ME.
TAMPA BAY HAS A TERRIBLE TEAM.
RIGHT, BUT...
IT IS JUST ME AND THE BABY
SO I'M THINKING THEY CAN TAKE US.
AND SO, I, UH... I JUST HEAVE IT DOWNFIELD!
WHAT, ARE YOU CRAZY?! THAT'S A BABY!
HE SHOULD TAKE THE SACK?
ANYWAY, SUDDENLY I'M DOWNFIELD, AND I REALIZE THATI'MTHE ONE
WHO'S SUPPOSED TO CATCH HIM, RIGHT?
ONLY I KNOW THERE IS NO WAY I'LL GET THERE IN TIME.
SO I AM RUNNING AND I'M RUNNING
AND THAT IS WHEN I WOKE UP.
SEE, I AM SO NOT READY TO BE A FATHER.
HEY, YOU'RE GOING TO BE FINE.
YOU'RE ONE OF THE MOST CARING
MOST RESPONSIBLE MEN
IN NORTH AMERICA.
YOU'LL MAKE A GREAT DAD.
YEAH. YOU AND THE BABY JUST NEED BETTER BLOCKING.
HAVE EITHER ONE OF YOU GUYS
EVER BEEN TO THE RAINBOW ROOM?
IS IT REAL EXPENSIVE?
ONLY IF YOU ORDER STUFF.
I'M TAKING URSULA TONIGHT.
IT'S HER BIRTHDAY.
WHOA. WHAT ABOUT PHOEBE'S BIRTHDAY?
WHEN'S THAT?
UH...
TONIGHT.
AH, MAN.
WHAT ARE THE ODDS OF THAT HAPPENING?
YOU TAKE YOUR TIME.
THERE IT IS.
SO WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
WHAT CAN I DO?
LOOK, I DON'T WANT TO SCREW IT UP WITH URSULA.
AND YOUR FRIEND PHOEBE?
IF SHE'S MY FRIEND, HOPEFULLY SHE'LL UNDERSTAND.
WOULDN'T YOU GUYS?
MAN, IF YOU TRIED SOMETHING LIKE THAT
ON MY BIRTHDAY
YOU'D BE STARING AT THE BUSINESS END
OF A HISSY FIT.
YOU ADD A PINCH OF SAFFRON.
IT MAKES ALL THE DIFFERENCE.
OKAY.
UHH... MONICA.
YES.
YES, SHE IS.
HI.
THIS IS MY FRIEND RACHEL.
HI, RACHEL.
I'M DR. MITCHELL.
AND I'M HIS FRIEND, DR. ROSEN.
UH... I'M OKAY HERE.
ACTUALLY, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I DON'T MIND AT ALL.
WHY DON'T YOU GO TAKE YOUR BREAK?
NO, NO, THIS IS WHY I BECAME A DOCTOR.
ANKLES, AND STUFF LIKE THAT.
AREN'T YOU A LITTLE CUTE TO BE A DOCTOR?
EXCUSE ME?
I MEANT "YOUNG."
YOUNG TO BE A DOCTOR.
GOOD, RACH.
THANK YOU.
RIGHT.
SO HE SAID IT WAS JUST A SPRAIN
AND THAT WAS IT.
YOU LEFT OUT THE STUPID PART.
IT'S NOT STUPID.
THE VERY CUTE, CUTE, CUTE DOCTORS ASKED US OUT
FOR TOMORROW NIGHT, AND I SAID YES.
I THINK IT'S TOTALLY INSANE.
I MEAN, THEY WORK FOR THE HOSPITAL.
IT'S LIKE RETURNING TO THE SCENE
OF THE CRIME.
I SAY WE BLOW OFF THE DATES.
WHAT?!
MONICA, THEY ARE CUTE.
THEY ARE DOCTORS.
CUTE DOCTORS.
DOCTORS WHO ARE CUTE.
ALL RIGHT.
WHAT HAVE WE LEARNED SO FAR?
OH, GOD. OKAY.
SURPRISE!
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?
YOU SCARED THE CRAP OUT OF ME.
WAS THAT THE CAKE?
YEAH. YEP.
I GOT A LEMON SHMUSH.
COME ON. SHE'LL BE HERE ANY MINUTE.
OH, I HOPE IT'S OKAY.
"HAPPY BIRTHDAY, PEEHEE."
MAYBE WE CAN MAKE A "B" OUT OF ONE OF THOSE ROSES.
WE'LL JUST USE OUR SPECIAL CAKE TOOLS.
HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
SURPRISE!
OH! OH! OH!
THIS IS SO GREAT!
OH, MY GOD!
THIS WAS NOT AT ALL SCARY.
OH, LOOK-- "HAPPY BIRTHDAY, PEEHEE."
WHAT A STRANGE NEW NICKNAME.
I LIKE IT!
OH, MY GOD!
HI, EVERYBODY. HI, BETTY.
BETTY! HI!
YOU FOUND BETTY!
THIS IS SO GREAT.
OH, EVERYBODY I LOVE IS IN THE SAME ROOM, OH.
WHERE'S JOEY?
DID YOU SEE BETTY?
I'LL TELL YOU ONE THING-- I WOULDN'T MIND HAVING
A PIECE OF THIS SUN DRIED
TOMATO BUSINESS.
FIVE YEARS AGO, IF SOMEBODY HAD SAID TO ME
"HERE'S A TOMATO THAT LOOKS LIKE A PRUNE"
I'D HAVE SAID, "GET OUT OF MY OFFICE."
DAD, BEFORE I WAS BORN, DID YOU FREAK OUT AT ALL?
I'M NOT FREAKING OUT!
I'M JUST SAYING IF SOMEONE HAD COME TO ME...
DAD, DAD, DAD...
I'M TALKING ABOUT THE WHOLE BABY THING.
DID YOU EVER GET THIS SORT OF...
PANICKY, "OH, MY GOD, I'M GOING TO BE A FATHER"
KIND OF A THING?
NO.
WE JUST HAD KIDS BACK THEN.
WE DIDN'T THINK ABOUT IT.
WHAT ELSE COULD THE SUN DRY, I WONDER?
DAD, COME ON. KIDS.
RIGHT. LOOK
YOUR MOTHER DID THE WORK.
I WAS BUSY WITH THE BUSINESS.
I WASN'T AROUND THAT MUCH.
IS THAT WHAT THIS IS ABOUT?
NO, DAD. I WAS JUST WONDERING...
BECAUSE THERE'S TIME TO MAKE UP FOR THAT.
YOU ALWAYS WANTED TO GO TO THAT COLONIAL WILLIAMSBURG.
HOW ABOUT WE DO THAT?
THANKS, DAD, REALLY.
I JU... YOU KNOW, I JUST...
I JUST... I JUST NEEDED TO KNOW, UM...
WHEN DID YOU START TO FEEL LIKE A FATHER?
OH.
WELL, I GUESS IT MUST HAVE BEEN...
THE DAY AFTER YOU WERE BORN.
WE WERE IN THE HOSPITAL ROOM.
YOUR MOTHER WAS ASLEEP
AND THEY BROUGHT YOU IN
AND GAVE YOU TO ME.
YOU WERE THIS UGLY LITTLE RED THING.
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN
YOU GRABBED MY FINGER WITH YOUR WHOLE FIST
AND YOU SQUEEZED IT SO TIGHT.
AND THAT'S WHEN I KNEW.
SO YOU DON'T WANT TO GO
TO WILLIAMSBURG?
WE CAN GO TO WILLIAMSBURG.
EAT YOUR FISH.
RACHEL, THE CUTE DOCTORS ARE HERE.
OKAY, COMING.
HI. COME ON IN.
HI.
WE BROUGHT WINE.
IT'S FROM THE CELLARS
OF ERNEST AND TOVA BORGNINE.
SO, HOW COULD WE RESIST?
OH, THAT'S GREAT! LOOK AT THAT.
MONICA, HOW'S THE ANKLE?
IT'S...
WHY DON'T YOU TELL THEM?
AFTER ALL, IT IS YOUR ANKLE.
IT'S FEELING A LOT BETTER.
THANK YOU.
LISTEN, GUYS, SIT DOWN
AND WE'LL GET YOU SOME GLASSES.
OKAY.
STAT.
LISTEN. I'M THINKING
WHY DON'T WE JUST TELL THEM WHO WE REALLY ARE.
I REALLY THINK IT'LL BE FINE.
IT WILL NOT BE FINE.
WE'LL GET IN TROUBLE.
WOULD YOU STOP BEING SUCH A WUSS.
A WUSS?
EXCUSE ME FOR LIVING IN THE REAL WORLD.
SO?
SO THEY STILL SEEM NORMAL.
THEY ARE NORMAL.
BUT YOU HAVE TO ADMIT
EVERY TIME WE GO OUT WITH WOMEN
WE MEET AT THE HOSPITAL...
RELAX. LOOK AROUND.
THERE ARE NO PAGAN ALTARS.
NO PILES OF BONES IN THE CORNERS.
THEY'RE FINE.
GO LIKE THIS.
I SAID WE ARE NOT GOING TO DO IT.
SOMETIMES YOU CAN BE SUCH A BIG BABY.
I AM NOT A BABY.
SERIOUS. I MEAN, EVERY TIME...
YOU KNOW WHAT? WHAT?
YOU KNOW WHAT? WHAT?!
EVERY DAY, YOU ARE BECOMING
MORE AND MORE LIKE YOUR MOTHER.
EXCUSE ME.
HELLO! HERE WE GO!
THIS IS A GREAT PLACE.
HOW LONG HAVE YOU LIVED HERE?
THANKS. I'VE BEEN HERE ABOUT SIX YEARS.
AND RACHEL MOVED IN A FEW MONTHS AGO.
YEAH.
SEE, I WAS SUPPOSED TO GET MARRIED, BUT, UM...
I LEFT THE GUY AT THE ALTAR.
HMM.
REALLY?
YEAH.
YEAH, I KNOW IT'S PRETTY SELFISH
BUT, HEY, THAT'S ME.
WHY DON'T YOU TRY THE HUMMUS?
SO, MONICA, WHAT DO YOU DO?
UHH... I AM A CHEF AT A RESTAURANT UPTOWN.
GOOD FOR YOU.
YEAH, IT IS.
MOSTLY BECAUSE I GET TO BOSS PEOPLE AROUND
WHICH I JUST LOVE TO DO.
WELL, THIS HUMMUS IS GREAT.
GOD BLESS THE CHICK PEA.
OH, GOD.
I AM SO SPOILED.
THAT'S IT.
I SHOPLIFT.
THAT WAS YEARS AGO, AND YOU HAD NO IDEA
THAT LIPSTICK WAS IN YOUR POCKET.
DID I TELL YOU THAT I THINK I AM SO MUCH CUTER THAN I AM?
AND BY THE WAY
HAVE I MENTIONED THAT BACK IN HIGH SCHOOL
I WAS A COW?
I USED TO WET MY BED.
I USED MY BREASTS TO GET PEOPLE'S ATTENTION.
WE BOTH DO THAT.
MONICA AND RACHEL'S APARTMENT.
UH, JUST ONE SECOND.
UH, RACHEL--
IT'S YOUR DAD.
HI, DAD.
NO. IT'S ME.
LISTEN, DAD, I CAN'T TALK RIGHT NOW.
BUT THERE'S SOMETHING, UM...
THERE'S SOMETHING THAT
I'VE BEEN MEANING TO TELL YOU.
EXCUSE ME A SECOND.
REMEMBER BACK IN FRESHMAN YEAR?
BILLY DRESKIN AND I HAD SEX
ON YOUR BED.
DADDY... DADDY, WHY?
WHY WOULD I SLEEP WITH BILLY DRESKIN?
HIS FATHER TRIED TO PUT YOU OUT OF BUSINESS.
YOU ARE DEAD!
HEY, RACHEL, ARE THESE YOUR CONDOMS?
OH, NO. NO, THAT WAS JUST MONICA.
SHE'S DRUNK AGAIN.
UH, PHEEBS, I DON'T THINK "SCRUNCHY" IS A WORD.
WHY NOT? IF "CRUNCHY" IS A WORD
WHY ISN'T SCRUNCHY?
WELL, OKAY, THEN I'M USING THAT SAME ARGUMENT
FOR "FLIGAMENT."
ROSS, HE'S GOT THE REMOTE AGAIN.
GOOD.
MAYBE HE CAN SWITCH IT BACK.
MAYBE NOT.
OKAY, DADDY
DADDY, THAT'S THE OTHER LINE.
OKAY, NO, NOT EVEN IN MY BEDROOM.
OKAY. OKAY. BYE BYE.
HELLO?
UM... YEAH. UH...
OKAY, HOLD ON A SECOND.
LET ME JUST SEE IF SHE'S HERE.
IT'S THE WOMAN FROM THE HOSPITAL
ADMISSIONS OFFICE.
THERE'S A PROBLEM WITH THE FORM.
OH, GOD. WHAT DO WE DO?
I DON'T KNOW.
FIND OUT WHAT THEY WANT.
OKAY. NO, YOU DO IT.
HELLO. THIS IS MONICA.
YEAH?
OH.
OKAY.
YES, WE'LL BE RIGHT DOWN.
THANK YOU.
WHAT?
WE FORGOT TO SIGN
ONE OF THE ADMISSIONS FORMS.
OKAY, YOU WERE RIGHT.
THIS WAS NOT WORTH IT.
THANK YOU.
OKAY, LET ME JUST CHANGE.
"GARGE?"
NAUTICAL TERM.
CHEATING MAN. OKAY.
HEY.
HEY. HI. HEY.
SHE STILL DIDN'T CALL?
NO.
TROUBLE?
YOUR SISTER STOOD ME UP THE OTHER NIGHT.
OH, NO. DON'T YOU HATE IT
WHEN PEOPLE AREN'T THERE FOR YOU?
WHAT IS THAT?
"TUSHY."
DID YOU TRY CALLING HER?
I'VE BEEN TRYING FOR TWO DAYS.
WHEN I CALLED THE RESTAURANT
THEY SAID SHE WAS TOO BUSY TO TALK.
I CAN'T BELIEVE SHE'S BLOWING ME OFF.
EXCUSE ME, WE HAD THE TWO CHEF'S SALADS.
OH, AND HOW WERE THEY?
NO, WE HAVEN'T HAD THEM YET.
WE'RE STILL HOPING TO HAVE THEM.
OKAY.
HEY.
OH.
HAVE YOU GOT A MINUTE?
YEAH. I'M JUST WORKING.
SO...
UH HUH.
UM... OH, I GOT YOU A BIRTHDAY PRESENT.
OH, WOW, YOU REMEMBERED.
OH, IT'S A JUDY JETSON THERMOS.
THE KIND YOU...
RIGHT.
I GOT SOMETHING FOR YOU TOO.
HOW'D YOU KNOW
I WAS COMING?
UM... YEAH, UM, TWIN THING.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU DID THIS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU... DID THIS.
SO...
WHAT'S THE DEAL WITH YOU AND JOEY?
OH, RIGHT.
HE IS SO GREAT.
BUT THAT'S OVER.
DOES HE KNOW?
WHO?
JOEY.
YOU KNOW, UM...
HE'S REALLY NUTSY ABOUT YOU.
HE IS? WHY?
YOU GOT ME.
EXCUSE ME.
DOESN'T THIS COME WITH A SIDE SALAD?
SO, ARE YOU GOING TO CALL HIM?
YOU THINK HE LIKES ME?
NO, JOEY.
OH. NO.
NO. HE IS SO SMART.
HE'LL FIGURE IT OUT.
DO YOU WANT SOME CHICKEN?
NO. NO FOOD WITH A FACE.
YOU HAVE NOT CHANGED.
YEAH, YOU TOO.
THANKS.
EXCUSE ME.
MY SIDE SALAD?
SERVICE IN HERE IS HORRIBLE.
NOW I KNOW WHAT PEOPLE MEAN.
HI. REMEMBER US?
MM HMM.
YOU JUST CALLED A LITTLE WHILE AGO
ABOUT NEEDING A SIGNATURE ON THE ADMISSIONS FORM.
WELL, IT TURNS OUT WE NEED A WHOLE NEW ONE
BECAUSE, YOU SEE, I PUT THE WRONG NAME AGAIN
BECAUSE, UM...
YOU'RE THAT STUPID.
I AM.
I'M THAT STUPID.
YEAH, AND I'M JUST GOING
TO PAY FOR THIS WITH A CHECK.
WELL, YOUR INSURANCE WILL COVER THAT.
YEAH, I KNOW.
I'M JUST NOT THAT BRIGHT EITHER.
MON, I'M SORRY ABOUT LAST NIGHT, WHAT I SAID.
I DON'T THINK YOU'RE ANYTHING LIKE YOUR MOTHER.
OH, THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
AND I DON'T THINK YOU WERE SELFISH
FOR RUNNING OUT ON BARRY.
OH, OH, AND I'M SORRY
THAT I SAID YOU WERE A COW IN HIGH SCHOOL.
AW, THAT'S OKAY.
I WAS A COW.
I KNOW.
I'M JUST SORRY I SAID IT.
OKAY, WORST CASE SCENARIO.
SAY YOU NEVER FEEL LIKE A FATHER.
SAY YOUR SON NEVER FEELS
CONNECTED TO YOU AS ONE.
SAY ALL OF HIS RELATIONSHIPS
ARE AFFECTED BY THIS.
DO YOU HAVE A POINT?
YOU KNOW, YOU'D THINK I WOULD.
WHAT'S UP WITH THE SIMIAN?
IT'S JUST A FURBALL.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, WHOSE TURN IS IT?
YOURS.
I JUST GOT 43 POINTS FOR "KIDNEY."
NO, YOU GOT ZERO POINTS FOR "IDNEY."
HEY, WHERE'S MY "K"?
YOU'VE GOT TO HELP ME.
MY MONKEY SWALLOWED A "K."
YOU'LL HAVE TO GET
THAT ANIMAL OUT OF HERE.
THE ANIMAL HOSPITAL IS WAY ACROSS TOWN.
HE'S CHOKING.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
MARCEL SWALLOWED A SCRABBLE TILE.
OH.
EXCUSE ME.
THIS HOSPITAL IS FOR PEOPLE.
LADY, HE IS PEOPLE.
HE HAS A NAME, OKAY?
HE WATCHES JEOPARDY
HE TOUCHES HIMSELF WHEN NOBODY'S WATCHING.
PLEASE, PLEASE, HAVE A HEART.
I'LL LOOK AT HIM.
OH, THANK YOU. OH, THANK YOU.
MICHAEL! MICHAEL!
RACHEL.
WHAT? OH. MONICA. HI.
HEY...
URS... WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I'VE BEEN TRYING TO CALL YOU.
LISTEN, UM...
NO, NO, NO, DON'T SAY, "LISTEN."
I KNOW THAT "LISTEN."
I'VE SAID THAT "LISTEN."
I'M SORRY.
I DON'T GET IT.
WHAT HAPPENED?
WHAT ABOUT EVERYTHING YOU SAID UNDER THE BRIDGE?
YEAH, UM...
YOU KNOW, YOU SHOULD JUST FORGET ABOUT
WHAT I SAID UNDER THE BRIDGE.
I WAS TALKING CRAZY THAT NIGHT.
I WAS SO DRUNK.
YOU DON'T DRINK.
THAT'S RIGHT, I DON'T.
BUT I WAS DRUNK ON YOU.
OH, URS.
YEAH, SO IT'S NOT GOING TO WORK.
WHY? IS IT BECAUSE I'M FRIENDS WITH PHOEBE?
IF IT WAS, WOULD YOU STOP HANGING OUT WITH HER?
NO.
NO. I COULDN'T DO THAT.
THEN, YEAH.
IT'S BECAUSE OF PHOEBE.
SO, IT'S EITHER HER OR ME.
THEN, UH... THEN I'M SORRY.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE GOING TO BE REALLY HARD TO GET OVER.
I KNOW.
I DON'T KNOW WHETHER IT'S JUST BECAUSE WE'RE BREAKING UP OR WHAT
BUT YOU HAVE NEVER LOOKED SO BEAUTIFUL.
REALLY?
PHEEBS?
YEAH? OH.
HE LOOKS SO TINY.
WE JUST GOT THE MESSAGE.
IS HE ALL RIGHT?
YEAH. THE DOCTOR GOT THE "K" OUT.
HE ALSO FOUND AN "M" AND AN "O."
WE THINK HE WAS TRYING TO SPELL OUT "MONKEY."
WELL, THE DOCTOR SAYS HE'S GOING TO BE FINE.
HE'S JUST SLEEPING NOW.
SO, YOU FEEL LIKE A DAD YET?
NO. WHY?
HEY, COME ON.
YOU CAME THROUGH.
YOU DID WHAT YOU HAD TO DO.
THAT IS VERY DAD.
OH, LOOK.
HE'S WAKING UP.
HEY, FELLA.
HOW YOU DOING?
? IN A NEW YORK MINUTE ?
? OOH ?
? EVERYTHING CAN CHANGE ?
? IN A NEW YORK MINUTE ?
? OOH ?
? THINGS CAN GET A LITTLE STRANGE ?
? IN A NEW YORK MINUTE... ?
¿A QUIEN PIDIO EL POLLOGENERAL TSO?
PUDO HABER SIDO GENERAL TSO.
MIRA, MIRA, EL VIEJO DESNUDO ESTA HACIENDO EL HULA HOOP.
HOLA, JOEY!
HOLA, AMIGOS.
MIRA, ROSS, MARCEL SE LLEVO EL CONTROL REMOTO.
POR ESO ES QUE NO LE GUSTA LA TELE.