THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE.
IT'S BEEN, LIKE, A HALF AN HOUR.
IF THIS WAS A CARTOON
YOU'D BE LOOKING LIKE A HAM RIGHT ABOUT NOW.
OH, THERE'S THE WAITRESS. EXCUSE ME, MISS?
HELLO? MISS?
IT'S PHOEBE.
HI. HI.
HI.
OKAY, WILL THAT BE ALL?
WAIT, WAIT. WH WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
YEAH, UM, I WAS OVER THERE, AND THEN YOU SAID
"EXCUSE ME. HELLO? MISS?"
SO NOW I'M HERE.
NO, NO. HOW COME YOU'RE WORKING HERE?
RIGHT, YEAH. BECAUSE IT'S CLOSE TO WHERE I LIVE
AND THE APRONS ARE REALLY CUTE, SO...
CAN WE START OVER?
YEAH, OKAY, GREAT, I'M GOING TO BE
OVER HERE. NO, NO, NO, NO!
SO, I DON'T KNOW WHETHER HE'S TESTING ME OR JUST ACTING OUT
BUT MY MONKEY IS OUT OF CONTROL.
BUT HE KEEPS ERASING
THE MESSAGES ON MY MACHINE.
SUPPOSEDLY BY ACCIDENT.
OH, YEAH-- I'VE DONE THAT.
AND THEN, LIKE, THREE DAYS IN A ROW
HE GOT TO THE NEWSPAPER BEFORE I DID
AND PEED ALL OVER THE CROSSWORD.
I'VE NEVER DONE THAT.
AND THEN LAST NIGHT, I DON'T KNOW WHAT HE DID
BUT THERE WERE CAPERS EVERYWHERE.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, LOOK AT HER AND TELL ME
SHE DOESN'T LOOK EXACTLY LIKE HER SISTER.
I'M SAYING I SEE A DIFFERENCE.
THEY'RE TWINS.
I DON'T CARE. PHOEBE'S PHOEBE.
URSULA'S... HOT.
YOU KNOW THAT THING
WHEN YOU AND I TALK TO EACH OTHER ABOUT THINGS?
YEAH.
LET'S NOT DO THAT ANYMORE.
HI, GUYS.
HEY, PHEEBS, GUESS WHO WE SAW TODAY.
OOH! OH, FUN! OKAY, UM...
LIAM NEESON?
NO.
MORLEY SAFER? NO.
THE WOMAN WHO CUTS MY HAIR? NO.
OKAY, LOOK, THIS COULD BE A REALLY LONG GAME.
YOUR SISTER URSULA.
OH, REALLY?
YEAH, YEAH. SHE WORKS OVER AT THAT PLACE...
RIFF'S. YEAH, I KNOW. OH, YOU DO?
BECAUSE SHE SAID YOU GUYS HAVEN'T TALKED IN, LIKE, YEARS.
MM HMM. YEAH.
SO, UM, IS SHE FAT?
NOT FROM WHERE I WAS STANDING.
WHERE WERE YOU STANDING?
UM, PHEEBS, SO YOU GUYS JUST DON'T GET ALONG?
IT'S MOSTLY JUST DUMB SISTER STUFF, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, LIKE EVERYONE ALWAYS THOUGHT OF HER
AS THE PRETTY ONE, YOU KNOW, AND...
OH, OH... SHE WAS
THE FIRST ONE TO START WALKING
EVEN THOUGH I DID IT... LATER THAT SAME DAY.
BUT TO MY PARENTS
BY THEN IT WAS LIKE, "YEAH, RIGHT. WELL, WHAT ELSE IS NEW?"
OH... PHEEBS, I'M SORRY-- I'VE GOT TO GO.
I'VE GOT LAMAZE CLASS.
OH, AND I'VE GOT EARTH SCIENCE
BUT I'LL CATCH YOU IN GYM?
SO IS THIS JUST GOING TO BE YOU AND CAROL?
NO. SUSAN'S GOING TO BE THERE, TOO.
WE'VE GOT DADS, WE'VE GOT LESBIANS--
THE WHOLE PARENTING TEAM.
WELL, ISN'T THAT GOING TO BE WEIRD?
NO, NO. I MEAN, IT MIGHT HAVE BEEN AT FIRST
BUT BY NOW, I THINK I'M PRETTY COMFORTABLE WITH THE WHOLE SITUATION.
ROSS, THAT'S MY JACKET.
I KNOW. I KNOW.
HI. WE'RE THE ROSTINS.
I'M J.C.
AND HE'S MICHAEL.
AND WE'RE HAVING A BOY... AND A GIRL.
GOOD FOR YOU.
ALL RIGHTY. NEXT?
HI. UM, I'M, UH...
I'M ROSS GELLER
AND THAT'S... THAT'S MY BOY IN THERE.
AND THIS IS CAROL WILLICK
AND THIS... IS SUSAN BUNCH.
SUSAN IS, UM... CAROL'S...
WHO'S NEXT?
I'M SORRY. I DIDN'T GET...
SUSAN IS...?
SUSAN'S CAROL'S... CAROL'S... FRIEND.
LIFE PARTNER. LIKE BUDDIES.
LIKE LOVERS.
YOU KNOW HOW CLOSE WOMEN CAN GET.
SUSAN AND I
LIVE TOGETHER.
ALTHOUGH I WAS MARRIED TO HER.
CAROL, NOT ME. UH, RIGHT.
IT'S A LITTLE COMPLICATED. A LITTLE.
BUT WE'RE FINE. ABSOLUTELY.
SO TWINS?
THAT'S, LIKE, TWO BIRTHS.
OUCH!
AND...  TO YOU TOO, HELEN.
Nina Bookbinder is here to see you.
OH, OKAY. SEND HER IN.
HI.
HI, NINA. COME ON IN.
YOU WANTED TO SEE ME? UH, YES.
YES. I WAS JUST GOING OVER YOUR DATA HERE
AND A LITTLE THING-- YOU'VE BEEN POSTDATING YOUR FRIDAY NUMBERS.
WHICH IS BAD, BECAUSE...?
WELL, IT THROWS MY WENUS OUT OF WHACK.
YOUR... EXCUSE ME?
WENUS-- WEEKLY ESTIMATED NET...
OH! NET USAGE STATISTICS. RIGHT.
GOTCHA. GOTCHA.
IT WON'T HAPPEN AGAIN.
I WOULDN'T WANT TO DO ANYTHING TO HURT YOUR... WENUS.
OKAY, I'LL TAKE "IDIOTS IN THE WORKPLACE" FOR $200 DOLLARS, ALEX.
OKAY, IT'S NOT...
IT'S NOT JUST THAT SHE'S CUTE, OKAY?
IT'S JUST THAT...
SHE'S REALLY, REALLY CUTE.
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
YOU DON'T DIP YOUR PEN IN THE COMPANY INK.
OH, GOD, I EVEN KNOW THAT
AND I'M PRETTY MUCH UNEMPLOYABLE.
ROSS, YOUR LITTLE CREATURE'S GOT THE REMOTE AGAIN.
MARCEL, MARCEL, GIVE ROSSY THE REMOTE.
MARCEL...
MARCEL, YOU GIVE ROSSY THE REMOTE RIGHT NOW.
GREAT.
RELAX. I'LL FIX IT.
OH, COOL.
"URKEL" IN SPANISH... IS "URKEL."
HOW DID HE DO THIS?
SO TELL ME SOMETHING-- IS LEAVING THE CHRISTMAS LIGHTS UP
PART OF YOUR PLAN TO KEEP US MERRY
ALL YEAR LONG?
NO. SOMEONE WAS SUPPOSED TO TAKE THEM DOWN
AROUND NEW YEAR'S, BUT OBVIOUSLY, SOMEONE FORGOT.
WELL, SOMEONE WAS SUPPOSED TO WRITE
"RACHE, TAKE DOWN THE LIGHTS"
AND PUT IT ON THE RE... FRIGERATOR.
HOW LONG HAS THAT BEEN THERE?
A REALLY LONG TIME.
HEY, WHERE YOU BEEN?
I WENT BACK TO RIFF'S.
I THINK URSULA LIKES ME.
ALL I ORDERED WAS COFFEE.
SHE BROUGHT ME A TUNA MELT AND FOUR PLATES OF CURLY FRIES.
SCORE.
SHE IS SO HOT!
YEAH, LISTEN, BEFORE YOU DO ANYTHING JOEY LIKE
YOU MIGHT WANT TO RUN IT BY, UH...
YEAH?
YEAH.
PHEEBS? YEAH?
DO YOU THINK IT WOULD BE OKAY
IF I ASKED OUT YOUR SISTER?
WHY? WHY WOULD YOU WANT TO DO THAT? WHY?
WELL, SO THAT IF WE WENT OUT ON A DATE
SHE'D BE THERE.
WELL, I MEAN, I'M NOT MY SISTER'S
YOU KNOW, WHATEVER
AND, UH... I MEAN...
IT'S TRUE WE WERE ONE EGG ONCE, BUT, UH...
WE'VE... WE'VE GROWN APART, SO, UM...
I DON'T KNOW. WHY NOT? OKAY.
COOL. THANKS.
ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH. I'M FINE.
YOU WANT TO WATCH LAVERNE Y SHIRLEY?
...cinco, seis, siete, ocho! Schlemiel! Schlamazel!
SORRY.
HI.
SORRY I'M LATE.
UH, WHERE'S... WHERE'S CAROL?
STUCK AT SCHOOL.
SOME PARENT TEACHER THING.
YOU CAN GO. I'LL GET THE INFORMATION.
NO...
NO, I THINK I SHOULD STAY.
I THINK WE SHOULD BOTH KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON.
OH, GOOD. THIS WILL BE FUN.
WE'RE GOING TO START
WITH SOME BASIC THIRD STAGE BREATHING EXERCISES
SO, MOMMIES, WHY DON'T YOU GET ON YOUR BACK
AND, COACHES, YOU SHOULD BE SUPPORTING MOMMY'S HEAD.
WHAT? WHAT? WHAT? WHAT?
I AM SUPPOSED TO BE THE MOMMY?
OKAY, I'M GOING TO PLAY MY SPERM CARD ONE MORE TIME.
I DON'T SEE WHY I SHOULD MISS OUT ON THE COACHING TRAINING
JUST BECAUSE I'M A WOMAN.
SO WHAT DO YOU PROPOSE TO DO?
I WILL FLIP YOU FOR IT.
NO, NO. HEADS.
ON YOUR BACK, MOM.
ALL RIGHT, MOMMIES.
TAKE A NICE, DEEP CLEANSING BREATH.
GOOD.
NOW IMAGINE YOUR VAGINA IS OPENING
LIKE A FLOWER.
MR. D., HOW'S IT GOING, SIR?
UH, IT'S BEEN BETTER.
THE ANNUAL NET USAGE STATISTICS ARE IN.
AND?
IT'S PRETTY UGLY.
WE HAVEN'T SEEN AN ANUS THIS BAD SINCE THE '70s.
WHAT DOES THIS MEAN?
WE'LL BE LAYING OFF PEOPLE
IN EVERY DEPARTMENT.
I KNOW I CAME IN LATE LAST WEEK
BUT I SLEPT FUNNY AND MY HAIR WAS...
NOT YOU.
RELAX.
EVER HAVE TO FIRE ANYONE?
NO, BUT THAT'S NOT A PROBLEM, SIR.
THAT'S WHY MY NAME'S ON THE DOOR.
BY THE WAY, DO YOU KNOW
WHEN I'M GETTING MY NAME ON THE DOOR?
I DON'T KNOW.
I I PUT IT IN THE THING.
IT'S OKAY.
SO, UH...
WHO'S IT GOING TO BE?
NINA?
NINA...
ARE YOU OKAY?
YES. YES, I AM.
LISTEN, THE REASON I CALLED YOU IN HERE TODAY WAS, UH...
PLEASE DON'T HATE ME.
WHAT?
WOULD YOU LIKE TO HAVE DINNER SOMETIME?
SO, PHEEBS, WHAT DO YOU WANT FOR YOUR BIRTHDAY?
WELL, WHAT I REALLY WANT IS FOR MY MOM TO BE ALIVE
AND ENJOY IT WITH ME, BUT...
OKAY...
LET ME PUT IT THIS WAY:
ANYTHING FROM CRABTREE & EVELYN?
OOH! BATH SALTS
WOULD BE NICE.
OH, OKAY. GOOD.
WHAT IS THIS PLACE?
YOU'RE COLD, I HAVE TO PEE
AND THERE'S A CUP OF COFFEE ON THE WINDOW.
HOW BAD COULD IT BE?
I THINK WE HAVE
AN ANSWER.
WHAT'S SHE DOING HERE?
THIS COULD BE GOD'S WAY OF TELLING US TO EAT AT HOME.
YOU THINK SHE GOT FIRED AT RIFF'S?
NO. WE WERE THERE LAST NIGHT.
SHE KEPT... BRINGING SWORDFISH.
ARE YOU GOING TO GO TO..?
I'LL WAIT UNTIL AFTER WE ORDER.
IT'S HER, RIGHT?
IT LOOKS LIKE... HER.
UM... EXCUSE ME?
YEAH?
HI! IT'S US.
RIGHT. AND IT'S ME.
SO YOU'RE HERE TOO.
AS MUCH AS YOU ARE.
YOUR TURN?
UH... WE KNOW
WHAT WE WANT.
OH, THAT'S GOOD.
ALL WE WANT IS TWO CAFFE LATTES.
AND SOME BISCOTTI COOKIES.
GOOD CHOICE.
IT'S DEFINITELY HER.
YEAH.
Buenos noches, John-Boy.
Buenos noches, Jim-Bob.
YOU STILL HAVEN'T TOLD THAT GIRL
SHE DOESN'T HAVE A JOB?
WELL, YOU STILL HAVEN'T TAKEN DOWN
THE CHRISTMAS LIGHTS.
CONGRATULATIONS.
I THINK YOU'VE FOUND THE WORLD'S THINNEST ARGUMENT.
I'M JUST TRYING TO FIND THE RIGHT MOMENT.
THAT SHOULDN'T BE SO HARD NOW THAT YOU'RE DATING.
SWEETHEART, YOU'RE FIRED, BUT HOW ABOUT A QUICKIE
BEFORE I GO TO WORK?
HEY.
HEY. HEY.
ONCE YOU'RE INSIDE
YOU DON'T HAVE TO KNOCK ANYMORE.
I'LL GET IT.
OH. HI, MR. HECKLES.
YOU'RE DOING IT AGAIN.
DOING WHAT?
WE'RE NOT DOING ANYTHING.
WE'RE JUST SITTING AROUND TALKING. QUIETLY.
I CAN HEAR YOU THROUGH THE CEILING.
MY CATS CAN'T SLEEP.
YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE CATS.
I COULD HAVE CATS.
GOOD BYE, MR. HECKLES.
WE'LL TRY TO KEEP IT DOWN.
PHOEBE, COULD YOU DO ME A FAVOR?
WOULD YOU TRY THIS ON?
I WANT TO MAKE SURE IT FITS.
OH, MY FIRST BIRTHDAY PRESENT.
OH, THIS IS REALLY...
OH, NO, NO, NO.
IT'S FOR URSULA.
I JUST FIGURED SIZE WISE...
OH. SURE. YEAH.
OKAY. FITS.
ARE YOU SEEING HER AGAIN?
YEP. ICE CAPADES.
THIS IS SERIOUS.
I'VE NEVER KNOWN YOU TO PAY MONEY
FOR ANY KIND OF CAPADE.
I DON'T KNOW.
I LIKE HER, YOU KNOW?
SHE'S DIFFERENT.
THERE'S, UH...
SOMETHING ABOUT HER...
THAT YOU LIKE.
WE GET IT.
YOU LIKE HER-- GREAT.
PHOEBE, I ASKED YOU
AND YOU SAID IT WAS OKAY.
MAYBE NOW IT'S NOT OKAY.
OKAY. WELL, MAYBE NOW I'M NOT OKAY WITH IT NOT BEING OKAY.
OKAY.
KNIT, GOOD WOMAN, KNIT! KNIT!
AND THAT'S THE CHRYSLER BUILDING RIGHT THERE.
NINA.
MR. DOUGLAS.
COOL TIE.
SHE'S STILL HERE.
YES. YES, SHE IS.
DIDN'T I MEMO YOU ON THIS?
AFTER I LET HER GO
UH, I GOT A CALL FROM HER PSYCHIATRIST
DR. FLANE... DR. FLENNEN, DR. FLEN
AND, UH...
HE INFORMED ME THAT, UH, SHE TOOK THE NEWS RATHER BADLY.
IN FACT, HE MENTIONED THE WORD "FRENZY."
Y YOU'RE KIDDING.
SHE SEEMED SO...
OH, NO, NO. NINA?
SHE IS WHOO WHOO WHOO- WHOO WHOO WHOO!
IN FACT, IF YOU ASKED HER RIGHT NOW
SHE WOULD HAVE NO RECOLLECTION OF BEING FIRED AT ALL.
THAT'S... UNBELIEVABLE.
AND YET BELIEVABLE.
SO I'VE DECIDED NOT TO FIRE HER AGAIN
UNTIL I CAN BE ASSURED THAT SHE WILL BE NO THREAT
TO HERSELF OR OTHERS.
I SEE. HMM.
I GUESS YOU NEVER REALLY KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON INSIDE A PERSON'S HEAD.
WELL, I GUESS THAT'S WHY THEY CALL IT PSYCHOLOGY, SIR.
The sound Mom and Dad will never forget.
For this, after all, is the miracle of birth.
LIGHTS, PLEASE.
AND THAT'S HAVING A BABY.
NEXT WEEK IS OUR FINAL CLASS.
SUSAN, GO DEEP.
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
IT'S JUST, JUST IMPOSSIBLE.
WHAT IS, HONEY?
WHAT THAT WOMAN... DID.
I AM NOT DOING THAT.
IT'S JUST GOING TO HAVE TO STAY IN, THAT'S ALL.
EVERYTHING'LL BE THE SAME.
IT'LL JUST STAY IN.
SHH. EVERYTHING'S GOING TO BE ALL RIGHT.
OH, WHAT DO YOU KNOW?!
NO ONE'S GOING UP TO YOU AND SAYING
"HI. IS THAT YOUR NOSTRIL?
MIND IF WE PUSH THIS POT ROAST THROUGH IT?!"
CAROL, CAROL, SWEETIE.
CLEANSING BREATH.
I KNOW IT'S FRIGHTENING
BUT, BIG PICTURE-- THE BIRTH PART IS JUST ONE DAY
AND WHEN IT'S OVER, WE'RE ALL GOING TO BE PARENTS
FOR THE REST OF OUR LIVES.
I MEAN, THAT'S WHAT THIS IS ALL ABOUT.
RIGHT? ROSS?
ROSS?
I'M GOING TO BE A FATHER.
THIS IS JUST OCCURRING TO YOU?
I ALWAYS KNEW I WAS HAVING A BABY.
I JUST NEVER REALIZED THE BABY WAS HAVING ME.
OH, YOU'RE GOING TO BE GREAT.
HOW CAN YOU SAY THAT?
I CAN'T EVEN GET MARCEL TO STOP EATING THE BATH MAT.
HOW AM I GOING TO RAISE A KID?
SOME SCIENTISTS ARE NOW SAYING
THAT MONKEYS AND BABIES ARE ACTUALLY DIFFERENT.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO LOOK INTO IT.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
OUT.
WITH?
YES.
CAN I JUST ASK YOU ONE QUESTION?
HAVE YOU TWO, YOU KNOW... LIKE, YOU KNOW?
YOU KNOW.
YET?
NOT THAT IT'S ANY OF YOUR BUSINESS
BUT NO, WE HAVEN'T. OKAY?
YOU MEANT SEX, RIGHT?
DO YOU HAVE A SEC?
UH, SURE, NINA. WHAT'S UP?
FOR THE PAST COUPLE OF DAYS, PEOPLE HAVE BEEN AVOIDING ME
AND GIVING ME REALLY STRANGE LOOKS.
OH, WELL, UH, MAYBE THAT'S BECAUSE THEY'RE, UH...
JEALOUS OF US.
MAYBE. BUT THAT DOESN'T EXPLAIN
WHY THEY KEEP TAKING MY SCISSORS.
UH, WELL, MAYBE THAT'S, UH
BECAUSE YOU'RE GETTING A BIG RAISE.
I AM?
SURE. WHY NOT?
OH, MY GOD!
YOU'RE AMAZING!
OH, YOU DON'T KNOW.
HELEN, MAKE SURE WE PUT THROUGH THE PAPER WORK
ON MS. BOOKBINDER'S RAISE.
You still want me to send her psychological profile
to Personnel?
WHAT?
HELEN DRINKS.
WILL YOU MARRY ME?
SO, AFTER THE PROPOSAL, I KIND OF UNRAVELED.
RIGHT, BECAUSE YOU WERE REALLY IN CONTROL UP UNTIL THEN.
I ENDED UP TELLING HER EVERYTHING.
HOW'D SHE TAKE IT?
PRETTY WELL, EXCEPT FOR THE STAPLER THING.
A LITTLE TIP: IF YOU'RE EVER IN A SIMILAR SITUATION
NEVER EVER LEAVE YOUR HAND ON THE DESK.
OKAY, I THINK I GET HOW TO DO THIS.
ALL RIGHT, SO CAN WE TURN THIS OFF
AND MAKE THEM GO AWAY?
I CAN'T WATCH THIS.
OKAY, PHEEBS, THEY'RE GONE.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH. IT'S JUST, YOU KNOW
IT'S THIS WHOLE STUPID URSULA THING.
CAN I ASK? SO HE'S GOING OUT WITH HER.
IS IT REALLY SO TERRIBLE?
UM, YEAH.
I'M NOT SAYING SHE'S, LIKE, EVIL, OR ANYTHING.
SHE JUST, YOU KNOW... SHE'S ALWAYS BREAKING MY STUFF.
WHEN I WAS EIGHT, AND I WOULDN'T LET HER
HAVE MY JUDY JETSON THERMOS, SO SHE THREW IT
UNDER THE BUS.
AND THEN WHEN I WAS 12, AND SHE BROKE MY COLLARBONE.
ALL RIGHT, I MEAN, SHE DIDN'T MEAN TO DO IT
BUT I THINK IT STILL COUNTS.
OH, AND THEN THERE'S RANDY BROWN
WHO WAS LIKE... HAVE YOU EVER HAD A BOYFRIEND
WHO WAS, LIKE, YOUR BEST FRIEND?
NO. NO.
WELL, BUT THAT'S WHAT HE WAS FOR ME
AND SHE, YOU KNOW, KIND OF STOLE HIM AWAY
AND THEN BROKE HIS HEART
AND THEN HE WOULDN'T EVEN TALK TO ME ANYMORE
BECAUSE HE SAID HE DIDN'T WANT TO BE AROUND ANYTHING
THAT LOOKED LIKE EITHER ONE OF US.
OH, PHEEBS...
I MEAN, I KNOW JOEY IS NOT MY BOYFRIEND
OR MY THERMOS...
YOU KNOW, OR ANYTHING, BUT...
HEY, YOU'RE NOT
GOING TO LOSE HIM.
YOU'VE GOT TO TALK TO JOEY.
YEAH.
HE DOESN'T KNOW THIS STUFF.
IF HE KNEW HOW YOU FELT...
HE'S FALLING IN LOVE WITH HER.
OH, PLEASE.
THEY'VE BEEN GOING OUT A WEEK.
THEY HAVEN'T EVEN SLEPT TOGETHER YET.
I MEAN, THAT'S NOT SERIOUS.
OKAY. OKAY.
OKAY. OH...
OH!
YEAH, UM...
MAY WE HELP YOU?
RACHEL, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
IT'S FREEZING OUT HERE.
WOULD YOU COME BACK INSIDE?
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
YOU WANTED ME TO TAKE THEM DOWN
SO I'M TAKING THEM DOWN, OKAY?
WHOA. WHOA!
RACHEL!
I'M OKAY! I'M OKAY!
MR. HECKLES?
MR. HECKLES, COULD YOU HELP ME, PLEASE?
SEE, THIS IS JUST THE KIND OF THING
OW, OW, OW. OW, OW, OW.
OW, OW, OW.
HI. MY FRIEND HERE WAS TAKING DOWN
OUR CHRISTMAS LIGHTS AND SHE FELL OFF THE BALCONY
AND MAY HAVE BROKEN HER FOOT OR ANKLE OR SOMETHING.
MY GOD, YOU STILL HAVE YOUR CHRISTMAS LIGHTS UP?!
FILL THIS OUT
AND BRING IT BACK TO ME.
OW, OW, OW. OW, OW, OW.
OKAY.
OOH. ALL RIGHT.
NAME.
ADDRESS.
OKAY, ARE YOU CURRENTLY ON ANY MEDICATION?
NO.
OH, WAIT!
WAIT, YES. BLISTEX.
UH,NO.
OKAY. IN CASE OF EMERGENCY, CALL..?
YOU.
REALLY?
YEAH.
OH, THAT'S SO SWEET.
OH, GOSH.
I LOVE YOU.