WOULD YOU LET IT GO?
IT'S NOT THAT BIG A DEAL.
NOT THAT BIG A DEAL? IT'S AMAZING, OKAY?
YOU JUST REACH IN THERE, THERE'S ONE LITTLE MANEUVER
AND BAM, A BRA, RIGHT OUT THE SLEEVE.
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED
THERE IS NOTHING A GUY CAN DO THAT EVEN COMES CLOSE.
AM I RIGHT HERE?
OH, COME ON!
YOU GUYS CAN PEE STANDING UP.
WE CAN? OKAY, I'M TRYING THAT.
ALL RIGHT, YOU KNOW WHAT BLOWS MY MIND?
WOMEN CAN SEE BREASTS ANYTIME THEY WANT.
YOU JUST LOOK DOWN, AND THERE THEY ARE.
HOW YOU GET ANY WORK DONE IS BEYOND ME.
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT I DON'T GET?
THE WAY GUYS CAN DO SO MANY MEAN THINGS
AND THEN NOT EVEN CARE.
MULTIPLE ORGASMS.
THERE YOU GO.
SO, SATURDAY NIGHT, THE BIG NIGHT
DATE NIGHT, SATURDAY NIGHT, SA TUR DAY NIGHT!
NO PLANS, HUH?
NOT A ONE.
NOT EVEN, SAY, BREAKING UP WITH JANICE?
OH, RIGHT, RIGHT.
SHUT UP.
CHANDLER, NOBODY LIKES BREAKING UP WITH SOMEONE.
EXCEPT FOR KEVIN MILMORE, MAY HE ROT IN HELL.
YOU JUST GOT TO DO IT.
I KNOW, BUT IT'S JUST SO HARD, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, YOU'RE SITTING THERE WITH HER.
SHE HAS NO IDEA WHAT'S HAPPENING.
THEN YOU FINALLY GET UP THE COURAGE TO DO IT
AND THERE'S THAT HORRIBLE AWKWARD MOMENT
WHEN YOU'VE HANDED HER THE NOTE...
YOU TRY TO, YOU KNOW, RUN OUT OF THE RESTAURANT
BEFORE SHE'S ACTUALLY FINISHED THE NOTE.
WHY DO YOU HAVE TO BREAK UP WITH HER?
BE A MAN.
JUST STOP CALLING.
IF YOU WANT, I'LL DO IT WITH YOU.
THANKS, BUT I THINK SHE'D FEEL LIKE WE'RE GANGING UP ON HER.
NO, I MEAN, YOU BREAK UP WITH JANICE
AND I'LL BREAK UP WITH TONY.
YOU'RE BREAKING UP WITH TONY?
YEAH, I KNOW HE'S SWEET, BUT IT'S JUST NOT FUN ANYMORE.
I DON'T KNOW IF IT'S ME OR HIS HUNGER STRIKE, OR...
DOES ANYBODY WANT ANYTHING ELSE?
OH, YEAH.
LAST WEEK YOU HAD A WONDERFUL
NUTTY, CHOCOLATY KIND OF A CAKEY PIE THING...
NOTHING. JUST, JUST... I'M FINE.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
WHY SO SCRUNCHY?
OH, IT'S MY FATHER.
HE WANTS TO GIVE ME A MERCEDES CONVERTIBLE.
THAT GUY... HE BURNS ME UP.
YEAH, WELL, IT'S A MERCEDES IF I MOVE BACK HOME.
UGH, IT'S HORRIBLE!
HE CALLED ME "YOUNG LADY."
OOH, I HATE WHEN MY FATHER CALLS ME THAT.
DID HE GIVE YOU
THAT WHOLE "YOU'RE NOT UP TO THIS" THING AGAIN?
OH, YEAH, YEAH. I ACTUALLY GOT THE EXTENDED DISCO VERSION
WITH THREE CHORUSES OF "YOU'LL NEVER MAKE IT ON YOUR OWN."
? UH HUH, UH HUH. ?
HI, JOEY.
OH, MY GOD-- ANGELA.
WOW. BEING DUMPED BY YOU OBVIOUSLY AGREES WITH HER.
ARE YOU GOING TO GO OVER THERE?
NO. YEAH. NO.
OKAY, BUT NOT YET.
I DON'T WANT TO SEEM TOO EAGER.
ONE MISSISSIPPI, TWO MISSISSIPPI
THREE MISSISSIPPI... THAT SEEMS PRETTY COOL.
HEY, ANGELA.
JOEY.
YOU LOOK GOOD.
THAT'S BECAUSE I'M WEARING A DRESS
THAT ACCENTS MY BOOBS.
YOU DON'T SAY.
SO, RACHEL, WHAT ARE YOU...
WHAT ARE YOU DOING TONIGHT?
OH, BIG GLAMOUR NIGHT
ME AND MONICA AT LAUNDERAMA.
OH. YOU, UH...
YOU WANT TO HEAR A FREAKISH COINCIDENCE?
GUESS WHO'S DOING LAUNDRY THERE TOO?
WHO?
ME.
WAS THAT NOT CLEAR?
UH, HEY, WHY DON'T, UH...
WHY DON'T I JUST JOIN YOU... BOTH... THERE?
DON'T YOU HAVE A LAUNDRY ROOM IN YOUR BUILDING?
YES.
I DO HAVE A LAUNDRY ROOM IN MY BUILDING.
UH, BUT THERE'S A RAT PROBLEM.
APPARENTLY, THEY'RE ATTRACTED TO THE DRYER SHEETS
AND THEY'RE GOING IN FINE
BUT THEY'RE COMING OUT ALL...
FLUFFY.
ANYWAY, SAY, SEVEN ISH?
SURE.
FORGET IT, JOEY.
I'M WITH BOB NOW.
BOB? MM HMM.
WHO THE HELL'S BOB?
BOB IS GREAT.
HE'S SMART, HE'S SOPHISTICATED
AND HE HAS A REAL JOB.
YOU, YOU GO ON THREE AUDITIONS A MONTH
AND YOU CALL YOURSELF AN ACTOR
BUT BOB...
COME ON.
WE WERE GREAT TOGETHER
AND NOT JUST AT THE FUN STUFF
BUT, LIKE, TALKING TOO.
YEAH...
YEAH, WELL, SORRY, JOEY.
YOU SAID "LET'S JUST BE FRIENDS"
SO GUESS WHAT?
WHAT?
WE'RE JUST FRIENDS.
FINE. FINE. SO, WHY DON'T THE FOUR OF US
GO OUT AND HAVE DINNER TOGETHER TONIGHT--
YOU KNOW, AS FRIENDS?
WHAT FOUR OF US?
WELL, YOU KNOW, YOU AND BOB
AND ME AND MY GIRLFRIEND, UH... UH...
MONICA.
I'M TELLING YOU
THIS GUY IS PERFECT FOR YOU.
FORGET IT.
NOT AFTER YOUR COUSIN
WHO COULD BELCH THE ALPHABET.
COME ON.
THIS GUY'S GREAT.
HIS NAME'S BOB.
HE'S ANGELA'S... BROTHER.
HE'S SMART, HE'S
SOPHISTICATED, AND HE HAS A REAL JOB.
ME, I GO ON THREE AUDITIONS A MONTH
AND CALL MYSELF AN ACTOR, BUT BOB IS...
OH, GOD HELP US.
WHAT?
UGLY NAKED GUYS LAYING KITCHEN TILE.
EEW! EEW!
LOOK, I'M ASKING A FAVOR HERE.
YOU KNOW, I'M THINKING
IF I DO THIS THING FOR HER BROTHER
MAYBE ANGELA WILL COME BACK TO ME.
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
YOU GO OUT WITH TONS OF GIRLS.
I KNOW, BUT...
SHE'S ONE OF A KIND, YOU KNOW?
LIKE A SNOWFLAKE, OR...
OR A...
SOMETHING ELSE LIKE A SNOWFLAKE?
YEAH. YEAH.
LOOK, I MADE A HUGE MISTAKE.
I NEVER SHOULD HAVE BROKE UP WITH HER.
WILL YOU HELP ME? PLEASE?
HOLD ON A SEC.
YOU NEED TO NOT TOUCH ANY OF THOSE.
OKAY. BYE.
WELL, MONICA'S NOT COMING.
IT'S JUST GOING TO BE ME AND RACHEL.
WELL, HOLD ON THERE, CAMPER.
YOU SURE YOU'VE THOUGHT THIS THROUGH?
IT'S LAUNDRY.
THE THINKING THROUGH IS PRETTY MINIMAL.
SEE, IT'S JUST YOU AND RACHEL, JUST THE TWO OF YOU?
THIS IS A DATE.
YOU'RE GOING ON A DATE.
NUH UH.
YUH HUH.
YEAH, I HAVEN'T DONE THAT IN A WHILE.
IS IT A DATE IF SHE DOESN'T KNOW WE'RE GOING ON A DATE?
YES. ABSOLUTELY.
SATURDAY NIGHT, ALL RULES APPLY.
SO, WHAT ARE YOU SAYING HERE--
I SHOULD SHAVE AGAIN, PICK UP SOME WINE? WHAT?
WELL, YOU, UH, MAY WANT
TO RETHINK THE DIRTY UNDERWEAR.
THIS IS BASICALLY THE FIRST TIME
SHE'S GOING TO SEE YOUR UNDERWEAR.
DO YOU WANT IT
TO BE DIRTY?
NO.
OH, AND, UH, THE FABRIC SOFTENER?
OKAY, OKAY, NOW, WHAT IS WRONG WITH MY SNUGGLES?
IT, WHAT? IT SAYS I'M A SENSITIVE, WARM KIND OF GUY
YOU KNOW, LIKE A LITTLE FUZZY BEAR.
ALL RIGHT, I CAN PICK SOMETHING ELSE UP...
THERE YOU GO.
THANK YOU.
SO, WHAT DOES THIS BOB GUY LOOK LIKE?
IS HE TALL, SHORT?
YUP.
WHICH?
WHICH WHAT?
YOU'VE NEVER MET BOB, HAVE YOU?
NO,BUTHE'S...
OH, MY GOD, JOEY
THIS GUY COULD BE HORRIBLY...
HEY, JOEY!
HORRIBLY ATTRACTIVE.
I'LL BE SHUTTING UP NOW.
WHERE ARE THEY?
THIS IS NICE.
WE NEVER DO ANYTHING JUST THE TWO OF US.
IT'S GREAT.
MAYBE TOMORROW WE CAN RENT A CAR
RUN OVER SOME PUPPIES.
EW. I DON'T WANT TO DO THAT.
HERE WE GO.
OKAY, HAVE A GOOD BREAK UP.
HEY, JANICE.
OH, MY GOD
I AM SO GLAD YOU CALLED ME.
I HAD THE MOST SUPREMELY AWFUL DAY.
HEY, THAT'S NOT GOOD.
CAN I GET AN ESPRESSO AND A LATTE OVER HERE, PLEASE?
WE GOT THE PROOFS BACK FROM THAT PHOTO SHOOT--
YOU KNOW, THE ONE WITH THE LITTLE VEGETABLES--
THEY PRETTY MUCH SUCKED
SO I BLEW OFF THE REST OF THE AFTERNOON.
I WENT SHOPPING, AND I GOT YOU...
I'M LOOKING, I'M LOOKING...
I'M LOOKING...
I GOT YOU...
WHAT?!
WHAT?
WHAT... DID YOU GET ME THERE?
I GOT YOU...
THESE.
BULLWINKLE SOCKS.
THAT'S SO SWEET.
WELL, I KNEW YOU HAD THE ROCKYS
AND SO I FIGURED, YOU KNOW, YOU COULD WEAR
BULLWINKLE AND BULLWINKLE, OR YOU COULD WEAR ROCKY AND ROCKY
OR YOU CAN MIX AND MATCH.
MOOSE AND SQUIRREL.
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
WELL, I'M GOING TO GET ANOTHER ESPRESSO.
MORE LATTE?
NO... NO, I I'M, I'M STILL WORKING ON MINE.
THAT'S IT?
YEAH, IT WAS REALLY HARD.
OH, YEAH, THE HUG LOOKED PRETTY BRUTAL.
OKAY, YOU WEREN'T THERE.
SORRY.
HOW'S IT GOING WITH JANICE?
THINGS ARE NOT GOING.
SHE GOT ME SOCKS.
OH, THESE GO WITH YOUR ROCKYS.
OH, MY GOD, SHE MUST REALLY CARE ABOUT YOU
I'M SORRY.
COMING THROUGH. MOVE, MOVE.
OH, EXCUSE ME.
I WAS KIND OF USING THAT MACHINE.
YEAH, WELL, NOW YOU'RE KIND OF NOT.
BUT, I I SAVED IT.
I I PUT MY BASKET ON TOP.
OH, I'M SORRY, IS THAT YOUR BASKET?
YES.
IT'S REALLY PRETTY.
UNFORTUNATELY, I DON'T SEE SUDS!
WHAT?
NO SUDS, NO SAVE. OKAY?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
HI. UH, NOTHING.
THIS HORRIBLE WOMAN JUST TOOK MY MACHINE.
WAS YOUR BASKET ON TOP?
YEAH, BUT THERE WERE NO SUDS.
SO?
WELL, YOU KNOW, "NO SUDS, NO SAVE."
NO SUDS, NO..? EXCUSE ME.
HOLD ON A SECOND.
THIS IS MY FRIEND'S MACHINE.
HEY, HEY, HEY, HER STUFF WASN'T IN IT.
HEY, HEY, HEY, THAT'S NOT THE RULE
AND YOU KNOW IT.
ALL RIGHT, SHOW'S OVER.
NOTHING TO SEE HERE.
OKAY, LET'S DO LAUNDRY.
THAT WAS AMAZING.
WELL...
I CAN'T EVEN SEND BACK SOUP.
WELL, THAT'S BECAUSE YOU'RE SUCH A SWEET, GENTLE, UH...
UM, UH, DO YOU, UH, OH, HEY
YOU MUST NEED DETERGENT. OH!
WHAT'S THAT?
UBERWEISS. IT'S NEW, IT'S GERMAN
IT'S EXTRA TOUGH.
RACH, ARE YOU GOING TO SEPARATE THOSE?
OH, GOD. OH!
AM I BEING, LIKE A TOTAL LAUNDRY SPAZ?
I MEAN, AM I SUPPOSED TO USE ONE MACHINE FOR SHIRTS
AND ANOTHER MACHINE FOR PANTS?
HAVE YOU..?
HAVE YOU NEVER DONE THIS BEFORE?
WELL, NOT MYSELF
BUT I KNOW OTHER PEOPLE THAT HAVE.
OKAY, YOU CAUGHT ME.
I'M A LAUNDRY VIRGIN.
UH, WELL, DON'T WORRY, I'LL USE THE GENTLE CYCLE.
OKAY, UH...
BASICALLY, YOU WANT TO USE ONE MACHINE
FOR ALL YOUR WHITES, OKAY?
A WHOLE NOTHER MACHINE FOR, FOR YOUR COLORS
AND, AND A THIRD FOR YOUR, UH...
UH... DELICATES, AND THAT WOULD BE
YOUR BRAS AND YOUR UNDER... PANTY THINGS.
OKAY, WELL, WHAT ABOUT...
THESE ARE WHITE COTTON PANTIES.
WOULD THEY GO WITH WHITES
OR WITH DELICATES?
UH, THAT, THAT...
THAT WOULD BE A JUDGMENT CALL.
HE'S SO CUTE.
SO, WHERE DID YOU GUYS GROW UP?
BROOKLYN HEIGHTS. CLEVELAND.
HA.
HOW DID THAT HAPPEN?
OH, MY GOD!
WHAT?
I, UH, SUDDENLY HAD THE FEELING
I WAS... FALLING.
BUT I'M NOT.
SO, YOU AND ANGELA, HUH?
YEP. PRETTY MUCH.
YOU'RE A LUCKY MAN.
YEAH.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MISS THE MOST ABOUT HER?
THAT CUTE NIBBLY NOISE SHE MAKES WHEN SHE EATS
LIKE A HAPPY LITTLE SQUIRREL OR...
OR A WEASEL.
I... I NEVER REALLY NOTICED.
OH, YEAH, YEAH.
LISTEN FOR IT.
MONICA...
MONICA IS GREAT.
YEAH. YEAH, SHE IS.
BUT, UH... IT'S NOT GOING TO LAST.
SHE'S TOO MUCH FOR ME IN BED.
SEXUALLY.
I'VE GOT TO TELL YOU.
BOB IS TERRIFIC.
YEAH. ISN'T HE?
IT IS SO GREAT TO MEET A GUY WHO'S SMART AND FUNNY
AND HAS AN EMOTIONAL AGE BEYOND, LIKE, EIGHT.
YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE?
HE'S UNBELIEVABLE IN BED.
WOW.
MY BROTHER NEVER EVEN TOLD ME WHEN HE LOST HIS VIRGINITY.
HUH.
THAT'S NICE.
YOU CAN DO THIS.
IT'S JUST LIKE PULLING OFF A BAND AID.
OKAY, JUST DO IT REALLY FAST AND THEN THE WOUND IS EXPOSED.
GO. GO.
JANICE...
HI, JANICE.
OKAY, HERE WE GO.
I DON'T THINK WE SHOULD GO OUT ANYMORE.
JANICE.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL...
WELL, THERE YOU GO.
STOP IT. STOP IT.
STOP IT.
LISTEN, JANICE, THIS ISN'T ABOUT YOU.
OH, I KNOW THIS IS NOT ABOUT ME.
THIS IS TOTALLY ABOUT YOUR FEAR OF COMMITMENT.
WHAT FEAR OF COMMITMENT? I DON'T HAVE A FEAR OF COMMITMENT.
OH, PLEASE. I DON'T.
OH, PLEASE. I DON'T! I'M READY TO COMMIT ANYTIME.
REALLY?
OKAY. I KNOW THIS IS GOING TO SOUND REALLY STUPID
BUT I FEEL... I FEEL THAT IF I CAN DO THIS...
YOU KNOW, IF I CAN ACTUALLY DO MY OWN LAUNDRY
THERE ISN'T ANYTHING I CAN'T DO.
THAT DOES NOT SOUND STUPID TO ME.
NO. IT'S LIKE THE... OKAY, THE FIRST TIME
I HAD TO MAKE DINNER FOR MYSELF AFTER CAROL LEFT ME.
I'M SORRY. THAT'S ALL THE TIME WE HAVE.
NEXT, ON ROSS...
OKAY.
UH OH.
WHAT "UH OH"?
UH OH...
UH OH... THE LAUNDRY'S DONE.
IT'S A... IT'S A SONG.
THE LAUNDRY SONG THAT WE SING.
? UH OH, THE LAUNDRY'S DONE ?
? UH OH, UH OH... ? ROSS, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
NOTHING. NOTHING.
? LEE LO, THE LAUNDRY'S DONE. ?
COME ON. SHOW ME. ALL RIGHT
ALL RIGHT, IT'S JUST THAT YOU LEFT A RED SOCK IN
WITH ALL YOUR WHITES
AND NOW...
EVERYTHING'S KIND OF PINK.
OH. EVERYTHING'S PINK.
YEAH.
EXCEPT FOR THE RED SOCK, WHICH IS STILL RED.
I'M SORRY. PLEASE DON'T BE UPSET.
IT COULD HAPPEN TO ANYONE, RACH.
OH, BUT IT DIDN'T. IT HAPPENED TO ME.
GOD! I'M GOING TO LOOK LIKE A BIG MARSHMALLOW PEEP.
WHAT AM I DOING? WHAT AM I DOING?
MY FATHER'S RIGHT.
I CAN'T LIVE ON MY OWN.
I CAN'T EVEN DO LAUNDRY.
SOMETHING WENT WRONG WITH UNDERDOG
AND THEY COULDN'T GET HIS HEAD TO INFLATE
SO, ANYWAY, UM...
HIS HEAD IS, LIKE, FLOPPING DOWN BROADWAY, RIGHT?
AND I'M JUST THINKING...
HOW INAPPROPRIATE THIS IS.
UM... I'VE GOT SOMETHING IN MY EYE.
JOEY, COULD WE CHECK IT IN THE LIGHT, PLEASE?
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT?
HELLO?!
WERE WE AT THE SAME TABLE?
IT'S LIKE COCKTAILS IN APPALACHIA.
COME ON. THEY'RE CLOSE.
CLOSE?
SHE'S GOT HER TONGUE IN HIS EAR.
OH. LIKE YOU'VE NEVER GOTTEN A LITTLE RAMBUNCTIOUS WITH ROSS?
JOEY, THIS IS SICK.
IT'S DISGUSTING.
IT'S... IT'S...
NOT REALLY TRUE, IS IT?
WHO'S TO SAY WHAT'S TRUE?
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING?
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, I'M NOT PROUD OF THIS, OKAY?
WELL, MAYBE I AM A LITTLE.
OH!
I'M OUT OF HERE.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT. COME ON.
YOU LIKE HIM. I WANT HER.
HE LIKES YOU.
REALLY?
YEAH.
LISTEN, I'M THINKING IF WE PUT OUR HEADS TOGETHER
BETWEEN THE TWO OF US, WE CAN BREAK THEM UP.
I'M SO SORRY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I DID THIS.
I JUST COULDN'T STOP LAUGHING
AT YOUR NORMAN MAILER STORY.
WAITER, ONE MORE PLATE OF CHICKEN WINGS OVER HERE.
HERE'S THE THING, JANICE.
YOU KNOW, I MEAN, IT'S LIKE, WE'RE DIFFERENT.
YOU KNOW, I'M LIKE THE BING, BING, BING.
YOU'RE LIKE THE BOOM, BOOM, BOOM. OW!
MY GOD!
I'M SO SORRY.
OW. ARE YOU OKAY?
OW.
IT'S JUST MY LENS. IT'S MY LENS.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
OW.
I HIT HER IN THE EYE.
I HIT HER IN THE EYE!
THIS IS THE WORST BREAKUP IN THE HISTORY OF THE WORLD.
OH, MY GOD.
HOW MANY OF THOSE HAVE YOU HAD?
I DON'T KNOW.
A MILLION?
CHANDLER, SHH.
EASY. EASY.
GO TO YOUR HAPPY PLACE.
? LA, LA, LA, LA, LA, LA... ?
I'M FINE. I'M FINE.
I'M FINE. ALL RIGHT.
I'M NOT FINE.
HERE SHE COMES.
SHH. WAIT HERE, OKAY?
BREATHE.
HOW DO YOU DO THAT?
IT'S LIKE A GIFT.
WE SHOULD ALWAYS, ALWAYS BREAK UP TOGETHER.
OH, I'D LIKE THAT.
YOU GOT THE CLOTHES CLEAN.
NOW, THAT'S THE IMPORTANT PART.
OH, I GUESS.
EXCEPT EVERYTHING LOOKS LIKE JAMMIES NOW.
OH, I'M SORRY.
EXCUSE ME.
WE HAD THIS CART.
YEAH, WELL, I HAD A 24 INCH WAIST.
YOU LOSE THINGS.
NOW, COME ON.
GET OUT OF MY WAY.
WELL, I'M SORRY. YOU KNOW, MAYBE I WASN'T BEING CLEAR.
THIS WAS OUR CART.
HEY, HEY, HEY! THERE WEREN'T ANY CLOTHES IN IT!
HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY! QUIT MAKING UP RULES!
LET GO!
ALL RIGHT, LISTEN, MITZI.
IF YOU WANT THIS CART
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO TAKE ME WITH IT.
YES.
DID YOU SEE THAT?
YOU WERE INCREDIBLE.
A BRAND NEW WOMAN, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN.
THANK YOU. I COULD NOT HAVE DONE THIS WITHOUT YOU.
OKAY, UM... UH...
MORE CLOTHES IN THE DRYER?
I'M FINE. I'M FINE.
ARE YOU HURT?
NO.
ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE OKAY?
YEAH.
DOES IT STILL HURT?
WHAT A NEAT IDEA.
ALL YOUR CLOTHES MATCH.
I'M GOING TO DO THIS.
HI.
HEY. HOW DID IT GO?
EXCELLENT.
WE RIPPED THAT COUPLE APART
AND KEPT THE PIECES FOR OURSELVES.
WHAT A BEAUTIFUL STORY.
HEY. I'M FINE, BY THE WAY.
OH, I'M...
HEY, WHERE'S CHANDLER?
HE NEEDED SOME TIME TO GRIEVE.
I'M FREE! I'M FREE!
THAT OUGHT TO DO IT.