SHE'S NOT HERE YET.
SHE'S HAVING MY BABY, AND SHE'S NOT HERE.
I'M SURE EVERYTHING'S FINE.
HAS HER WATER BROKEN YET?
I DON'T KNOW
BUT WHEN I SPOKE TO HER
SHE SAID SHE HAD ALREADY PASSED THE MUCUS PLUG.
DO WE HAVE TO KNOW ABOUT THAT?
JOEY, WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO
WHEN YOU HAVE A BABY?
I'M GOING TO BE IN THE WAITING ROOM
HANDING OUT CIGARS.
JOEY'S MADE ARRANGEMENTS
TO HAVE HIS BABY IN A MOVIE FROM THE 50s.
I DON'T BELIEVE THIS.
SHE COULD BE GIVING BIRTH IN THE CAB.
OH, ROSS, RELAX.
IT'S PROBABLY ONLY, LIKE, $2 FOR THE FIRST CONTRACTION
AND THEN 50 CENTS EACH ADDITIONAL CONTRACTION.
WHAT?
IT'S OKAY WHEN CHANDLER DOES IT?
YOU HAVE TO PICK YOUR MOMENTS.
DID I MISS IT?
SHE'S NOT EVEN HERE YET.
WHAT'S WITH THE GUITAR?
I JUST THOUGHT WE MIGHT BE HERE FOR A WHILE.
YOU KNOW, THINGS MIGHT GET MUSICAL.
WHERE THE HELL HAVE YOU BEEN?!
THE GIFT SHOP.
I WAS LOOKING AT STUFFED ANIMALS
AND SUSAN WANTED A CHUNKY.
SUSAN WANTED...
YOU'RE HAVING A BABY, OKAY?!
YOU DON'T STOP FOR CHUNKYS!
I USED TO HAVE THAT BUMPER STICKER.
YOU SEE WHAT I MEAN.
STOPPED FOR A CHUNKY.
LET IT GO, ROSS.
I GOT AN EXTRA ONE.
YOU WANT THIS?
NO.
HEY, HOW'S MY FAVORITE PARENTING TEAM DOING?
DR. FRANZBLAU, HI.
SO, I UNDERSTAND YOU'RE THINKING OF HAVING A BABY?
WELL, I SEE YOU'RE NINE MONTHS PREGNANT.
THAT'S A GOOD START.
HOW YOU DOING WITH YOUR CONTRACTIONS?
OH, I LOVE THEM.
EACH ONE'S LIKE A LITTLE PARTY IN MY UTERUS.
THEY'RE EVERY FOUR MINUTES, AND LAST 55 SECONDS.
59 SECONDS.
QUARTZ. HA!
SWISS QUARTZ. HA HA!
AM I ALLOWED TO DRINK ANYTHING?
JUST ICE CHIPS-- THEY'RE AT THE NURSES' STATION.
I GOT IT. I GOT IT.
I'M GETTING IT!
HI!
I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT LIKE SOME ICE CHIPS.
THANKS.
AND IF YOU NEED ANYTHING ELSE
I...
DO NOT BELIEVE WE HAVE MET.
HI.
I'M RACHEL GREEN.
I'M CAROL'S EX HUSBAND'S SISTER'S ROOMMATE.
IT IS NICE TO MEET YOU.
I'M DR. FRANZBLAU.
I'M YOUR ROOMMATE'S BROTHER'S EX WIFE'S OBSTETRICIAN.
OH... THAT'S FUNNY!
I WANT A BABY.
NOT TONIGHT, HONEY.
I GOT AN EARLY DAY TOMORROW.
GET UP.
LET'S GET SOME COFFEE.
OH, OKAY...
BECAUSE WE NEVER DO THAT.
SHOOT! SHOOT! SHOOT!
SHOOT... OR JUST FALL DOWN.
THAT'S GOOD, TOO.
KNICK FAN?
OH, YEAH.
OH, BOY, DO THEY SUCK.
HEY, LISTEN, LADY...
WHOA.
LOOK.
LOOK AT YOUR MAN EWING. NICE SHOT.
HE COULDN'T HIT WATER
IF HE WAS STANDING ON A BOAT.
OH, YEAH? AND WHO DO YOU LIKE?
THE CELTICS.
CELTICS? HA!
THEY COULDN'T HIT A BOAT IF...
WAIT.
THEY SUCK, ALL RIGHT?
OH, SHUT UP-- IT'S A REBUILDING YEAR.
YOU WA.... WAAH!
WHA? WHA AH? LET ME GET A FATHER.
HEY, WE NEED A FATHER OVER HERE!
WE NEED A FATHER!
THERE IS... NO FATHER.
OH...OH.
SORRY.
OH, THAT'S OKAY.
I'M FINE.
I'M... OH!
OH! UH... OKAY.
RIGHT THIS WAY.
ALL THE OTHER PREGNANT WOMEN SEEM TO BE GOING IN HERE.
?? THEY'RE TINY AND CHUBBY AND SO SWEET TO TOUCH ??
?? AND SOON THEY'LL GROW U P AND RESENT YOU SO MUCH ??
?? NOW THEY'RE YELLING AT YO U AND YOU DON'T KNOW WHY ??
?? YOU CRY AND YOU CRY ??
?? AND YOU CRY ??
?? AND YOU CRY AND YOU CRY AND YOU... ??
THANKS, ROSS.
I'M PAYING YOU TO STOP.
OKAY.
OH, LOOK. TWINS.
HI, GUYS.
OH, CUTE, CUTE.
NO FAIR.
I DON'T EVEN HAVE ONE.
HOW COME THEY GET TWO?
YOU'LL GET ONE.
OH, YEAH? WHEN?
ALL RIGHT, I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
WHEN WE'RE 40, IF NEITHER OF US ARE MARRIED
WHAT DO YOU SAY YOU AND I GET TOGETHER AND HAVE ONE?
WHY WON'T I BE MARRIED WHEN I'M 40?
OH, NO, NO.
I JUST MEANT HYPOTHETICALLY.
OKAY, HYPOTHETICALLY-- WHY WON'T I BE MARRIED WHEN I'M 40?
NO... NO, NO.
NO. WHAT IS IT? SERIOUSLY.
IS THERE SOMETHING FUNDAMENTALLY UNMARRIABLE ABOUT ME?
UH... UH...
WELL?
DEAR GOD!
THIS PARACHUTE IS A KNAPSACK!
HEY.
HEY. OOH!
LOOK AT YOU, DRESSY DRESS.
DID YOU GO HOME AND CHANGE?
YEAH, WELL, IT'S AN IMPORTANT DAY.
I WANT TO LOOK NICE.
UM... HAS DR. FRANZBLAU BEEN BY?
NO. I HAVEN'T SEEN HIM.
WELL, WHERE IS HE?
HE IS SUPPOSED TO BE HERE.
WHAT IF THE BABY
NEEDS HIM?
RACHEL, WHAT IS THE DEAL WITH YOU AND DOCTORS ANYWAY?
IS, LIKE, YOUR FATHER A DOCTOR?
YEAH. WHY?
NO REASON.
MOM, WE'VE BEEN THROUGH THIS.
NO, I AM NOT CALLING HIM.
I DON'T CARE IF IT IS HIS KID.
THE GUY'S A JERK.
NO, I AM NOT ALONE.
JOEY'S HERE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, JOEY WHO?
TRIBBIANI.
JOEY TRIBBIANI.
YES... OKAY.
HOLD ON.
SHE WANTS TO TALK TO YOU.
TAKE THE PHONE.
HI.
YEAH, IT'S ME.
OH, NO, NO, NO, NO.
WE'RE JUST FRIENDS.
YEAH, I'M SINGLE.
25.
AN ACTOR.
HELLO?
SHE'S NOT MUCH OF A PHONE PERSON.
YEAH.
SO, UH, WHAT'S THE DEAL WITH THIS FATHER GUY?
IF SOMEONE WAS HAVING MY BABY SOMEWHERE
I'D WANT TO KNOW ABOUT IT.
HEY, KNICK FAN, AM I INTERESTED IN YOUR VIEWS ON FATHERHOOD?
UM,NO.
OKAY.
LOOK, MAYBE I SHOULD JUST GO.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD.
GOOD LUCK.
AND TAKE CARE, HUH?
YOU KNOW WHAT THE CELTICS' PROBLEM IS?
THEY LET THE PLAYERS RUN THE TEAM.
OH, THAT IS SO NOT TRUE.
OH, IT IS. IT ISN'T.
IT IS! ISN'T!
BREATHE. BREATHE.
YOU'RE GONNA KILL ME!
15 MORE SECONDS. 14, 13, 12...
COUNT FASTER.
IT'S OKAY.
JUST REMEMBER-- WE'RE DOING IT FOR JORDIE.
FOCUS. HE'LL BE HERE BEFORE YOU KNOW IT.
... FOUR, THREE, TWO...
WHO THE HELL IS JORDIE?
YOUR SON.
I DON'T HAVE A SON NAMED JORDIE.
WE ALL AGREED MY SON'S NAME IS JAMIE.
WELL, JAMIE WAS THE NAME OF SUSAN'S FIRST GIRLFRIEND
SO WE WENT BACK TO JORDIE.
WHOA-- WHAT DO YOU MEAN BACKTO JORDIE?
WE NEVER LANDED ON JORDIE.
WE JUST PASSED BY IT
DURING THE WHOLE JESSE CODY DYLAN FIASCO.
OW! OW! OW! LEG CRAMP! LEG CRAMP!
I GOT IT! I GOT IT!
HEY! YOU GET TO SLEEP WITH HER, I GET THE CRAMPS.
OH... NO, YOU DON'T.
THAT IS IT.
I WANT BOTH OF YOU OUT.
HE STARTED IT!
YOU STARTED IT!
I DON'T CARE!
I AM TRYING TO GET A PERSON OUT OF MY BODY HERE
AND YOU'RE NOT MAKING IT ANY EASIER.
NOW GO!
THANKS A LOT.
SEE WHAT YOU DID.
OUT!
BREATHE, BREATHE, BREATHE.
OH, NO.
EW!
WHAT WAS THAT?
SOMETHING EXPLODED!
THAT'S NOT THE BABY, IS IT?
IT'S JUST HER WATER BREAKING. CALM DOWN.
WATER BREAKING? WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WHAT'S THAT-- WATER BREAKING?
BREATHE.
OKAY, OKAY.
LET'S DISCUSS THIS.
OH, PLEASE, THIS IS SO YOUR FAULT.
HOW? HOW IS THIS MY FAULT?
CAROL NEVER THREW ME OUT OF A ROOM
BEFORE YOU CAME ALONG.
THERE'S A LOT OF THINGS CAROL NEVER DID
BEFORE I CAME ALONG.
OH, YOU'RE TRYING TO BE CLEVER?
YOU KNOW WHAT YOUR PROBLEM IS?
YOU'RE SO THREATENED BY ME...
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S IT!
GET IN HERE!
COME ON.
MY GOD, YOU GUYS, I DON'T BELIEVE YOU.
THERE ARE CHILDREN COMING INTO THE WORLD
IN THIS VERY BUILDING
AND YOUR NEGATIVE FIGHTING NOISES
ARE NOT THE FIRST THING THEY SHOULD BE HEARING
SO JUST STOP ALL THE YELLING.
JUST STOP IT!
YEAH, SUSAN.
DON'T MAKE ME DO THIS AGAIN.
I DON'T LIKE MY VOICE LIKE THIS.
OKAY, WHO WANTS TO HEAR SOMETHING IRONIC?
ARE! THEY! HERE! YET?!
NO, HONEY, THEY'RE NOT
BUT WE'RE GOING TO FIND THEM
AND UNTIL WE DO
WE ARE ALL HERE FOR YOU, OKAY?
OKAY. OKAY?
OKAY? OKAY.
SO YOU WERE TELLING ME ABOUT PARIS.
THERE WAS THIS GREAT LITTLE PASTRY SHOP
RIGHT BY MY HOTEL.
THERE YOU GO, DEAR.
YOU...
DID YOU FIND THEM?
I CHECKED THE GIFT SHOP, THE CAFETERIA...
WHERE ARE PHOEBE AND JOEY?
I THINK THERE'S SOMETHING SINISTER
GOING ON IN THIS HOSPITAL.
IF YOU FIND ANYONE-- ORPARTSOF ANYONE--
SCREAM.
AND SCREAM AGAIN.
HELP! HELP!
COME ON! I'M HAVING A BABY IN THERE!
HELLO!
HELP!
OKAY, EVERYONE STAND BACK.
OW.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
GOOD THING WE'RE IN A HOSPITAL.
COME ON, LYDIA, YOU CAN DO IT. PUSH!
PUSH THEM OUT, PUSH THEM OUT, HARDER, HARDER.
PUSH THEM OUT, PUSH THEM OUT, WAY OUT!
LET'S GET THAT BALL AND REALLY MOVE!
HEY HEY! HO HO! LET'S...
I WAS JUST...
YEAH, OKAY. PUSH.
PUSH. PUSH.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO,SUCK
THE DOOR OPEN?
HELP! HELP!
HELP!
?? THEY FOUND THEIR BODIES THE VERY NEXT DAY ??
?? THEY FOUND THEIR BODIES THE VERY NEXT... ??
?? LA LA LA ??
?? LA LA LA... ??
HELP! HELP!
MOM, EVERYTHING'S GOING FINE, REALLY.
YEAH, ROSS IS GREAT.
HE'S, UH...
HE'S IN A WHOLE OTHER PLACE.
NO, HE'S GONE.
NO, NO, YOU DON'T HAVE TO FLY BACK, REALLY.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, THIS MIGHT BE YOUR ONLY CHANCE?
WOULD YOU STOP?
I'M ONLY 26.
I'M NOT EVEN THINKING
ABOUT BABIES YET.
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
OH, JUST HAD A BABY.
MAZEL TOV!
I DON'T KNOW-- COULD BE AN HOUR
COULD BE THREE, BUT RELAX
SHE'S DOING GREAT.
SO, UH, TELL ME, ARE YOU...
CURRENTLY INVOLVED WITH ANYONE?
NO. NO, NOT AT THE MOMENT
NO, I'M NOT. NO.
ARE ARE YOU IN...?
NO. NO, IT'S HARD ENOUGH
TO GET WOMEN TO GO OUT WITH ME.
RIGHT. YEAH.
I'VE HEARD THAT ABOUT CUTE DOCTORS.
NO, NO, REALLY.
I I SUPPOSE IT'S BECAUSE
I SPEND SO MUCH TIME, YOU KNOW...
WHERE I DO.
OH.
MMM, I TRY NOT TO LET WORK AFFECT MY PERSONAL LIFE
BUT IT'S HARD WHEN YOU DO... WHAT I DO.
IT'S LIKE, UH...
WELL, FOR INSTANCE, WHAT DO YOU DO?
I'M A WAITRESS.
OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
WELL, AREN'T THERE TIMES WHEN YOU COME HOME
AT THE END OF THE DAY, AND YOU'RE JUST, LIKE
IF I SEE ONE MORE CUP OF COFFEE...
YEAH. GOTCHA.
I'M GOING TO CHECK UP ON YOUR FRIEND.
OKAY, THAT'S FINE.
SO, HOW DID YOU KNOW I WAS EVEN HERE?
YOUR MOM CALLED ME.
IS THIS HER?
NO. THIS IS A LOANER.
OURS IS AT THE SHOP.
GOD, I HOPE SHE HAS MY BRAINS.
I'M SORRY YOU HAD TO DO THIS BY YOURSELF.
I WASN'T BY MYSELF.
I HAD A... A DOCTOR, A NURSE
AND A HELPER... GUY.
SO, DID YOU SEE WHO WON THE GAME?
YEAH. KNICKS BY TEN.
THEY SUCK.
AW, THEY'RE NOT SO BAD.
ON! COME ON. COME
I THINK YOU'RE DOING IT TOO HARD.
YOU HAVE TO DO IT HARD, OR ELSE IT DOESN'T...
DAMN IT! DAMN IT!
DAMN IT, DAMN IT!
THIS IS ALL YOUR FAULT.
THIS WAS SUPPOSED TO BE, LIKE
THE GREATEST DAY OF MY LIFE.
MY SON IS BEING BORN, AND I SHOULD BE IN THERE.
INSTEAD, I'M STUCK IN A CLOSET WITH YOU.
THE WOMAN I LOVE IS HAVING A BABY.
I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR THIS JUST AS MUCH AS YOU.
BELIEVE ME, NO ONE HAS BEEN WAITING FOR THIS
AS MUCH AS I HAVE, OKAY?
AND YOU KNOW WHAT THE FUNNY THING IS?
WHEN THIS DAY IS OVER
YOU GET TO GO HOME WITH THE BABY.
WHERE DOES THAT LEAVE ME?
YOU GET TO BE THE BABY'S FATHER.
EVERYONE KNOWS WHO YOU ARE, AND WHO AM I?
THERE'S FATHER'S DAY, THERE'S MOTHER'S DAY.
THERE'S NO... LESBIAN LOVER DAY.
EVERY DAY IS LESBIAN LOVER DAY.
THIS IS SO GREAT.
YOU WANT TO EXPLAIN THAT?
I MEAN, BECAUSE WHEN I WAS GROWING UP
YOU KNOW, MY DAD LEFT AND MY MOTHER DIED
AND MY STEPFATHER WENT TO JAIL
SO I BARELY HAD ENOUGH PIECES OF PARENTS
TO MAKE ONE WHOLE ONE
AND HERE'S THIS LITTLE BABY
WHO HAS, LIKE
THREE WHOLE PARENTS
WHO CARE ABOUT IT SO MUCH THAT THEY'RE FIGHTING
OVER WHO GETS TO LOVE IT THE MOST
AND IT'S NOT EVEN BORN YET.
IT'S JUST... IT'S JUST THE LUCKIEST BABY
IN THE WHOLE WORLD.
I'M SORRY. YOU WERE FIGHTING.
WHERE ARE THEY?
THEY'LL BE HERE SOON.
YEAH, HONEY, THEY WOULDN'T MISS THIS.
RELAX. YOU'RE ONLY AT NINE CENTIMETERS
AND THE BABY'S AT ZERO STATION.
HEY, YOU ARE REALLY FRIGHTENING ME.
SOMEBODY WANT TO HELP ME?
TRYING TO RIP OUT MY HEART.
UH, THAT'S GREAT.
ANYBODY SEEN A NIPPLE?
ALL RIGHT, TEN CENTIMETERS.
HERE WE GO.
HONEY, TIME TO START PUSHING.
THEY'RE NOT HERE YET.
SORRY. I CAN'T TELL THE BABY TO WAIT FOR THEM.
OH, GOD!
OKAY, GOT THE VENT OPEN.
HI. I'M BEN.
I'M HOSPITAL WORKER BEN.
IT'S BEN TO THE RESCUE!
?? DA DA DA DA! ??
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
BEN, YOU READY?
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, GIVE ME YOUR FOOT.
OKAY, ON THREE, BEN.
ONE, TWO, THREE!
OKAY, THAT'S IT, BEN.
OKAY.
WHAT DO YOU SEE?
WELL, SUSAN, I SEE WHAT APPEARS TO BE A DARK VENT.
YES, IT IS, IN FACT, A DARK VENT.
PHEEBS!
EN! IT'S OPEN! IT'S OP
WAIT! YOU FORGOT YOUR LEGS!
PUSH! PUSH!
WE'RE HERE!
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?!
LONG STORY, HONEY.
CAROL, I NEED YOU TO KEEP PUSHING.
I I NEED... EXCUSE ME, CAN I HAVE THIS?
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT
THERE'S A FEW TOO MA NY PEOPLE IN THIS ROOM
THERE'S ABOUT TO BE ONE MORE
SO ANYBODY WHO'S NOT AN EX HUSBAND
OR A LESBIAN LIFE PARTNER
OUT YOU GO!
GOOD LUCK, YOU GUYS
GOOD LUCK.
LET ME ASK YOU
DO YOU HAVE TO BECAROL'S LESBIAN LIFE PARTNER?
OUT!
HE'S CROWNING.
HERE HE COMES.
LET ME SEE!
I GOT TO SEE, I GOT TO SEE!
O OH...!
OH, A HEAD.
OH, IT'S, IT'S HUGE.
CAROL, HOW ARE YOU DOING THIS?
YOU'RE NOT HELPING.
YOU'RE DOING GREAT.
YOU'RE DOING FINE.
HELLO! OH, SORRY.
WHAT DO YOU SEE? WHAT DO YOU SEE?
WE GOT A HEAD, WE GOT SHOULDERS
WE GOT ARMS, OH LOOK AT THE LITTLE...
THE FINGERS...
OH, A CHEST AND A STOMACH
AND... IT'S A BOY, DEFINITELY A BOY!
ALL RIGHT! OKAY
LEGS, KNEES AND FEET.
HE'S HERE.
HE'S A PERSON.
OH! LOOK AT THAT.
WHAT DOES HE LOOK LIKE?
KIND OF LIKE MY UNCLE ED COVERED IN JELL O.
REALLY?
YOU GUYS, HE'S BEAUTIFUL!
OH, THANKS, PHEEBS.
NO SHOUTING, BUT WE STILL NEED A NAME
FOR THIS LITTLE GUY.
WELL, HOW ABOUT BEN?
I LIKE BEN.
BEN.
BEN'S GOOD.
HOW COME YOU NEVER MENTIONED BEN BEFORE?
WE, UH, WE JUST COOKED IT UP.
THAT'S WHAT WE WERE OFF DOING.
HI.
CAN WE COME IN?
YEAH, COME IN, COME IN.
EVERYBODY, THERE'S SOME ONE
I'D LIKE YOU TO MEET.
UH, THIS IS BEN.
HI, BEN.
BEN, THIS IS EVERYBODY.
HEY, BEN.
SUSAN, HE LOOKS JUST LIKE YOU.
OH, GOD, I CAN'T BELIEVE
ONE OF US ACTUALLY HAS ONE OF THESE.
I KNOW. I STILL AM ONE OF THESE.
ROSS?
YEAH?
CAN I...?
THE HEAD, THE HEAD.
HI, BEN. HI.
I'M YOUR AUNT MONICA.
YES, I AM.
I...
I WILL ALWAYS HAVE GUM.
BEN, I WANT YOU TO KNOW
THAT THERE MAY BE SOME TIMES WHEN I MAY NOT BE AROUND
UM, LIKE THIS...
BUT I'LL STILL ALWAYS COME BACK...
LIKE THIS.
AND SOMETIMES I MAY BE AWAY LONGER, LIKE THIS...
BUT I'LL STILL ALWAYS COME BACK...
LIKE THIS.
AND SOMETIMES, I'LL WANT YOU TO STEAL THIRD
AND I'LL GO LIKE THIS.
HE IS SO AMAZING.
OH, I KNOW.
LOOK AT HIM.
BEN? BEN?
HEY, BEN.
NOTHING.
I DON'T THINK THAT'S HIS NAME.
OH, LOOK, LOOK
HE'S CLOSING HIS EYES.
OH, LOOK, HE'S OPENING HIS EYES.
HE DOESN'T DO MUCH, DOES HE?
NO. THIS IS PRETTY MUCH IT.
YOU GUYS WANT TO GET SOME COFFEE?
YEAH. YEAH.
SEE YOU GUYS LATER.
HE'S CLOSING HIS EYES AGAIN.