OH, LOOK! LOOK, LOOK! THERE'S JOEY'S PICTURE.
THIS IS SO EXCITING.
YOU CAN ALWAYS SPOT SOMEONE
WHO'S NEVER SEEN ONE OF HIS PLAYS BEFORE.
NOTICE-- NO FEAR, NO SENSE OF IMPENDING DOOM.
LOOK-- "THE ROLE OF MAN #3
WILL NOT BE PLAYED BY VIC SHAPIRO."
WELL, WE CAME ON THE WRONG NIGHT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I FORGOT TO BRING A MAGAZINE.
COME ON, YOU GUYS. THIS MIGHT BE GOOD.
I DON'T KNOW.
THE EXCLAMATION POINT IN THE TITLE SCARES ME.
YOU KNOW, IT'S NOT JUST FREUD; IT'S FREUD!
SHH. THE MAGIC IS ABOUT TO HAPPEN.
WELL, EVA
WE'VE DONE SOME EXCELLENT WORK HERE
AND I WOULD HAVE TO SAY
YOUR PROBLEM IS QUITE CLEAR.
I FEEL VIOLATED.
DID ANYONE ELSE FEEL LIKE THEY JUST WANTED
TO PEEL THE SKIN OFF THEIR BODY
TO HAVE SOMETHING ELSE TO DO?
ROSS, 10:00.
IS IT? FEELS LIKE 2:00.
NO, 10:00.
WHAT?
THERE'S A BEAUTIFUL WOMAN AT 8:00, 9:00, 10:00.
OH. HELLO.
SHE'S AMAZING!
SHE MAKES THE WOMEN I DREAM ABOUT
LOOK LIKE SHORT, FAT, BALD MEN.
WELL, GO OVER TO HER.
SHE'S NOT WITH ANYONE.
OH... YEAH, RIGHT. AND WHAT WOULD MY OPENING LINE BE?
"EXCUSE ME...
COME ON, SHE'S A PERSON.
YOU CAN DO IT.
OH, PLEASE. COULD SHE BE MORE OUT OF MY LEAGUE?
ROSS, BACK ME UP HERE.
HE COULD NEVER GET A WOMAN LIKE THAT IN A MILLION YEARS.
THANK YOU, BUDDY.
YOU KNOW, YOU ALWAYS SEE THESE REALLY BEAUTIFUL WOMEN
WITH THESE REALLY NOTHING GUYS.
YOU COULD BE ONE OF THOSE GUYS.
YOU COULD DO THAT. YOU THINK?
YEAH. ABSOLUTELY.
OH, GOD. I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M EVEN CONSIDERING THIS.
I'M VERY, VERY AWARE OF MY TONGUE.
COME ON, COME ON.
YES.
STAND BACK, EVERYONE.
INCOMING EGO SHRAPNEL.
ALL RIGHT, I CAN DO THIS.
YES?
HI.
UM... OKAY, NEXT WORD WOULD BE...
UH, CHANDLER...
CHANDLER IS MY NAME.
AND UH... UH... HI.
YES, YOU SAID THAT.
YES... YES, I DID.
BUT WHAT I DIDN'T SAY...
WHAT I WANTED TO SAY WAS
WOULD YOU LIKE TO GO OUT WITH ME SOMETIME?
THANK YOU. GOOD NIGHT.
CHANDLER...
HEY! I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU COULD DANCE. YOU WERE IN A PLAY!
WHAT DID YOU THINK?
YOU WERE IN A PLAY!
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU COULD DANCE.
COME ON, YOU GUYS. IT WASN'T THAT BAD.
I WAS THE LEAD. IT WAS BETTER
THAN THAT THING I DID WITH THE TROLLS.
AT LEAST YOU GOT TO SEE MY HEAD.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
SAW YOUR HEAD. SAW YOUR HEAD.
AND HEY, HEY-- HOW ABOUT THAT GERMAN ACCENT?
OH, YA, YA.
ALL OF YOUR Ws WERE Vs.
SHE SAID YES! SHE SAID YES!
GREAT!
AWFUL PLAY, MAN.
WHOA!
HER NAME'S AURORA AND SHE'S ITALIAN
AND SHE PRONOUNCES MY NAME "CHAND LER."
"CHAND LER."
I THINK I LIKE IT BETTER THAT WAY.
OH, LISTEN-- THE USHER GAVE ME THIS TO GIVE TO YOU.
"THE ESTELLE LEONARD TALENT AGENCY."
WOW! AN AGENCY LEFT ME ITS CARD.
MAYBE THEY WANT TO SIGN ME.
BASED ON THIS PLAY?
BASED ON THIS PLAY.
LOOK, LOOK, LOOK--
THERE'S A NOTE ON THE BACK.
"LOVED YOUR WORK.
CALL ME A SAP."
SHE WAS OBVIOUSLY VERY MOVED.
AND YOU SHOULD PROBABLY CALL HER FAIRLY QUICKLY.
YEAH, AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
COME IN.
HI. UM, I'M HERE TO SEE ESTELLE LEONARD.
JUST A MOMENT.
LET ME SEE IF SHE'S IN.
HELLO.
YOU'RE ESTELLE LEONARD?
I KNOW, I KNOW, YOU WEREN'T EXPECTING
SOMEONE SO FANTASTICALLY BEAUTIFUL.
SO... LOVE LUMP...
TAKE A LOAD OFF ALREADY, DARLING.
SIT. SIT, ALREADY.
MISS LEONARD, I CAN'T TELL YOU
HOW EXCITED I AM JUST TO EVEN BE HERE.
WHY NOT?
WELL, WHAT I MEANT WAS...
YOU DON'T MIND IF I EAT WHILE WE TALK, DO YOU?
NO, NO.
SO, JOEY, SWEETHEART, LET ME ASK YOU A QUESTION.
DID YOU EVER SEE THE MOVIE SLEEPLESS IN SEATTLE?
YEAH. WOW. DO YOU REPRESENT THOSE ACTORS?
NO.
BUT YOU KNOW, AT THE END OF THE MOVIE
THE PART WHERE THEY'RE ALL SO HAPPY WITH EACH OTHER?
THAT'S GOING TO BE YOU AND ME.
WOW. YOU MEAN YOU WANT TO SIGN ME?
NO. I WANT TO GO UP ON TOP
OF THE EMPIRE STATE BUILDING AND MAKE OUT.
OF COURSE I WANT TO SIGN YOU!
OH, MISS LEONARD, I'M SO...
OH, GOD!
WHOA! RIDE THEM, COWBOY!
I'M SORRY.
OH, GOD...
I DON'T SEE IT. I DON'T SEE IT.
TRY TO LOOKPAST THE BOOK.
YEAH, YOU JUST HAVE TO UNFOCUS YOUR EYES.
WHO'S FOCUSING?
THERE'S NOTHING TO FOCUS ON.
OH, IT'S THE STATUE OF LIBERTY! RIGHT!
WHAT?!
WHERE'S THE STATUE OF LIBERTY? WHERE?
RIGHT THERE.
GOD, I CAN'T NOT SEE IT NOW.
HEY, KIDS.
CHANDLER, COME HERE. DO YOU SEE ANYTHING RIGHT HERE?
YEAH, LOOKS LIKE A BOAT.
"A BOAT." HA.
YEAH, RIGHT THERE IN FRONT OF THE STATUE OF LIBERTY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I'VE BEEN HERE ALMOST SEVEN SECONDS
AND YOU HAVEN'T ASKED HOW MY DATE WENT.
HOW WAS YOUR DATE, CHAND LER?
IT WAS UNBELIEVABLE.
I'VE NEVER MET ANYONE LIKE HER.
SHE'S HAD THE MOST AMAZING LIFE.
SHE WAS IN THE ISRAELI ARMY...
LUCKILY, NONE OF THE BULLETS HIT THE ENGINE BLOCK.
SO, WE MADE IT TO THE BORDER
BUT JUST BARELY, AND I...
I'VE BEEN TALKING ABOUT MYSELF ALL NIGHT LONG.
I'M SORRY.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
TELL ME ONE OF YOUR STORIES.
ALL RIGHT, ONCE...
ONCE I GOT ON THE SUBWAY, RIGHT?
AND IT WAS AT NIGHT
AND I RODE IT ALL THE WAY TO BROOKLYN
JUST FOR THE HELL OF IT.
WE TALKED TILL, LIKE, 2:00.
IT WAS THIS PERFECT EVENING...
MORE OR LESS.
ALL OF SUDDEN, WE REALIZE WE'RE IN YEMEN.
I'M SORRY. SOWEIS?
WE WOULD BE ME AND RICK.
WHO'S RICK?
MY HUSBAND.
EW! EW! EW!
OH, SO YOU'RE DIVORCED?
NO.
OH, I'M SORRY.
SO YOU'RE WIDOWED... HOPEFULLY?
NO. I'M STILL MARRIED.
SO, TELL ME, HOW DO YOU THINK
YOUR HUSBAND WOULD FEEL ABOUT YOU SITTING HERE WITH ME
SLIDING YOUR FOOT SO FAR UP MY PANT LEG
YOU CAN COUNT THE CHANGE
IN MY POCKET?
DON'T WORRY. I IMAGINE
HE'D BE OKAY WITH YOU
BECAUSE REALLY HE'S OKAY
WITH ETHAN.
ETHAN?
THERE'S AN ETHAN?
MM... ETHAN IS MY...
BOYFRIEND.
WHAT?!
SO, EXPLAIN SOMETHING TO ME, HERE.
WHAT KIND OF RELATIONSHIP DO YOU IMAGINE US HAVING
IF YOU ALREADY HAVE A HUSBAND AND A BOYFRIEND?
I SUPPOSE MAINLY SEXUAL.
HUH.
I'M SORRY IT DIDN'T WORK OUT.
WHAT NOT WORK OUT?
I'M SEEING HER AGAIN ON THURSDAY.
DIDN'T YOU LISTEN TO THE STORY?
THIS IS TWISTED.
HOW COULD YOU GET INVOLVED WITH A WOMAN LIKE THIS?
I HAD SOME TROUBLE WITH IT AT FIRST, TOO
BUT THE WAY I LOOK AT IT, I GET ALL THE GOOD STUFF.
ALL THE FUN, ALL THE TALKING, ALL THE SEX
AND NONE OF THE RESPONSIBILITY.
THIS IS EVERY GUY'S FANTASY.
OH, YEAH, THAT IS NOT TRUE.
ROSS, IS THIS YOUR FANTASY?
NO, OF COURSE NOT.
YEAH. YEAH, IT IS.
SO YOU GUYS DON'T MIND GOING OUT WITH SOMEONE ELSE
WHO'S GOING OUT WITH SOMEONE ELSE?
I COULDN'T DO IT.
GOOD FOR YOU, JOEY.
WHEN I'M WITH A WOMAN, I NEED TO KNOW THAT I'M GOING OUT
WITH MORE PEOPLE THAN SHE IS.
YOU KNOW, ONE TIME I WENT OUT WITH A GUY
WHO HAD JUST GOTTEN DIVORCED
AND IT WAS REALLY HARD.
HIS KIDS LIKED ME BETTER THAN HIM.
PHOEBE, WHAT DOES THIS
HAVE TO DO WITH CHANDLER'S THING?
OH. NOTHING.
BUT I DIDN'T HAVE ANYTHING ON THAT TOPIC
SO I WENT ANOTHER WAY.
WELL, YOU KNOW
MONOGAMY CAN BE A TRICKY CONCEPT.
I MEAN, ANTHROPOLOGICALLY SPEAKING...
FINE, FINE. ALL RIGHT, NOW YOU'LL NEVER KNOW.
WE'RE KIDDING. GO. TELL US.
COME ON, ROSS.
ALL RIGHT.
THERE'S A THEORY PUT FORTH BY RICHARD LEAKEY...
TA DAH!
ARE WE GREETING EACH OTHER THIS WAY NOW
BECAUSE I LIKE THAT.
LOOK. I CLEANED!
I DID THE WINDOWS, I DID THE FLOORS
I EVEN USED ALL THOSE
VACUUM ATTACHMENTS
EXCEPT FOR THAT LITTLE ROUND ONE
WITH THE BRISTLES.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT'S FOR.
NOBODY KNOWS AND WE'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO ASK.
WELL, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
VERY CLEAN.
REALLY, IT LOOKS GREAT.
OH, I SEE YOU MOVED THE GREEN OTTOMAN.
UH OH. UH OH. UH OH.
HOW DID THAT HAPPEN?
I DON'T KNOW.
I THOUGHT IT LOOKED BETTER THERE.
AND ALSO IT'S AN EXTRA SEAT AROUND THE COFFEE TABLE.
IT'S INTERESTING.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT? JUST FOR FUN
LET'S SEE WHAT IT LOOKED LIKE IN THE OLD SPOT.
JUST TO COMPARE.
LET'S SEE.
HA! WELL, IT LOOKS GOOD THERE, TOO.
LET'S JUST LEAVE IT THERE FOR A WHILE.
CAN'T BELIEVE YOU TRIED TO MOVE THE GREEN OTTOMAN.
THANK GOD YOU DIDN'T TRY
AND FAN OUT THE MAGAZINES.
SHE'LL SCRATCH YOUR EYES RIGHT OUT.
GUYS, I AM NOT THAT BAD.
YEAH, YOU ARE, MONICA.
REMEMBER WHEN I LIVED WITH YOU?
YOU WERE LIKE A LITTLE...
THAT IS SO UNFAIR.
OH, COME ON. WHEN WE WERE KIDS
YOURS WAS THE ONLY RAGGEDY ANN DOLL
THAT WASN'T RAGGEDY.
OKAY, SO I'M RESPONSIBLE.
I'M ORGANIZED.
BUT, HEY, I CAN BE A KOOK.
ALL RIGHT, YOU MADCAP GAL.
TRY TO IMAGINE THIS.
THE PHONE BILL ARRIVES
BUT YOU DON'T PAY IT RIGHT AWAY.
WHY NOT?
BECAUSE YOU'RE A KOOK.
INSTEAD, YOU WAIT UNTIL THEY SEND YOU A NOTICE.
I COULD DO THAT.
OKAY, OKAY, THEN YOU LET ME GO GROCERY SHOPPING...
NO PROBLEM.
I'M NOT DONE YET.
OH.
AND I BUY LAUNDRY DETERGENT
BUT IT'S NOT THE ONE WITH THE EASY POUR SPOUT.
WHY WOULD SOMEONE DO THAT?
ONE MIGHT WONDER.
BUT... I WOULD BE FINE WITH THAT.
SOMEONE'S LEFT
A GLASS ON THE COFFEE TABLE. THERE'S NO COASTER.
IT'S A COLD DRINK, IT'S A HOT DAY.
LITTLE BEADS OF CONDENSATION ARE INCHING
THEIR WAY CLOSER AND CLOSER TO THE SURFACE OF THE WOOD.
STOP IT!
OH, MY GOD.
IT'S TRUE.
WHO AM I?
MONICA, YOU'RE MOM.
UH HUH... UH HUH...
OH, MY GOD!
OKAY.
OKAY, I'LL BE THERE.
HUH, THAT WAS MY AGENT.
MY AGENT HAS JUST GOTTEN ME A JOB...
IN THE NEW AL PACINO MOVIE!
WHAT? YOU'RE KIDDING.
THAT'S GREAT!
WHAT'S THE PART?
CAN YOU BELIEVE THIS?
AL PACINO!
THIS GUY'S THE REASON I BECAME AN ACTOR.
"I'M OUT OF ORDER?
"YOU'RE OUT OF ORDER.
THIS WHOLE COURTROOM'S OUT OF ORDER."
SERIOUSLY, WHAT'S THE PART?
"JUST WHEN I THOUGHT I WAS OUT
THEY PULL ME BACK IN."
SERIOUSLY, JOEY, WHAT'S THE PART?
UH...
YOU'RE  WHAT?
I'M HIS BUTT DOUBLE, OKAY?
I PLAY AL PACINO'S BUTT.
ALL RIGHT?
HE GOES INTO THE SHOWER
AND THEN I'M HIS BUTT.
OH, MY GOD.
COME ON, YOU GUYS.
THIS IS A REAL MOVIE, AND AL PACINO'S IN IT
AND THAT'S BIG.
OH, NO, IT'S TERRIFIC.
IT'S, IT'S... NO, YOU DESERVE THIS.
AFTER YOUR YEARS OF STRUGGLING
YOU'VE FINALLY BEEN ABLE TO CRACK YOUR WAY
INTO SHOW BUSINESS.
OKAY, FINE, MAKE JOKES.
I DON'T CARE.
THIS IS A BIG BREAK FOR ME.
YOU'RE RIGHT, YOU'RE RIGHT, IT IS.
YEAH.
SO, YOU GOING TO INVITE US ALL TO THE BIG OPENING?
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
YEAH?
HERE. I NEED TO BORROW SOME MOISTURIZER.
FOR WHAT?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
TODAY'S THE BIG DAY.
AND YOU GOT TWEEZERS?
I THINK I HAVE A ROGUE HAIR.
OH, GOD. OKAY, GO INTO THE BATHROOM
USE WHATEVER YOU WANT.
JUST DON'T EVER TELL ME WHAT YOU DID IN THERE.
THANK YOU.
WHERE'S JOEY? HIS MOM'S ON THE PHONE.
HE'S IN THE BATHROOM.
I DON'T THINK YOU DON'T WANT TO GO IN THERE.
OH, COME ON. WE'RE ROOMMATES.
MY EYES! MY EYES!
I WARNED YOU.
WHO IS BEING LOUD?
OH, THAT WOULD BE MONICA.
HEY, LISTEN, CAN I BORROW
A COUPLE OF THINGS?
AURORA SPENT THE NIGHT.
I REALLY WANT TO MAKE HER BREAKFAST.
OH, YOU GOT THE WHOLE NIGHT, HUH?
YEAH. WELL, I ONLY HAVE 20 MINUTES
TILL ETHAN, SO YOU KNOW...
OOH, DO I SENSE A LITTLE BIT OF RESENTMENT?
NO, NO, NO RESENTMENT.
BELIEVE ME, IT'S WORTH IT, OKAY.
YOU KNOW HOW IN A RELATIONSHIP
YOU HAVE THESE KEY MOMENTS
THAT YOU KNOW YOU'LL REMEMBER FOR THE REST OF YOUR LIFE?
WELL, EVERY... SINGLE... SECOND IS LIKE THAT WITH AURORA.
AND I'VE JUST WASTED ABOUT 35 OF THEM TALKING TO YOU PEOPLE.
SO, UH, MONICA, CAN YOU HELP ME WITH THE DOOR?
SURE.
OH, UM, CHANDLER, YOU KNOW
THE OLD MONICA WOULD REMIND YOU
TO SCRUB THAT TEFLON PAN WITH A PLASTIC BRUSH.
BUT I'M NOT GOING TO DO THAT.
UH, EXCUSE ME.
COULD YOU SEE IF THEY COULD WARM IT UP IN HERE?
I'M A LITTLE CONCERNED ABOUT GOOSE BUMPS.
OKAY, EVERYBODY READY?
LISTEN, I JUST WANT TO THANK YOU FOR THIS GREAT OPPORTUNITY.
BUT, I MEAN, LISTEN--
I KNOW THIS IS JUST A FIRST STEP
BUT I HOPE THAT SOMEDAY...
LOSE THE ROBE.
RIGHT. OKAY. LOSING THE ROBE.
OKAY. AND THE ROBE IS LOST.
OKAY, EVERYBODY, I'D LIKE TO GET THIS
IN ONE TAKE, PLEASE. LET'S ROLL IT.
WATER'S WORKING.
AND... ACTION.
AND... CUT.
HEY, BUTT GUY, WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?
WELL... I'M SHOWERING.
NO. THAT WAS "CLENCHING."
OH. WELL, THE WAY I SEE IT, THE GUY'S UPSET, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, HIS WIFE'S DEAD, HIS BROTHER'S MISSING.
I THINK HIS BUTT WOULD BE ANGRY HERE.
I THINK HIS BUTT
WOULD LIKE TO GET THIS SHOT BEFORE LUNCH.
ONCE AGAIN, ROLLING.
WATER WORKING.
AND... ACTION.
AND... CUT.
WHAT WAS THAT?
I WAS GOING FOR QUIET DESPERATION.
BUT IF YOU HAVE TO ASK...
GOD, I LOVE THESE FINGERS.
THANK YOU.
NO, ACTUALLY I MEANT MY FINGERS.
LOOK AT THEM.
LOOK HOW HAPPY THEY ARE.
OH... OH, MY GOD, I'M LATE.
OH, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
DON'T GO, DON'T GO.
OKAY, OKAY.
NO, I HAVE TO.
LOOK AT THAT-- SHE'S LEAVING.
I'M SORRY. HE'LL BE WAITING FOR ME.
WELL, I THOUGHT YOU TALKED TO RICK.
IT'S... NOT RICK.
BUT ETHAN-- HE GOT TO SPEND THE WHOLE DAY WITH YOU.
NO, IT'S... IT'S ANDREW.
I KNOW THERE'LL BE MANY MOMENTS IN YEARS TO COME
WHEN I'LL REGRET ASKING THE FOLLOWING QUESTION, BUT...
AND ANDREW IS...?
HE'S... NEW.
SO, WHAT YOU'RE SAYING
IS YOU'RE NOT COMPLETELY FULFILLED
BY RICK, ETHAN AND MYSELF?
NO, THAT'S NOT EXACTLY WHAT...
MOST WOMEN WOULD KILL FOR THREE GUYS LIKE US.
SO WHAT DO YOU WANT?
YOU.
YOU HAVE ME.
NO, NO, JUST YOU.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
LOSE THE OTHER GUYS.
LIKE... ALL OF THEM?
COME ON, WE'RE GREAT TOGETHER!
WHY NOT?
WHY CAN'T WE JUST HAVE WHAT WE HAVE NOW--
WHY CAN'T WE JUST TALK AND LAUGH AND MAKE LOVE
WITHOUT FEELING OBLIGATED TO ONE ANOTHER?
AND UP UNTIL TONIGHT
I THOUGHT THAT'S WHAT YOU WANTED, TOO.
YOU KNOW, PART OF ME WANTS THAT
BUT IT'S LIKE I'M TWO GUYS, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, ONE GUY'S SAYING, "SHUT UP! THIS IS GREAT!"
BUT THERE'S THIS OTHER GUY--
ACTUALLY IT'S THE GUY WHO WELLS UP
EVERY TIME THE GRINCH'S HEART GROWS THREE SIZES
AND BREAKS THAT MEASURING DEVICE?--
AND HE'S SAYING, YOU KNOW
"THIS IS TOO HARD! GET OUT! GET OUT!"
SO, WHICH ONE OF THE TWO GUYS WILL YOU LISTEN TO?
I DON'T KNOW.
I HAVE TO LISTEN TO BOTH OF THEM.
THEY DON'T EXACTLY
LET EACH OTHER FINISH.
WHICH ONE?
THE SECOND GUY.
I SEE.
WELL...
CALL ME IF YOU CHANGE YOUR MIND.
SORRY. THE FIRST GUY RUNS THE LIPS.
LOOK AT IT THIS WAY-- YOU DUMPED HER.
RIGHT? I MEAN, THIS WOMAN WAS UNBELIEVABLY SEXY
AND BEAUTIFUL, INTELLIGENT, UNATTAINABLE...
TELL ME WHY YOU DID THIS AGAIN?
HEY.
HEY, MOVIE STAR.
HEY, WAIT. AREN'T YOU THE GUY WHO PLAYS THE BUTT
IN THE NEW AL PACINO MOVIE?
NOPE.
NO? WHAT HAPPENED, BIG GUY?
"BIG GUY"?
IT FELT LIKE A "BIG GUY" MOMENT.
I GOT FIRED.
OH...
THEY SAID I "ACTED" TOO MUCH
WITH IT.
I TOLD EVERYBODY ABOUT THIS.
NOW EVERYONE IS GOING TO GO TO THE THEATER EXPECTING TO SEE ME...
JOE, YOU KNOW WHAT? NO ONE IS GOING TO BE ABLE TO TELL.
MY MOM WILL.
THERE'S SOMETHING SO SWEET...
AND DISTURBING ABOUT THAT.
YOU KNOW, I'VE DONE NOTHING BUT CRAPPY PLAYS FOR SIX YEARS
AND I FINALLY GET MY SHOT, AND I BLOW IT!
MAYBE THIS WASN'T YOUR SHOT.
YEAH. I THINK WHEN IT'S YOUR SHOT
YOU KNOW, YOU KNOW IT'S YOUR SHOT.
DID... DID IT FEEL LIKE YOUR SHOT?
HARD TO TELL.
I WAS NAKED.
I DON'T THINK THIS WAS YOUR SHOT.
I DON'T EVEN THINK YOU JUST GET ONE SHOT.
I REALLY BELIEVE BIG THINGS ARE GOING TO HAPPEN FOR YOU.
I DO, AND YOU'VE GOT TO JUST KEEP THINKING ABOUT THE DAY
THAT SOME KID IS GOING TO RUN UP TO HIS FRIENDS AND GO
"I GOT THE PART! I GOT THE PART!
I'M GOING TO BE JOEY TRIBBIANI'S ASS!"
YOU THINK? THAT'S SO NICE!
OH... COME ON.
I'M SORRY, JOEY.
I'M GOING TO GO TO BED, GUYS.
GOOD NIGHT, MONICA.
MON... YOU'RE GOING TO LEAVE YOUR SHOES OUT HERE?
OH.
UH HUH.
REALLY? JUST CASUALLY STREWN ABOUT
IN THAT RECKLESS, HAPHAZARD MANNER?
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
I'LL GET THEM TOMORROW... OR NOT.
WHENEVER.
SHE IS A KOOK.
MM HMM.
IF IT BOTHERS YOU THAT MUCH, JUST GO OUT AND GET THE SHOES.
NO. DON'T DO THIS.
THIS IS STUPID!
I DON'T HAVE TO PROVE ANYTHING.
I'M GOING TO GO GET THEM.
BUT THEN EVERYONE WILL KNOW.
UNLESS I GET THEM
AND THEN WAKE UP REALLY EARLY AND PUT THEM BACK.
I NEED HELP.
? ALL YOU WANT IS A DINKLE... ?
OH, NO. NOT THAT SONG.
? ALL YOU ENVY'S A SCHWANG ?
COME ON, YOU GUYS.
? A THING THROUGH WHICH YOU CAN TINKLE ?
? OR PLAY WITH OR SIMPLY LET HANG ?
HEY!
? ALL YOU WANT IS A DINKLE ?
? WHAT YOU ENVY'S A SCHWANG ?
? A THING THROUGH WHICH YOU CAN TINKLE ?
? OR PLAY WITH OR SIMPLY LET HANG. ?
HEY!