EVERYBODY? SHH, SHH.
CENTRAL PERK IS PROUD TO PRESENT
THE MUSIC OF MISS PHOEBE BUFFAY!
HI. I WANT TO START WITH A SONG THAT'S ABOUT THAT MOMENT
WHEN YOU SUDDENLY REALIZE WHAT LIFE IS REALLY ALL ABOUT.
OKAY. HERE WE GO.
OKAY.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
WHAT THE..?
OH, GREAT.
THIS IS JUST...
WOW, THIS IS SO COOL.
THE ENTIRE CITY
IS BLACKED OUT.
MOM SAYS IT'S ALL OF MANHATTAN
PARTS OF BROOKLYN AND QUEENS, AND THEY HAVE NO IDEA
WHEN IT'S COMING BACK ON.
GUYS, THIS IS BIG.
PANTS AND A SWEATER? WHY, MOM?
WHO AM I GOING TO MEET IN A BLACKOUT
POWER COMPANY GUYS? ELIGIBLE LOOTERS?
CAN WE TALK ABOUT THIS LATER?
OKAY.
CAN I BORROW THE PHONE?
I WANT TO CALL MY APARTMENT
AND CHECK ON MY GRANDMA.
WHAT'S MY NUMBER?
WELL, I NEVER CALL ME.
OH, MY GOD. IT'S HER.
IT'S THAT VICTORIA'S SECRET MODEL--
SOMETHING "GOODACRE."
HI, MOM. IT'S JILL.
SHE'S RIGHT. IT'S JILL.
OH, MY GOD.
I AM TRAPPED IN AN A.T.M. VESTIBULE
WITH JILL GOODACRE.
IS IT A VESTIBULE?
MAYBE IT'S AN ATRIUM.
YEAH. THAT IS THE PART TO FOCUS ON, YOU IDIOT.
YEAH, I'M FINE.
I'M STUCK AT THE BANK IN AN A.T.M. VESTIBULE.
JILL SAYS "VESTIBULE."
I'M GOING WITH "VESTIBULE."
I'M FINE.
NO, I'M NOT ALONE.
I DON'T KNOW.
SOME GUY.
OH! "SOME GUY."
I AM "SOME GUY."
"HEY, JILL, I SAW YOU WITH SOME GUY LAST NIGHT.
YES. HE WAS SOME GUY."
HEY, EVERYONE.
AND OFFICIATING AT TONIGHT'S BLACKOUT
IS RABBI TRIBBIANI.
WELL, CHANDLER'S OLD ROOMMATE WAS JEWISH
AND THESE ARE THE ONLY CANDLES WE HAVE
SO, HAPPY HANUKKAH, EVERYONE.
EWW, LOOK.
UGLY NAKED GUY
LIT A BUNCH OF CANDLES.
OOH... OOH...
OOH!
OH, THAT HAD TO HURT!
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
IT'S BEEN 14 MINUTES
AND YOU STILL HAVE NOT SAID ONE WORD.
OH, GOD. DO SOMETHING.
JUST MAKE CONTACT. SMILE.
THERE YOU GO.
YOU'RE DEFINITELY SCARING HER.
HELLO?
OH, HI, MOM.
MOM...
MOM, YOU'RE TRIPPING.
DEXTER'S A DOG.
WELL, THE BLACKOUT'S SCARING HIM.
WELL, YOU'D PEE IN DAD'S SHOES, TOO, IF YOU DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT WAS GOING ON.
ALL RIGHT. CALL ME BACK.
MOTHERS.
YEAH.
ATTABOY!
A WORD.
THAT WASN'T SO HARD-- "MOTHERS."
YEAH, MOTHERS.
YEAH.
DON'T SMILE.
UH, WOULD YOU LIKE TO CALL SOMEBODY?
YEAH. ABOUT 300 GUYS I WENT TO HIGH SCHOOL WITH.
THANKS.
HELLO.
HEY, IT'S ME.
IT'S CHANDLER.
ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH, I'M FINE.
I'M TRAPPED IN AN A.T.M. VESTIBULE
WITH JILL GOODACRE.
WHAT?!
I'M TRAPPED IN AN A.T.M. VESTIBULE
WITH JILL GOODACRE.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT YOU SAID.
OH, PUT JOEY ON THE PHONE.
WHAT'S UP, MAN?
I'M TRAPPED...
IN AN A.T.M. VESTIBULE
WITH JILL GOODACRE.
OH, MY GOD!
HE'S TRAPPED IN AN A.T.M. VESTIBULE
WITH JILL GOODACRE!
CHANDLER, LISTEN, LISTEN!
YEAH, LIKE THAT THOUGHT NEVER ENTERED MY MIND.
OKAY, SOMEBODY, SOMEBODY.
I'LL GO, I'LL GO.
SENIOR YEAR OF COLLEGE ON A POOL TABLE.
POOL TABLE! OOH HOO!
THAT'S MY SISTER.
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
MY WEIRDEST PLACE WOULD HAVE TO BE...
THE WOMEN'S ROOM ON THE SECOND FLOOR
OF THE NEW YORK CITY PUBLIC LIBRARY.
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT WERE YOU DOING IN A LIBRARY?
HEY, PHEEBS, WHAT ABOUT YOU?
OH, UM, MILWAUKEE.
IT'S A REALLY WEIRD PLACE.
UH, ROSS?
DISNEYLAND, 1989
"IT'S A SMALL WORLD AFTER ALL."
NO WAY.
YEAH, THE RIDE BROKE DOWN
SO CAROL AND I WENT
BEHIND A COUPLE OF THOSE MECHANICAL
DUTCH CHILDREN.
THEY FIXED THE RIDE
AND WE WERE ASKED NEVER TO RETURN
TO THE MAGIC KINGDOM.
SO, UH, LET'S SEE  THAT WOULD LEAVE...
OOH, RACHEL?
COME ON, I ALREADY WENT.
YOU DID NOT.
YES, I DID.
COME ON.
ALL RIGHT, UH...
THE WEIRDEST PLACE WOULD HAVE TO BE
OH... THE FOOT OF THE BED.
STEP BACK.
WE HAVE A WINNER.
HEY, YOU KNOW, THIS MUST BE WHAT THE FRIDGE LOOKS LIKE WITH THE DOOR CLOSED.
SPOOKY.
ANYBODY HUNGRY?
WE'VE GOT A KLONDIKE... SOUP.
I'VE NEVER HAD A RELATIONSHIP
WITH THAT KIND OF PASSION
WHERE YOU HAVE TO HAVE SOMEBODY RIGHT THERE IN THE MIDDLE
OF A THEME PARK.
WELL, IT WAS THE ONLY THING TO DO THERE
THAT DIDN'T HAVE A LINE.
WELL, SEE? BARRY WOULDN'T EVEN KISS ME
ON A MINIATURE GOLF COURSE.
COME ON.
NO.
HE SAID WE WERE HOLDING UP THE PEOPLE BEHIND US.
AND YOU DIDN'T MARRY HIM BECAUSE...
DO YOU THINK THERE ARE PEOPLE THAT GO THROUGH LIFE
NEVER HAVING THAT KIND OF..?
PROBABLY.
REALLY?
BUT I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING
PASSION IS WAY OVERRATED.
YEAH, RIGHT.
IT IS. EVENTUALLY, IT KIND OF BURNS OUT
BUT, HOPEFULLY
WHAT YOU'RE LEFT WITH IS TRUST AND SECURITY
AND, WELL, IN THE CASE
OF MY EX WIFE, LESBIANISM.
SO FOR ALL THOSE WHO MISS OUT ON THAT PASSION THING
THERE'S ALL THAT OTHER GOOD STUFF.
OKAY.
BUT I DON'T THINK THAT WILL BE YOU.
YOU DON'T?
HMM.
SEE, I SEE, UH... BIG PASSION IN YOUR FUTURE.
REALLY?
MM HMM.
YOU DO? I DO.
OH, ROSS, YOU'RE SO GREAT.
IT'S NEVER GOING TO HAPPEN.
WHAT?
YOU AND RACHEL.
WHA... ME AND RA... WHA..?
WHY NOT?
BECAUSE YOU WAITED TOO LONG TO MAKE YOUR MOVE
AND NOW YOU'RE IN "THE FRIEND ZONE."
NO, NO, NO, I'M NOT IN THE ZONE.
NO. ROSS, YOU'RE MAYOR OF THE ZONE.
LOOK, I'M TAKING MY TIME, ALL RIGHT?
I'M LAYING THE GROUNDWORK.
YEAH, EVERY DAY, I GET JUST A LITTLE BIT CLOSER TO...
PRIESTHOOD.
ROSS, I'M TELLING YOU
SHE HAS NO IDEA WHAT YOU'RE THINKING.
OH, YEAH?
SHE JUST RAN HER FINGERS THROUGH MY HAIR.
WERE YOU MISSING THAT INTERACTION?
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
THIS IS RUNNING FINGERS  THROUGH YOUR HAIR, OKAY?
NOW, THIS...
IS A TOUSLE.
LOOK, ROSS, IF YOU DON'T ASK HER OUT SOON
YOU'LL END UP STUCK IN THE ZONE FOREVER.
I WILL, I WILL.
I'M JUST... SEE, I'M WAITING FOR THE, UH...
THE RIGHT MOMENT.
WHAT?
WHAT? NOW?
DUH..!
WHAT'S MESSING YOU UP?
THE WINE, THE CANDLES, THE MOONLIGHT, HUH?
JUST GO UP TO HER AND SAY, "LOOK, RACHEL..."
SHH SHH SHH!
WHAT ARE WE SHUSHING?
WE'RE SHUSHING BECAUSE... WE'RE TRYING TO HEAR SOMETHING.
WHAT?
SHH.
DON'T YOU HEAR THAT?
AHH!
SEE?
WOULD YOU LIKE SOME GUM?
OH, IS IT SUGARLESS?
NO. SORRY, IT'S NOT.
THEN, NO THANKS.
WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?
MENTAL NOTE: IF JILL GOODACRE OFFERS YOU GUM, YOU TAKE IT.
IF SHE OFFERS YOU MANGLED ANIMAL CARCASS, YOU TAKE IT.
? NEW YORK CITY HAS NO POWER ?
? AND THE MILK IS GETTING SOUR ?
? BUT TO ME IT IS NOT SCARY ?
? BECAUSE I STAY AWAY FROM DAIRY... ?
? LA LA LA LA LA LA LA... ?
OKAY, HERE GOES.
YOU GONNA DO IT?
WANT ME TO HELP?
YOU COME OUT THERE
YOU'RE A DEAD MAN.
ROSS...
GOOD LUCK, MAN.
THANKS.
OKAY.
WHERE YOU GOING?
OUTSIDE.
YOU CAN'T GO OUT THERE.
WHY NOT?
BECAUSE OF, UH... THE REASON.
AND THAT WOULD BE?
I, UH... I CAN'T TELL YOU.
JOEY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
OKAY, LISTEN, YOU GOT TO PROMISE
YOU'LL NEVER, EVER TELL ROSS THAT I TOLD YOU.
ABOUT WHAT?
HE'S PLANNING YOUR BIRTHDAY PARTY.
OH, MY GOD, I LOVE HIM.
AND YOU BETTER ACT SURPRISED.
ABOUT WHAT?
MY SURPRISE PARTY.
WHAT SURPRISE PARTY?
OH, STOP IT.
JOEY ALREADY TOLD ME.
WELL, HE DIDN'T TELL ME.
HEY, DON'T LOOK AT ME.
THIS IS ROSS'S THING.
THIS IS SO TYPICAL.
I'M THE LAST ONE TO KNOW EVERYTHING.
YOU ARE NOT. WE TELL YOU STUFF.
YUH HUH. I WAS THE LAST TO KNOW
WHEN CHANDLER GOT BIT BY THE PEACOCK AT THE ZOO.
LAST TO KNOW YOU HAD A CRUSH ON JOEY
WHEN HE WAS MOVING IN.
WHAT?
OH, LOOKS LIKE I WAS SECOND TO LAST.
YOU, UH... YOU HAD A CRUSH ON ME?
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, IT WASN'T A CRUSH.
IT WAS A...
A DENT.
BIG DENT?
OH... ALL RIGHT, LOOK
YOU WERE MOVING YOUR FURNITURE UPSTAIRS.
I THOUGHT YOU HAD... NICE ARMS.
THAT'S ALL.
NICE ARMS, HUH?
HEY, MON...
I'M MOVING THE CHAIR.
DO ANYTHING FOR YOU?
YOU KNOW, WITH ALL THE LIGHTS OUT
YOU CAN ACTUALLY SEE THE STARS.
MM. IT'S SO NICE.
MM.
HEY, I HAVE A QUESTION.
WELL, ACTUALLY, IT'S NOT SO MUCH A QUESTION
AS MORE OF A GENERAL WONDERING... MENT.
OKAY.
UH, HERE GOES.
UM, WELL, FOR A WHILE NOW, I'VE BEEN WANTING TO, UM...
OH...
YES, YES.
OH, WOOK AT
THE WIDDLE KITTY.
WHAT?
? ...TOP OF THE WORLD LOOKIN' ?
? DOWN ON CREATION ?
? AND THE ONLY EXPLANATION I CAN FIND ?
? IS THE LOVE THAT I'VE FOUND ?
? EVER SINCE YOU'VE BEEN AROUND ?
? YOU JUST PUT ME AT THE TOP OF THE WORLD ?
? TOP OF THE WORLD LOOKIN' ?
? DOWN ON CREATION AND THE ONLY... ?
ALL RIGHT, THIS IS JUST BACTINE.
IT WON'T HURT.
OW, OW.
SORRY. THAT WAS WAX.
THIS POOR LITTLE TOOTY
IS SCARED TO DEATH.
WE SHOULD FIND HIS OWNER.
LET'S PUT THE POOR LITTLE TOOTY IN THE HALL.
DURING A BLACKOUT?
SHE'LL GET TRAMPLED.
YEAH..?
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT-- DAMAGE CONTROL.
GET BACK TO THE GUM.
ON SECOND THOUGHT, GUM WOULD BE PERFECTION.
"GUM WOULD BE PERFECTION"?
"GUM WOULD BE PERFECTION."
COULD HAVE SAID, "GUM WOULD BE NICE."
COULD HAVE SAID, "I'LL HAVE A STICK."
BUT NO, NO, NO, NO, FOR ME GUM IS PERFECTION.
I LOATHE MYSELF.
OH, NO. THE MELLMANS.
THEY HATE ALL LIVING THINGS.
HI. WE JUST FOUND THIS CAT.
WE'RE LOOKING FOR THE OWNER.
UM, YEAH, IT'S, UH, IT'S MINE.
IT SEEMS TO HATE YOU.
ARE YOU SURE?
YEAH. GIVE ME MY CAT.
WELL, WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT'S HIS NAME?
UM, BU- BUTTONS.
BOB BUTTONS?
UH HUH. BOB BUTTONS.
OHH!
YOU ARE A VERY BAD MAN.
YOU OWE ME A CAT.
HERE, KITTY, KITTY, KITTY.
HERE, KITTY, KITTY.
WHERE DID YOU GO, LITTLE KITTY, KITTY, KITTY?
KITTY, KITTY, KITTY.
COME HERE, KITTY, KITTY, KITTY, KITTY
KITTY... KITTY... KITTY... KITTY...
KITTY...
HI.
BENE SERA.
OH, WOW.
HEY, MON, WANT TO GO FOR A RIDE IN MY RACE CAR?
I'LL BRING MY ARMS.
THAT'D BE NICE.
THEN WE CAN BRING MY WHEELBARROW
TO CARRY YOUR TEETH.
COME ON, LUCKY SIXES.
EVERYBODY?
THIS IS PAOLO.
PAOLO, I WANT YOU
TO MEET MY FRIENDS.
THIS IS MONICA.
HI.
AND JOEY.
AND ROSS.
HI.
HE DOESN'T SPEAK MUCH ENGLISH.
MONOPOLY.
LOOK AT THAT.
SO, UH...
WHERE DID, UH, PAOLO COME FROM?
UH, ITALY, I THINK.
NO, I MEAN TONIGHT, IN THE BUILDING...
SUDDENLY INTO OUR LIVES.
WELL, THAT CAT.
THE CAT TURNED OUT TO BE PAOLO'S CAT.
ISN'T THAT FUNNY?
HA!
THAT THAT IS FUNNY
AND RACHEL KEEPS TOUCHING HIM.
I LOOKED ALL OVER THE BUILDING
AND I COULDN'T FIND THE KITTY ANYWHERE.
I FOUND HIM.
IT WAS PAOLO'S CAT.
AH, WELL, THERE YOU GO-- LAST TO KNOW AGAIN.
AND I'M GUESSING SINCE NOBODY TOLD ME
THIS IS PAOLO.
OH, PAOLO.
THIS IS PHOEBE.
HI.
YOU BETCHA.
ALL RIGHT, OKAY.
WHAT NEXT?
BLOW A BUBBLE.
A BUBBLE'S GOOD.
IT'S GOT A BOYISH CHARM.
IT'S IMPISH.
HERE WE GO.
NICE GOING, IMP.
OKAY, IT'S OKAY.
ALL I NEED TO DO IS
REACH OVER AND PUT IT BACK
IN MY MOUTH.
GOOD SAVE.
WE'RE BACK ON TRACK, AND I'M...
CHEWING SOMEONE ELSE'S GUM.
GOD! OH, THIS IS NOT MY GUM!
OH, MY GOD! OH, MY GOD!
AND NOW YOU'RE CHOKING.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
OH, MY GOD, YOU'RE CHOKING!
BETTER?
YES.
THANK YOU.
THAT WAS...
PERFECTION?
BLAH BLAH BLAH- BLAH BLAH.
BLAH BLAH BLAH- BLAH BLAH BLAH.
BL BL BL BL BLAH.
THAT WAS NO TOUSLE.
HEY, WHAT DID HE SAY THAT WAS SO FUNNY?
I HAVE ABSOLUTELY NO IDEA.
THAT'S, THAT'S CLASSIC.
MY GOD, YOU GUYS, WHAT AM I DOING?
THIS IS SO UN ME.
IF YOU WANT, I'LL DO IT.
I KNOW.
I JUST WANT TO BITE HIS BOTTOM LIP.
BUT I WON'T.
WHEN HE FIRST SMILED
THOSE THREE SECONDS WERE MORE EXCITING
THAN THREE WEEKS IN BERMUDA WITH BARRY.
DID YOU RENT MOPEDS?
BECAUSE I'VE HEARD...
IT'S NOT ABOUT THAT RIGHT NOW. OKAY.
I KNOW IT'S TOTALLY SUPERFICIAL AND WE HAVE NOTHING IN COMMON
AND WE DON'T EVEN SPEAK THE SAME LANGUAGE
BUT, GOD!
PAOLO, HI.
ROSS.
LISTEN, UH...
LISTEN, UM, SOMETHING YOU SHOULD KNOW.
UH, RACHEL AND I ARE...
WE'RE KIND OF A...
KIND OF A THING.
THING?
THING. YES, THING.
YOU HAVE THE SEX.
NO.
NO, NO, UM...
TECHNICALLY THE, THE SEX IS NOT BEING HAD
BUT THAT'S, UH...
SEE, BUT THAT'S NOT THE POINT.
SEE, UM, THE POINT IS, UH...
WELL, RACHEL AND I SHOULD BE, UH...
WELL, RACHEL AND I SHOULD BE TOGETHER, YOU KNOW?
AND IF YOU GET IN THE, UM...
IN BED.
NO.
NO, NOT WHERE I WAS GOING.
UH, IF YOU GET IN THE WAY...
WAY OF US BECOMING A THING
THEN, UH, I WOULD BE, WELL, VERY SAD.
OH, OH.
SO DO YOU, UM...
CEVICHE?
SI, SI.
SI?
SI.
OKAY.
SO YOU, UH... YOU DO KNOW A LITTLE ENGLISH.
POCO. LITTLE.
DO YOU KNOW THE WORD "CRAPWEASEL"?
NO.
NO? THAT'S FUNNY
BECAUSE YOU ARE A HUGE CRAPWEASEL.
GRAZIE.
CHANDLER, WE'VE BEEN DOING THIS FOR AN HOUR.
NOW WATCH.
OKAY.
READY?
MM HMM.
OKAY, NOW TRY IT.
NO, WHIP IT.
OH, LOOK, LOOK, LOOK, LOOK.
THE LAST CANDLE'S ABOUT TO BURN OUT.
TEN, NINE
EIGHT, SEVEN...
MINUS 46, MINUS 47
MINUS 48...
THANK YOU.
THANKS.
KIND OF SPOOKY WITHOUT ANY LIGHTS.
MWAAAHH! HA HA HA!
GUYS, GUYS, I HAVE THE DEFINITIVE ONE.
BWAAAAA!
HA HA..!
UH, ROSS
THIS PROBABLY ISN'T THE BEST TIME
TO BRING IT UP
BUT YOU HAVE TO THROW A PARTY FOR MONICA.
WELL, THIS HAS BEEN FUN.
YES, AND THANKS FOR LETTING ME USE YOUR PHONE
AND FOR SAVING MY LIFE.
WELL, GOOD BYE, CHANDLER.
I HAD A GREAT BLACKOUT.
SEE YA.
HI.
I'M ACCOUNT NUMBER 7143457
AND I DON'T KNOW IF YOU GOT ANY OF THAT
BUT I WOULD REALLY LIKE A COPY OF THE TAPE.