THERE'S NOTHING TO TELL.
IT'S JUST SOME GUY I WORK WITH.
YOU'RE GOING OUT WITH HIM.
THERE'S GOT TO BE SOMETHING WRONG WITH HIM.
ALL RIGHT, JOEY, BE NICE.
SO, DOES HE HAVE A HUMP?
A HUMP AND A HAIRPIECE?
WAIT, DOES HE EAT CHALK?
I DON'T WANT HER
TO GO THROUGH
WHAT I WENT THROUGH WITH CARL.
OKAY, EVERYBODY RELAX.
THIS IS NOT A DATE.
IT'S TWO PEOPLE GOING OUT TO DINNER
AND NOT HAVING SEX.
SOUNDS LIKE A DATE TO ME.
SO I'M BACK IN HIGH SCHOOL.
I'M STANDING IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE CAFETERIA
AND I REALIZE I AM TOTALLY... NAKED.
I'VE HAD THAT DREAM.
THEN, I LOOK DOWN
AND I REALIZE THERE IS A PHONE...
THERE.
INSTEAD OF..?
THAT'S RIGHT.
NEVER HAD THAT DREAM.
ALL OF A SUDDEN, THE PHONE
STARTS TO RING.
NOW, I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
EVERYBODY STARTS LOOKING AT ME.
THEY WEREN'T LOOKING AT YOU BEFORE?
FINALLY I FIGURE I'D BETTER ANSWER IT
AND IT TURNS OUT IT'S MY MOTHER
WHICH IS VERY, VERY WEIRD BECAUSE...
SHE NEVER CALLS ME.
HI.
THIS GUY SAYS "HELLO, I WANT TO KILL MYSELF."
ARE YOU OKAY, SWEETIE?
I FEEL LIKE SOMEONE REACHED DOWN MY THROAT
GRABBED MY SMALL INTESTINE, PULLED IT OUT OF MY MOUTH
AND TIED IT AROUND MY NECK.
COOKIE?
CAROL MOVED HER STUFF OUT TODAY.
OH...
LET ME GET YOU SOME COFFEE.
THANKS.
OOH. UGH...
NO. OH, NO. NO, DON'T.
STOP CLEANSING MY AURA.
NO, JUST
LEAVE MY AURA ALONE, OKAY?
FINE. BE MURKY.
I'LL BE FINE, ALL RIGHT?
I HOPE SHE'LL BE VERY HAPPY.
NO, YOU DON'T.
TO HELL WITH HER. SHE LEFT ME.
AND YOU NEVER KNEW SHE WAS A LESBIAN?
NO. OKAY?
WHY DOES EVERYONE KEEP FIXATING ON THAT?
SHE DIDN'T KNOW.
HOW SHOULD I KNOW?
SOMETIMES I WISH I WAS A LESBIAN.
DID I SAY THAT OUT LOUD?
I TOLD MOM AND DAD LAST NIGHT.
THEY SEEMED TO TAKE IT PRETTY WELL.
OH, REALLY?
SO, THAT HYSTERICAL PHONE CALL
I GOT FROM A WOMAN SOBBING AT 3 A.M.--
"I'LL NEVER HAVE GRANDCHILDREN, I'LL NEVER HAVE GRANDCHILDREN"
WAS, WHAT, A WRONG NUMBER?
SORRY.
ALL RIGHT, ROSS, LOOK
YOU'RE FEELING A LOT OF PAIN RIGHT NOW.
YOU'RE ANGRY. YOU'RE HURTING.
CAN I TELL YOU WHAT THE ANSWER IS?
STRIP JOINTS!
OH, COME ON.
YOU'RE SINGLE.
HAVE SOME HORMONES.
SEE, BUT I DON'T WANT TO BE SINGLE, OKAY?
I JUST, I JUST, I JUST WANT TO BE MARRIED AGAIN.
AND I JUST WANT A MILLION DOLLARS.
RACHEL?
OH, GOD, MONICA, HI. THANK GOD.
I JUST WENT TO YOUR BUILDING
AND YOU WEREN'T THERE
AND THEN THIS GUY WITH A BIG HAMMER
SAID THAT YOU MIGHT BE HERE, AND YOU ARE, YOU ARE.
CAN I GET YOU SOME COFFEE?
DECAF.
OKAY, EVERYBODY, THIS IS RACHEL
ANOTHER LINCOLN HIGH SURVIVOR.
THIS IS EVERYBODY.
THIS IS CHANDLER
AND PHOEBE, AND JOEY
AND YOU REMEMBER
MY BROTHER ROSS?
SURE.
HI. OH!
SO, YOU WANT TO TELL US NOW
OR ARE WE WAITING FOR FOUR WET BRIDESMAIDS?
OH, GOD. WELL, IT STARTED
ABOUT A HALF HOUR BEFORE THE WEDDING.
I WAS IN THIS ROOM
WHERE WE WERE KEEPING ALL THE PRESENTS
AND I WAS LOOKING AT THIS GRAVY BOAT--
THIS REALLY GORGEOUS LIMOGES GRAVY BOAT--
WHEN ALL OF A SUDDEN I REALIZED...
SWEET AND LOW?
I REALIZED THAT I WAS MORE TURNED ON
BY THIS GRAVY BOAT THAN BY BARRY
AND THEN I GOT REALLY FREAKED OUT
AND THAT'S WHEN IT HIT ME
HOW MUCH BARRY LOOKS LIKE MR. POTATO HEAD.
I MEAN, I ALWAYS KNEW HE LOOKED FAMILIAR, BUT...
ANYWAY, I JUST HAD TO GET OUT OF THERE
AND I STARTED WONDERING, "WHY AM I DOING THIS
AND WHO AM I DOING THIS FOR?"
SO, ANYWAY, I JUST DIDN'T KNOW WHERE TO GO
AND I KNOW THAT YOU AND I HAVE DRIFTED APART
BUT YOU'RE THE ONLY PERSON I KNEW
WHO LIVED IN THE CITY.
WHO WASN'T INVITED TO THE WEDDING.
OH, I WAS KIND OF HOPING THAT WOULDN'T BE AN ISSUE.
Embarazada de Marcela...
I'M GUESSING
THAT HE BOUGHT HER THE BIG PIPE ORGAN
AND SHE'S REALLY NOT HAPPY ABOUT IT.
TUNA OR EGG SALAD--
DECIDE!
I'LL HAVE
WHATEVER CHRISTINE IS HAVING.
DADDY, I JUST...
I CAN'T MARRY HIM.
I'M SORRY.
I JUST DON'T LOVE HIM.
WELL, IT MATTERS TOME.
IF I LET GO OF MY HAIR
MY HEAD WILL FALL OFF.
OOH, SHE SHOULD NOT BE WEARING THOSE PANTS.
I SAY PUSH HER DOWN THE STAIRS.
PUSH HER DOWN THE STAIRS!
PUSH HER DOWN
THE STAIRS!
ALL RIGHT!
COME ON, DADDY, LISTEN TO ME.
ALL OF MY LIFE
EVERYONE HAS ALWAYS TOLD ME, "YOU'RE A SHOE.
"YOU'RE A SHOE.
YOU'RE A SHOE. YOU'RE A SHOE."
AND THEN TODAY JUST STOPPED AND SAID
"WHAT IF I DON'T WANT TO BE A SHOE?
"WHAT IF I WANT TO BE A PURSE?
OR A HAT?"
NO, I DON'T WANT YOU TO BUY ME A HAT.
I'M SAYING THAT I AM A HAT...
IT'S A METAPHOR, DADDY!
YOU CAN SEE WHERE HE'D HAVE TROUBLE.
LOOK, DADDY, IT'S MY LIFE.
WELL, MAYBE I'LL JUST STAY HERE WITH MONICA.
WELL, I GUESS WE'VE ESTABLISHED SHE'S STAYING HERE WITH MONICA.
WELL, MAYBE THAT'S MY DECISION.
WELL, MAYBE I DON'T NEED YOUR MONEY.
WAIT, WAIT! I SAID MAYBE!
OKAY, JUST BREATHE. THAT'S IT.
JUST TRY TO THINK OF NICE, CALM THINGS.
? RAINDROPS ON ROSES ?
? AND WHISKERS ON KITTENS ?
? DOORBELLS AND SLEIGH BELLS ?
? AND SOMETHING WITH MITTENS ?
? LA LA LA SOMETHING ?
? AND NOODLES WITH STRING ?
? THESE ARE A... ?
I'M ALL BETTER NOW. THANK YOU.
I HELPED.
OKAY, LOOK, THIS IS PROBABLY FOR THE BEST.
INDEPENDENCE...
TAKING CONTROL OF YOUR LIFE.
THE WHOLE... HAT THING.
AND HEY, YOU NEED ANYTHING
YOU CAN ALWAYS COME TO JOEY.
ME AND CHANDLER
LIVE RIGHT ACROSS THE HALL
AND HE'S AWAY A LOT.
STOP HITTING ON HER.
IT'S HER WEDDING DAY.
LIKE THERE'S A RULE OR SOMETHING?
I GOT IT.
PLEASE DON'T DO THAT AGAIN.
IT'S A HORRIBLE SOUND.
Uh, it's-- it's Paul.
OH, GOD, IS IT 6:30?
BUZZ HIM IN.
WHO'S PAUL?
"PAUL THE WINE GUY" PAUL?
MAYBE.
YOUR "NOT A REAL DATE" TONIGHT
IS WITH "PAUL THE WINE GUY"?
HE FINALLY ASKED YOU OUT?
YES.
A "DEAR DIARY" MOMENT.
RACH, WAIT. I CAN CANCEL.
PLEASE, NO, GO. I'LL BE FINE.
ROSS, ARE YOU OKAY?
I MEAN, DO YOU WANT ME TO STAY?
THAT WOULD BE GOOD.
REALLY?
NO! GO ON!
IT'S "PAUL THE WINE GUY"!
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
DOES HE SELL IT, DRINK IT
OR HE JUST COMPLAINS A LOT?
HI. COME IN.
PAUL, THIS IS...
EVERYBODY.
EVERYBODY, THIS IS PAUL.
"PAUL THE WINE GUY"!
I DIDN'T CATCH YOUR NAME.
PAUL, WAS IT?
OKAY, I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
I'VE JUST GOT TO GO, UH...
GO, UH...
A WANDERING?
CHANGE.
OKAY, SIT DOWN.
TWO SECONDS.
I JUST PULLED OUT FOUR EYELASHES.
THAT CAN'T BE GOOD.
HEY, PAUL.
HERE'S A LITTLE TIP.
SHE REALLY LIKES IT
WHEN YOU RUB HER NECK IN THE SAME SPOT
OVER AND OVER AND OVER AGAIN
TILL IT STARTS TO GET A LITTLE RED.
SHUT UP, JOEY!
SO, RACHEL, WHAT ARE YOU UP TO TONIGHT?
I WAS KIND OF SUPPOSED TO BE HEADED FOR ARUBA
ON MY HONEYMOON.
SO NOTHING.
RIGHT. YOU'RE NOT EVEN GETTING YOUR HONEYMOON.
GOD...
NO... ARUBA.
THIS TIME OF YEAR, TALK ABOUT YOUR...
BIG LIZARDS.
ANYWAY, IF YOU DON'T FEEL LIKE BEING ALONE TONIGHT
JOEY AND CHANDLER ARE HELPING ME PUT TOGETHER
MY NEW FURNITURE.
AND WE'RE VERY EXCITED ABOUT IT.
THANKS, BUT I'M GOING TO HANG OUT HERE TONIGHT.
IT'S BEEN A LONG DAY.
OH, SURE. OKAY, SURE.
PHEEBS, YOU WANT TO HELP?
I WISH I COULD, BUT I DON'T WANT TO.
? LOVE IS SWEET AS SUMMER SHOWERS ?
? LOVE IS A WONDROUS WORK OF ART ?
? BUT YOUR LOVE, OH, YOUR LOVE, YOUR LOVE... ?
? IS LIKE A GIANT PIGEON... ?
? CRAPPING ON MY HEART ?
? LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA... ?
THANK YOU!
? LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA ?
? OOH... ?
I'M SUPPOSED TO ATTACH
A BRACKETY THING TO THE SIDE THINGS
USING A BUNCH OF THESE LITTLE WORM GUYS.
I HAVE NO BRACKETY THING.
I SEE NO WORM GUYS WHATSOEVER.
AND I CANNOT FEEL MY LEGS.
I'M THINKING WE GOT A BOOKCASE HERE.
IT'S A BEAUTIFUL THING.
WHAT'S THIS?
I WOULD HAVE TO SAY
THAT IT'S AN "L" SHAPED BRACKET.
WHICH GOES WHERE?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
DONE WITH THE BOOKCASE!
ALL FINISHED!
THIS WAS CAROL'S FAVORITE BEER.
SHE ALWAYS DRANK IT OUT OF THE CAN.
I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN.
HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO START WITH THAT STUFF
WE'RE OUT OF HERE.
PLEASE DON'T SPOIL ALL THIS FUN.
ROSS, LET ME ASK YOU A QUESTION.
SHE GOT THE FURNITURE, THE STEREO, THE GOOD TV.
WHAT DID YOU GET?
YOU GUYS.
YOU GOT SCREWED. OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD.
I KNOW. I'M SUCH AN IDIOT.
I GUESS I SHOULD HAVE CAUGHT ON
WHEN SHE STARTED GOING TO THE DENTIST
FOUR AND FIVE TIMES A WEEK.
I MEAN, HOW CLEAN CAN TEETH GET?
MY BROTHER'S GOING THROUGH THAT NOW.
HE'S SUCH A MESS.
HOW DID YOU GET THROUGH IT?
HE MIGHT TRY ACCIDENTALLY BREAKING
SOMETHING VALUABLE OF HERS--
SAY, HER...
LEG?
THAT'S ONE WAY OF GOING THROUGH IT.
ME, I WENT FOR THE WATCH.
YOU ACTUALLY BROKE HER WATCH?
WOW. THE WORST THING THAT I EVER DID WAS
I SHREDDED MY OLD BOYFRIEND'S FAVORITE BATH TOWEL.
OOH, STEER CLEAR OF YOU.
THAT'S RIGHT.
BARRY, I AM SORRY. I AM SO SORRY.
I KNOW YOU PROBABLY THINK
THIS IS ALL ABOUT WHAT I SAID THE OTHER NIGHT
ABOUT YOU MAKING LOVE WITH YOUR SOCKS ON
BUT IT ISN'T.
IT'S ABOUT ME, AND I DID...
HI. MACHINE CUT ME OFF AGAIN.
ANYWAY...
LOOK, I KNOW THAT SOME GIRL IS GOING TO BE
INCREDIBLY LUCKY TO BECOME MRS. BARRY FINKEL
BUT IT ISN'T ME.
IT'S NOT ME.
NOT THAT I HAVE ANY IDEA WHO "ME" IS RIGHT NOW
BUT YOU JUST HAVE TO GIVE ME A CHANCE TO...
I'M DIVORCED.
I'M ONLY 26, AND I'M DIVORCED.
SHUT UP.
ROSS, YOU MUST STOP.
THAT ONLY TOOK ME AN HOUR.
ROSS, YOU'VE GOT TO UNDERSTAND.
BETWEEN US, WE HAVEN'T HAD A RELATIONSHIP
THAT'S LASTED LONGER THAN A MENTO.
YOU, HOWEVER, HAVE HAD THE LOVE OF A WOMAN FOR FOUR YEARS.
FOUR YEARS OF CLOSENESS AND SHARING
AT THE END OF WHICH SHE RIPPED YOUR HEART OUT
AND THAT IS WHY WE DON'T DO IT.
I DON'T THINK THAT WAS MY POINT.
YOU KNOW WHAT THE SCARIEST PART IS?
WHAT IF THERE'S ONLY ONE WOMAN FOR EVERYBODY?
WHAT IF YOU GET ONE WOMAN AND THAT'S IT?
UNFORTUNATELY, IN MY CASE
THERE WAS ONLY ONE WOMAN FOR HER.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
ONE WOMAN.
THAT'S LIKE SAYING
THERE'S ONLY ONE FLAVOR OF ICE CREAM FOR YOU.
LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING, ROSS.
THERE'S LOTS OF FLAVORS OUT THERE.
THERE'S ROCKY ROAD AND COOKIE DOUGH
AND BING CHERRY VANILLA.
YOU CAN GET THEM WITH JIMMIES OR NUTS
OR WHIPPED CREAM.
THIS IS THE BEST THING
THAT EVER HAPPENED TO YOU.
YOU GOT MARRIED.
YOU WERE LIKE, WHAT, EIGHT?
WELCOME BACK TO THE WORLD.
GRAB A SPOON.
I HONESTLY DON'T KNOW IF I'M HUNGRY OR HORNY.
THEN STAY OUT
OF MY FREEZER.
EVER SINCE SHE WALKED OUT ON ME, I...
WHAT?
WHAT, YOU WANT TO SPELL IT OUT WITH NOODLES?
NO, IT'S MORE OF A FIFTH DATE KIND OF REVELATION.
OH, SO, THERE'S GOING TO BE A FIFTH DATE?
ISN'T THERE?
YEAH, YEAH, I THINK THERE IS.
WHAT WERE YOU GOING TO SAY?
WELL, WELL...
EVER SINCE SHE LEFT ME, UM...
I HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO PERFORM...
SEXUALLY.
OH, GOD. I'M SO SORRY.
IT'S OKAY.
BEING SPIT ON
IS PROBABLY NOT WHAT YOU NEED RIGHT NOW.
UM...
HOW LONG?
TWO YEARS.
WOW.
I I I'M GLAD YOU SMASHED HER WATCH.
SO, YOU STILL THINK YOU, UM...
MIGHT WANT THAT FIFTH DATE?
YEAH.
YEAH, I DO.
We are gathered here to join together
Joanie Louise Cunningham
and Charles... Chachi
Chachi, Chachi...
in the bond of holy matrimony.
OOH! SEE?
BUT JOANIE LOVES CHACHI.
THAT'S THE DIFFERENCE.
GRAB A SPOON.
DO YOU KNOW HOW LONG IT'S BEEN SINCE I GRABBED A SPOON?
DO THE WORDS "BILLY, DON'T BE A HERO"
MEAN ANYTHING TO YOU?
GREAT STORY...
BUT I GOT TO GO.
I GOT A DATE WITH ANDREA.
ANGELA. ANDREA.
OH, MAN.
ANDREA'S THE SCREAMER.
ANGELA HAS CATS.
THAT'S RIGHT. THANKS.
IT'S JULIE. I'M OUT OF HERE.
YOU KNOW, HERE'S THE THING.
EVEN IF I COULD GET IT TOGETHER ENOUGH
TO ASK A WOMAN OUT...
WHO AM I GOING TO ASK?
? IF YOU EVER NEED HOLDING ?
? CALL MY NAME ?
? I'LL BE THERE ?
? IF YOU EVER NEED HOLDING... ?
ISN'T THIS AMAZING?
I HAVE NEVER MADE COFFEE IN MY ENTIRE LIFE.
THAT IS AMAZING.
CONGRATULATIONS.
YOU KNOW, I FIGURE IF I CAN MAKE COFFEE
THERE ISN'T ANYTHING I CAN'T DO.
YOU KNOW, I THINK IT'S "IF I CAN INVADE POLAND
THERE ISN'T ANYTHING I CAN'T DO."
IF YOU FEEL LIKE YOU GOT TO MAKE A WESTERN OMELETTE...
ACTUALLY, I'M REALLY NOT THAT HUNGRY THIS MORNING.
OH, GOOD.
LENNY AND SQUIGGY ARE HERE.
MORNING.
MORNING. MORNING.
MORNING, PAUL.
HELLO, PAUL.
HI. PAUL, IS IT?
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU SO MUCH. STOP.
NO, I'M TELLING YOU, LAST NIGHT WAS...
IT WAS LIKE ALL MY BIRTHDAYS, BOTH GRADUATIONS
PLUS THE BARN RAISING SCENE INWITNESS.
WE'LL TALK LATER.
YEAH.
THANK YOU.
THAT WASN'T A REAL DATE.
WHAT THE HELL DO YOU DO ON A REAL DATE?
SHUT UP AND PUT MY TABLE BACK.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, KIDS, I GOT TO GET TO WORK.
IF I DON'T INPUT THOSE NUMBERS...
IT DOESN'T MAKE MUCH OF A DIFFERENCE.
SO, LIKE, YOU GUYS ALL HAVE JOBS?
YEAH, WE ALL HAVE JOBS.
SEE, THAT'S HOW WE BUY STUFF.
YEAH. I'M AN ACTOR.
WOW. HAVE I SEEN YOU IN ANYTHING?
I DOUBT IT.
MOSTLY REGIONAL WORK.
UNLESS YOU CAUGHT
THE WEE ONES PRODUCTION OF PINOCCHIO
AT THE LITTLE THEATER IN THE PARK.
IT WAS A JOB, ALL RIGHT?
"LOOK, GEPPETTO, I'M A REAL LIVE BOY."
I WILL NOT TAKE THIS ABUSE.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'M SORRY.
? ONCE I WAS A WOODEN BOY, A LITTLE WOODEN BOY. ?
YOU SHOULD BOTH KNOW THAT HE'S A DEAD MAN.
OH, CHANDLER?
SO, HOW YOU DOING TODAY?
DID YOU SLEEP OKAY?
DID YOU TALK TO BARRY?
I CAN'T STOP SMILING.
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU SLEPT
WITH A HANGER IN YOUR MOUTH.
I KNOW.
HE'S JUST SO...
YOU REMEMBER YOU AND TONY DEMARCO?
OH, YEAH.
WELL, IT'S LIKE THAT--
WITH FEELINGS.
OH, WOW, ARE YOU IN TROUBLE.
BIG TIME!
WANT A WEDDING DRESS?
HARDLY USED.
I THINK WE'RE GETTING A LITTLE AHEAD OF OURSELVES HERE.
OKAY. OKAY. I AM JUST GOING TO GET UP, GO TO WORK
AND NOT THINK ABOUT HIM ALL DAY.
OR ELSE I'M JUST GOING TO GET UP AND GO TO WORK.
OH, WISH ME LUCK.
WHAT FOR?
I'M GOING TO GET
ONE OF THOSE JOB THINGS.
HEY, MONICA.
FRANNIE, WELCOME BACK.
HOW WAS FLORIDA?
YOU HAD SEX, DIDN'T YOU?
HOW DO YOU DO THAT?
OH, I HATE YOU.
I'M PUSHING MY AUNT ROZ THROUGH PARROT JUNGLE
AND YOU'RE HAVING SEX.
SO, WHO?
YOU KNOW PAUL?
PAUL, THE WINE GUY?
OH,YEAH,I KNOW PAUL.
YOU MEAN, YOU KNOW PAUL LIKE I KNOW PAUL?
ARE YOU KIDDING?
I TAKE CREDIT FOR PAUL.
BEFORE ME, THERE WAS NO SNAP IN HIS TURTLE
FOR TWO YEARS.
OF COURSE IT WAS A LINE.
WHY WOULD ANYBODY DO SOMETHING LIKE THAT?!
I ASSUME WE'RE LOOKING FOR AN ANSWER
MORE SOPHISTICATED THAN "TO GET YOU INTO BED."
I HATE MEN.
OH, NO, DON'T HATE. YOU DON'T WANT
TO PUT THAT OUT IN THE UNIVERSE.
IS IT ME?
IS IT LIKE I HAVE SOME SORT OF BEACON THAT ONLY DOGS
AND MEN WITH SEVERE EMOTIONAL PROBLEMS CAN HEAR?
ALL RIGHT, COME HERE, GIVE ME YOUR FEET.
I JUST THOUGHT HE WAS NICE, YOU KNOW?
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU DIDN'T KNOW IT WAS A LINE.
GUESS WHAT?
YOU GOT A JOB?
ARE YOU KIDDING?
I'M TRAINED FOR NOTHING.
I WAS LAUGHED OUT OF 12 INTERVIEWS.
YET YOU'RE SURPRISINGLY UPBEAT.
YOU WOULD BE, TOO, IF YOU FOUND JOAN AND DAVID BOOTS ON SALE
50 PERCENT OFF.
OH, HOW WELL YOU KNOW ME.
THEY'RE MY NEW
I DON'T NEED A JOB- I DON'T NEED MY PARENTS-
I'VE GOT GREAT BOOTS BOOTS.
HOW DID YOU PAY FOR THEM?
A CREDIT CARD.
AND WHO PAYS FOR THAT?
UM... MY FATHER.
COME ON, YOU GUYS, IS THIS REALLY NECESSARY?
I MEAN, I CAN STOP CHARGING ANYTIME I WANT.
YOU CAN'T LIVE OFF YOUR PARENTS
YOUR WHOLE LIFE.
THAT'S WHY I WAS GETTING MARRIED.
COME ON, GIVE HER A BREAK.
IT'S HARD BEING ON YOUR OWN THE FIRST TIME.
THANK YOU.
I REMEMBER WHEN I FIRST CAME HERE.
I WAS 14, MY MOM HAD JUST KILLED HERSELF
AND MY STEPDAD WAS BACK IN PRISON.
I GOT HERE AND DIDN'T KNOW ANYBODY.
I ENDED UP LIVING WITH THIS ALBINO GUY
WHO WAS CLEANING WINDSHIELDS OUTSIDE PORT AUTHORITY
AND THEN HE KILLED HIMSELF, AND THEN I FOUND AROMATHERAPY
SO BELIEVE ME, I KNOW EXACTLY HOW YOU FEEL.
THE WORD YOU'RE LOOKING FOR IS "ANYWAY..."
ALL RIGHT.
YOU READY?
NO. NO, NO, I'M NOT READY.
HOW CAN I BE READY?
"HEY, RACH, YOU READY TO JUMP OUT OF THE AIRPLANE
WITHOUT A PARACHUTE?"
COME ON, I CAN'T DO THIS.
YOU CAN. I KNOW YOU CAN.
I DON'T THINK SO.
COME ON, YOU MADE COFFEE.
YOU CAN DO ANYTHING.
CUT. CUT.
CUT. CUT. CUT. CUT. CUT.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK I CAN JUST LEAVE IT AT THAT.
KIND OF LIKE A SYMBOLIC GESTURE.
RACHEL, THAT WAS A LIBRARY CARD.
CUT, CUT, CUT, CUT, CUT...
YOU KNOW, IF YOU LISTEN VERY CLOSELY
YOU CAN HEAR 1,000 RETAILERS SCREAM.
WELCOME TO THE REAL WORLD.
IT SUCKS.
YOU'RE GOING TO LOVE IT.
THAT'S IT.
YOU WANT TO CRASH ON THE COUCH?
NO. I GOT TO GO HOME.
YOU GOING TO BE OKAY?
YEAH.
HEY, MON, LOOK WHAT I JUST FOUND ON THE FLOOR.
WHAT?
THAT'S PAUL'S WATCH.
YOU CAN JUST PUT IT BACK WHERE YOU FOUND IT.
OH, BOY.
ALL RIGHT, GOOD NIGHT, EVERYBODY.
GOOD NIGHT.
HMM.
OH, SORRY. OH, NO. GO. GO.
REALLY, I DON'T WANT IT.
SPLIT IT?
OKAY.
THANKS.
YOU PROBABLY DIDN'T KNOW THIS
BUT BACK IN HIGH SCHOOL I HAD A MAJOR CRUSH ON YOU.
I KNEW.
YOU DID? OH.
I ALWAYS FIGURED YOU JUST THOUGHT
I WAS MONICA'S GEEKY OLDER BROTHER.
I DID.
OH.
LISTEN, DO YOU THINK--
AND TRY NOT TO LET MY INTENSE VULNERABILITY
BECOME ANY KIND OF A FACTOR HERE--
BUT DO YOU THINK IT WOULD BE OKAY
IF I ASKED YOU OUT SOMETIME MAYBE?
YEAH.
MAYBE.
OKAY.
OKAY, MAYBE I WILL.
GOOD NIGHT.
SEE YOU.
MM HMM.
WAIT, WAIT.
HEY, WHAT'S WITH YOU?
I JUST GRABBED A SPOON.
I CAN'T BELIEVE WHAT I'M HEARING.
? I CAN'T BELIEVE WHAT I'M HEARING HERE. ?
I SAID YOU HAD...
? I SAID YOU HAD... ?
WOULD YOU STOP?
OH, WAS I DOING IT AGAIN?
YES!
I SAID THAT YOU HAD A NICE BUTT.
IT'S JUST NOT A GREAT BUTT.
AH, YOU WOULDN'T KNOW A GREAT BUTT
IF IT CAME UP AND BIT YOU.
THERE'S AN IMAGE.
WOULD ANYBODY LIKE MORE COFFEE?
DID YOU MAKE IT, OR ARE YOU JUST SERVING IT?
I'M JUST SERVING IT.
YEAH. YEAH. YEAH.
KIDS, NEW DREAM.
I'M IN LAS VEGAS.
UH, MISS, MORE COFFEE?
EXCUSE ME, COULD YOU GIVE THIS TO THAT GUY OVER THERE?
GO AHEAD.
THANK YOU.
SORRY. OKAY, LAS VEGAS.
OKAY, SO, I'M IN LAS VEGAS.
I'M LIZA MINELLI.