OH, RACH, WE'RE RUNNING LOW
ON RESUMES OVER HERE.
DO YOU REALLY WANT A JOB WITH POPULAR MECHANICS?
WELL, IF YOU'RE GOING TO WORK FOR MECHANICS
THOSE ARE THE ONES TO WORK FOR.
HEY, LOOK, YOU GUYS, I'M GOING FOR ANYTHING HERE, OKAY?
I CANNOT BE A WAITRESS ANYMORE. I MEAN IT.
I'M SICK OF THE LOUSY TIPS
SICK OF BEING CALLED "EXCUSE ME."
OW! OH, PAPER CUT, PAPER CUT!
HERE, HERE, HERE.
GRAPEFRUIT JUICE! GRAPEFRUIT JUICE!
OKAY, YOU GUYS, WE'RE ALMOST DONE.
WE'VE ONLY GOT 20 MORE TO GO.
RACH, DID YOU PROOFREAD THESE?
UH, YEAH. WHY?
UH, NOTHING.
I'M SURE THEY'LL BE IMPRESSED
WITH YOUR EXCELLENT "COMPUPER" SKILLS.
OH, MY GOD!
OH, DO YOU THINK IT'S ON ALL OF THEM?
OH, NO.
I'M SURE THE XEROX MACHINE CAUGHT A FEW.
?  ?
? AND IT HASN'T BEEN YOUR DAY ?
YOU KNOW, I KNOW THEY CALL THIS A LOVE SEAT
BUT I'M NOT REALLY FEELING ANYTHING SPECIAL TOWARDS YOU.
HEY, GUYS.
HEY.
HI, LADIES.
UH, CAN I GET YOU ANYTHING?
DID YOU BRING THE MAIL?
LOTS OF RESPONSES.
REALLY?
SURE WE HAVE SCONES LEFT.
OKAY, READ THEM TO ME.
"DEAR MS. GREEN, THANK YOU FOR YOUR INQUIRY.
HOWEVER..."
WE HAVE APPLE CINNAMON...
OKAY, "DEAR MS. GREEN..."
YEP, YEP, YEP.
NO.
WOW.
WHAT?
YOUR VISA BILL IS HUGE.
GIVE ME THAT.
YOU KNOW, I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU. LINDA IS SO GREAT.
WHY WON'T YOU GO OUT WITH HER AGAIN?
I DON'T KNOW.
IS THIS STILL ABOUT HER WHOLE
"THE FLINTSTONES
COULD HAVE REALLY HAPPENED" THING?
NO. IT'S NOT JUST THAT.
IT'S JUST I WANT SOMEONE WHO DOES SOMETHING FOR ME.
WHO GETS MY HEART POUNDING.
WHO... WHO MAKES ME, UH...
LITTLE PLAY THINGS WITH YARN?
WHAT?
COULD YOU WANT HER MORE?
WHO?
DEE, THE SARCASTIC SISTER FROM WHAT'S HAPPENING.
LOOK, I...
LOOK, I AM TOTALLY, TOTALLY OVER HER, OKAY...
HI.
HI. CAN I HELP YOU?
NO. WE'RE FINE.
OKAY.
SHUT UP!
WE'RE NOT SAYING ANYTHING.
WHAT?
UH, JOEY CRIED LAST NIGHT.
THANK YOU.
WE WERE PLAYING POKER, ALL RIGHT...
THERE WAS CHOCOLATE ON THE THREE.
IT LOOKED LIKE
AN EIGHT, ALL RIGHT?
OH, YOU SHOULD HAVE SEEN HIM.
"READ THEM AND WEEP."
AND THEN HE DID.
WELL, NOW, HOW COME YOU GUYS
HAVE NEVER PLAYED POKER WITH US?
YEAH, WHAT IS THAT--
LIKE, SOME KIND OF GUY THING?
LIKE, SOME KIND OF SEXIST GUY THING?
LIKE, IT'S POKER, SO ONLY GUYS CAN PLAY.
NO. WOMEN ARE WELCOME TO PLAY.
OH, OKAY, SO THEN WHAT IS IT?
SOME KIND OF, YOU KNOW, LIKE...
LIKE SOME KIND OF, YOU KNOW, LIKE...
ALL RIGHT, WHAT IS IT?
THERE JUST DON'T HAPPEN
TO BE ANY WOMEN IN OUR GAME.
YEAH, WE JUST DON'T HAPPEN TO KNOW ANY WOMEN
THAT KNOW HOW TO PLAY POKER.
OH, PLEASE, THAT IS SUCH A LAME EXCUSE.
I MEAN, IT'S A TYPICAL GUY RESPONSE.
EXCUSE ME, DO ANY OF YOU KNOW HOW TO PLAY?
NO.
BUT YOU COULD TEACH US.
OKAY, SO NOW...
WE DRAW CARDS.
SO, I WOULDN'T NEED ANY, RIGHT?
BECAUSE I HAVE A STRAIGHT.
OH, GOOD FOR YOU!
CONGRATULATIONS!
OKAY, PHEEBS, HOW MANY DO YOU WANT?
OKAY. I JUST NEED TWO.
THE TEN OF SPADES AND THE SIX OF CLUBS.
NO, PHEEBS, YOU CAN'T DO...
OH, WAIT, I HAVE THE TEN OF SPADES.
HERE, YOU WANT IT? NO, NO...
UH, NO, SEE, YOU CAN'T DO THAT.
OH, NO, NO, NO, THAT'S OKAY.
I DON'T NEED THEM. I'M GOING FOR FOURS.
OH, YOU'RE...
YOU'RE GOING... YOU'RE GOING FOR FOURS.
UH, CHANDLER, COULD YOU...?
YEAH.
THANKS, MAN.
ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
WE GOT SALMON ROULETTES AND ASSORTED CRUDITES.
WHOA, WHOA, MONICA, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
THIS IS A POKER GAME.
YOU CAN'T SERVE FOOD
WITH MORE THAN ONE SYLLABLE.
IT'S GOT TO BE LIKE CHIPS, OR DIP, OR PRETZ...
WELL, I HOPE YOU'LL LET IT SLIDE JUST THIS ONCE.
YOU SEE, I WAS ALL OUT OF PRETZ.
OKAY, SO AT THIS POINT, THE DEALER...
ALL RIGHT, YOU KNOW, WE GOT IT, WE GOT IT.
LET'S PLAY FOR REAL. HIGH STAKES, BIG BUCKS.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, YOU'RE SURE?
PHOEBE JUST THREW AWAY TWO JACKS
BECAUSE THEY DIDN'T LOOK HAPPY.
BUT I'M READY, SO JUST DEAL.
OKAY. LAST MINUTE LESSON, LAST MINUTE LESSON.
JOEY, THREE...
EIGHT.
EIGHT, THREE.
ALL RIGHT. VERY GOOD.
DAMM IT! DAMM IT! DAMM IT!
YEAH, SEE MONICA, JOEY HAD TWO FIVES SHOWING
SO FOR YOU TO RAISE...
YES?
DOWNRIGHT GUTSY.
YEAH.
I SEE. SO THEN, UM, YOU WERE LYING.
ABOUT WHAT?
ABOUT HOW GOOD YOUR CARDS WERE.
I WAS BLUFFING.
UH HUH.
AND WHAT IS BLUFFING?
IS IT NOT ANOTHER WORD FOR LYING?
OKAY. SORRY TO BREAK UP
THIS PARTY, BUT I'VE GOT TO GO FAX A BUNCH OF RESUMES...
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
RACH, RACH, WE GOT TO SETTLE.
SETTLE WHAT?
THE JAMESTOWN COLONY OF VIRGINIA.
YOU SEE
KING GEORGE IS GIVING US THE LAND...
THE GAME, RACHEL, THE GAME.
YOU OWE US MONEY FOR THE GAME.
OH. RIGHT.
YOU KNOW WHAT, YOU GUYS, IT'S THEIR FIRST TIME.
WHY DON'T WE JUST FORGET ABOUT THE MONEY.
HELL, NO, WE'LL PAY.
OKAY, MONICA, I HAD ANOTHER ANSWER ALL READY.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
WE WANT A REMATCH.
WELL, THAT'S FINE WITH ME.
COULD USE THE MONEY.
OH, YOU REALLY ARE ENJOYING THIS, AREN'T YOU?
WELL... YEAH, I AM.
SO BASICALLY, YOU GET YOUR YA YAS
BY TAKING MONEY FROM ALL OF YOUR FRIENDS.
YEAH.
YES, AND I GET MY YA YAS FROM IKEA.
YOU HAVE TO PUT THEM TOGETHER YOURSELF
BUT THEY COST
A LITTLE LESS.
LOOK, RACH, THIS IS POKER.
I PLAY TO WIN, ALL RIGHT?
AND IN ORDER FOR ME TO WIN, OTHER PEOPLE HAVE TO LOSE.
SO IF YOU'RE GOING TO PLAY POKER WITH ME
DON'T EXPECT ME TO BE A NICE GUY.
OKAY, BECAUSE ONCE THOSE CARDS ARE DEALT...
YEAH?
I'M NOT A NICE GUY.
ALL RIGHT, BOYS, LET'S EAT.
OH, DID YOU GET THAT
FROM THE "I LOVE RACHEL" PIZZERIA?
YOU STILL ON THAT?
COME ON, WHAT WAS WITH THAT WHOLE BLACK BART SPEECH?
"WHEN I PLAY POKER, I'M NOT A NICE GUY."
YOU ARE WAY OFF, PAL.
NO, I DON'T THINK SO, SEE, ROSS
BECAUSE I THINK YOU LOVE HER.
UH, NO.
SEE, I MIGHT HAVE HAD FEELINGS FOR HER AT ONE TIME...
NOT ANYMORE.
MARCEL!
WHERE ARE YOU GOING WITH THAT DISK?
YOU ARE NOT PUTTING THAT ON AGAIN.
MARCEL, OKAY, IF YOU PRESS THAT BUTTON, YOU ARE IN VERY
VERY BIG TROUBLE.
? A WEEM AWAY, A WEEM AWAY ?
? A WEEM AWAY, A WEEM AWAY... ?
DO YOU BELIEVE WHAT A JERK ROSS WAS BEING?
YEAH, I KNOW.
HE CAN GET REALLY COMPETITIVE.
WHAT?
HELLO, KETTLE?
THIS IS MONICA.
YOU'RE BLACK.
PLEASE.
I AM NOT AS BAD AS ROSS.
OH, I BEG TO DIFFER.
THE PICTIONARY INCIDENT.
THAT WAS NOT AN INCIDENT.
I WAS GESTURING
AND THE PLATE SLIPPED OUT OF MY HAND.
OH...
OH! I GOT AN INTERVIEW!
YOU'RE KIDDING.
I GOT AN INTERVIEW! WHERE?
SAKS FIFTH AVENUE.
OH, RACHEL.
IT'S LIKE THE MOTHER SHIP IS CALLING YOU HOME.
WHAT'S THE JOB?
ASSISTANT BUYER.
OH!
I WOULD BE SHOPPING...
FOR A LIVING!
OKAY, LOOK, THAT IS AUNT IRIS.
THIS WOMAN HAS BEEN PLAYING POKER
SINCE SHE WAS FIVE.
YOU GOT TO LISTEN TO EVERY WORD SHE SAYS.
HI. IS TONY RANDALL DEAD?
NO.
I DON'T THINK SO.
WELL, HE MAY BE NOW
BECAUSE I THINK I HIT HIM WITH MY CAR.
REALLY?!
NO. THAT'S BLUFFING--
LESSON NUMBER ONE.
LISTEN
LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING.
EVERYTHING YOU HEAR AT A POKER GAME
IS PURE CRAP.
NICE EARRINGS.
THANK YO...
GIRLS, SIT DOWN.
UM, AUNT IRIS, THIS IS PHOEBE, AND THAT'S...
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH. LISTEN, I AM PARKED AT A METER.
LET'S DO IT, OKAY?
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE GOING TO START WITH A LITTLE FIVE CARD DRAW
AND THEN WE'RE GOING TO GO INTO THE STUDS AND THE HOLD EMS
AND I TAUGHT YOUR COUSIN NATHAN YESTERDAY.
AH!
DON'T TOUCH YOUR CARDS
WHEN SOMEBODY'S DEALING.
SO, HOW IS NATHAN?
HOW IS HE EVER?
NOW HE THINKS HE'S A MAN TRAPPED IN A WOMAN'S BODY.
DON'T YOU MEAN HE THINKS HE'S A WOMAN TRAPPED IN A MAN'S BODY?
IT SHOULD BE SO SIMPLE.
ROSS, COULD WE PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE, LISTEN TO ANYTHING ELSE?
ALL RIGHT.
I'M GOING TO PAY FOR THAT TONIGHT.
HI. HEY.
GUYS, GUESS WHAT? GUESS WHAT?
OKAY. THE FIFTH DENTIST CAVED
AND NOW THEY'RE ALL RECOMMENDING TRIDENT?
NO, THE INTERVIEW!
UNBELIEVABLE! SHE LOVED ME.
SHE ABSOLUTELY LOVED ME.
WE TALKED FOR LIKE TWO AND A HALF HOURS.
WE HAVE THE SAME TASTE IN CLOTHES.
OH, AND I WENT TO CAMP WITH HER COUSIN.
AND, OH, THE JOB IS PERFECT.
I CAN DO THIS. I CAN DO THIS WELL.
OH! AND THEN SHE TOLD THE FUNNIEST STORY.
GREAT. YOU'LL TELL US AND WE'LL LAUGH.
LET'S PLAY POKER.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, LISTEN, YOU GUYS, WE TALKED ABOUT IT
AND IF YOU DON'T WANT TO PLAY
WE'D COMPLETELY UNDERSTAND.
OH, YES, YES. WE COULD PLAY SOME OTHER GAME
LIKE, I DON'T KNOW, PICTIONARY?
VERY FUNNY, VERY FUNNY.
BUT I THINK WE'D LIKE TO GIVE POKER ANOTHER TRY.
SHALL WE, LADIES?
YES, I THINK WE SHOULD.
UH, RACH, DO YOU WANT ME TO SHUFFLE THOSE?
NO, NO. THAT'S OKAY.
I THINK I'M GOING TO GIVE IT A GO.
ALL RIGHT...
UM...
SO, PHEEBS OWES 7.50, MONICA, YOU OWE TEN DOLLARS
AND, RACHEL, YOU OWE
15 BIG ONES.
AND, HEY
THANKS FOR TEACHING US
CROSS EYED MARY.
WE GOT TO PLAY THAT
AT OUR REGULAR GAME.
ALL RIGHT, HERE'S MY SEVEN FIFTY,
BUT I THINK YOU SHOULD KNOW THAT THIS MONEY IS CURSED.
WHAT?
OH, I CURSED IT.
SO NOW BAD THINGS WILL HAPPEN TO HE WHO SPENDS IT.
AH, THAT'S ALL RIGHT, I'LL TAKE IT.
BAD THINGS HAPPEN TO ME ANYWAY.
THIS WAY I CAN SPLIT THEM UP WITH A MOVIE.
SO THAT JUST LEAVES THE BIG, GREEN POKER MACHINE
WHO OWES 15.
COULD YOU BE ANY SMUGGER?
HUH, LET'S SEE.
UM... SAY, RACH, I'M OPENING UP A NEW ART GALLERY
AND I COULD SURE USE
THE PORTRAITS OF LINCOLN AND HAMILTON.
HMM... OH, IT'S SO TYPICAL.
OOH, I'M A MAN.
OOH, I HAVE A PENIS.
OOH, I HAVE TO WIN MONEY TO EXERT MY POWER
OVER WOMEN.
YOU KNOW WHAT? THIS IS NOT OVER.
WE WILL PLAY YOU AGAIN, AND WE WILL WIN
AND YOU WILL LOSE
AND YOU WILL BEG, AND WE WILL LAUGH
AND WE WILL TAKE EVERY LAST DIME YOU HAVE
AND YOU WILL HATE YOURSELVES FOREVER.
HMM. YOU KIND OF STEPPED ON MY POINT THERE, MON.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU LOST.
HOW MUCH DID THEY TAKE FROM YOU?
I DON'T KNOW-- LIKE 30 BUCKS?
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M GOING TO DO?
I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU THAT MONEY BACK.
REALLY? REALLY? REALLY?
NO, I'M BLUFFING!
YOU GUYS HAVEN'T LEARNED CRAP!
HAND ME THE CARDS.
CAN I TOUCH...?
YES.
SO, YOU GALS WANT TO HAND OVER YOUR MONEY NOW?
THAT WAY WE DON'T HAVE TO GO
THROUGH THE FORMALITY OF ACTUALLY PLAYING.
OH, THAT'S FINE.
WE'LL SEE WHO HAS THE LAST LAUGH THERE, MONKEY BOY.
OKAY, WE DONE WITH THE CHIT CHAT?
ARE WE READY TO PLAY SERIOUS POKER?
HEY, YOU GUYS, LOOK.
THE ONE EYED JACK FOLLOWS ME WHEREVER I GO.
RIGHT, OKAY. SERIOUS POKER.
HEY, MON, YOU GOT ANY MORE OF THOSE LITTLE SALMON THINGS?
DO YOU WANT TO EAT OR DO YOU WANT TO PLAY POKER?
EXCUSE ME. WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
UH, TO THE BATHROOM.
DO YOU WANT TO GO TO THE BATHROOM
OR DO YOU WANT TO PLAY POKER?
I WANT TO GO TO THE BATHROOM.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, I'M GOING TO ORDER A PIZZA.
OH, NO, NO. I'M STILL WAITING
TO HEAR FROM THAT JOB
AND THE STORE CLOSES AT NINE AM, SO YOU CAN EAT THEN.
THAT'S FINE.
I'LL JUST HAVE A TIC TAC TO HOLD ME OVER.
ALL RIGHT.
CINCINNATI, NO BLIND.
EVERYBODY ANTE.
YES!
OR NO.
ALL RIGHT!
YOUR MONEY'S MINE, GREEN.
YOUR FLY IS OPEN, GELLER.
YOU GUYS, YOU KNOW WHAT I JUST REALIZED?
"JOKER" IS "POKER" WITH A "J."
COINCIDENCE?
HEY, THAT'S...
THAT'S "JOINCIDENCE" WITH A "C."
UH, PHOEBE? PHOEBE?
YEAH. UM, I'M OUT.
I'M IN.
ME TOO.
ME TOO. ALL RIGHT, WHAT DO YOU GOT?
WELL, YOU'D BETTER HOP OUT OF THE SHOWER
BECAUSE I GOTTA FLUSH.
WELL, WELL, WELL, HOP BACK IN, BUCKO
BECAUSE I GOT FOUR SIXES.
I GOT FOUR SIXES.
I WON.
I ACTUALLY WON.
OH, MY...
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK I'M GOING TO MAKE A LITTLE ROSS PILE.
YEAH, OH, LOOK.
I THINK THAT ONE WAS ROSS'S
AND, OOH, THAT ONE WAS ROSS'S.
? WELL, I HAVE GOT YOUR MONEY ?
? AND YOU'LL NEVER SEE IT ?
? AND YOUR FLY'S STILL OPEN ?
? HAH, I MADE YOU LOOK. ?
I'M IN.
I COULDN'T BE INNER.
MONICA, IN OR OUT?
I HATE THIS GAME.
OKAY, JOEY, YOUR BET.
I FOLD LIKE A CHEAP HOOKER WHO GOT HIT IN THE STOMACH
BY A FAT GUY WITH SORES ON HIS FACE.
OH, I'M OUT.
ROSS?
OH, I'M VERY IN.
CHANDLER?
COULDN'T BE MORE OUT.
ME TOO.
RACHEL.
UM, I WILL SEE YOU...
AND I'LL RAISE YOU.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
YOU WANT TO WASTE ANOTHER BUCK?
NOPE, NOT THIS TIME.
SO, WHAT DID YOU HAVE?
I'M NOT TELLING.
COME ON, SHOW THEM TO ME.
NO.
SHOW THEM TO ME.
GET YOUR HANDS
OUT OF THERE.
YOU KNOW, I'VE HAD DATES LIKE THIS.
BOY, YOU REALLY CAN'T STAND TO LOSE, CAN YOU?
YOUR WHOLE FACE IS GETTING RED.
THE LITTLE VEIN'S
POPPING OUT OF YOUR TEMPLE.
PLUS, THAT SHIRT DOESN'T REALLY MATCH THOSE PANTS.
FIRST OF ALL, I'M NOT LOSING...
HELLO. RACHEL GREEN.
MM MM MM MM MM.
EXCUSE ME.
IT'S ABOUT THE JOB.
BARBARA, HI.
HOW ARE YOU?
UH HUH.
NO, I UNDERSTAND.
YEAH, OH, WELL, COME ON
NO, I'M FINE.
DON'T BE SILLY.
YEAH, BUT, YOU KNOW, IF ANYTHING ELSE OPENS UP
PLEASE... HELLO?
HELLO?
HMM...
SORRY, RACH.
YEAH, YOU KNOW, THERE'S GOING TO BE LOTS OF OTHER STUFF.
YEAH. OKAY.
WHERE WERE WE?
OH. OKAY.
FIVE CARD DRAW.
UH... JACKS OR BETTER.
NOTHING WILD.
EVERYBODY ANTE.
LOOK, RACH, WE DON'T HAVE TO DO THIS.
YES, WE DO.
ALL RIGHT, CHECK.
CHECK.
I'M IN FOR 50 CENTS.
CALL.
I'M IN.
I SEE YOUR 50 CENTS...
AND I RAISE YOU...
FIVE DOLLARS.
I THOUGHT IT WAS A 50 CENT LIMIT.
WELL, I JUST LOST A JOB
AND I'D LIKE TO RAISE THE BET FIVE BUCKS.
DOES ANYBODY HAVE A PROBLEM WITH THAT?
NOT AT ALL. NO. NO, NO.
LOSER?
NO, I FOLD.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN YOU FOLD? HEY, COME ON, WHAT IS THIS?
I THOUGHT THAT ONCE THE CARDS ARE DEALT, I'M NOT A NICE GUY.
I MEAN, WHAT, WERE YOU JUST FULL OF IT?
I'M IN.
HOW MANY YOU WANT?
ONE.
DEALER TAKES TWO.
WHAT DO YOU BET?
I BET TWO DOLLARS.
OKAY.
SEE YOUR TWO...
AND I RAISE YOU...
TWENTY.
WHA...
I'LL SEE YOUR 20...
RAISE YOU 25.
SEE YOUR 25...
AND, UH... MONICA, GET MY PURSE.
RACHEL, THERE'S NOTHING IN IT.
OKAY, THEN GET ME YOUR PURSE.
OKAY...
HERE YOU GO. GOOD LUCK.
THANK YOU.
I SAW YOUR 25, AND I RAISE YOU...
SEVEN.
TEEN.
JOEY, I'M A LITTLE SHY.
THAT'S OKAY, ROSS.
YOU CAN ASK ME.
WHAT DO YOU NEED?
FIFTEEN.
HERE'S TEN.
HERE, I GOT FIVE, I GOT FIVE.
THANK YOU.
GOOD LUCK.
OKAY, I AM CALLING YOUR 17.
WHAT DO YOU GOT?
FULL HOUSE.
YOU GOT ME.
OH! OH!
? DA, DA, DA, DA, DA DA ?
? DA, DA, DA, DA, DA DA... ?
OH...
OH!
THAT'S ALL RIGHT. THAT'S A TOUGH HAND TO BEAT.
I THOUGHT WE HAD THEM.
WELL, WHEN YOU DON'T HAVE THE CARDS
YOU DON'T HAVE THE CARDS, YOU KNOW?
BUT LOOK HOW HAPPY SHE IS.
FINGERNAIL. AIRPLANE. AIRPORT.
AIRPORT 75! AIRPORT 77!
AIRPORT 79!
UH! TIME'S UP.
BYE, BYE... BIRDIE!
WHAT?
THAT'S A BIRD?
THAT'S A BIRD.
OKAY, OKAY, IT'S MY TURN.
GO.
UH, BEAN.
BEAN.
THE UNBEARABLE LIGHTNESS OF BEING!
YES!
THAT'S IT!
THAT YOU GET?