WHY?
I JUST WANT TO CHECK MY HOROSCOPE
TO SEE IF IT WAS RIGHT.
OH, MY GOD!
PHOEBE, DON'T LOOK NOW
BUT BEHIND YOU THERE IS A GUY
WHO HAS THE POTENTIAL TO BREAK OUR HEARTS
AND PLUNGE US INTO A PIT OF DEPRESSION.
WHERE?
OOH, COME TO MAMA.
HE'S COMING. BE COOL.
BE COOL. BE COOL.
NICE HAT.
THANKS.
WE SHOULD DO SOMETHING-- WHISTLE.
WE ARE NOT GOING TO WHISTLE.
YEAH, COME ON, DO IT! NO!
DO IT! DO IT! DO IT! DO IT!
WHOO HOO!
OH! I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU DID THAT!
IT'S ALL MY FAULT.
NO, IT'S MINE.
WHY DID I "WHOO HOO"?
I MEAN, WHAT WAS I HOPING WOULD HAPPEN?
THAT HE'D TURN AROUND AND SAY
"OOH. I LOVE THAT SOUND.
I MUST HAVE YOU NOW."
I JUST WISH THERE WAS SOMETHING
WE COULD DO.
HELLO.
HELLO, COMA GUY.
GET UP, YOU GIRL SCOUT! UP! UP! UP!
PHOEBE, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
MAYBE NOBODY'S TRIED THIS.
I WISH WE AT LEAST KNEW HIS NAME.
I KNOW. I HATE THAT THEY'RE CALLING HIM
JOHN DOE. IT'S SO SAD.
IT'S LIKE HE'S A DEER, A FEMALE DEER.
PHOEBE...
OH, I WAS GOING TO STOP.
WOULD YOU LOOK AT THAT FACE?
I MEAN, EVEN SLEEPING, HE LOOKS SMART.
YEAH, BUT DID YOU SEE THE DENTS IN HIS KNUCKLES?
THAT MEANS HE'S ARTISTIC.
OKAY. HE'S A LAWYER
WHO TEACHES SCULPTING ON THE SIDE.
AND HE CAN DANCE.
AND, HE'S THE KIND OF GUY
WHO, WHEN YOU'RE TALKING, HE'S LISTENING, YOU KNOW
AND NOT SAYING, "YEAH, I UNDERSTAND."
BUT REALLY WONDERING WHAT YOU LOOK LIKE NAKED.
OH, DEFINITELY!
I WISH ALL GUYS COULD BE LIKE HIM.
I KNOW.
I DON'T GET IT.
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW THIS GUY.
YEAH, ARE THERE NO CONSCIOUS MEN
IN THE CITY FOR YOU TWO?
HE DOESN'T HAVE ANYONE.
YEAH. WE FEEL KIND OF RESPONSIBLE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU SAID "WHOO HOO."
I DON'T EVEN SAY "WHOO HOO."
OH! SHE'S COMING UP! SHE'S COMING UP!
Folks, when we come back, we'll be talking about
her new book Euphoria Unbound.
The always interesting Nora Tyler Bing.
You might want to put the kids to bed for this one...
YOU KNOW, WE DON'T HAVE TO WATCH THIS.
WEEKEND AT BERNIE'S IS ON SHOWTIME, HBO,  AND CINEMAX.
NO WAY!
OH, COME ON.
SHE'S YOUR MOM.
EXACTLY.
WEEKEND AT BERNIE'S!
DEAD GUY GETTING HIT IN THE GROIN 20, 30 TIMES!
NO?
CHANDLER, I'VE GOT TO TELL YOU.
I LOVE YOUR MOM'S BOOKS.
I LOVE HER BOOKS.
I CANNOT GET ON A PLANE WITHOUT ONE.
I MEAN, THIS IS SO COOL.
YEAH, WELL, YOU WOULDN'T THINK IT'S COOL
IF YOU WERE 11 YEARS OLD
AND ALL YOUR FRIENDS WERE PASSING AROUND
PAGE 79 OF MISTRESS BITCH.
OH. I REMEMBER PAGE 79.
YOW!
OH, YEAH, THE THING AFTER THE OPERA
WITH THE GIRL WITH THE TRICK HIP, HUH?
COME ON, CHANDLER, I LOVE YOUR MOM.
I THINK SHE'S A BLAST.
YOU CAN SAY THAT BECAUSE SHE'S NOT YOUR MOM.
PLEASE.
BUONA SERA.
HI, SWEETIE.
WHEN DID RIGATONI GET BACK FROM ROME?
LAST NIGHT.
REALLY? SO THEN HIS PLANE DIDN'T EXPLODE
IN A BIG BALL OF FIRE?
JUST A DREAM I HAD.
BUT, PHEW!
HEY! HEY! SHE'S ON!
AH! NORA BING!
Before we get to the book
now what is this about you
being arrested in London?
What is that all about?
YOUR MOM WAS ARRESTED?
SHH! SHH!
I'M BUSY BEAMING WITH PRIDE.
THIS IS KIND OF EMBARRASSING, BUT...
OCCASIONALLY, AFTER I'VE BEEN INTIMATE WITH A MAN...
NOW, WHY WOULD SHE SAY THAT'S EMBARRASSING?
SHH!
I JUST GET THIS CRAVING FOR KUNG PAO CHICKEN.
THAT'S TOO MUCH INFORMATION!
Needless to say
HE GOT A HUGE TIP.
OH, GOD, I LOVE HER!
I THINK I'M HAVING A STROKE.
ALL RIGHT, SO NOW YOU'RE DOING THIS WHOLE BOOK TOUR THING.
HOW IS THAT GOING?
OH, FINE. I'M LEAVING
FOR NEW YORK TOMORROW-- WHICH I HATE.
BUT I GET TO SEE MY SON, WHO I LOVE.
AW!
OH. AND THIS IS THE WAY THAT I FIND OUT.
MOST MOMS USE THE PHONE.
YOU KNOW, I... DON'T TAKE THIS WRONG--
I JUST DON'T SEE YOU AS A MOM
SOMEHOW-- I DON'T MEAN THAT BAD.
OH. NO. I AM A FABULOUS MOM.
I BOUGHT MY SON HIS FIRST CONDOMS.
AND THEN HE BURST INTO FLAMES.
? NOTHING YOU CAN SAY ?
? CAN TEAR ME AWAY FROM MY GUY... ?
OH. LET'S SEE.
CONGRESS IS DEBATING A NEW DEFICIT REDUCTION BILL.
THE MAYOR WANTS TO RAISE SUBWAY FARES AGAIN.
THE HIGH TODAY WAS 45.
AND... OH, AND TEAMS PLAYED SPORTS.
? ...LIKE BIRDS OF FEATHER, WE STICK TOGETHER ?
? I'M TELLING YOU FROM THE START ?
? I CAN'T BE TORN APART FROM MY GUY ?
? NOTHING YOU CAN DO ?
? COULD MAKE ME UNTRUE TO MY GUY ?
?MY GUY?
? NOTHING YOU COULD BUY ?
? COULD MAKE ME TELL A LIE TO MY GUY ?
?MY GUY...?
WHAT ABOUT "GLEN"?
HE COULD BE A "GLEN."
UH UH.
NOT SPECIAL ENOUGH.
OOH, HOW ABOUT "AGAMEMNON"?
WAY TOO SPECIAL.
? YOU BEST BE BELIEVIN' ?
? I WON'T BE DECEIVIN' MY GUY. ?
MMM. I AM FAMISHED.
WHAT DO I WANT?
PLEASE, GOD.
DON'T LET IT BE KUNG PAO CHICKEN.
OH! YOU WATCHED THE SHOW!
WHAT DID YOU THINK?
I THINK YOU NEED
TO COME OUT OF YOUR SHELL
JUST A...
WHAT IS THIS DIVE?
ONLY YOU COULD HAVE PICKED THIS PLACE.
OH!
COME ON. SHUT UP. IT'S FUN.
GIVE ME A HUG.
I HEARD ABOUT THE DIVORCE.
LESBIAN, HUH?
YEAH.
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY:
BE CAREFUL WHAT YOU WISH FOR.
WELL, I THINK WE'RE READY FOR SOME TEQUILA.
I KNOW I AM. WHO'S DOING SHOTS?
YEAH. I'M IN.
THERE YOU GO... ROSS?
UH, I'M NOT REALLY A SHOT DRINKING KIND OF GUY.
SORRY! SORRY! WE'RE LATE.
WE, UH, KIND OF JUST
YOU KNOW, LOST TRACK OF TIME.
BUT A MAN CAN CHANGE.
ANYONE WANT ME TO APPRAISE ANYTHING?
WELL, I'M GOING TO GO TO TINKER TOWN.
MRS. BING, I HAVE TO TELL YOU
I HAVE READ EVERYTHING YOU'VE EVER WRITTEN.
NO, I MEAN IT.
I MEAN, WHEN I READ EUPHORIA AT MIDNIGHT
ALL I WANTED TO DO WAS BECOME A WRITER.
OH! PLEASE, HONEY!
LISTEN, IF I CAN DO IT, ANYBODY CAN.
YOU JUST START
WITH HALF A DOZEN EUROPEAN CITIES
THROW IN 30 EUPHEMISMS FOR MALE GENITALIA--
AND, BAM! YOU HAVE GOT YOURSELF A BOOK.
MY MOTHER, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN.
YEAH. ANY MESSAGES FOR ROOM 226?
YOU OKAY, SLUGGER?
OH. YEAH. I'M FINE. I'M FINE.
WHAT IS WITH YOU TONIGHT?
NOTHING.
NOTHING. NOTHING. NOTHING.
OKAY. THANK YOU.
IT'S THE ITALIAN HAND LICKER, ISN'T IT?
NO. IT'S THE ONE HE'S LICKING.
SHE'S SUPPOSED TO BE WITH YOU.
YOU'RE GOOD.
OH, ROSS, LISTEN TO ME.
I HAVE SOLD A HUNDRED MILLION
COPIES OF MY BOOKS-- AND YOU KNOW WHY?
A GIRL ON THE COVER
WITH HER NIPPLES SHOWING?
NO. BECAUSE I KNOW HOW TO WRITE MEN
THAT WOMEN FALL IN LOVE WITH.
BELIEVE ME. I CANNOT SELL A PAOLO.
PEOPLE WILL NOT TURN 325 PAGES FOR A PAOLO.
COME ON. THE GUY'S A SECONDARY CHARACTER.
HE'S JUST, UH, YOU KNOW
A COMPLICATION YOU EVENTUALLY KILL OFF.
WHEN?
HE'S NOT A HERO.
YOU KNOW WHO OUR HERO IS?
THE GUY ON THE COVER WITH HIS NIPPLES SHOWING?
NO. IT'S YOU.
PLEASE.
NO. REALLY. COME ON.
YOU'RE SMART. YOU'RE SEXY.
OH. RIGHT.
YES, YOU ARE.
AND THE FACT THAT YOU DON'T THINK YOU ARE
MAKES YOU EVEN SEXIER.
LISTEN TO ME, KIDDO.
YOU'RE GOING TO BE FINE.
BELIEVE ME.
UH OH.
UH...
I'LL JUST PEE IN THE STREET.
HEY, IS CHANDLER HERE?
YEAH.
OKAY, COME HERE.
OKAY. ABOUT LAST NIGHT.
YOU KNOW. CHANDLER. YOU DIDN'T TELL...
OKAY! BECAUSE I'M THINKING
WE DON'T NEED TO TELL CHANDLER.
I MEAN, IT WAS JUST A KISS, RIGHT?
ONE KISS-- NO BIG DEAL, RIGHT?
RIGHT, NO BIG DEAL.
OKAY.
IN BIZARRO WORLD!
YOU BROKE THE CODE.
WHAT CODE?
YOU DON'T KISS YOUR FRIEND'S MOM.
SISTERS ARE OKAY, MAYBE A HOT LOOKING AUNT
BUT NOT A MOM.
NEVER A MOM!
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING OUT HERE?
AH, WELL, JOEY AND I HAD DISCUSSED
GETTING IN AN EARLY MORNING RACQUETBALL GAME
BUT, APPARENTLY, SOMEBODY OVERSLEPT.
YEAH, WELL, YOU DON'T HAVE YOUR RACQUET.
NO. NO, I DON'T BECAUSE IT'S BEING RESTRUNG.
SOMEBODY WAS SUPPOSED TO BRING ME ONE.
YEAH, WELL, YOU DIDN'T CALL AND LEAVE YOUR GRIP SIZE.
YOU GUYS SPEND WAY TOO MUCH TIME TOGETHER.
OKAY, I'M SCUM. I'M SCUM.
ROSS, HOW COULD YOU LET THIS HAPPEN?
I DON'T KNOW!
IT'S NOT LIKE SHE'S A REGULAR MOM.
YOU KNOW, SHE'S SHE'S SEXY. SHE'S...
YOU DON'T THINK MY MOM'S SEXY?
WELL, NOT IN THE SAME WAY.
HEY!
I'LL HAVE YOU KNOW THAT GLORIA TRIBBIANI
WAS A HANDSOME WOMAN IN HER DAY, ALL RIGHT?
YOU THINK IT'S EASY GIVING BIRTH TO SEVEN CHILDREN?
HUH?
OKAY. I THINK WE'RE GETTING INTO A WEIRD AREA HERE.
HEY. HEY.
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING OUT HERE?
WELL, NOT PLAYING RACQUETBALL.
HE FORGOT TO LEAVE HIS GRIP SIZE.
HE DIDN'T GET THE GOGGLES.
OH.
WELL... SOUNDS LIKE YOU TWO HAVE ISSUES.
BYE, BABY.
CIAO, BELLA.
DO THEY WAIT FOR ME
TO DO THIS?
SO, ARE YOU GOING TO TELL HIM?
NO, I'M NOT GOING TO TELL HIM.
WHY WOULD I TELL HIM?
HOW ABOUT... BECAUSE IF YOU DON'T, HIS MOTHER MIGHT?
OH.
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING HERE?
AH, HE'S NOT EVEN WEARING A JOCK STRAP.
WHAT DID I ASK?
HI.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
NOTHING. I JUST THOUGHT I'D STOP BY
YOU KNOW, AFTER THE, AH, THAT I, YOU KNOW.
SO, WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
UM, I'M NOT REALLY HERE.
I JUST THOUGHT I'D DROP THESE OFF ON...
THE WAY. MY WAY.
DO YOU, UM, COME HERE A LOT...
WITHOUT ME?
NO.
NO! NO!
SO, UM, DO YOU THINK HE'S
DOING ANY BETTER THAN HE WAS THIS MORNING?
HOW WOULD I KNOW?
I I WASN'T HERE.
REALLY? NOT EVEN TO, UM...
CHANGE HIS PAJAMAS?!
OH, MY GOD.
YOU'RE MY FRIEND. I...
I HAD TO TELL YOU.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
PAOLO KISSED MY MOM?
YEAH. I DON'T KNOW IF YOU NOTICED
BUT HE HADA LOT TO DRINK.
YOU KNOW HOW HE GETS WHEN HE'S DRU...
I CAN'T DO THIS. I DID IT.
IT WAS ME. I'M SORRY.
I KISSED YOUR MOM.
WHAT?
I WAS REALLY UPSET ABOUT RACHEL AND PAOLO
AND I THINK I HAD TOO MUCH TEQUILA AND NORA...
UM, MRS. MOM, YOUR BING, WAS, AH...
SHE WAS JUST BEING NICE
YOU KNOW, BUT NOTHING HAPPENED
NOTHING. ASK JOEY.
JOEY CAME IN...
YOU KNEW ABOUT THIS?
UH... YOU KNOW, KNOWLEDGE IS A TRICKY THING.
I SPENT THE ENTIRE DAY WITH YOU.
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME?
HEY, HEY, HEY. YOU'RE LUCKY I CAUGHT THEM
WHEN I DID, OR ELSE WHO KNOWS WHAT WOULD HAVE HAPPENED?
THANKS, MAN. BIG HELP.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS!
WHAT THE HELL WERE YOU THINKING?!
I WASN'T. I DON'T KNOW...
YOU KNOW, OF ALL MY FRIENDS
NO ONE KNOWS THE CRAP I GO THROUGH
WITH MY MOM MORE THAN YOU.
I KNOW. I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU DID THIS.
ME NEITHER. YOU KNOW WHAT...?
I'M STILL MAD AT YOU FOR NOT TELLING ME.
YOU GOTTA LET ME SLAM THE DOOR!
CHANDLER, I DIDN'T KISS HER; HE DID.
SEE WHAT HAPPENS WHEN YOU BREAK THE CODE?
JOEY!
AH... UH?!
HI, RACH.
HEY.
AH...
A WOMAN UNDONE, BY RACHEL KAREN GREEN.
YEAH. THOUGHT I'D GIVE IT A SHOT.
I'M STILL ON THE FIRST CHAPTER.
NOW, DO YOU THINK HIS LOVE STICK
CAN BE LIBERATED FROM ITS DENIM PRISON?
YEAH. I'D SAY SO.
AND THERE'S NO "J" IN ENGORGED.
HEY, RACH.
HEY. HELLO.
HELLO.
GOING TO THE HOSPITAL TONIGHT?
NO. YOU?
YOU JUST ASKED ME.
OKAY. MAYBE IT WAS A TRICK QUESTION.
UM, RACHEL, CAN WE DO THIS NOW?
OKAY.
I AM SO HOT!
HERE'S A PICTURE OF MY MOTHER AND FATHER ON THEIR WEDDING DAY.
NOW YOU TELL ME SHE'S NOT A KNOCKOUT.
HUH?
I CANNOT BELIEVE WE'RE HAVING THIS CONVERSATION.
COME ON. JUST TRY TO PICTURE HER NOT PREGNANT. THAT'S ALL.
CENTRAL PERK IS PROUD TO PRESENT MISS PHOEBE BUFFAY.
THANKS.
HI. UM, OKAY. I'D LIKE TO START WITH A SONG
THAT'S ABOUT A MAN THAT I RECENTLY MET
WHO'S, UM, COME TO BE VERY IMPORTANT TO ME.
OKAY.
? YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE AWAKE TO BE MY MAN ?
? LONG AS YOU HAVE BRAIN WAVES ?
? I'LL BE THERE TO HOLD YOUR HAND ?
? THOUGH WE JUST MET THE OTHER DAY, THERE'S SOMETHING ?
? I HAVE GOT TO SAY... ?
OKAY. THANK YOU VERY MUCH
I'M GOING TO TAKE A SHORT BREAK.
HEY, THAT WAS PHOEBE BUFFAY, EVERYBODY.
WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?
OH, UH, PHOEBE JUST STARTED HER...
I BELIEVE I WAS TALKING TO JOEY.
ALL RIGHT THERE, MOTHER KISSER?
MOTHER KISSER!
I'LL SHUT UP.
CHANDLER, CAN I JUST SAY SOMETHING?
I KNOW YOU'RE STILL MAD AT ME.
I JUST WANT TO SAY THAT
THERE WERE TWO PEOPLE THERE THAT NIGHT.
OKAY? THERE WERE TWO SETS OF LIPS.
YES, WELL, I EXPECT THIS FROM HER.
OKAY? SHE'S ALWAYS BEEN A FREUDIAN NIGHTMARE.
IF SHE ALWAYS BEHAVES LIKE THIS
WHY DON'T YOU SAY SOMETHING?
BECAUSE IT'S COMPLICATED.
IT'S COMPLEX. IT'S...
HEY! YOU KISSED MY MOM!
WE'RE REHEARSING A GREEK PLAY.
THAT'S VERY FUNNY.
ARE WE DONE NOW? NO.
YOU MEAN, YOU'RE NOT GOING TO TALK TO HER?
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO TELL HER HOW YOU FEEL?
THAT WOULD BE A NO.
LOOK, JUST BECAUSE YOU PLAYED TONSIL TENNIS WITH MY MOM
DOESN'T MEAN YOU KNOW HER.
ALL RIGHT, TRUST ME, YOU CAN'T TALK TO HER.
OKAY. YOU CAN'T OR YOU CAN'T?
OKAY. THAT'S MY FINGER.
OKAY. THAT'S MY KNEE.
STILL DOING THE PLAY.
ALL RIGHT. WHAT'D YOU DO WITH HIM?
YOU'RE AWAKE!
LOOK AT YOU!
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
AH, A LITTLE WOOZY BUT BASICALLY OKAY.
GOSH, YOU LOOK GOOD.
I FEEL GOOD.
WHO ARE YOU?
OH, SORRY!
I'M PHOEBE BUFFAY.
I'M MONICA GELLER. I'VE BEEN TAKING CARE OF YOU.
WELL, WE BOTH HAVE.
SO THE ETCH A SKETCH IS FROM YOU GUYS?
ACTUALLY, IT'S JUST FROM ME.
I GOT YOU THE FOOT MASSAGER.
YOU KNOW WHO SHAVED YOU?
THAT WAS ME.
I READ TO YOU.
I SANG. HAH!
WELL... THANKS.
MY PLEASURE.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
SO... I GUESS I'LL SEE YOU AROUND.
WHAT, THAT'S IT?
"SEE YOU AROUND"?
WELL, WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO SAY?
OH, I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE, UH, "THAT WAS NICE."
IT MEANT SOMETHING TO ME.
I'LL CALL YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
I DON'T THINK YOU MEAN THAT.
THIS IS SO TYPICAL.
YOU KNOW, WE GIVE AND WE GIVE AND WE GIVE
AND THEN WE JUST GET NOTHING BACK
AND THEN ONE DAY, IT'S JUST
YOU KNOW, YOU WAKE UP AND "SEE YOU AROUND."
LET'S GO, PHOEBE.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
WE THOUGHT YOU WERE DIFFERENT
BUT I GUESS IT WAS JUST THE COMA.
HEY, KIDDO. CAR'S RUNNING DOWNSTAIRS.
I JUST WANTED TO DROP OFF THESE COPIES
OF MY BOOK FOR YOUR FRIENDS.
AUTOGRAPHED.
AND GIVE YOU A GOOD BYE KISS.
SO... HERE'S A KISS.
HERE'S THE GOOD BYE.
ANYTHING YOU WANT FROM LISBON?
NO, NO. JUST KNOWING YOU'RE GOING TO BE THERE IS ENOUGH.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, BE GOOD.
I LOVE YOU.
YOU KISSED MY BEST ROSS!
OR SOMETHING TO THAT EFFECT.
OKAY.
LOOK, IT WAS STUPID.
REALLY STUPID.
REALLY STUPID AND...
I DON'T EVEN KNOW HOW IT HAPPENED.
I'M SORRY, HONEY, AND I PROMISE IT WILL NEVER HAPPEN AGAIN.
REALLY, REALLY STUPID.
ARE WE OKAY NOW?
YEAH... NO.
NO.
AH. THE FORBIDDEN LOVE OF A MAN AND HIS DOOR.
SHH!
HE DID IT! HE TOLD HER OFF
AND NOT JUST ABOUT THE KISS, ABOUT EVERYTHING.
YOU'RE KIDDING!
HE SAID, "WHEN YOU GONNA GROW UP AND START BEING A MOM?"
WOW! WAIT! SHE THEN CAME BACK WITH
"THE QUESTION IS: WHEN ARE YOU GOING TO GROW UP
AND REALIZE I HAVE A BOMB?"
OKAY, WAIT A MINUTE. ARE YOU SURE SHE DIDN'T SAY
"WHEN ARE YOU GOING TO GROW UP AND REALIZEI AM YOUR MOM?"
THAT MAKES MORE SENSE.
YOU THINK? YEAH.
SO WHAT'S GOING ON NOW? I DON'T KNOW.
I'VE BEEN STANDING HERE SPELLING IT OUT FOR YOU.
I DON'T HEAR ANYTHING.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT!
WHAT DO YOU SEE?
IT'S HARD TO TELL. THEY'RE SO TINY AND UPSIDE DOWN.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT!
THEY'RE WALKING AWAY, THEY'RE WALKING AWAY...
NO! NO, THEY'RE NOT!
THEY'RE COMING RIGHT AT US!
RUN, RUN!
YOU OKAY, KIDDO?
YEAH, I'M OKAY.
ALL RIGHT. YOU BE GOOD.
FLY SAFE.
MRS. BING.
MR. GELLER.
HEY.
YOU MEAN THAT?
YEAH.
WHY NOT?
SO I TOLD HER.
OH... HOW DID IT GO?
AWFUL... AWFUL.
COULDN'T HAVE GONE WORSE.
WELL... HOW DO YOU FEEL?
PRETTY GOOD.
I TOLD HER.
WELL, SEE?
SO MAYBE IT WASN'T SUCH A BAD IDEA
YOU KNOW, ME KISSING YOUR MOM.
HUH? HUH?
BUT WE DON'T HAVE TO GO DOWN THAT ROAD.
OKAY. NOW, THIS IS JUST THE FIRST CHAPTER
AND I WANT YOUR ABSOLUTE HONEST OPINION. OKAY?
OH! AND ON PAGE TWO, HE'S NOT REACHING FOR HER HEAVING BEASTS.
WHY? SHE COULD HAVE HEAVING BEASTS.
RIGHT, RIGHT. BUT IN THIS CASE, SHE DOESN'T.
WHAT'S A NIFFLE?
YOU CAN USUALLY FIND THEM ON THE HEAVING BEASTS.
OH!
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT. SO I'M NOT A GREAT TYPIST.
WAIT. DID YOU GET TO THE PART ABOUT HIS HUGE THROBBING PENS?
I TELL YOU, DON'T WANT TO BE AROUND
WHEN HE STARTS WRITING WITH THOSE.
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S IT, GIVE THEM BACK.
NO. OH, NO.
OH, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, NO.
NO, I JUST GOT TO THE PART ABOUT HER PUBLIC HAIR.
COME ON, THAT'S IT! COME ON!