OH, HERE'S LITTLE BEN FALLING ASLEEP.
OH, A LITTLE BIT LATER.
IS HE GOING TO SLEEP?
IS HE GOING TO?
YUP! OUT LIKE A LIGHT.
LOOK AT THAT.
BOY THIS SURE TRUMPS THE "HAS HE POOPED" SERIES.
REALLY, LOOK, ROSS, WE LOVE HIM, OKAY
BUT RIGHT NOW HE'S JUST A LITTLE NAKED FAT GUY.
HOW EXCITED CAN WE GET?
HEY!
HEY. HEY. HEY.
HEY, WHAT  YOU GOT THERE?
400 PICTURES OF BEN ON A RUG.
OH!
AND HERE'S LITTLE BEN NODDING OFF.
OH, LOOK AT AUNT MONICA'S LITTLE BOY.
OH, LOOK, HE'S GOT ROSS'S HAIRCUT.
OH, LET ME SEE.
OH, GOD, IS HE JUST THE SWEETEST THING.
YOU MUST JUST WANT TO KISS HIM ALL OVER.
THAT WOULD BE NICE.
PARDON?
NOTHING. JUST A LITTLE EXTRA AIR IN MY MOUTH.
HEY, CHAN, CAN YOU HELP ME OUT HERE?
I PROMISE I'LL PAY YOU BACK.
OH, YEAH, RIGHT, OKAY.
INCLUDING THE WAFFLES LAST WEEK
YOU NOW OWE ME...
17 JILLION DOLLARS.
I WILL, REALLY. I'LL PAY YOU BACK THIS TIME.
AND WHERE'S THIS MONEY COMING FROM?
I'M HELPING OUT DOWN AT THE N.Y.U. MED SCHOOL
WITH SOME RESEARCH.
WHAT KIND OF RESEARCH?
UH, JUST, YOU KNOW, SCIENCE.
SCIENCE.
YEAH, I THINK I'VE HEARD OF THAT.
IT'S A FERTILITY STUDY.
OH.
JOEY, PLEASE TELL ME
YOU'RE ONLY DONATING YOUR TIME.
UH... ACTUALLY, A LITTLE BIT MORE THAN THAT.
THANK YOU, GOD.
THIS WILL BRING US SO MUCH JOY.
ALL RIGHT, COME ON, YOU GUYS.
IT'S NOT THAT BIG A DEAL.
REALLY, I MEAN, I JUST GO DOWN THERE EVERY OTHER DAY
AND MAKE MY CONTRIBUTION TO THE PROJECT.
HEY, HEY, BUT AT THE END OF TWO WEEKS I GET $700 DOLLARS.
HEY. WOW.
OOH, YOU'RE GOING TO BE MAKING MONEY HAND OVER FIST.
THAT'S FUNNY... VERY FUNNY.
NO, THIS IS REALLY, REALLY GREAT.
I'M GOING TO ACTUALLY KNOW SOMEBODY WHO LOVES WHAT THEY DO.
YEAH, BUT WHAT DO YOU DO TO UNWIND AFTER A TOUGH DAY?
OKAY, WE GOT THE COLESLAW, WE GOT THE BUNS...
WE'VE GOT THE GROUND UP FLESH
OF FORMERLY CUTE COWS AND TURKEYS. EWW...
YOU KNOW, I JUST LOVE BARBECUING WITH YOU.
MEN ARE HERE.
WE MAKE FIRE.
COOK MEAT.
THEN PUT OUT FIRE BY PEEING
NO GET INVITED BACK. CUTE, CUTE.
OH, JOEY, MELODY CALLED, SAID SHE'S GOING TO BE LATE.
OH, OKAY.
SO HOW ARE THINGS GOING WITH YOU TWO?
IS SHE BECOMING YOUR SPECIAL SOMEONE?
I DON'T KNOW.
SHE'S, UH... SHE'S PRETTY GREAT.
YEAH?
WHAT DOES SHE THINK OF YOU R LITTLE "SCIENCE PROJECT"?
WHAT-- YOU THINK I'M GOING TO TELL A GIRL I LIKE
THAT I'M ALSO SEEING A CUP?
MAN'S GOT A POINT.
YEAH, WELL, THE TOUGH THING IS
SHE REALLY WANTS TO HAVE SEX WITH ME.
CRAZY BITCH.
YEAH, WELL, I STILL GOT A WEEK LEFT TO GO IN THE PROGRAM
AND ACCORDING TO THE RULES, IF I WANT TO GET THE MONEY
I'M NOT ALLOWED TO CONDUCT ANY PERSONAL EXPERIMENTS
IF YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
JOEY, WE ALWAYS KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN.
HEY. HEY.
HOW LONG DID YOU THINK THIS BARBECUE WAS GOING TO LAST?
I'M GOING TO CHINA.
GEEZ, YOU SAY ONE THING...
YOU'RE GOING TO CHINA?
IT'S FOR THE MUSEUM.
SOMEONE FOUND A BONE.
WE WANT THE BONE, BUT THEY DON'T WANT US TO HAVE THE BONE
SO I'M GOING OVER THERE TO TRY AND PERSUADE THEM TO GIVE US...
IT'S A WHOLE BIG BONE THING.
ANYWAY, I'M GOING TO BE GONE FOR LIKE A WEEK.
SO IF YOU WANT TO REACH ME, YOU CAN'T
SO HERE'S MY ITINERARY.
UM, HERE'S A PICTURE OF ME.
OH, LET ME SEE.
COULD YOU TAKE IT TO CAROL'S EVERY NOW AND THEN
AND SHOW IT TO BEN JUST SO HE DOESN'T FORGET ME?
YEAH.
HI, BEN, I'M YOUR FATHER.
I AM THE HEAD!
ALL RIGHT. THIS BARBECUE'S GOING TO BE VERY FUN.
HEY, IS RACHEL HERE?
I WANTED TO WISH HER A HAPPY BIRTHDAY BEFORE I LEFT.
OH, NO, SHE'S OUT HAVING DRINKS WITH CARL.
OH.
HEY, WHO'S CARL?
YOU KNOW, THAT GUY
THAT SHE MET AT THE COFFEEHOUSE.
NO.
WELL, SEE, THERE'S THIS GUY THAT SHE MET...
AT THE COFFEEHOUSE, RIGHT.
SO YOU DO KNOW WHO HE IS.
OKAY, I'M GOING TO GO SAY GOOD BYE TO THE GUYS.
OKAY. HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT? TELL THEM THAT BONE STORY.
HI.
HEY.
I HAVE TO GO TO CHINA.
THE COUNTRY?
NO, NO. THIS BIG PILE OF DISHES IN MY MOM'S BREAKFRONT.
DO YOU GUYS KNOW
WHO CARL IS?
LET'S SEE... ALVIN, SIMON, THEODORE...
NO.
WELL, RACHEL'S HAVING DRINKS WITH HIM TONIGHT.
OH, NO!
HOW CAN SHE DO THAT
WHEN SHE'S NEVER SHOWN ANY INTEREST IN YOU?
FORGET ABOUT HER.
HE'S RIGHT, MAN. PLEASE.
MOVE ON. GO TO CHINA.
EAT CHINESE FOOD.
OF COURSE, THERE THEY JUST CALL IT "FOOD."
YEAH, I GUESS.
I DON'T KNOW.
ALL RIGHT. JUST... JUST GIVE HER THIS FOR ME, OKAY?
LISTEN, BUDDY, WE'RE JUST LOOKING OUT FOR YOU.
WE WANT YOU TO BE HAPPY.
AND I MAY ONLY HAVE A COUPLE BEERS IN ME
BUT I LOVE YOU, MAN.
I'M STILL ON MY FIRST.
I JUST THINK YOU'RE NICE.
ANYWAY, THAT'S WHEN ME AND MY FRIEND
STARTED THIS WHOLE FRUITBASKET BUSINESS.
WE CALL OURSELVES "THE THREE BASKETEERS."
LIKE THE THREE MUSKETEERS, ONLY WITH FRUIT.
OH.
OKAY.
HOW DOES EVERYBODY LIKE THEIR BURGERS?
OH, NO, NO, PRESENTS FIRST, FOOD LATER.
I DON'T CARE WHAT RACHEL SAYS, WE'RE DOING PRESENTS FIRST.
HEY, HOLD  ON THERE, TIGER.
HOW'S IT GOING? HOW YOU HOLDING UP?
WELL, NOT SO GOOD.
SHE DEFINITELY THINKS TONIGHT'S THE NIGHT
WE'RE GOING TO COMPLETE THE TRANSACTION
IF YOU KNOW WHAT...
AND YOU DO.
SO HAVE YOU EVER THOUGHT ABOUT BEING THERE FOR HER?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOU KNOW, JUST BE THERE FOR HER.
NOT FOLLOWING YOU.
THINK ABOUT IT.
OKAY, I'M GUESSING THIS IS FROM...
WELL, THANK YOU, MELANIE.
OKAY, THIS ONE RIGHT HERE IS FROM ME.
OKAY.
IT'S LIGHT.
IT RATTLES.
IT'S...
TRAVEL SCRABBLE.
WOW. THANK YOU.
THIS ONE'S FROM JOEY.
FEELS LIKE A BOOK, I THINK IT'S A BOOK, FEELS LIKE A BOOK.
AND IT'S A BOOK.
OH, IT'S DR. SEUSS!
THAT BOOK GOT ME THROUGH SOME TOUGH TIMES.
THERE IS A LITTLE CHILD INSIDE THIS MAN.
YES. THE DOCTORS SAY IF THEY REMOVE IT
HE'LL DIE.
WHO'S THIS FROM?
OH, THAT'S ROSS'S.
OH.
OH, MY GOD.
HE REMEMBERED.
REMEMBERED WHAT?
IT WAS, LIKE, MONTHS AGO.
WE WERE WALKING BY THIS ANTIQUE STORE
AND I SAW THIS PIN IN THE WINDOW
AND I TOLD HIM THAT IT WAS JUST LIKE ONE
MY GRANDMOTHER HAD WHEN I WAS A LITTLE GIRL.
OH! I CAN'T BELIEVE HE REMEMBERED.
WELL, SURE, BUT CAN YOU PLAY IT ON A PLANE?
IT'S SO PRETTY.
THIS MUST HAVE COST HIM A FORTUNE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HE DID THIS.
COME ON, ROSS? YOU REMEMBER BACK IN COLLEGE
WHEN HE FELL IN LOVE WITH CAROL AND BOUGHT HER
THAT RIDICULOUSLY EXPENSIVE CRYSTAL DUCK?
WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY?
CRYSTAL DUCK.
NO, NO, NO.
THE, UM... THE LOVE PART?
FOR... FLANIN...
OH, MY GOD!
OH, NO, NO, NO, NO.
THAT'S GOOD. JUST KEEP RUBBING YOUR HEAD.
THAT WILL TURN BACK TIME.
THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE.
I MEAN, THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE.
I KNOW. THIS IS REALLY, REALLY HUGE.
NO, IT'S NOT.
IT'S SMALL. IT'S TINY.
IT'S PETITE. IT'S WEE.
UH UH. I DON'T THINK ANY OF OUR LIVES
ARE EVER GOING TO BE THE SAME EVER AGAIN.
IS THERE A MUTE BUTTON ON THIS WOMAN?
I THINK THIS IS SO GREAT.
I MEAN, YOU AND ROSS!
DID YOU HAVE ANY IDEA?
NO. NONE.
I MEAN, MY FIRST NIGHT IN THE CITY HE MENTIONED
SOMETHING ABOUT ASKING ME OUT
BUT NOTHING EVER HAPPENED SO I JUST...
WELL, WHAT ELSE DID HE SAY?
I MEAN, DOES HE, LIKE, WANT TO GO OUT WITH ME?
WELL, GIVEN THAT HE'S DESPERATELY IN LOVE WITH YOU
HE PROBABLY WOULDN'T MIND GETTING A CUP
OF COFFEE OR SOMETHING.
ROSS?
ALL THIS TIME?
WELL, I'VE GOT TO TALK TO HIM.
HE'S IN CHINA!
THE COUNTRY.
WELL, DID HIS FLIGHT LEAVE YET?
ARE YOU KIDDING?
HE'S AT HIS SEAT WATCHING A WOMAN DO THIS...
HE'S GONE.
NO, NO, WAIT.
HIS FLIGHT DOESN'T LEAVE FOR ANOTHER 45 MINUTES.
WHAT ABOUT THE TIME DIFFERENCE?
FROM HERE TO THE AIRPORT?
YES!
YOU'RE NEVER GOING TO MAKE IT.
WELL, I'VE GOT TO TRY.
RACHEL, WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO SAY TO HIM?
I I I DON'T KNOW.
WELL, THEN MAYBE YOU SHOULDN'T GO.
HE'S RIGHT, BECAUSE IF YOU'RE GOING
TO JUST, LIKE, BREAK HIS HEART
THAT'S THE KIND OF THING THAT CAN WAIT.
YEAH, BUT IF IT'S GOOD NEWS, YOU SHOULD TELL HIM NOW.
I DON'T KNOW. MAYBE I'LL KNOW WHEN I SEE HIM.
HERE, LOOK.
ALL RIGHT. DOES THIS HELP?
NO...
LOOK, ALL I KNOW IS THAT I CANNOT WAIT A WEEK UNTIL I SEE HIM.
I MEAN, THIS IS JUST TOO BIG.
YOU KNOW, I'VE JUST GOT... I'VE JUST TO TALK TO HIM.
I'VE GOT TO... OKAY. I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
RACHEL, I LOVE YOU!
DEAL WITH ME FIRST!
ZAI JIAN.
WO DE FENGZHENG YOU CHONGZI...
ALL RIGHTY!
NI XIAO SHI MA!
ROSS!
PARDON ME! HI.
MAY I SEE YOUR BOARDING PASS?
NO, NO, I DON'T HAVE ONE.
I JUST NEED TO TALK TO MY FRIEND.
OH, I'M SORRY. YOU ARE NOT ALLOWED ON THE JETWAY
UNLESS YOU HAVE A BOARDING PASS.
I KNOW, BUT HE JUST WENT ON. HE'S RIGHT THERE.
HE'S GOT THE BLUE JACKET ON.
I'M SORRY. FEDERAL REGULATIONS.
OKAY. ALL RIGHT. OKAY.
THEN COULD YOU PLEASE
JUST GIVE HIM A MESSAGE FOR ME?
PLEASE? THIS IS VERY IMPORTANT.
ALL RIGHT. WHAT'S THE MESSAGE?
I DON'T KNOW.
EXCUSE ME. SIR! SIR!
EXCUSE ME. SIR!
I HAVE A MESSAGE FOR YOU.
WHAT?
IT'S FROM RACHEL.
SHE SAID THAT SHE LOVED THE PRESENT
AND SHE'LL SEE YOU WHEN YOU GET BACK.
TOBY, OH, FOR GOD'S SAKE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT SHE'S TALKING ABOUT.
THERE'S NO RACHEL!
DON'T GIVE ME THAT DEEP FREEZE.
MMM...
OH, JOEY, JOEY, JOEY.
I THINK I BLACKED OUT THERE FOR A MINUTE.
IT WAS NOTHING.
WELL, NOW WE'VE GOT
TO FIND SOMETHING FUN FOR YOU.
UH... YOU KNOW WHAT?
FORGET ABOUT ME.
LET'S, UH...
LET'S GIVE YOU ANOTHER TURN.
ME AGAIN?
SURE! WHY NOT?
BOY! SOMEBODY'S GOING TO GET A BIG FRUIT BASKET TOMORROW.
OH! I'VE GOT TO TELL YOU, JOEY
YOU ARE NOTHING LIKE I THOUGHT YOU WOULD BE.
HOW DO YOU MEAN?
I DON'T KNOW. I GUESS I JUST HAD YOU PEGGED
AS ONE OF THOSE GUYS WHO ARE ALWAYS "ME, ME, ME."
BUT YOU...
YOU'RE A GIVER.
YOU'RE, LIKE, THE MOST GENEROUS MAN I'VE EVER MET.
I MEAN...
YOU'RE PRACTICALLY A WOMAN.
YOU'RE JUST SAYING THAT.
SO?
I MISSED HIM.
OH, I'M SO SORRY.
THAT'S TOO BAD.
YEAH, RIGHT.
NO, I FEEL BAD FOR HER, I REALLY DO.
I CAN THINK OF SOMEBODY OTHER THAN MYSELF.
ALL RIGHT, I'M GOING TO BED.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, RACH, HANG IN THERE.
THANKS.
YES!
PIZZA COUPONS.
WELL, GOD.
ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS WANT HELP CLEANING UP WITH THIS MESS HERE?
YEAH, THAT'D BE GREAT.
UH, SO, UH, RACH
YOU WANT TO SAVE THIS WRAPPING PAPER?
I MEAN, IT'S ONLY A LITTLE BIT TORN.
SO ARE YOU GOING TO GO FOR IT WITH ROSS
OR SHOULD I JUST THROW IT OUT?
I DON'T KNOW.
I THOUGHT ABOUT IT ALL THE WAY THERE
AND I THOUGHT ABOUT IT ALL THE WAY BACK.
AND, UH, OH, YOU GUYS, YOU KNOW, IT'S ROSS.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
I MEAN, IT'S ROSS.
SURE. SURE.
I DON'T KNOW.
I MEAN, THIS IS JUST MY INITIAL GUT FEELING...
BUT I'M THINKING...
I'M THINKING IT'D BE REALLY GREAT.
OH, MY GOD, ME, TOO!
WE'LL BE LIKE FRIENDS IN LAW.
YOU KNOW WHAT THE BEST PART IS?
THE BEST PART IS THAT YOU ALREADY KNOW EVERYTHING ABOUT HIM.
IT'S LIKE STARTING ON THE 15th DATE.
YEAH, BUT YOU KNOW.
IT WOULD BE LIKE STARTING ON THE 15th DATE.
ANOTHER GOOD POINT.
NO. I MEAN...
WHEN YOU'RE AT THE 15th DATE
YOU'RE ALREADY IN A VERY RELATIONSHIPPY PLACE.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE COMMITTED.
HUH?
WELL, I MEAN, THEN WHAT HAPPENS IF IT DOESN'T WORK OUT?
WHY ISN'T IT WORKING OUT?
I DON'T KNOW, SOMETIMES IT DOESN'T.
IS HE NOT CUTE ENOUGH FOR YOU?
DOES HE NOT MAKE ENOUGH MONEY?
NO. I'M JUST...
MAYBE THERE'S SOMEONE ELSE.
WHA... IS THERE?
IS THERE SOMEONE ELSE?
NO! THERE IS NO ONE ELSE!
THEN WHY THE HELL ARE YOU DUMPING MY BROTHER?
WELL...
HEY, BIG...
SHH!
SPENDER.
SHE'S STILL ASLEEP.
SO, HOW'D IT GO?
IT WAS AMAZING.
YOU KNOW HOW YOU ALWAYS THINK YOU'RE GREAT IN BED?
THE FACT THAT YOU'D EVEN ASK THAT QUESTION
SHOWS HOW LITTLE YOU KNOW ME.
WELL, IT'S LIKE, LAST NIGHT
I COULDN'T DO THE THING THAT USUALLY MAKES ME GREAT.
SO I HAD TO DO ALL THIS OTHER STUFF
AND THE RESPONSE I GOT-- MAN, OH, MAN!
IT WAS LIKE A TICKER TAPE PARADE.
YES, I KNOW.
AS IT HAPPENS, MY ROOM
IS VERY, VERY CLOSE TO THE PARADE ROUTE.
IT WAS AMAZING.
AND NOT JUST FOR HER, UH UH.
FOR ME, TOO.
IT'S LIKE ALL OF A SUDDEN, I'M BLIND.
BUT ALL MY OTHER SENSES ARE HEIGHTENED, YOU KNOW?
IT'S LIKE I WAS ABLE TO APPRECIATE IT
ON ANOTHER LEVEL.
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU HAD ANOTHER LEVEL.
I KNOW. NEITHER DID I.
HEY, IS SOMETHING GOING ON WITH OJ?
HEY, GREAT SKIRT!
BIRTHDAY PRESENT?
YEAH.
WELL, FROM WHO?
FROM YOU-- I EXCHANGED THE BLOUSE
YOU GOT ME.
WELL, IT'S THE THOUGHT.
HEY, DOESN'T ROSS' FLIGHT GET IN IN A COUPLE OF HOURS...
AT GATE 27B?
UH, YEAH. UH, MONICA, YOU KNOW, HONEY
I'VE BEEN THINKING ABOUT IT
AND I'VE DECIDED THIS WHOLE ROSS THING
IS JUST NOT A GOOD IDEA.
WHY?
BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE
I WOULDN'T JUST BE GOING OUT WITH HIM
I WOULD BE GOING OUT WITH ALL OF YOU.
THERE WOULD JUST BE ALL THIS PRESSURE...
NO. NO PRESSURE! NO PRESSURE!
MONICA, NOTHING HAS EVEN HAPPENED YET
AND YOU ARE ALREADY SO...
I AM NOT "SO"!
OKAY. I WAS A TEENSY BIT WEIRD AT FIRST
BUT I'LL BE GOOD. I PROMISE.
OKAY?
WHO IS IT?
It's me, Carl.
COME ON UP.
BEHIND MY BROTHER'S BACK?
IS EXACTLY THE KIND OF CRAZY THING
YOU WON'T BE HEARING FROM ME.
700 BUCKS!
ALL RIGHT! YOU DID IT!
DO WE HAVE ANY FRUIT?
MAN, HELL OF A TWO WEEKS, HUH?
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT, THOUGH?
I REALLY FEEL LIKE I LEARNED SOMETHING.
REALLY? SO YOU'RE GOING TO STICK WITH THIS
"IT'S ALL FOR HER" THING?
WHAT ARE YOU? CRAZY?
WHEN A BLIND MAN GETS HIS SIGHT BACK
DOES HE WALK AROUND LIKE THIS?
I'M JUST SAYING
IF I SEE ONE MORE PICTURE OF ED BEGLEY, JR.
IN THAT STUPID ELECTRIC CAR
I'M GOING TO SHOOT MYSELF!
I MEAN, DON'T GET ME WRONG
I'M NOT AGAINST ENVIRONMENTAL ISSUES PER SE.
IT'S JUST THAT GUY!
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'D RATHER GO OUT WITH HIM THAN ME.
WOULD YOU EXCUSE ME, PLEASE.
I'M TRYING TO HAVE A DATE HERE.
FINE. JUST STOP THINKING ABOUT ME.
CAN'T DO IT, CAN YOU?
SO, I'M THINKING ABOUT YOU.
SO WHAT?
I DON'T GET IT.
WHAT DO YOU SEE IN THIS GUY, ANYWAY?
WELL, HE SEEMS TO BE A VERY NICE... GUY.
I MEAN, COME ON, BUDDY! GET A REAL CAR!
RACHEL, COME ON.
GIVE US A CHANCE.
ROSS, IT'S TOO HARD.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA-- WHY?
BECAUSE IT MIGHT GET WEIRD FOR EVERYONE ELSE?
WHO CARES ABOUT THEM? THIS IS ABOUT US.
LOOK, I'VE BEEN IN LOVE WITH YOU SINCE, LIKE, THE NINTH GRADE.
ROSS, YOU'RE LIKE MY BEST FRIEND.
IF WE BROKE UP AND I LOST YOU...
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
WHAT MAKES YOU THINK WE'RE GOING TO BREAK UP?
WELL, HAVE YOU BEEN INVOLVED WITH SOMEONE
WHERE YOU HAVEN'T BROKEN UP?
NO.
BUT IT ONLY HAS TO HAPPEN ONCE.
LOOK, YOU AND I BOTH KNOW
WE ARE PERFECT FOR EACH OTHER.
RIGHT? I MEAN, SO THE ONLY QUESTION IS
ARE YOU ATTRACTED TO ME?
I DON'T KNOW.
I MEAN, I'VE NEVER LOOKED AT YOU THAT WAY BEFORE.
WELL, START LOOKING.
WOW.
EXACTLY!
AND YOU JUST KNOW I'M GOING TO BE THE GUY
CAUGHT BEHIND THIS HAMMERHEAD IN TRAFFIC.
UH, RIGHT.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
WHAT?
I FORGOT I'M SUPPOSED
TO PICK UP A FRIEND AT THE AIRPORT.
I AM SO SORRY.
SO, IF YOU WANT TO STAY AND FINISH YOUR DRINKS
PLEASE DO.
I'M SORRY. I'VE GOT TO GO. I'M SORRY.
BUT...
HEY, WHERE YOU GOING?
TO GET ROSS.
WHAT? OH, MY GOD!
THIS IS SO EXCITING!
YEAH, I KNOW.
MONICA, LISTEN, IF YOU WANT THE REST OF MY DATE
I'M NOT GOING TO FINISH IT.
RACHEL, HE'S NOT A SANDWICH.
NO, HE'S AN INVESTMENT BANKER WITH TICKETS TO THE OPERA.
HELLOOOO!
HEY, RACH, WHERE YOU GOING?
AIRPORT.
OH, NO, NO, YOU CAN'T TELL HIM.
THERE'S SO MUCH STUFF I HAVEN'T DONE IN MY LIFE.
I HAVEN'T WATCHED BAYWATCH SINCE THEY BROUGHT ON YASMINE BLEETH.
OKAY, CHANDLER, RELAX.
THIS IS A GOOD GOING TO THE AIRPORT.
OH! OH, WELL, THEN FLY, GOOD WOMAN.
FLY LIKE THE WIND.
I'M FLYING.
DON'T FORGET TO TELL HIM I'M THE ONE WHO BLEW IT.
YES, ANOTHER SUCCESSFUL CASE FOR THE LOVE DOCTOR.
EXCUSE ME. PARDON ME.
EXCUSE ME. EXCUSE ME. SORRY.
TOBY, FOR GOD'S SAKE. WILL YOU LET IT GO?
THERE'S NO RACHEL!
EXCUSE ME. SORRY.
OH, HEY. HEY. I GOT THAT.
OH, THANKS. SWEETIE.
NO PROBLEM.
I CANNOT WAIT FOR YOU TO MEET MY FRIENDS.
REALLY? YEAH.
YOU DON'T THINK
THEY'LL JUDGE AND RIDICULE ME?
NO, NO. THEY WILL. I JUST...
CAN'T WAIT.
COME ON, THEY'RE GOING TO LOVE YOU.