OKAY, OKAY, I CHECKED.
WE HAVE EARL GREY, ENGLISH BREAKFAST
CINNAMON STICK, CHAMOMILE, MINT MEDLEY, BLACKBERRY
AND, UH... OH, WAIT.
THERE'S ONE MORE.
UM, LEMON SOOTHER.
YOU'RE NOT THE GUY THAT ASKED FOR THE TEA, ARE YOU?
MAIL CALL, RACHEL GREEN, BUNK SEVEN.
THANK YOU.
OH, COOL.
A FREE SAMPLE OF COFFEE.
OH, GOOD, BECAUSE WHERE ELSE WOULD WE GET ANY?
OH. RIGHT.
OH, GREAT.
WHAT IS IT?
COUNTRY CLUB NEWSLETTER.
MY MOTHER SENDS ME THE ENGAGEMENT NOTICES
FOR INSPIRATION.
OH, MY GOD. OH, MY GOD, IT'S BARRY AND MINDY.
BARRY WHO YOU ALMOST...?
BARRY WHO I ALMOST...
AND MINDY, YOUR MAID OF...?
MINDY, MY MAID OF...
LET ME SEE THAT.
THAT'S MINDY?
WOW. SHE IS PRETTY.
LUCKY.
TO HAVE HAD A FRIEND LIKE YOU.
AND NOW IT'S QUIET TIME.
SHH! SHH! SHH! SHH!
MARCEL, BRING ME THE RICE.
COME ON, BRING ME THE RICE. COME ON.
GOOD BOY. GOOD BOY.
COME ON, GIVE ME THE RICE.
THANK YOU. GOOD BOY.
I SEE HE'S FINALLY MASTERED THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN "BRING ME THE..." AND "PEE IN THE..."
"BRING ME THE..." AND...
RACH.
WHAT?
HI.
OH. I'M SORRY.
OH, THIS IS SO STUPID.
I MEAN, I GAVE BARRY UP, RIGHT?
MMM.
I SHOULD BE HAPPY FOR THEM.
I AM. I'M HAPPY FOR THEM.
REALLY?
NO.
OH.
OH, I GUESS IT WOULD BE DIFFERENT
IF I WERE WITH SOMEBODY.
WHOA. WHAT, UH...?
WHAT HAPPENED TO, UH... "FORGET RELATIONSHIPS"?
"I'M DONE WITH MEN"?
THE WHOLE, UH, PENIS EMBARGO?
OH, I DON'T KNOW.
I GUESS IT'S... IT'S NOT ABOUT NO GUYS.
IT'S ABOUT THE RIGHT GUY, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, WITH BARRY
IT WAS SAFE AND IT WAS EASY, BUT THERE WAS NO HEAT.
YOU KNOW, WITH PAOLO, THAT'S ALL THERE WAS
WAS HEAT.
IT WAS JUST THIS RAW, ANIMAL, SEXUAL...
RIGHT, RIGHT. I GOT IT.
I WAS THERE.
WELL, I MEAN
DO YOU THINK IT CAN EVER HAVE BOTH?
YOU KNOW, SOMEONE WHO'S, LIKE, YOUR BEST FRIEND
BUT THEN ALSO CAN MAKE YOUR TOES CURL?
YES, YES.
YES, YES, I DO.
I REALLY DO.
UH, IN FACT, IT'S FUNNY.
VERY OFTEN SOMEONE WHO YOU WOULDN'T THINK
COULD, COULD...
CURL YOUR TOES
MIGHT JUST BE THE ONE WHO, UH... WHO...
HI.
GETS INTERRUPTED. HI.
HEY, GUYS, HOW WAS THE MOVIE?
WONDERFUL. SO GOOD.
SUCK FEST.
TOTAL CHICK FLICK.
I'M SORRY IT WASN'T ONE OF THOSE MOVIES
WITH, LIKE, YOU KNOW, LIKE, GUNS AND BOMBS
AND, LIKE, BUSES GOING REALLY FAST.
HEY, I DON'T NEED VIOLENCE TO ENJOY A MOVIE
JUST SO LONG AS THERE'S A LITTLE NUDITY.
THERE WAS NUDITY.
I MEANT FEMALE NUDITY.
I DON'T NEED TO SEE LOU GRANT FROLICKING.
HUGH. HUGH.
HUGH GRANT. HUGH GRANT.
ALL RIGHT, I'VE GOT TO GO.
COME ON, MARCEL. COME ON.
WE'RE GOING TO GO TAKE A BATH.
YES, WE ARE, AREN'T WE? YES, WE ARE.
THEY'RE STILL JUST FRIENDS, RIGHT?
AND I WILL SEE YOU TOMORROW.
THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU'RE GOING TO SPEND TOMORROW
AT AUNT RACHEL'S, AREN'T YOU, HUH?
HANG ON, HANG ON.
DOES AUNT MONICA GET A SAY IN THIS?
PLEASE, AUNT MONICA?
PLEASE?
OH, UNCLENCH. YOU'RE NOT EVEN GOING
TO BE HERE.
YOU KNOW, I CANNOT BELIEVE
WE ARE EVEN HAVING THIS DISCUSSION.
I AGREE. I'M, LIKE, IN DISBELIEF.
I MEAN, DON'T YOU THINK
IF THINGS WERE GOING TO HAPPEN WITH RACHEL
THEY WOULD HAVE HAPPENED ALREADY?
I'M TELLING YOU, SHE SAID SHE'S LOOKING FOR A RELATIONSHIP
WITH SOMEONE EXACTLY LIKE ME.
SHE REALLY SAID THAT?
WELL, I ADDED THE "EXACTLY LIKE ME" PART.
BUT SHE SAID SHE'S LOOKING FOR SOMEONE
AND SOMEONE IS GOING TO BE THERE TONIGHT.
TONIGHT TONIGHT?
WELL, I THINK IT'S PERFECT, YOU KNOW?
IT'S JUST GOING TO BE THE TWO OF US.
SHE SPENT ALL DAY TAKING CARE OF MY MONKEY.
I CAN'T REMEMBER THE LAST TIME
I GOT A GIRL TO TAKE CARE OF MY MONKEY.
ANYWAY, I FIGURED AFTER WORK
I'D GO PICK UP A BOTTLE OF WINE
GO OVER THERE AND TRY TO WOO HER.
HEY, YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU SHOULD DO?
YOU SHOULD TAKE HER BACK TO THE 1890s
WHEN THAT PHRASE WAS LAST USED.
She keeps this up, honey,
I swear you'll be finished with this sucker
by the end of the week
NOW, NOW THE ONE IN THE FEATHER BOA...
THAT'S DR. FRANCIS.
NOW SHE USED TO BE A MAN.
OKAY? OH, LOOK. SEE, NOW THERE'S RAVEN
AND WE HATE HER.
WE'RE GLAD SHE'S DYING AND THAT...
MARCEL, ARE YOU PLAYING WITH MONICA'S SHOES?
YOU KNOW YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO PLAY...
WHOA. WHOA.
MARCEL, DID YOU POO IN THE SHOE?
OH, MARCEL, BAD MONKEY.
OH, GOSH.
OH.
SORRY, BARRY.
LITTLE ENGAGEMENT GIFT.
I'M SURE YOU DIDN'T REGISTER FOR THAT.
WHO DIED? WHO DIED?
ROLL HIM OVER.
OH, COME ON, ROLL HIM OVER.
OH. WELL...
WE KNOW IT WASN'T DEXTER, RIGHT, MARCEL?
BECAUSE...
MARCEL?
MARCEL? MAR...
HOW COULD YOU LOSE HIM?
I DON'T KNOW, I DON'T KNOW.
WE WERE WATCHING TV
AND THEN HE POOPED IN MONICA'S SHOE...
WAIT...
HE POOPED IN MY SHOE?
WHICH ONE?
I DON'T KNOW.
THE LEFT ONE.
WHICH ONES?
OH. THOSE LITTLE CLUNKY AMISH THINGS YOU THINK
GO WITH EVERYTHING.
HEY. HEY. HEY.
WHOA. OH.
WHY IS THE AIR IN HERE SO NEGATIVE?
RACHEL LOST MARCEL.
OH, NO. HOW?
HE POOPED IN MY SHOE.
WHICH ONE?
THOSE CUTE BLACK ONES I WEAR ALL THE TIME.
NO. WHICH ONE?
THE RIGHT OR LEFT?
BECAUSE THE LEFT ONE IS LUCKY.
COME ON, YOU GUYS, WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
ALL RIGHT. YOU'RE A MONKEY.
YOU'RE LOOSE IN THE CITY.
WHERE DO YOU GO?
OKAY, IT'S HIS FIRST TIME OUT
SO HE'S PROBABLY GOING TO WANT TO DO
SOME OF THE TOURISTY THINGS.
I'LL GO TO CATS.
YOU GO TO THE RUSSIAN TEA ROOM.
OH, MY GOD.
COME ON.
HE'S GOING TO BE HOME ANY MINUTE.
HE'S GOING TO KILL ME.
OKAY, WE'LL START WITH THE BUILDING.
YOU GUYS TAKE THE FIRST AND SECOND FLOOR.
PHOEBE AND I'LL TAKE THIRD AND FOURTH.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA. WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?
OKAY, YOU STAY HERE, JUST WAIT BY THE PHONE
SPRAY LYSOL IN MY SHOE AND WAIT FOR ROSS TO KILL YOU.
DOES ANYBODY WANT TO TRADE?
OH...
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
MR. HECKLES, OUR FRIEND LOST A MONKEY.
HAVE YOU SEEN IT?
I LEFT A BELGIAN WAFFLE OUT HERE.
DID YOU TAKE IT?
NO.
WHY WOULD YOU LEAVE YOUR BELGIAN WAFFLE IN THE HALL?
I WASN'T READY FOR IT.
THE MONKEY. HAVE YOU SEEN A MONKEY?
SAW REGIS PHILBIN ONCE.
OKAY, THANK YOU, MR. HECKLES.
YOU OWE ME A WAFFLE.
OKAY, HE'S A BLACK CAPUCHIN MONKEY
WITH A WHITE FACE...
WITH RUSSIAN DRESSING AND PICKLES ON THE SIDE.
OKAY, THANKS.
HI.
HI. HOW DID IT GO TODAY?
OH, GREAT!
IT WENT GREAT, REALLY GREAT.
HEY, IS THAT WINE?
YEAH, YEAH.
YOU WANT SOME?
OH, I WOULD LOVE SOME.
YEAH?
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT? YOU KNOW WHAT?
LET'S NOT DRINK IT HERE.
I'M FEELING KIND OF CRAZY.
YOU WANT TO GO TO NEWARK?
UH, OKAY.
YEAH, WE COULD DO THAT.
BUT BEFORE WE HEAD OFF
TO THE MURDER CAPITAL OF THE NORTHEAST
I WAS, UH... KIND OF WANTED TO RUN SOMETHING BY YOU.
YOU KNOW HOW WE WERE, YOU KNOW, TALKING BEFORE
ABOUT, UH, RELATIONSHIPS AND STUFF? WELL...
OH, GOD, ROSS, I CANNOT DO THIS.
OKAY, QUICK AND PAINFUL.
OH, GOD.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, OKAY.
ROSS, PLEASE DON'T HATE ME.
OH, WHY?
WHAT? WHAT?
UH... YOU KNOW MARCEL?
YEAH?
WELL, I I KIND OF...
I KIND OF LOST HIM.
I I I... I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
I MEAN, ALL I ASKED YOU TO DO
WAS KEEP HIM IN THE APARTMENT.
I KNOW, I KNOW. I'M SORRY.
NO, YOU KNOW WHAT? I GUESS IT'S PARTIALLY MY FAULT.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE ASKED YOU TO START OFF WITH A MONKEY.
I SHOULD HAVE STARTED YOU OFF WITH LIKE A PEN OR A PENCIL.
ROSS, I'M DOING EVERYTHING THAT I CAN.
I'VE GOT EVERYBODY LOOKING FOR HIM AND I...
OH!
WHO IS IT?
Animal Control.
SEE, I'VE EVEN GOT ANIMAL CONTROL.
YOU CALLED ANIMAL CONTROL?
UH HUH.
W WHY? DO YOU NOT LIKE THEM?
MARCEL IS AN ILLEGAL, EXOTIC ANIMAL.
I'M NOT ALLOWED TO HAVE HIM IN THE CITY.
IF THEY FIND HIM, THEY'LL TAKE HIM AWAY FROM ME.
OH, OKAY. WELL, NOW, SEE.
YOU NEVER, EVER, EVER TOLD US THAT.
THAT'S RIGHT, BECAUSE I DIDN'T EXPECT YOU
WERE GOING TO INVITE THEM TO THE APARTMENT.
HI, THANKS FOR COMING.
SOMEBODY CALLED ABOUT A MONKEY?
OH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
THAT WAS A COMPLETE MISUNDERSTANDING.
WE THOUGHT WE HAD A MONKEY, BUT WE DIDN'T.
TURNED OUT IT WAS A HAT.
CAT! CAT!
WHAT DID I SAY?
HI. WE CHECKED THE THIRD AND FOURTH FLOOR
AND NO ONE'S SEEN MARCEL.
MARCEL?
MY UNCLE MARCEL.
OH, IS THAT WHO THE MONKEY'S NAMED AFTER?
OKAY, ARE YOU AWARE THAT POSSESSION
OF AN ILLEGAL EXOTIC
IS PUNISHABLE BY UP TO TWO YEARS IN PRISON
AND CONFISCATION OF THE ANIMAL.
OH, MY GOD.
YOU'D PUT THAT POOR, LITTLE CREATURE IN JAIL?
PHEEBS, REMEMBER HOW WE TALKED ABOUT
SAYING THINGS QUIETLY TO YOURSELF FIRST?
YES, BUT THERE ISN'T ALWAYS TIME.
LOOK, I'M SURE THERE IS SOME FRIENDLY WAY
TO RECONCILE THIS.
HAVE A SEAT.
FIRST OF ALL, WE HAVEN'T BEEN INTRODUCED.
I'M MONICA GELLER.
OH, MY GOD! YOU ARE!
AND YOU'RE RACHEL GREEN!
YEAH.
LOUISA GIANETTI.
LINCOLN HIGH?
I SAT BEHIND YOU GUYS IN HOMEROOM.
OH! LOUISA!
OH, MY GOD!
MONICA, IT'S LOUISA!
HEY, I WENT THERE, TOO.
OH, LOUISA FROM HOMEROOM!
YES.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHO I AM, DO YOU?
NO. NOT AT ALL.
NONE.
WELL, MAYBE THAT'S BECAUSE
YOU SPENT FOUR YEARS IGNORING ME.
I MEAN, WOULD IT HAVE BEEN
SO HARD TO SAY, "MORNING, LOUISA"
OR "NICE OVERALLS"?
OH, I I'M SO SORRY.
AW, IT'S NOT SO MUCH YOU.
YOU WERE FAT.
YOU HAD YOUR OWN PROBLEMS.
BUT YOU!
WHAT A BITCH!
WHAT?!
YOU KNOW WHAT?
BE THAT AS IT MAY
YOU THINK YOU COULD HELP US OUT
ON THAT MONKEY THING, YOU KNOW, JUST FOR OLD TIME'S SAKE?
GO, BOBCATS!
I COULD... BUT I WON'T.
IF I FIND THAT MONKEY, HE'S MINE.
? DUN DUN DAH! ?
SORRY.
MARCEL?
HI, CAN I HELP YOU?
UH, WE'RE KIND OF HAVING AN EMERGENCY
AND WE WERE LOOKING FOR SOMETHING.
A MONKEY.
YES, HAVE YOU SEEN ANY?
NO. I HAVEN'T SEEN A MONKEY.
DO YOU KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT FIXING RADIATORS?
SURE. DID YOU TRY TURNING THE KNOB
BACK THE OTHER WAY?
OF COURSE.
OH, THEN, NO.
TASTE THIS DAIQUIRI.
IS THERE TOO MUCH RUM IN HERE?
JUST A SECOND.
HOPE YOU FIND YOUR MONKEY.
OH, NO! WAIT! WAIT! WAIT!
UM... WE MAY NOT
KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT RADIATORS PER SE
BUT WE DO HAVE A CERTAIN AMOUNT OF EXPERTISE
IN THE HEATING AND COOLING MILIEU.
UH, AREN'T WE KIND OF IN THE MIDDLE OF SOMETHING HERE?
YES, BUT THESE WOMEN ARE VERY HOT
AND THEY NEED OUR HELP.
AND THEY'RE VERY HOT.
WE CAN'T, ALL RIGHT?
UH, WE'RE SORRY.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA HOW SORRY.
BUT WE PROMISED WE'D FIND THIS MONKEY.
IF YOU SEE HIM, HE'S ABOUT YEA HIGH
AND ANSWERS TO THE NAME "MARCEL."
SO IF WE COULD GET PICTURES OF YOU
YOU'D REALLY BE HELPING US OUT.
OKAY, FROM NOW ON
YOU DON'T GET TO TALK TO OTHER PEOPLE.
MARCEL!
Phoebe and  MARCEL?
MARCEL?
MARCEL! MARCEL?
OH, MY GOD!
WHAT?!
SOMETHING JUST BRUSHED UP
AGAINST MY RIGHT LEG.
WHAT IS IT?
OH, IT'S OKAY.
IT WAS JUST MY LEFT LEG.
LOOK, PHOEBE!
OH, YEAH.
OH, MARCEL.
OH, COME HERE.
STEP ASIDE, LADIES.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
JUST A SMALL TRANQUILIZER.
RUN, MARCEL, RUN!
ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH, I THINK SO.
I JUST... OH.
HUH...
WHOA.
OH...
OH, GOSH.
MARCEL?
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
WE'VE BEEN ALL OVER THE NEIGHBORHOOD.
HE'S GONE. HE'S JUST GONE.
ROSS, YOU DON'T KNOW THAT.
OH, COME ON. IT'S COLD. IT'S DARK.
HE DOESN'T KNOW THE VILLAGE.
OH... AND NOW I HAVE A BROKEN FOOT.
OH, MY...
I HAVE NO MONKEY AND A BROKEN FOOT.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
ROSS, YOU KNOW, I'VE SAID "I'M SORRY" LIKE A MILLION TIMES.
WHAT DO YOU WANT
ME TO DO, HUH?
YOU WANT ME TO BREAK MY FOOT TOO? OKAY.
HERE, I'M GOING TO BREAK MY FOOT RIGHT NOW. OW!
OH! GOD! OH... MY GOD.
THERE, ARE YOU HAPPY NOW?
YEAH, NOW THAT YOU KICKED THE SIGN, HEY...
I DON'T MISS MARCEL ANYMORE.
YOU KNOW, IT IS NOT LIKE I DID THIS ON PURPOSE.
NO, NO.
NO, THIS IS JUST VINTAGE RACHEL.
I MEAN, THINGS JUST SORT OF HAPPEN AROUND YOU.
I MEAN, YOU'RE OFF IN RACHEL- LAND, DOING YOUR RACHEL THING
TOTALLY OBLIVIOUS TO PEOPLE'S MONKEYS
OR TO PEOPLE'S FEELINGS.
ROSS...
I DON'T EVEN WANT TO HEAR IT.
FORGET IT, HUH?
ROSS!
WHAT? WHAT? WHAT?
HEY!
HEY, BANANA MAN! HEY
OH, THIS IS SO INTENSE.
ONE SIDE OF MY BUTT IS TOTALLY ASLEEP
AND THE OTHER SIDE HAS NO IDEA.
WHAT'S WITH PHOEBE?
TRANQUILIZER DART.
OH, SURE.
HI. DID YOU ORDER SOME BANANAS?
WHAT ABOUT IT?
GIVE ME MY MONKEY BACK!
I DON'T HAVE A MONKEY.
THEN WHAT'S WITH ALL THE BANANAS?
POTASSIUM.
MARCEL?
MARCEL? OKAY, WHERE IS HE?
WHERE IS HE?
MARCEL, MARCEL?
YOU'RE WASTING YOUR TIME.
WHAT? WHAT?!
MARCEL?
MARCEL?!
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE TO HIM?
THAT'S MY MONKEY.
THAT'S PATTY.
PATTY THE MONKEY.
ARE YOU INSANE?
COME HERE, MARCEL, COME ON.
COME HERE, PATTY.
COME HERE, MARCEL.
HERE, MONKEY, HERE, MONKEY.
HERE, MONKEY.
GOTCHA!
OKAY, GIVE ME MY MONKEY BACK.
THAT'S MY MONKEY.
YOU'RE BOTH GOING TO HAVE TO TAKE THIS UP WITH THE JUDGE.
THAT'S NOT MY MONKEY.
JUST THE DRESS IS MINE.
YOU CAN SEND IT BACK WHENEVER.
ALL RIGHT, I WANT MY MONKEY.
NO!
OH, COME ON, LOUISA.
SORRY, PROM QUEEN.
YOU HAD TO BE A BITCH IN HIGH SCHOOL.
YOU COULDN'T HAVE BEEN FAT.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK.
OKAY, IN HIGH SCHOOL, I WAS THE PROM QUEEN
AND I WAS THE HOMECOMING QUEEN
AND THE CLASS PRESIDENT
AND YOU...
WERE ALSO THERE.
BUT THIS ISN'T HIGH SCHOOL ANYMORE--
THIS IS REAL LIFE, OKAY?
AND WE ARE ALL ADULTS HERE.
HECKLES. CAN I HAVE THIS?
FOR THE MOST PART.
LOOK, IF YOU TAKE THIS MONKEY
I WILL LOSE ONE OF THE MOST
IMPORTANT PEOPLE IN MY LIFE.
YOU CAN HATE ME IF YOU WANT
BUT PLEASE DO NOT PUNISH HIM.
COME ON, LOUISA, YOU HAVE A CHANCE TO BE THE BIGGER PERSON HERE.
TAKE IT!
NO.
ALL RIGHT.
THEN HOW ABOUT I CALL YOUR SUPERVISOR
AND I TELL HER
THAT YOU SHOT MY FRIEND IN THE ASS WITH A DART?
HEY, IT'LL BE NICE TO GET THIS OFF FINALLY, WON'T IT?
YES, IT...
OR WE CAN LEAVE IT ON FOR NOW, THAT'S FINE.
YOU KNOW, WITH THE RIGHT PAIR OF PUMPS
THAT WOULD BE A GREAT LITTLE OUTFIT.
LISTEN, I'M I'M SORRY I WAS SO HARD ON YOU BEFORE.
YOU KNOW, I JUST...
OH, ROSS, COME ON. NO, NO, IT WAS MY FAULT.
I ALMOST LOST YOUR...
NO, BUT YOU WERE THE ONE WHO GOT HIM BACK, YOU KNOW?
YOU... YOU YOU WERE GREAT.
HEY, WE STILL HAVE THAT... THAT BOTTLE OF WINE.
ARE YOU IN THE MOOD FOR, UH...
SOMETHING GRAPE?
SURE. THAT WOULD BE GOOD.
ALL RIGHT.
OH!
THE, UH, NEIGHBORS MUST BE VACUUMING.
WELL, AS LONG AS WE'RE HERE
AND, UH, NOT ON THE SUBJECT
UM... I WAS THINKING ABOUT, UH...
HOW MAD WE GOT AT EACH OTHER BEFORE.
OH...
AND, UH... I WAS THINKING
MAYBE IT WAS PARTIALLY BECAUSE OF HOW WE, UH...
RACHEL?
BARRY!
I CAN'T.
I CAN'T DO IT.
I CAN'T MARRY MINDY.
I THINK I'M STILL
IN LOVE WITH YOU.
OH! OH!
WE HAVE GOT TO START LOCKING THAT DOOR.
SHOW US!
COME ON!
IT WAS SUCH A LONG TIME AGO.
OKAY, OKAY, FINE. ALL RIGHT.
THIS IS ME IN THE SOUND OF MUSIC.
YOU SEE THE VON TRAPP KIDS?
NO. THAT'S BECAUSE I'M IN FRONT OF THEM.
WHOA, BIG NUN.
YEAH, I THOUGHT THAT WAS AN ALP.
WELL, HIGH SCHOOL WAS NOT MY FAVORITE TIME.
I DON'T KNOW.
I LOVED HIGH SCHOOL, YOU KNOW?
IT WAS JUST, LIKE, FOUR YEARS OF PARTIES AND DATING AND SEX.
WELL, I WENT TO BOARDING SCHOOL WITH 400 BOYS.
AND ANY SEX I HAD WOULD HAVE INVOLVED
A MAJOR LIFESTYLE CHOICE.
GOSH, DOESN'T IT SEEM LIKE A MILLION YEARS AGO?
OOH, OH, OH!
OH! OOH! MY BUTT CHEEK IS WAKING UP! OH!