I'M SORRY. I'M SORRY.
THAT IS IT!
YOU JUST BARGE IN HERE.
YOU DON'T KNOCK.
I'M SORRY.
YOU HAVE NO RESPECT FOR ANYBODY'S PRIVACY!
RACHEL, WAIT. NO! YOU WAIT!
CAN I JUST SAY ONE THING?
WHAT?! WHAT?!
THAT'S A RELATIVELY OPEN WEAVE
AND I CAN STILL SEE YOUR...
NIPPULAR AREA.
OH!
I'M SORRY. I'M SORRY.
I COULD. I COULD.
OH, HONEY, HONEY
TELL THEM THE STORY ABOUT YOUR PATIENT
WHO THINKS THINGS ARE LIKE OTHER THINGS
YOU KNOW?
SO, LIKE WHEN THE PHONE RINGS AND SHE TAKES A SHOWER.
THAT'S PRETTY MUCH IT.
OOPS.
BUT YOU TELL IT REALLY WELL, SWEETIE.
THANKS.
OKAY.
NOW GO AWAY SO WE CAN TALK ABOUT YOU.
OKAY. I'LL MISS YOU.
ISN'T HE GREAT?
HE'S SO CUTE.
AND HE SEEMS TO LIKE YOU SO MUCH.
I KNOW. I KNOW.
HE'S SO SWEET, OH, AND SO COMPLICATED, YOU KNOW.
AND FOR A SHRINK, HE'S NOT TOO SHRINKY.
SO YOU THINK YOU'LL DO IT ON HIS COUCH?
OH, I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK THAT'S A LITTLE WEIRD, YOU KNOW.
IT'S VINYL.
OKAY. YOU GUYS WANT ANYTHING ELSE?
OH, YES, COULD I HAVE..?
NO. I'M SORRY, WE'RE ALL OUT OF THOSE.
ANYBODY ELSE?
DID I, UH, DID I MISS SOMETHING BETWEEN...?
NO. SHE'S STILL UPSET BECAUSE I SAW HER BOOBIES.
WHAT WERE YOU DOING SEEING HER BOOBIES?
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
IT'S NOT LIKE I WAS ACROSS THE STREET
WITH A TELESCOPE AND A BOX OF DOUGHNUTS.
OKAY, OKAY.
COULD WE CHANGE THE SUBJECT, PLEASE?
YEAH. YOU KNOW, THESE ARE NOT HER BOOBIES.
THESE ARE HER BREASTS.
OKAY, PHEEBS.
I WAS HOPING OF MORE OF A CHANGE.
YOU KNOW, I ALWAYS LIKED "BAZOOMBAS."
KIND OF GIVES THEM A LATIN SPIN.
CAN WE, CAN WE DR DROP THIS ALREADY, PLEASE?
YOU KNOW, I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU'RE SO EMBARRASSED.
THEY WERE VERY NICE BOOBIES.
NICE?
THEY WERE NICE?
I MEAN, THAT'S IT.
I MEAN, MITTENS ARE NICE.
OKAY.
ROCK.
HARD PLACE.
ME.
YOU'RE... YOU'RE...
YOU'RE SO FUNNY.
HE'S REALLY FUNNY.
OF COURSE, I WOULDN'T WANT TO BE THERE
WHEN THE LAUGHTER STOPS.
WHOA, WHOA. BACK UP THERE, SPARKY.
WHAT DID YOU MEAN BY THAT?
IT JUST SEEMS AS THOUGH
THAT MAYBE YOU HAVE INTIMACY ISSUES
THAT YOU USE YOUR HUMOR
AS A WAY OF KEEPING
PEOPLE AT A DISTANCE.
HUH.
I MEAN, HEY, I JUST MET YOU.
I DON'T KNOW YOU FROM ADAM.
ONLY CHILD, RIGHT?
PARENTS DIVORCED BEFORE YOU HIT PUBERTY.
UH HUH.
HOW DID YOU KNOW THAT?
IT'S TEXTBOOK.
HEY, YOU GUYS.
YOU ALL KNOW MY DAD.
HEY, HOW LONG YOU IN THE CITY?
JUST FOR A COUPLE OF DAYS. I GOT A JOB MIDTOWN.
I FIGURE I'M BETTER OFF STAYING WITH THE KID
THAN HAULING MY ASS BACK AND FORTH ON A FERRY.
I DON'T KNOW THIS ONE.
OH. THIS IS MY FRIEND ROGER.
HI.
HEY, GOOD TO MEET YOU, ROGER.
YOU, TOO, SIR.
WHAT HAPPENED TO THE PUPPET GUY?
DAD.
OH, OH. EXCUSE ME.
SO, ROSS, HOW'S THE WIFE?
"O" FOR TWO, HUH?
CHANDLER, QUICK, SAY SOMETHING FUNNY.
I GOT TO GO.
MISS YOU, TOO.
I LOVE YOU, BUT IT'S GETTING REAL LATE.
LET ME SAY HI.
HEY, MA, LISTEN.
I MADE THE APPOINTMENT WITH DR. BOZITA AND...
EXCUSE ME.
DID YOU KNOW THIS ISN'T MA?
HER NAME'S RONNI.
SHE'S A PET MORTICIAN.
SURE.
SO HOW LONG YOU BEEN...?
REMEMBER WHEN YOU WERE LITTLE A KID
I USED TO TAKE YOU TO THE NAVY YARD
AND SHOW YOU THE BIG SHIPS?
SINCE THEN?
NO. IT'S ONLY BEEN SIX YEARS.
I JUST WANTED TO PUT A NICE MEMORY IN YOUR HEAD
SO YOU'D KNOW THAT I WASN'T ALWAYS
SUCH A TERRIBLE GUY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
CHOPPING GARLIC.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO CRUSH IT?
HEY, YOU'RE HAVING AN AFFAIR;
I'M CHOPPING THE GARLIC.
IT'S A WACKY WORLD.
JOE, YOU EVER BEEN IN LOVE?
I DON'T KNOW.
THEN YOU HAVEN'T.
YOU'RE BURNING YOUR TOMATOES.
YOU'RE ONE TO TALK.
JOE, YOUR DAD'S IN LOVE BIG TIME
AND THE WORST PART OF IT IS
IT'S WITH TWO DIFFERENT WOMEN.
OH, MAN, PLEASE TELL ME ONE OF THEM IS MA.
OF COURSE.
OF COURSE ONE OF THEM'S MA.
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU?
IT'S LIKE IF YOU WOKE UP ONE DAY
AND FOUND OUT YOUR DAD WAS LEADING THIS DOUBLE LIFE.
HE'S, LIKE, ACTUALLY SOME SPY WORKING FOR THE C.I.A.
THAT WOULD BE COOL.
THIS BLOWS.
DO YOU THINK DAD EVER CHEATED ON MOM?
WELL, NO, I DON'T THINK SO.
BECAUSE THAT WOULD INVOLVE HAVING SEX
AND I WOULD LIKE TO THINK THAT OUR PARENTS
DON'T DO THAT SORT OF THING.
YEAH. I KNOW.
I MEAN, WHY CAN'T PARENTS JUST STAY PARENTS?
WHY DO THEY HAVE TO BECOME PEOPLE?
WHY DO THEY HAVE..?
WHY...
CAN'T YOU STOP STARING AT MY BREASTS?
WHAT?
DID YOU NOT GET
A GOOD ENOUGH LOOK THE OTHER DAY?
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE ALL ADULTS HERE.
THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY TO RESOLVE THIS.
SINCE YOU SAW HER BOOBIES
I THINK YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO SHOW HER YOUR PEE PEE.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T SEE THAT HAPPENING.
COME ON. HE'S RIGHT.
TIT FOR TAT.
WELL, I'M NOT SHOWING YOU MY TAT.
HELLO.
It's Phoebe.
And Rog.
COME ON UP.
OH, GOOD.
ROG IS HERE.
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH ROG?
AH, IT'S NOTHING.
IT'S A LITTLE THING.
I HATE THAT GUY.
ALL RIGHT, SO HE WAS A LITTLE ANALYTICAL.
THAT'S WHAT HE DOES, YOU KNOW?
COME ON, HE'S NOT THAT BAD.
YOU SEE, THAT'S WHERE YOU'RE WRONG.
WHY WOULD I MARRY HER
IF I THOUGHT ON ANY LEVEL THAT SHE WAS A LESBIAN?
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE YOU WANTED YOUR MARRIAGE TO FAIL.
WHY?
WHY WOULD I?
WHY? WHY? WHY? WHY?
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE...
MAYBE LOW SELF ESTEEM.
MAYBE TO COMPENSATE FOR OVERSHADOWING A SIBLING.
WAIT. GO BACK TO THAT SIBLING THING.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S CONCEIVABLE
THAT YOU WANTED TO SABOTAGE YOUR MARRIAGE
SO THAT THE SIBLING WOULD FEEL LIKE
LESS OF A FAILURE IN THE EYES OF THE PARENTS.
THAT'S... THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
I DON'T FEEL GUILTY FOR HER FAILURES.
SO YOU THINK I'M A FAILURE.
ISN'T HE GOOD?
YEAH.
NO, NO, THAT'S NOT WHAT I WAS SAYING.
YOU KNOW, I MEAN, ALL THESE YEARS
I THOUGHT YOU WERE ON MY SIDE
BUT MAYBE WHAT YOU WERE DOING
WAS SUCKING UP TO MOM AND DAD
SO THEY'D KEEP LIKING YOU BETTER.
HEY, I MARRIED A LESBIAN TO MAKE YOU LOOK GOOD!
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I MEAN, YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT WASN'T JUST THE WEEBLES
BUT IT WAS THE WEEBLE PLAY PALACE
AND...
AND THE WEEBLES CRUISE SHIP--
OH, WHICH HAD THIS LITTLE LIFEBOAT
FOR THE WEEBLES TO WOBBLE IN.
AND AND MOM JUST GAVE THEM ALL AWAY.
THAT'S TOUGH, TOUGH STUFF.
COME ON, PHEEPS.
IF WE'RE GOING TO CATCH THAT MOVIE
WE GOT TO GET GOING.
OKAY. FEEL BETTER, RACHEL, OKAY?
PHEEBS, WE'RE GOING TO BE LATE, SWEETIE.
OKAY. LISTEN, THANKS FOR EVERYTHING, MON.
NO PROBLEM.
LISTEN, GUYS, IT WAS GREAT SEEING YOU AGAIN.
YEAH.
MON, EASY ON THOSE COOKIES, OKAY?
REMEMBER, THEY'RE JUST FOOD.
THEY'RE NOT LOVE.
I HATE THAT GUY.
GOOD NIGHT, YOU GUYS.
OH, LOOK.
IT'S THE WOMAN WE ORDERED.
HEY. CAN WE HELP YOU?
AW, NO, THANKS.
I'M JUST WAITING FOR JOEY TRIBBIANI.
I'M JOEY TRIBBIANI.
OH, NO, NOT YOU.
BIG JOEY.
OH, MY GOD.
YOU'RE SO MUCH CUTER THAN YOUR PICTURES.
I'M RONNI.
CHEESE NIP?
UH... JOEY'S HAVING AN EMBOLISM
BUT I'D GO FOR A NIP.
YOU KNOW?
NOW, YOU SEE, MOST PEOPLE, WHEN THEIR PETS PASS ON
THEY WANT THEM SORT OF LAID OUT LIKE THEY'RE SLEEPING.
BUT, OCCASIONALLY, YOU GET YOUR PERSON WHO WANTS THEM IN A POSE
LIKE, AH, CHASING THEIR TAIL...
OR JUMPING TO CATCH A FRISBEE.
JOEY, IF I GO FIRST
I WANT TO BE LOOKING FOR MY KEYS.
THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
HEY, JOE.
DAD, RONNI'S HERE.
HUH?
HI.
HEY.
HELLO, BABE.
WHAT ARE...
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
OH, UH...
WELL, YOU LEFT YOUR GOOD HAIR AT MY APARTMENT.
I FIGURED YOU'D NEED IT TOMORROW FOR YOUR MEETING.
THANK YOU.
SO, WHO'S UP FOR A BIG GAME OF KERPLUNK?
LOOK, I, UH... I SHOULDN'T HAVE COME.
I BETTER GET GOING.
I DON'T WANT TO MISS THE LAST TRAIN.
NO, NO, HON.
I DON'T WANT YOU TAKING THAT THING THIS LATE.
OH, WHERE AM I GOING TO STAY, HERE?
WHOA HO.
WE'LL GO TO A HOTEL.
NO, YOU WON'T.
NO, WE WON'T.
IF YOU GO TO A HOTEL
YOU'LL BE... DOING STUFF.
I WANT YOU RIGHT HERE
WHERE I CAN KEEP AN EYE ON YOU.
YOU'RE GOING TO KEEP AN EYE ON US?
THAT'S RIGHT, MISTER.
AND I DON'T CARE HOW OLD YOU ARE.
AS LONG AS YOU'RE UNDER MY ROOF
YOU'RE GOING TO LIVE BY MY RULES. OKAY?
AND THAT MEANS NO SLEEPING WITH YOUR GIRLFRIEND.
WOW. HE'S STRICT.
NOW, DAD, YOU'LL BE IN MY ROOM.
RONNI, YOU CAN STAY IN CHANDLER'S ROOM.
AND CHANDLER WILL BE...?
OUT HERE WITH ME, BUNKING UP ON THE HIDE A BED.
OOH, "BUNKING UP."
IF YOU SMELL S'MORES, DON'T BE ALARMED.
THANKS. YOU'RE, UH... YOU'RE A GOOD KID.
COME ON.
I'LL SHOW YOU TO MY ROOM.
THAT SOUNDS SO WEIRD WHEN IT'S NOT FOLLOWED BY
"NO, THANKS. IT'S LATE."
OKAY, NOW THIS IS JUST FOR TONIGHT.
STARTING TOMORROW, YOU GOT TO MAKE A CHANGE.
SIX YEARS IS LONG ENOUGH.
WHAT KIND OF CHANGE?
EITHER YOU BREAK IT OFF WITH RONNI...
I CAN'T DO THAT.
THEN YOU GOT TO COME CLEAN WITH MA.
THIS IS NOT RIGHT.
YEAH, BUT THIS...
I DON'T WANT TO HEAR IT.
NOW GO TO MY ROOM.
HEY, KICKY...
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
JUST TRYING TO GET COMFORTABLE.
I CAN'T SLEEP IN MY UNDERWEAR.
WELL, YOU'RE GONNA.
I'VE BEEN THINKING.
YOU KNOW, ABOUT HOW I'M ALWAYS SEEING
GIRLS ON TOP OF GIRLS.
ARE THEY END TO END OR TALL LIKE PANCAKES?
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
ABOUT HOW I'M ALWAYS GOING OUT WITH ALL THESE WOMEN.
BECAUSE I ALWAYS FIGURED
WHEN THE RIGHT ONE COMES ALONG
I'D BE ABLE TO BE STAND UP GUY
AND GO THE DISTANCE, YOU KNOW?
NOW I'M LOOKING AT MY DAD, THINKING...
HEY, YOU'RE NOT HIM; YOU'RE YOU.
WHEN THEY WERE ALL OVER YOU
TO GO INTO YOUR FATHER'S PIPE- FITTING BUSINESS, DID YOU CAVE?
NO.
NO. YOU DECIDED
TO GO INTO THE OUT OF WORK ACTOR BUSINESS
AND THAT WASN'T EASY, BUT YOU DID IT
AND I'D LIKE TO BELIEVE THAT WHEN
THE RIGHT WOMAN COMES ALONG, YOU WILL HAVE THE COURAGE
AND THE GUTS TO SAY, "NO, THANKS. I'M MARRIED."
YOU REALLY THINK SO?
YEAH, I REALLY DO.
THANKS, CHANDLER.
GET OFF.
HI. HI.
MAY I HELP YOU?
YEAH. JOEY SAID I COULD USE YOUR SHOWER
SINCE CHANDLER'S IN OURS.
OKAY... WHO ARE YOU?
OH! I'M RONNI.
RONNI RAPPELANO.
THE MISTRESS.
UM, COME ON IN.
OH, THANKS.
I'M RACHEL. HI.
BATHROOM'S UP THERE. HEY, LISTEN, RONNI.
HOW LONG WOULD YOU SAY CHANDLER'S BEEN IN THE SHOWER?
OH, LIKE, UH, FIVE MINUTES.
PERFECT.
FASTEN YOUR SEAT BELTS.
IT'S PEE PEE TIME.
HEY, MR. TRIB.
HEY. GOOD MORNING, DEAR.
CHANDLER BING, IT'S TIME TO SEE YOUR THING.
WHAT'S THE MATTER
WITH YOU?!
I THOUGHT IT WAS CHANDLER!
WHAT? WHAT?
YOU WERE SUPPOSED TO BE IN THERE
SO I COULD SEE YOUR THING!
SORRY. MY THING WAS IN THERE WITH ME.
HEY, PHEEBS. HEY, PHEEBS.
HOW'S IT GOING?
GOOD. OH, OH, ROGER'S HAVING A DINNER THING
AND HE WANTED ME TO INVITE YOU GUYS.
SO WHAT'S GOING ON?
NOTHING. IT'S, UM...
IT'S JUST, UH...
IT'S ROGER.
UM...
I DON'T KNOW, THERE'S SOMETHING ABOUT...
BASICALLY, WE JUST FEEL THAT HE'S, UH...
WE HATE THAT GUY.
WE HATE HIM.
WE'RE SORRY, PHEEBS.
UH HUH, OKAY.
DON'T YOU THINK MAYBE, THOUGH, THAT IT'S JUST
THAT HE'S SO PERCEPTIVE THAT IT FREAKED YOU OUT?
NO, WE HATE HIM.
I'M SORRY.
MA! WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I CAME TO GIVE YOU THIS
AND THIS!
OW! BIG RING.
WHY DID YOU HAVE TO FILL YOUR FATHER'S HEAD
WITH ALL THAT GARBAGE ABOUT MAKING THINGS RIGHT?
THINGS WERE FINE
THE WAY THEY WERE.
THERE'S CHICKEN IN THERE.
PUT IT AWAY.
FOR GOD'S SAKE, JOEY.
REALLY!
HOLD ON.
YOU KNEW?
OF COURSE I KNEW!
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
YOUR FATHER IS NO JAMES BOND.
YOU SHOULD HAVE HEARD SOME OF HIS COVER STORIES.
"I'M SLEEPING OVER AT MY ACCOUNTANT'S."
I MEAN, WHAT IS THAT?
PLEASE!
SO, THEN, HOW COULD YOU...?
DO YOU REMEMBER HOW YOUR FATHER USED TO BE?
ALWAYS YELLING. ALWAYS YELLING.
NOTHING MADE HIM HAPPY.
NOTHING MADE HIM HAPPY, NOTHING.
NOT THAT WOOD SHOP
NOT THOSE STUPID LITTLE SHIPS IN THE BOTTLE--
NOTHING. NOW HE'S HAPPY.
I MEAN, IT'S NICE. HE HAS A HOBBY.
MA, I DON'T MEAN TO BE DISRESPECTFUL, BUT...
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
ME? I'M FINE.
LOOK, HONEY...
IN AN IDEAL WORLD, THERE'D BE NO HER
AND YOUR FATHER WOULD LOOK LIKE STING.
AND I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING ELSE--
EVER SINCE THAT POODLE STUFFER CAME ALONG
HE'S BEEN SO ASHAMED OF HIMSELF
THAT HE'S BEEN MORE ATTENTIVE.
HE'S BEEN MORE LOVING.
IT'S LIKE EVERY DAY'S OUR ANNIVERSARY.
I'M... HAPPY FOR YOU?
WELL, DON'T BE.
BECAUSE NOW EVERYTHING'S SCREWED UP.
I JUST WANT IT THE WAY IT WAS.
MA, I'M SORRY.
I... I JUST DID WHAT I THOUGHT YOU'D WANT.
I KNOW YOU DID, COOKIE.
OH, I KNOW YOU DID.
SO TELL ME...
DID YOU SEE HER?
YEAH.
HMM.
YOU'RE TEN TIMES PRETTIER THAN SHE IS.
THAT'S SWEET.
COULD I TAKE HER?
HUH... WITH THIS RING?
NO CONTEST.
OH! OH! NO! DON'T EVER DO THAT, EVER!
WHY? OH, I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY, I JUST... I HAVE A THING.
I HAVE A THING, WHICH MEANS YOU CAN'T EVER DO THAT.
WHY? WHAT'S WRONG, SWEETIE?
NOTHING. NOTHING.
NO, NO, NO. WHAT'S WRONG? COME ON.
OH, OKAY.
IT'S... I MEAN, IT'S NOTHING. I'M FINE.
IT'S JUST, UM... IT'S MY FRIENDS.
THEY HAVE A LIKING PROBLEM WITH YOU
IN THAT, UM, THEY DON'T.
OH. THEY DON'T?
BUT, YOU KNOW, THEY DON'T SEE
ALL THE WONDERFULNESS THAT I SEE.
YOU KNOW, THEY DON'T SEE ALL THE GOOD STUFF
AND ALL THE SWEET STUFF.
THEY JUST, YOU KNOW, THEY THINK YOU'RE A LITTLE...
WHAT?
INTENSE AND CREEPY.
OH.
BUT I DON'T.
ME, PHOEBE.
WELL, I'M NOT AT ALL SURPRISED
THEY FEEL THAT WAY.
YOU'RE NOT? SEE, THAT'S WHY YOU'RE SO GREAT.
ACTUALLY, IT'S QUITE TYPICAL BEHAVIOR WHEN YOU HAVE
THIS KIND OF DYSFUNCTIONAL GROUP DYNAMIC.
YOU KNOW, THIS KIND OF CO- DEPENDENT, EMOTIONALLY STUNTED
SITTING IN YOUR STUPID COFFEE HOUSE
WITH YOUR STUPID BIG CUPS
WHICH, I'M SORRY, MIGHT AS WELL HAVE NIPPLES ON THEM
AND YOU'RE ALL, LIKE
"OH, DEFINE ME!
"DEFINE ME!
LOVE ME! I NEED LOVE!"
SO YOU TALKED TO YOUR DAD, HUH?
YEAH, HE'S GOING TO KEEP CHEATING ON MY MA
LIKE SHE WANTED
MY MA'S GOING TO KEEP PRETENDING SHE DOESN'T KNOW
EVEN THOUGH SHE DOES
AND MY LITTLE SISTER, TINA, CAN'T SEE HER HUSBAND ANYMORE
BECAUSE HE GOT A RESTRAINING ORDER.
WHICH HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH ANYTHING
EXCEPT THAT I FOUND OUT TODAY.
THINGS SURE HAVE CHANGED
HERE ON WALTON'S MOUNTAIN.
SO, JOE, ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH, I GUESS.
IT'S JUST... YOU KNOW, THEY'RE PARENTS.
AFTER A CERTAIN POINT, YOU GOT TO LET GO.
EVEN IF YOU KNOW BETTER
YOU GOT TO LET THEM MAKE THEIR OWN MISTAKES.
AND JUST THINK, IN A COUPLE OF YEARS
WE GET TO TURN INTO THEM.
OH, PLEASE DON'T SAY THAT.
IF I TURN INTO MY PARENTS, I'LL EITHER BE
AN ALCOHOLIC BLONDE CHASING AFTER 20 YEAR OLD BOYS OR...
I'LL END UP LIKE MY MOM.
HEY.
HEY, PHEEBS.
HOW'S IT GOING?
OH, OKAY, EXCEPT I BROKE UP WITH ROGER.
OH.
YEAH, RIGHT.
NO, NO, NO. REALLY.
WHAT HAPPENED?
I DON'T KNOW.
I MEAN, HE'S A GOOD PERSON, AND HE CAN BE REALLY SWEET
AND IN SOME WAYS, I THINK HE IS SO RIGHT FOR ME.
IT'S JUST... I HATE THAT GUY.
HI, JOEY.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
CLEAR THE TRACKS
FOR THE BOOBIE PAYBACK EXPRESS.
NEXT STOP: RACHEL GREEN.
JOEY, WHAT THE HELL WERE YOU DOING?!
SORRY. WRONG BOOBIES.
HELLO, JOEY.
HUH? HELLO, DEAR.