PLEASE TELL HIM.
SHUT UP.
TELL ME WHAT?
LOOK AT YOU-- YOU WON'T EVEN LOOK AT HIM.
OH, COME ON, TELL ME.
I COULD USE ANOTHER REASON WHY WOMEN WON'T LOOK AT ME.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
LAST NIGHT, I HAD A DREAM THAT, UM, YOU AND I WERE, UH...
DOING IT ON THIS TABLE.
WOW!
EXCELLENT DREAM SCORE.
WHY, WHY... WHY WOULD YOU DREAM THAT?
MORE IMPORTANTLY:
WAS I ANY GOOD?
WELL, YOU WERE PRETTY DAMN "ANY GOOD."
INTERESTING, BECAUSE IN MY DREAMS
I'M SURPRISINGLY INADEQUATE.
WELL, LAST NIGHT, YOU SEEMED TO KNOW YOUR WAY
AROUND THE TABLE.
I LOVE IT WHEN WE SHARE.
YOU OKAY THERE?
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU TWO HAD SEX IN HER DREAM.
WELL, I'M SORRY.
IT WAS A ONE TIME THING.
I WAS VERY DRUNK
AND IT WAS SOMEONE ELSE'S SUBCONSCIOUS.
HELLO, RACHEL.
GET OFF.
OOH! GIVE ME.
CAN YOU SEE ME
OPERATING A DRILL PRESS?
I DON'T KNOW. WHAT ARE YOU WEARING?
PHEEBS, WHY WOULD YOU WANT TO OPERATE A DRILL PRESS?
JUST FOR SOME SHORT TERM WORK.
YOU KNOW, TILL I GET BACK SOME OF MY MASSAGE CLIENTS.
PIRATES AGAIN?
NO. NOTHING LIKE THAT.
I'M JUST... SUCH A DUMMY.
I TAUGHT THIS "MASSAGE YOURSELF AT HOME" WORKSHOP.
AND THEY ARE.
HEY, HEY, CHAN--
SHE COULD WORK FOR YOU.
THANKS, JOEY. THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
I COULD. I COULD DO IT!
WHAT IS IT?
MY SECRETARY WILL BE OUT FOR A COUPLE WEEKS.
SHE'S HAVING ONE
OF HER BOOBS REDUCED.
IT'S A WHOLE BIG BOOB STORY.
WELL, I COULD BE A SECRETARY.
WELL, YOU KNOW, PHEEBS, I DON'T KNOW IF IT'S YOUR KIND OF THING
BECAUSE IT INVOLVES A LOT OF BEING NORMAL...
FOR A LARGE PORTION OF THE DAY.
I COULD DO THAT.
WHAT ARE YOU PLAYING WITH?
OH, IT'S MY NEW BEEPER.
WHAT THE HELL DOES A PALEONTOLOGIST
NEED A BEEPER FOR?
IS IT LIKE FOR DINOSAUR EMERGENCIES?
"HELP! COME QUICK! THEY'RE STILL EXTINCT!"
NO. IT'S FOR WHEN CAROL GOES INTO LABOR.
SHE CAN GET ME WHEREVER I AM.
ALL SHE HAS TO DO IS DIAL 55 JIMBO.
A COOL PHONE NUMBER
AND A POSSIBLE NAME FOR THE KID.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL SEE YOU GUYS LATER.
OFF TO SEE YOUNG ETHAN?
THANK YOU.
HOW YOUNG IS YOUNG ETHAN? YOUNG?
HE'S... OUR AGE.
WHEN WE WERE...?
OKAY. HE'S A SENIOR IN COLLEGE.
COLLEGE?
WHOA.
OOH, ROB THAT CRADLE.
YEAH, WELL, HE'S SMART AND AND MATURE AND GROWN UP.
MATURE AND GROWN UP.
HE'S A BIG BOY.
AND THIS MAN CHILD HAS NO PROBLEM
WITH HOW OLD YOU ARE?
NO. OF COURSE NOT.
IT'S NOT EVEN AN ISSUE.
BECAUSE I TOLD HIM I WAS 22.
WHAT?
OH, I CAN'T PASS FOR 22?
WELL, MAYBE 25, 26.
I AM 26.
THERE YOU GO.
CAN YOU HEAR THAT?
YEAH.
YOU SEE, THAT'LL STOP
WHEN YOU PICK UP THE PHONE.
OH!
OOH! I'M ON.
OKAY.
MR. BING'S OFFICE.
NO, I'M SORRY.
HE'S IN A MEETING RIGHT NOW.
I'M NOT IN A MEETING.
WILL HE KNOW WHAT THIS IS IN REFERENCE TO?
AND HE HAS YOUR NUMBER?
I'LL SEE THAT HE GETS THE MESSAGE.
BYE BYE.
WHA...
ROSS SAYS HI.
AH.
THIS IS SO FUN.
WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
WELL, NOW, I ACTUALLY HAVE TO GET TO WORK.
"MOST LIKELY."
OKAY. I'M GOING TO BE OUT THERE.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
BYE BYE.
YES?
What you doin'?
OKAY, WINDOWS ARE CLEAN.
CANDLES ARE LIT.
OOH, BELT'S TOO TIGHT.
GOT TO CHANGE IT.
DID I TURN THE FISH?
NOPE. BECAUSE I MADE LASAGNA.
AM I OUT OF CONTROL?
JUST A TOUCH.
MON, I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I MEAN, YOU'VE BEEN DATING THIS GUY
SINCE LIKE, WHAT, HIS MIDTERMS.
I MEAN, WHY ALL OF A SUDDEN
ARE YOU SO...
OHHH.
WHAT?
COULD TONIGHT BE THE NIGHT?
I DON'T KNOW.
LOOK, HE'S A GREAT GUY AND I LOVE BEING WITH HIM
BUT, YOU KNOW, THINGS HAPPEN WHEN THEY HAPPEN.
YOU DON'T PLAN THESE THINGS.
OH. SO DID YOU SHAVE YOUR LEGS?
YEAH.
UH HUH.
WOULD YOU LET IT GO, ROSS?
IT WAS JUST A DREAM.
IT DOESN'T MEAN...
OOH HOO!
OOH, THIS IS IT!
OH, MY GOD! IT'S BABY TIME, BABY TIME!
RELAX, JUST RELAX. BE COOL. BE COOL.
YEAH, HI. I WAS JUST BEEPED.
NO. ANDRE IS NOT HERE.
THIRD TIME TODAY.
YES, I AM SURE.
NO, SIR, I DO NOT PERFORM THOSE KIND OF SERVICES.
SERVICES?
OOH. SERVICES.
YEAH, YOU WANT 55 JUMBO.
YEP.
THAT'S RIGHT.
THAT'S RIGHT. JUMBO WITH A "U," SIR.
NO. BELIEVE ME, YOU DON'T WANT ME.
JUDGING BY HIS NUMBER
I'D BE A HUGE DISAPPOINTMENT.
ALL RIGHTY. BYE BYE.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
HEY, HEY!
HOW WAS THE FIRST DAY?
OH. EXCELLENT.
EVERYONE WAS SO, SO NICE.
SEE? IT PAYS TO KNOW THE MAN WHO WEARS MY SHOES.
ME.
OH.
NO, I DIDN'T TELL
ANYBODY THAT I KNEW YOU.
WHY NOT?
WELL, BECAUSE, YOU KNOW...
THEY DON'T LIKE YOU.
WHAT?
I THOUGHT YOU KNEW THAT.
NUH UH.
WHO DOESN'T LIKE ME?
EVERYONE.
EXCEPT FOR, UM...
NO. EVERYONE.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
DON'T FEEL BAD.
YOU KNOW, THEY USED TO LIKE YOU A LOT.
BUT THEN YOU GOT PROMOTED, AND, YOU KNOW
NOW YOU'RE ALL, LIKE, MR. BOSS MAN.
YOU KNOW, MR. BING. MR. BING-- BOSS MAN BING.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
YEAH, YEAH. THEY EVEN DO YOU.
THEY DO ME?
YOU KNOW, LIKE, UM... OKAY.
"COULD THAT REPORT BE ANY LATER?"
I DON'T SOUND LIKE THAT.
OH, OH, CHANDLER... YEAH, YOU DO.
"THE HILLS ARE ALIVE WITH THE SOUND...
OF MUSIC."
MY SCONE!
OKAY, I DON'T SOUND LIKE THAT.
THAT IS SO NOT TRUE.
THAT IS SO NOT...
THAT IS SO NO...
THAT...
OH, SHUT UP!
YOU DID NOT.
I AM TELLING YOU, UP UNTIL I WAS, LIKE, NINE
I THOUGHT THAT GUNPOINT WAS AN ACTUAL PLACE WHERE CRIMES HAPPENED.
HOW IS THAT POSSIBLE?
WELL, THINK ABOUT IT.
IT'S ALWAYS ON THE NEWS:
"A MAN IS BEING HELD UP AT GUNPOINT."
"TOURISTS ARE BEING TERRORIZED AT GUNPOINT."
AND I JUST KEPT THINKING
"WHY DO PEOPLE CONTINUE TO GO THERE?"
OH, AH... I SHOULD GO.
OKAY.
UNLESS...
WHAT?
UH, UH, UNLESS YOU WANT TO STAY OVER.
I MEAN, I'M GOING TO, SO...
YEAH. I'D REALLY LIKE THAT.
UH...
BEFORE WE GET INTO ANY STAYING OVER STUFF
THERE'S SOMETHING YOU SHOULD KNOW.
OKAY.
IS THIS LIKE
"I HAVE AN EARLY CLASS TOMORROW
OR, "I'M SECRETLY MARRIED TO A GOAT"?
WELL, IT'S SOMEWHERE IN BETWEEN.
YOU SEE, IN A STRICTLY TECHNICAL SENSE, OF COURSE
I'M NOT, UH...
WELL, I MEAN, I HAVEN'T EVER, UM...
ETHAN? YEAH?
ARE YOU A VIRGIN?
WELL... IF THAT'S WHAT YOU KIDS
ARE CALLING IT THESE DAYS
THEN, YES, I AM.
WOW!
I MEAN...
WELL, YOU'RE JUST SUCH A GOOD KISSER
I WOULD NEVER HAVE KNOWN.
OH, WELL, I'VE EXCELLED AT EVERY LEVEL I'VE BEEN TO
I JUST...
I JUST HAVEN'T BEEN TO THAT PARTICULAR ONE... YET.
I, UH, I'VE KIND OF BEEN WAITING
FOR THE RIGHT PERSON.
REALLY?
YEAH.
YOU DO KNOW
I WAS TALKING ABOUT YOU, RIGHT?
WOW!
YOU KEEP SAYING THAT.
YOU KNOW, YOU READ ABOUT IT.
YOU SEE IT IN THE MOVIES
EVEN WHEN YOU PRACTICE IT AT HOME
MAN, OH, MAN...
IT IS NOTHING LIKE THAT.
OH!
LISTEN.
UM, YOU TOLD ME SOMETHING
THAT WAS REALLY DIFFICULT FOR YOU
AND I FIGURE IF YOU CAN BE HONEST
THEN I CAN, TOO.
OH, GOD! DON'T TELL ME I DID IT WRONG.
NO, NO, NO.
NOTHING WRONG ABOUT THAT.
OH.
UM, OKAY. HERE GOES.
I'M NOT 22.
I'M, I'M 25...
AND 13 MONTHS.
HUH.
BUT I FIGURE, YOU KNOW
THAT SHOULDN'T CHANGE ANYTHING.
I MEAN, WHAT THE HELL DOES IT MATTER HOW OLD WE ARE?
I MEAN, BASICALLY, I AM NUTS ABOUT YOU.
YOU KNOW, I KNEW IT THE FIRST TIME THAT WE KISSED
AND I HAD THAT TIC TAC UNDER MY TONGUE
AND YOU DIDN'T EVEN MENTION IT.
I JUST THOUGHT YOU WERE NATURALLY MINTY.
UH, LISTEN, UM...
AS LONG AS WE'RE TELLING STUFF, UH...
I HAVE ANOTHER ONE FOR YOU.
I'M A LITTLE
YOUNGER THAN I SAID.
YOU'RE NOT A SENIOR?
OH, I'M A SENIOR...
IN HIGH SCHOOL.
O KAY.
WHAT WE DID WAS WRONG.
OH, GOD. I JUST HAD SEX
WITH SOMEONE WHO WASN'T ALIVE
DURING THE BICENTENNIAL.
I JUST HAD SEX.
ETHAN, FOCUS.
HOW COULD YOU NOT TELL ME?
YOU NEVER
TOLD ME HOW OLD YOU WERE.
WELL, THAT'S DIFFERENT.
MY LIE DIDN'T MAKE ONE OF US A FELON IN 48 STATES.
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING?
I WASN'T THINKING. I WAS TOO BUSY FALLING...
DON'T SAY IT.
IN LOVE WITH YOU.
REALLY?
SORRY.
WELL, FALL OUT OF IT.
YOU KNOW, YOU SHOULDN'T EVEN BE HERE.
IT'S A SCHOOL NIGHT.
OH, GOD. OH, GOD.
I'M LIKE THOSE WOMEN THAT YOU SEE
WITH SHINY GUYS NAMED CHAD.
I'M JOAN COLLINS.
WHO?
OKAY, ANDRE SHOULD BE THERE IN ABOUT 45 MINUTES.
UH, YES, SIR, THE KIMONOS ARE EXTRA.
ALL RIGHTY. BYE BYE.
UH... IT'S JUST EASIER THAT WAY.
OH, COME ON.
YOU TOLD ME ABOUT THE LAST DREAM.
NO! FORGET IT.
WELL, WHY NOT? WAS I DOING SOMETHING PARTICULARLY...
SAUCY?
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
UM...
WELL, YOU WERE NOT THE ONLY ONE THERE.
JOEY WAS THERE TOO.
ALL RIGHT.
WAS THERE, UH...?
ANYBODY... ANYBODY ELSE THERE?
NO.
YOU SURE?
NOBODY HANDING OUT MINTS OR ANYTHING?
NO. IT WAS JUST THE THREE OF US.
OH.
SO, TELL ME, WAS IT LIKE YOU AND CHANDLER
AND THEN YOU AND ME
OR YOU AND ME AND CHANDLER?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
WHAT?
THERE WERE TIMES...
WHEN IT WASN'T EVEN ME.
OOH... OOH...
THAT IS SO SWEET, YOU GUYS.
HEY, MON.
HEY.
MON, ETHAN CALLED AGAIN.
MON?
MON!
WHAT?
ETHAN CALLED AGAIN.
OH.
WHAT, YOU'RE NOT SEEING HIM ANYMORE?
NO.
YOU KNOW, SOMETIMES JUST THINGS DON'T WORK OUT.
AND THIS HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH THE FACT
THAT HE NEEDS A NOTE
TO GET OUT OF GYM?
I DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING.
I DID NOT SAY ANYTHING.
I SWEAR.
HE STOPPED BY.
UH, LISTEN, NEXT TIME YOU TALK TO HIM
COULD YOU ASK HIM WHICH ONE THE STRONGEST POWER RANGER IS.
OH, YEAH.
OH, MY LIFE IS JUST SO AMUSING.
CAN WE DROP IT NOW?
SURE.
SORRY.
IT'S MORPHIN TIME!
STEGOSAURUS!
TYRANNOSAURUS!
OOH, OH, I GOT TO GO.
WHOA. OOH, HEAD RUSH.
OH.
ONE MORE AND THEN I HAVE TO GO.
COOL.
WHERE YOU GOING?
UM... OH, I GOT A BIRTHDAY PARTY WITH SOME WORK PEOPLE.
WORK PEOPLE?
NOBODY TOLD ME.
NO, I KNOW.
THAT'S PART OF THE WHOLE, YOU KNOW
THEM NOT LIKING YOU EXTRAVAGANZA.
YOU KNOW WHAT, I DON'T GET THIS.
A MONTH AGO THESE PEOPLE WERE MY FRIENDS, YOU KNOW?
JUST BECAUSE I'M IN CHARGE
DOESN'T MEAN I'M A DIFFERENT PERSON.
WELL, THEN YOU SHOULD COME TONIGHT, YOU KNOW, JUST HANG OUT WITH THEM
LET THEM SEE WHAT A GREAT GUY YOU STILL ARE.
YOU THINK I SHOULD?
I REALLY DO. YEAH.
OKAY.
OH, BUT, UM, COULD WE NOT GO TOGETHER?
I DON'T WANT TO BE THE GEEK WHO INVITED THE BOSS, YOU KNOW?
HEY, YOU OKAY?
YEAH.
YOU KNOW, THIS, UM...
THIS CAN'T BE EASY FOR HIM EITHER.
I KNOW.
I MEAN, THIS MAY TAKE SOME TIME
FOR HIM TO GET OVER IT, YOU KNOW
BUT THEN AT 4:00 MUPPET BABIES IS ON.
WALT, GO DEEP, DEEP, DEEP!
SORRY, SHELLY.
SEE, WITH THE FUN?
AND I THINK LAST NIGHT WAS GREAT
YOU KNOW, THE KARAOKE THING
TRACY AND I DOING "EBONY AND IVORY."
YOU WERE GREAT, BUT THEY STILL MADE FUN OF YOU.
WHAT?
YOU KNOW, NOW YOU'RE MORE LIKE MR. CARING BOSS--
MR. I'M ONE OF YOU BOSS
MR. I WANT TO BE YOUR BUDDY BOSS MAN BING.
THEN I DON'T GET IT.
WELL... YOU KNOW WHAT, CHANDLER
I THINK YOU JUST GOT TO FACE IT.
YOU'RE LIKE THE GUY IN THE BIG OFFICE, YOU KNOW?
YOU'RE THE ONE THAT HIRES THEM AND FIRES THEM.
THEY STILL SAY YOU'RE A GREAT BOSS.
THEY DO?
UH HUH, BUT THEY'RE NOT
YOUR FRIENDS ANYMORE.
BUT I JUST WANT TO...
BUT YOU CAN'T.
BUT I JUST WANT...
NUH UH.
AREN'T YOU GOING TO..?
OH, CAROL AND I HAVE A NEW SYSTEM.
IF SHE PUNCHES IN 911 IT MEANS SHE'S HAVING A BABY.
OTHERWISE, I JUST IGNORE IT.
WHAT ABOUT ANDRE?
WELL, THIS MORNING HE GOT A CALL
FROM WHAT I THINK WAS OUR COUSIN NATHAN
AND FRANKLY, IT WAS A LITTLE MORE
THAN I NEEDED TO KNOW.
HEY.
THAT WAS GOING TO BE MY OPENER.
HEY... DID YOU GUYS CHECK OUT
THOSE NEW HAND DRYERS IN THE BATHROOM?
I THOUGHT THAT WAS JUST A RUMOR.
TRUE STORY.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, I GOT TO TELL YOU SOMETHING.
I'M NOT 17. I ONLY SAID THAT
SO YOU'D THINK I WAS CUTE AND VULNERABLE.
I'M ACTUALLY 30.
I HAVE A WIFE, I HAVE A JOB.
I'M YOUR CONGRESSMAN.
MONICA, THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
WE ARE GREAT TOGETHER.
WE CAN TALK, WE MAKE EACH OTHER LAUGH
AND THE SEX...
OKAY. I HAVE NO FRAME OF REFERENCE
BUT I THOUGHT THAT WAS GREAT.
IT WAS.
THEN WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
ETHAN IT'S, UM...
IT'S ICKY.
ICKY?
YOU'RE ACTUALLY GOING TO THROW THIS AWAY
BECAUSE IT'S ICKY?
LOOK, THIS ISN'T EASY FOR ME EITHER.
I WISH THINGS WERE DIFFERENT.
IF YOU WERE A FEW YEARS OLDER
OR I WAS A FEW YEARS YOUNGER OR...
WE LIVED IN BIBLICAL TIMES...
I COULD REALLY...
NO, DON'T SAY IT.
LOVE YOU.
ARE YOUR HANDS STILL WET?
MOIST.
LET'S DRY THEM AGAIN.
I'M LIKE, "COULD THESE MARGARITASBEANY STRONGER?"
HEY, CHANDLER.
HELLO, MR. BING.
LOVED YOUR STEVIE WONDER LAST NIGHT.
THANKS. LISTEN, ABOUT THE WEEKLY NUMBERS
I'M GOING TO NEED THEM ON MY DESK BY 9 AM.
SURE.
NO PROBLEM.
YOU HAVE TO GIVE THEM SOMETHING, YOU KNOW.
THAT WAS GERSTON, SANTOS...
AND WHO'S THE GUY WITH THE MOUSTACHE?
PEETRIE.
PEETRIE, RIGHT, RIGHT.
OKAY, WELL, SOME PEOPLE ARE GOING TO BE WORKING...
THIS WEEKEND.
OH, THAT'S NICE.
OHH...
OH.
OH, ROSS!
ROSS?
I'M HERE.
YOU ARE?
UM...
WE WERE, UM...
WE WERE... JUST...
WOW.
WHAT?
GREAT. NOW I'M HAVING A BABY.
WHAT?!
WHOA!
I'M HAVING A BABY!
OH, MY GOD!
THE PHONE, THE PHONE!
I DON'T HAVE THE PHONE.
ROSS?
I'M HURT.
MONICA, LET'S GO!
COME ON, NOW, PEOPLE! WOMAN IN LABOR.
HEY, ROSS, LOOK WHAT I GOT GOING HERE.
YEAH, SAVE IT FOR THE CAB, OKAY?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING? WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WE'RE GOING TO A HOSPITAL.
WHAT, SO I CAN'T LOOK NICE?
THERE MIGHT BE DOCTORS THERE.
JOEY, GET OUT OF THE FRIDGE.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
WHAT IS THAT?
FOR THE RIDE.
YEAH, LIKE IN A CAB...
SAVE IT!
OKAY. HATING THIS.
MONICA, COME ON, NOW! LET'S GO!
BABY COMING.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
I'M GOING TO BE AN AUNT.
I'M GOING TO HAVE A NEPHEW.
OH, THAT'S NICE.
GET OUT.
LET'S GO. COME ON.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT. I'M GOING.
HERE WE GO.
ROSSY...
COME ON.
COME ON, ROSSY.
ROSSY, COME ON.