ALL RIGHT, PHOEBE.
OKAY. IF I WERE OMNIPOTENT FOR A DAY
I WOULD WANT, UM, WORLD PEACE
NO MORE HUNGER
GOOD THINGS FOR THE RAIN FOREST.
AND BIGGER BOOBS.
WELL, SEE. YOU TOOK MINE.
CHANDLER
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
IF I WERE OMNIPOTENT FOR A DAY
I'D MAKE MYSELF OMNIPOTENT FOREVER.
SEE, THERE'S ALWAYS ONE GUY.
"IF I HAD A WISH
"I'D WISH FOR THREE MORE WISHES."
HEY, JOEY
WHAT WOULD YOU DO IF YOU WERE
OMNIPOTENT?
PROBABLY KILL MYSELF.
EXCUSE ME?
HEY, IF LITTLE JOEY'S DEAD
THEN I GOT NO REASON TO LIVE.
JOEY, UH...
OM NIPOTENT.
YOU ARE?
ROSS, I'M S...
I HAD NO IDEA.
I THOUGHT IT WAS, LIKE, A THEORETICAL QUESTION.
[ TELEVISION]
?  ?
? AND IT HASN'T BEEN YOUR DAY ?
? WHEN THE RAIN STARTS TO FALL ?
?  ?
? BECAUSE YOU'RE THERE FOR ME TOO. ?
HOW DOES SHE DO THAT?
I CANNOT SLEEP IN A PUBLIC PLACE.
LIBRARIES, AIRPLANES, MOVIE THEATERS...
WHEN YOU WERE LITTLE, YOU SLEPT THROUGH
THE GRAND CANYON. HELLO. MOM AND DAD
NEVER TOOK US TO THE GRAND CANYON.
MOM AND DAD TOOK US TO THE GRAND CANYON?
WOULD YOU LOOK AT HER?
SHE'S SO PEACEFUL.
WHAT? WHAT?
HI.
IT'S OKAY, YOU KNOW.
YOU JUST NODDED OFF AGAIN.
WHAT'S GOING ON WITH YOU?
I GOT NO SLEEP LAST NIGHT.
WHY?
MY GRANDMOTHER HAS THIS NEW BOYFRIEND
AND THEY'RE BOTH KIND OF INSECURE IN BED.
AND DEAF.
THEY'RE CONSTANTLY, LIKE, HAVING TO REASSURE EACH OTHER
THAT THEY'RE HAVING A GOOD TIME.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA HOW LOUD THEY ARE.
WELL, IF YOU WANT, YOU CAN STAY
WITH RACHEL AND ME TONIGHT.
THANKS.
...95, 96, 97.
SEE, I TOLD YOU.
LESS THAN 100 STEPS FROM OUR PLACE TO HERE.
YOU GOT WAY TOO MUCH FREE TIME.
HEY, THERE'S THE BIRTHDAY BOY.
ROSS, CHECK IT OUT.
HOCKEY TICKETS, RANGERS PENGUINS
TONIGHT AT THE GARDEN, AND WE'RE TAKING YOU.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, PAL
WE LOVE YOU, MAN.
THAT'S FUNNY.
MY BIRTHDAY WAS SEVEN MONTHS AGO.
SO?
SO, I'M GUESSING YOU HAD AN EXTRA TICKET
AND COULDN'T DECIDE
WHICH ONE OF YOU GET TO BRING A DATE.
AREN'T WE MR. THE GLASS IS HALF EMPTY?
OH, MY GOD.
OH. IS TODAY THE 20th, OCTOBER 20th?
I WAS HOPING YOU WOULDN'T REMEMBER.
WHAT'S WITH THE 20th?
11 DAYS BEFORE HALLOWEEN--
ALL THE GOOD COSTUMES ARE GONE?
TODAY'S THE DAY CAROL AND I FIRST...
CONSUMMATED OUR...
PHYSICAL RELATIONSHIP.
WITH SEX.
YOU TOLD YOUR SISTER THAT?
BELIEVE ME, I TOLD EVERYONE.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'D BETTER PASS ON THE GAME.
I THINK I'M JUST GOING TO GO HOME
AND THINK ABOUT MY EX WIFE AND HER LESBIAN LOVER.
TO HELL WITH HOCKEY. LET'S ALL DO THAT.
COME ON, ROSS.
YOU, ME, JOEY
ICE, GUYS NIGHT OUT.
WHAT DO YOU SAY, BIG GUY? HUH?
HUH? HUH?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
COME ON, ROSS.
ALL RIGHT.
MAYBE IT WILL TAKE MY MIND OFF IT.
YOU PROMISE TO BUY ME A BIG FOAM FINGER?
YOU GOT IT.
LOOK. LOOK. LOOK.
MY FIRST PAYCHECK.
LOOK IN THE WINDOW.
THERE'S MY NAME.
HI,ME.
I REMEMBER THE DAY
I GOT MY FIRST PAYCHECK.
THERE WAS A CAVE IN IN ONE OF THE MINES.
EIGHT PEOPLE WERE KILLED.
WOW. YOU WORKED IN A MINE?
NO. I WORKED AT A DAIRY QUEEN. WHY?
OH! ISN'T THIS EXCITING?
I EARNED THIS.
I WIPED TABLES FOR IT.
I STEAMED MILK FOR IT.
AND IT WAS TOTALLY...
NOT WORTH IT.
WHO'S "FICA"?
WHY'S HE GETTING ALL MY MONEY?
I MEAN, WHAT..?
CHANDLER, LOOK AT THAT.
OH. THIS IS NOT THAT BAD.
OH. YOU'RE FINE FOR A FIRST JOB.
YOU CAN TOTALLY
TOTALLY LIVE ON THIS.
YEAH.
HEY, BY THE WAY, GREAT SERVICE TODAY.
HOCKEY!
RACHEL?
OH, MY GOD!
I SWEAR, I'VE SEEN BIRDS DO THIS
ON WILD KINGDOM.
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING HERE?
WELL, WE WERE IN THE CITY SHOPPING
AND YOUR MOM SAID YOU WORK HERE
AND IT'S TRUE!
LOOK AT YOU IN THE APRON.
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU'RE IN A PLAY.
GOD, LOOK AT YOU.
YOU ARE SO BIG.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
I KNOW. I KNOW.
I'M A DUPLEX.
KIKI, YOU LOOK PHENOMENAL.
I MEAN, YOU'VE LOST
LIKE, A TON OF WEIGHT.
AND YOU SHOULD...
REALLY, REALLY, IT'S TIME TO STOP.
YOU LOOK PERFECT.
ANYWAY, SO WHAT'S GOING ON WITH YOU?
WELL, GUESS WHO MY DAD'S MAKING
PARTNER IN HIS FIRM?
AND WHILE WE'RE ON THE SUBJECT OF NEWS...
LOOK. LOOK. I HAVE ELBOWS.
Mc TAVISH CROSSES THE BLUE LINE
PASSES TO LEECH
LEECH SPOTS MESSIER IN THE CREASE.
HERE'S THE PASS...
WE'LL TAKE A BRIEF TIME OUT
WHILE MESSIER STOPS TO LOOK AT SOME WOMEN'S SHOES.
CAROL WAS WEARING BOOTS JUST LIKE THOSE
THE NIGHT THAT WE...
WE FIRST, YOU KNOW...
IN FACT, SHE, UH, NEVER TOOK THEM OFF.
SORRY. SORRY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE KEENAN...
WHAT?
PEACH PIT.
YES, BUNNY?
THAT NIGHT WE, UH, WE HAD...
PEACHES?
ACTUALLY, NECTARINES.
BUT, BASICALLY...
COULD HAVE BEEN A PEACH.
THEN WE, UH... THEN WE GOT DRESSED
AND I WALKED HER TO THE...
THE BUS STOP.
I'M FINE.
HEY, THAT WOMAN'S GOT AN ASS LIKE CAROL'S.
WHAT?
I THOUGHT WE WERE TRYING TO FIND STUFF.
COME ON, YOU GUYS, TELL ME ALL THE DIRT.
WELL, THE BIGGEST NEWS IS STILL YOU DUMPING BARRY
AT THE ALTAR.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S TALK REALITY FOR A SECOND.
WHEN ARE YOU COMING HOME?
WHAT... I'M NOT.
COME ON, THIS IS US.
I'M NOT.
THIS IS WHAT I'M DOING NOW.
I'VE GOT THIS JOB, YOU KNOW?
I EVEN DO MY OWN LAUNDRY.
OOH!
THIS IS WHAT I'M DOING NOW.
WAITRESSING?
I'M NOT JUST WAITRESSING.
I MEAN... I, UM...
I WRITE THE SPECIALS ON THE SPECIALS BOARD
AND I... I, UH...
I TAKE THE DEAD FLOWERS OUT OF THE VASE
OH, AND SOMETIMES ARTURO
LETS ME PUT THE CHOCOLATE BLOBBIES ON THE COOKIES.
WELL, YOUR MOM DIDN'T TELL US ABOUT THE BLOBBIES.
HOW WAS IT WITH YOUR FRIENDS?
OKAY, HOW WOULD YOU LIKE SOME TIKI DEATH PUNCH?
WHAT'S THAT?
WELL, IT'S RUM AND...
OKAY.
WE THOUGHT SINCE PHOEBE WAS STAYING OVER TONIGHT
WE'D HAVE KIND OF A SLUMBER PARTY THING.
WE GOT SOME TRASHY MAGAZINES
WE GOT COOKIE DOUGH, WE GOT "TWISTER"...
OH, AND I BROUGHT "OPERATION"
BUT I LOST THE TWEEZERS SO WE CAN'T OPERATE.
BUT WE CAN PREP THE GUY.
RACH, IT'S THE VISA CARD PEOPLE.
OH, GOD, ASK THEM WHAT THEY WANT.
COULD YOU PLEASE TELL ME WHAT THIS IS
IN REFERENCE TO?
YES... THEY SAY THERE'S BEEN SOME UNUSUAL ACTIVITY
ON YOUR ACCOUNT.
BUT I HAVEN'T USED MY CARD IN WEEKS.
THAT IS THE UNUSUAL ACTIVITY.
LOOK, THEY JUST WANT TO SEE
IF YOU'RE OKAY.
THEY WANT TO KNOW IF I'M OKAY.
OKAY, THEY WANT TO KNOW IF I'M OKAY.
OKAY, LET'S SEE...
WELL, THE FICA GUYS TOOK ALL MY MONEY.
EVERYONE I KNOW IS EITHER GETTING MARRIED
OR GETTING PREGNANT OR GETTING PROMOTED
AND I'M GETTING COFFEE, AND IT'S NOT EVEN FOR ME.
SO IF THAT SOUNDS LIKE I'M OKAY
THEN YOU CAN TELL THEM I'M OKAY. OKAY?
UH, RACHEL HAS LEFT THE BUILDING.
CAN YOU CALL BACK?
ALL RIGHT, COME ON...
LET'S PLAY "TWISTER."
SORRY... SORRY... SORRY.
UH OH.
WHAT?
THERE WAS ICE THERE THAT NIGHT WITH CAROL?
PLASTIC SEATS?
4,000 ANGRY PITTSBURGH FANS?
NO, ACTUALLY, I WAS JUST SAYING
LOOKS LIKE WE'RE NOT SITTING TOGETHER.
BUT NOW THAT YOU MENTION IT, THERE WAS ICE THERE THAT NIGHT.
IT WAS THE FIRST FROST.
WE WERE...
SIT, SIT... SIT DOWN, SIT.
YOU SHOULD FEEL GREAT ABOUT YOURSELF.
YOU'RE DOING THIS AMAZING INDEPENDENT THING.
MONICA, WHAT IS SO AMAZING?
I GAVE UP, LIKE, EVERYTHING.
AND FOR WHAT?
YOU ARE JUST LIKE JACK.
JACK FROM DOWNSTAIRS?
NO, JACK AND THE BEANSTALK.
AH, THE OTHER JACK.
YEAH, RIGHT.
SEE, HE GAVE UP SOMETHING
BUT THEN HE GOT THOSE MAGIC BEANS
AND THEN HE WOKE UP
AND THERE WAS THIS BIG PLANT OUTSIDE OF HIS WINDOW
FULL OF POSSIBILITIES AND STUFF
AND HE LIVED IN A VILLAGE, AND YOU LIVE IN THE VILLAGE...
OKAY, BUT PHEEBS, PHEEBS...
JACK GAVE UP A COW.
I GAVE UP AN ORTHODONTIST.
I KNOW I DIDN'T LOVE HIM.
SEE, JACK DID LOVE THE COW.
BUT, SEE, IT WAS A PLAN.
IT WAS CLEAR.
EVERYTHING WAS FIGURED OUT
AND NOW EVERYTHING'S KIND OF LIKE...
FLOOPY?
YEAH.
YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE.
HALF THE TIME, WE DON'T KNOW WHERE WE'RE GOING.
I MEAN, YOU JUST GOT TO FIGURE
AT SOME POINT, IT'S ALL GOING TO COME TOGETHER
AND IT'S JUST GOING TO BE... UN FLOOPY.
LIKE THAT'S A WORD.
BUT, MONICA, WHAT IF IT DOESN'T COME TOGETHER?
PHEEBS?
WELL, BECAUSE YOU JUST LIKE... I DON'T LIKE THIS QUESTION.
OKAY, SEE, SEE, YOU GUYS--
WHAT IF WE DON'T GET MAGIC BEANS?
WHAT IF ALL WE'VE GOT ARE... BEANS?
GET HIM, GET HIM.
YES!
YOU'RE NOT LAUGHING NOW
ARE YOU, PAL?
THAT'S ALL YOU NEEDED-- A BUNCH OF TOOTHLESS GUYS
HITTING EACH OTHER WITH STICKS
WELL, PASS IT!
PASS IT.
HE'S OPEN.
SHOOT IT!
OHH...
HEY, LOOK, WE'RE ON THAT TV THING.
HEY, LOOK AT THAT, HEY!
EXCUSE ME.
IT SAYS TO CALL THIS NUMBER
IF YOU'RE NOT COMPLETELY SATISFIED
WITH THIS CANDY BAR.
WELL, I'M NOT COMPLETELY SATISFIED.
YEAH, WELL, THE LABEL PROMISES NUTTY GOODNESS.
LISTEN, IT'S KIND OF AN EMERGENCY.
WELL, I GUESS YOU'D KNOW THAT
OR WE'D BE IN THE PREDICAMENT ROOM.
HOLD ON.
FILL THESE OUT. SIT OVER THERE.
LOOK, I DON'T WANT TO MAKE ANY TROUBLE
BUT I'M IN A LOT OF PAIN.
MY FACE IS DENTED.
YOU'LL HAVE TO WAIT YOUR TURN.
HOW LONG DO YOU THINK
IT'LL BE?
ANY MINUTE NOW.
HEY, MISS...
UH...
OH...
I'M SO SORRY, YOU GUYS.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO BRING YOU DOWN.
NO, YOU WERE RIGHT-- I DON'T HAVE A PLAN.
PIZZA GUY!
OH, THANK GOD.
FOOD!
PHOEBE?
WHAT?
DO YOU HAVE A PLAN?
I DON'T EVEN HAVE A "PLA."
HI. ONE MUSHROOM, GREEN PEPPER AND ONION?
NO, NO... NO, THAT'S NOT WHAT WE ORDERED!
WE ORDERED A FAT FREE CRUST WITH EXTRA CHEESE!
WAIT. YOU'RE NOT G. STEPHANOPOULOS?
MAN, MY DAD'S GOING TO KILL ME!
WAIT! DID YOU SAY G. STEPHANOPOULOS?
YEAH. THIS ONE GOES
ACROSS THE STREET.
I MUST HAVE GIVEN HIM YOURS.
BONEHEAD! BONEHEAD!
YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU DO THAT
YOU'RE ONLY HITTING YOURSELF.
WAS THIS A SMALL MEDITERRANEAN GUY
WITH CURIOUSLY INTELLIGENT GOOD LOOKS?
YEAH. THAT SOUNDS ABOUT RIGHT.
WAS HE... WAS HE WEARING A STUNNING BLUE SUIT?
AND A POWER TIE?
NO. PRETTY MUCH JUST A TOWEL.
OH, GOD.
SO YOU GUYS WANT ME
TO TAKE THIS BACK?
WHAT? ARE YOU NUTS?
WE'VE GOT GEORGE STEPHANOPOULOS' PIZZA!
HERE.
UH, PHEEBS...
WHO IS GEORGE SNUFFLEUPAGUS?
THAT'S BIG BIRD'S FRIEND.
I SEE PIZZA!
I WANT TO SEE! LET ME SEE!
HELLO? WHO ARE WE SPYING ON?
YOU KNOW THE WHITE HOUSE ADVISOR?
CLINTON'S CAMPAIGN GUY
GREAT HAIR, SEXY SMILE, REALLY CUTE BUTT?
OH, HIM! THE LITTLE GUY!
OH, I LOVE HIM!
UH, WAIT.
WAIT. I SEE A WOMAN.
TELL ME IT'S HIS MOTHER.
IT'S DEFINITELY NOT HIS MOTHER.
OH, NO...
WAIT. SHE'S WALKING ACROSS THE FLOOR.
SHE'S WALKING... SHE'S WALKING...
SHE'S GOING FOR THE PIZZA...
HEY, THAT'S NOT FOR YOU, BITCH!
EXCUSE ME. WE'VE BEEN HERE
OVER AN HOUR
AND PEOPLE LESS SICK THAN MY FRIEND
HAVE GONE IN.
I MEAN, THAT GUY WITH THE TOE THING?
WHO'S HE SLEEPING WITH?
OH, COME ON, DORA, DON'T BE MAD.
I KNOW WE BOTH SAID SOME THINGS WE...
DIDN'T MEAN, BUT...
THAT DOESN'T MEAN WE STILL DON'T LOVE EACH OTHER.
YOU KNOW, I... I FEEL LIKE I'VE LOST HER.
BAH!
COME ON, PUSH ME.
NO.
NO. YOU'RE GOING TO GET IN TROUBLE.
DON'T BE A BABY. PUSH ME.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
I'M GOING TO PUSH YOU, OKAY?
HOW ABOUT I PUSH YOU LIKE THIS?
YOU'RE GOING TO BE IN THE WHEELCHAIR
THE REST OF YOUR LIFE
PALLY WALLY... WHA...
I'M SO VERY SORRY.
UH, CAN I... SIGN YOU?
LIGHTS STILL OUT?
YEAH.
WELL, MAYBE THEY'RE NAPPING.
OH, PLEASE.
THEY'RE HAVING SEX.
SHUT UP!
SO... WHAT DO YOU THINK GEORGE IS LIKE?
I THINK
HE'S SHY.
YEAH?
I THINK YOU HAVE TO DRAW HIM OUT, AND THEN...
WHEN YOU DO, HE'S A PREPPY ANIMAL.
HEY, WHAT DO YOU THINK THE GUYS ARE LIKE?
OUR GUYS?
YEAH, OUR GUYS.
OH, I DON'T KNOW.
I FEEL FUNNY TALKING ABOUT THAT.
OH, COME ON.
OKAY.
WELL, JOEY'S LIKE
ONE OF THOSE LITTLE KIDDIE RIDES
OUT IN FRONT OF A SUPERMARKET, YOU KNOW?
YOU JUST HAVE TO PUT THE QUARTER IN
AND IT JUST GOES.
I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK HE MIGHT SURPRISE YOU.
ONE TIME HE WAS HELPING ME PUT ON MY COAT
AND HE WAS REALLY TENDER.
COME ON, BABY, COME ON...
LET'S GO...
YES!
CHANDLER'S HARD TO READ.
HE'S, LIKE, ONE OF THOSE REPRESSED GUYS
THAT YOU WOULD HAVE TO SEDUCE.
I THINK THAT'S PART OF THE ACT.
I HAVE A FEELING THAT CHANDLER
IS A LOT MORE SOPHISTICATED THAN HE SEEMS.
YOU KNOW WHO'S KIND OF SEXY?
DON'T. ROSS.
NO. GUYS, PLEASE, HE IS MY BROTHER.
I KNOW EXACTLY WHAT YOU MEAN.
HE CAN BE REALLY SMOOTH.
GOD, CAN'T YOU JUST PICTURE HIM IN BED?
I REALLY DON'T WANT TO.
COME ON, LAUGH, LAUGH.
I REMEMBER THE MOONLIGHT
COMING IN THROUGH THE OPEN WINDOW.
HER FACE HAD THE MOST
INCREDIBLE GLOW.
YES, THE MOON, THE GLOW, THE MAGICAL FEELING.
YOU DID THIS PART.
COULD I GET SOME PAINKILLERS OVER HERE, PLEASE?
HE'S RIGHT.
ENOUGH ALREADY.
WHAT IS THE BIG DEAL ABOUT TODAY?
SO YOU SLEPT WITH HER
FOR THE FIRST TIME-- SO WHAT?
YOU SLEPT WITH HER
FOR SEVEN YEARS AFTER THAT.
IT'S JUST A LITTLE MORE COMPLICATED.
FOR WHAT, WHAT... WHAT IS IT?
THAT SHE LEFT YOU, THAT SHE LIKES WOMEN
THAT SHE LEFT YOU FOR ANOTHER WOMAN THAT LIKES WOMEN?
A LITTLE LOUDER, OKAY?
THERE'S A MAN ON THE 12th FLOOR IN A COMA
WHO DIDN'T QUITE HEAR YOU.
THEN WHAT?
MY FIRST TIME WITH CAROL WAS...
MY FIRST TIME.
WHAT?
IT WAS MY FIRST... TIME.
WITH CAROL?
OH...
SO IN YOUR WHOLE LIFE
YOU'VE ONLY BEEN WITH ONE... OH.
WHOA, BOY, HOCKEY WAS A BIG MISTAKE.
THERE'S A WHOLE BUNCH OF STUFF WE COULD HAVE DONE TONIGHT.
OKAY, I GOT ONE.
DO YOU REMEMBER THAT VEGETARIAN PATE THAT I MADE
THAT YOU LOVED SO MUCH?
UH HUH.
WELL, UNLESS GOOSE IS A VEGETABLE...
OH! OH!
OKAY, FINE, FINE.
NOW I DON'T FEEL SO BAD ABOUT SLEEPING WITH JASON HURLEY.
WHAT?! YOU SLEPT WITH JASON?
YOU'D ALREADY BROKEN UP.
HOW LONG?
JUST A COUPLE HOURS.
OH, THAT'S NICE.
OKAY, OKAY, I GOT ONE.
ANYWAY, THE VALENTINE TOMMY ROLLERSON LEFT IN YOUR LOCKER
WAS REALLY FROM ME!
EXCUSE ME?
OH, HELLO? LIKE HE WAS REALLY GOING TO SEND YOU ONE.
SHE WAS A BIG GIRL.
REALLY? WELL, AT LEAST BIG GIRLS
DON'T PEE IN THEIR PANTS IN SEVENTH GRADE.
I WAS LAUGHING!
YOU MADE ME LAUGH!
THERE HE IS!
WHERE?
RIGHT WHERE WE'VE BEEN LOOKING ALL NIGHT.
OH, HE'S SO CUTE.
OH, GEORGE, BABY, DROP THE TOWEL!
DROP THE TOWEL. DROP THE TOWEL.
WOW! WOW! WOW!
MAN, CAN YOU BELIEVE HE'S ONLY HAD SEX
WITH ONE WOMAN?
I THINK IT'S GREAT.
YOU KNOW, IT'S SWEET, IT'S ROMANTIC...
REALLY?
NAH. YOU KIDDING?
THE GUY'S A FREAK.
HEY! HEY, BUDDY!
HUH? HUH?
OH... THAT'S ATTRACTIVE.
OH, I THOUGHT YOU WERE GREAT
IN SILENCE OF THE LAMBS.
OH, COME ON, ADMIT IT--
ALL THINGS CONSIDERED, YOU HAD FUN TONIGHT.
FUN? WHERE WAS THE FUN?
TELL ME SPECIFICALLY WHICH PART WAS THE FUN PART?
WHERE'S MY PUCK?
OH, THE KID HAS IT.
THE KID?
EXCUSE ME. THAT'S... THAT'S MY PUCK.
I FOUND IT.
FINDERS KEEPERS, LOSERS WEEPERS.
YOU GOT TO DO IT, MAN.
OH, YEAH? WELL, I'M RUBBER, YOU'RE GLUE.
WHATEVER YOU... NAH.
LISTEN, UH...
GIVE ME BACK MY PUCK.
NO.
YES. HOW ABOUT?
NO! NO!
GIVE ME MY PUCK...
HEY! NO ROUGH HOUSING IN MY E.R.!
GIVE ME MY PUCK!
NOW,THAT WAS FUN.
OKAY, MONICA, "RIGHT FOOT RED."
WE COULD HAVE PLAYED MONOPOLY, BUT NO...
THANKS.
OKAY, PHEEBS, "RIGHT HAND BLUE."
HEY, ROSS, SWITCH PLACES WITH ME
AND PHOEBE COULD BE YOUR NUMBER TWO, HUH?
WHAT?
NOTHING. IT'S A TWISTER THING.
THE RULES ARE ON THE BACK OF THE BOX.
HELLO?
OH, UH, RACHEL, IT'S THE VISA CARD PEOPLE.
WILL YOU TAKE MY PLACE?
ALL RIGHT. YES, THIS IS RACHEL.
NO!
HELLO? OH, YEAH, I KNOW.
I HAVEN'T BEEN USING IT MUCH.
OH! WELL, THANKS, BUT I'M OKAY, REALLY.
TO THE GRAY, TO THE GRAY.
I'VE GOT MAGIC BEANS.
NO, NO, NEVER... NEVER MIND.
I'M FINE.