WHAT YOU GUYS DON'T UNDERSTAND IS
FOR US, KISSING IS AS IMPORTANT
AS ANY PART OF IT.
YEAH, RIGHT.
YOU SERIOUS?
OH, YEAH.
EVERYTHING YOU
NEED TO KNOW IS IN THAT FIRST KISS.
ABSOLUTELY.
YEAH, I THINK FOR US
KISSING IS PRETTY MUCH LIKE AN OPENING ACT, YOU KNOW?
IT'S LIKE THE STAND UP COMEDIAN YOU HAVE TO SIT THROUGH
BEFORE PINK FLOYD COMES OUT.
YEAH, AND IT'S NOT THAT WE DON'T LIKE THE COMEDIAN.
IT'S JUST THAT THAT'S...
THAT'S NOT WHY WE BOUGHT THE TICKET.
THE PROBLEM IS, THOUGH
AFTER THE CONCERT'S OVER
NO MATTER HOW GREAT THE SHOW WAS
YOU GIRLS ARE ALWAYS
LOOKING FOR THE COMEDIAN AGAIN.
I MEAN WE'RE IN THE CAR, FIGHTING TRAFFIC.
BASICALLY, JUST TRYING TO STAY AWAKE.
YEAH, WELL, WORD OF ADVICE--
BRING BACK THE COMEDIAN.
OTHERWISE, NEXT TIME
YOU'RE GOING TO FIND YOURSELF SITTING AT HOME
LISTENING TO THAT ALBUM ALONE.
ARE WE STILL TALKING ABOUT SEX?
NO, IT'S GOOD.
IT IS GOOD.
IT'S JUST THAT, HMM...
DOESN'T SHE SEEM A LITTLE ANGRY?
WELL, SHE HAS ISSUES.
DOES SHE?
YOU THINK IT'S EASY
TRYING TO LIVE WITH MR. "HEY, I'M EVOLVING"?
HE'S OUT BANGING OTHER WOMEN IN THE HEAD
WITH A CLUB, WHILE SHE SITS AT HOME
TRYING TO GET THE MASTODON SMELL OUT OF THE CARPET.
OKAY, OKAY...
MARSHA, YOU SEE THESE ARE CAVE PEOPLE.
THEY HAVE ISSUES LIKE
"GEE, THAT GLACIER'S GETTING KIND OF CLOSE." SEE?
SPEAKING OF ISSUES
ISN'T THAT YOUR EX WIFE?
MY..? NO, NO.
YES, IT IS.
CAROL, HI. OKAY, YES, YES, IT IS.
HOW ABOUT I'LL CATCH UP WITH YOU IN THE ICE AGE?
CAN I STAY? THAT WOULD BE NO.
HI.
IS THIS A BAD TIME?
NO, NO, IT'S, IT'S, IT'S...
THE STONE AGE.
YOU LOOK GREAT.
I, UH...
I HATE THAT.
SORRY. THANKS.
YOU LOOK GOOD TOO.
AH, WELL, YOU KNOW, IN HERE ANYONE WHO...
STANDS ERECT...
SO, WHAT'S NEW?
STILL, UH...
A LESBIAN?
WELL...
YOU NEVER KNOW.
HOW'S, UM... HOW'S THE FAMILY?
MARTY'S STILL TOTALLY PARANOID.
OH, AND THAT'S...
CAROL, WHY ARE YOU
HERE, CAROL?
I'M PREGNANT.
PREGNANT.
Ha! It looks like she didn't leave in such a hurry after all.
I THINK THIS IS THE EPISODE OF THREE'S COMPANY
WHERE THERE'S SOME KIND OF MISUNDERSTANDING.
OH, THEN I'VE ALREADY SEEN THIS ONE.
ARE YOU THROUGH WITH THAT?
YEAH, SORRY. THE SWALLOWING SLOWED ME DOWN.
WHOSE LITTLE BALL OF PAPER IS THIS?
OH, THAT WOULD BE MINE.
SEE, I WROTE A NOTE TO MYSELF
THEN I REALIZED
I DIDN'T NEED IT, SO I BALLED IT UP...
AND NOW I WISH I WAS DEAD.
SHE ALREADY FLUFFED THAT PILLOW.
MONICA, YOU ALREADY...
BUT IT'S FINE.
LOOK, I'M SORRY, GUYS, I JUST DON'T WANT TO GIVE THEM
ANY MORE AMMUNITION THAN THEY ALREADY HAVE.
YES, AND WE ALL KNOW HOW CRUEL A PARENT CAN BE
ABOUT THE FLATNESS OF A CHILD'S PILLOW.
WOULD YOU RELAX?
YOU DO THIS EVERY TIME THEY COME.
THE PLACE LOOKS GREAT.
YOU GOT A BEAUTIFUL LASAGNA HERE
THAT LOOKS GOOD ENOUGH TO...
AVOID TOUCHING.
MONICA? HI.
UM, MONICA?
YOU'RE SCARING ME.
I MEAN, YOU'RE LIKE ALL CHAOTIC AND TWIRLY, YOU KNOW?
AND NOT IN A GOOD WAY.
YEAH, CALM DOWN.
YOU DON'T SEE ROSS GETTING ALL
CHAOTIC AND TWIRLY
EVERY TIME THEY COME.
THAT'S BECAUSE AS FAR AS MY PARENTS ARE CONCERNED
ROSS CAN DO NO WRONG.
YOU SEE, HE'S THE PRINCE.
APPARENTLY, THEY HAD SOME BIG CEREMONY BEFORE I WAS BORN.
EW, EW, EW, EW, EW!
WHAT?
UGLY NAKED GUY GOT A THIGH MASTER.
EW...
HAS ANYBODY SEEN MY ENGAGEMENT RING?
YEAH, IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
OH, GOD. OH, GOD.
OH, GOD. OH, GOD. OH, GOD.
NO, DON'T TOUCH THAT.
OH, LIKE I WASN'T DREADING TOMORROW ENOUGH--
HAVING TO GIVE IT BACK TO HIM.
"HI, BARRY. REMEMBER ME?
"I'M THE GIRL IN THE VEIL
THAT STOMPED ON YOUR HEART IN FRONT OF YOUR ENTIRE FAMILY."
OH, GOD, NOW I'M GOING TO HAVE TO RETURN THE RING
WITHOUT THE RING, WHICH MAKES IT SO MUCH HARDER.
EASY, RACH. WE'LL FIND IT.
WON'T WE?
OH. YEAH.
IT'S GOING TO BE OKAY.
YOU'RE GOING TO GIVE IT BACK TO HIM
IT'LL ALL BE OVER, AND WE'LL EAT A LOT OF ICE CREAM.
OKAY, IT'S A LITTLE PEAR SHAPED DIAMOND...
I TELL YOU WHAT-- ANY DIAMOND RING WE FIND
WE'LL RUN IT BY YOU.
ALL RIGHT, WHEN DID YOU HAVE IT ON LAST?
DOY. PROBABLY RIGHT BEFORE SHE LOST IT.
YOU DON'T GET A LOT OF "DOY" THESE DAYS.
NO, I HAD IT THIS MORNING
AND I KNOW I HAD IT WHEN I WAS IN THE KITCHEN WITH...
DINAH?
OH, DON'T BE MAD.
YOU DIDN'T.
OH, I'M SORRY.
I GAVE YOU ONE JOB.
OH, BUT LOOK HOW STRAIGHT THOSE NOODLES ARE.
MONICA, YOU KNOW
THAT'S NOT HOW YOU LOOK FOR AN ENGAGEMENT RING
IN A LASAGNA.
I JUST CAN'T DO IT.
BOYS?
WE'RE GOING IN.
HI.
OH, THAT IS NOT A HAPPY "HI."
CAROL'S PREGNANT.
OOH, I FOUND IT!
WELL, WHAT..?
WHA WHA..? WHAT..?
YEAH.
DO THAT FOR ANOTHER TWO HOURS
YOU MIGHT BE WHERE I AM RIGHT ABOUT NOW.
KIND OF PUTS THAT WHOLE PILLOW THING
IN PERSPECTIVE, HUH, MON?
HOW DO YOU FIT INTO THIS WHOLE THING?
WELL, CAROL SAYS SHE AND SUSAN
WANT ME TO BE INVOLVED
BUT IF I'M NOT COMFORTABLE WITH IT
I DON'T HAVE TO BE INVOLVED.
BASICALLY, IT'S TOTALLY UP TO ME.
SHE IS SO GREAT.
I MISS HER.
WELL, WHAT DOES SHE MEAN BY "INVOLVED"?
PRESUMABLY, THE BIGGEST PART
OF YOUR JOB IS DONE.
AND THE MOST ENJOYABLE.
PHOEBE, SAY SOMETHING.
ANYWAY
THEY WANT ME TO GO DOWN TO THIS SONOGRAM THING
WITH THEM TOMORROW.
WOW.
YEAH. REMEMBER BACK WHEN LIFE WAS SIMPLER
AND SHE WAS JUST A LESBIAN?
AH, THOSE WERE THE DAYS.
WELL, SO, WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
NO MATTER WHAT I DO, THOUGH
I'M STILL GOING TO BE A FATHER.
THIS IS STILL RUINED, RIGHT?
OH, MARTHA LUDWIN'S DAUGHTER IS GOING TO CALL YOU.
HMM, WHAT'S THAT CURRY TASTE?
CURRY.
MMM.
I THINK THEY'RE GREAT.
I REALLY DO.
YOU REMEMBER THE LUDWINS.
THE BIG ONE HAD A THING FOR YOU, DIDN'T SHE?
THEY ALL HAD A THING FOR HIM.
OH, MOM.
I'M SORRY. WHY IS
THIS GIRL GOING TO CALL ME?
SHE JUST GRADUATED, AND SHE WANTS TO BE SOMETHING
IN COOKING OR FOOD OR... I DON'T KNOW.
I TOLD HER YOU HAVE A RESTAURANT...
NO, MOM. I DON'T
HAVE A RESTAURANT.
I WORKIN A RESTAURANT.
WELL, THEY DON'T HAVE
TO KNOW THAT.
ROSS, COULD YOU
COME AND HELP ME WITH THE SPAGHETTI, PLEASE?
YES.
OH, WE'RE HAVING SPAGHETTI.
THAT'S... EASY.
ACTUALLY, WE WERE GOING TO HAVE LASAGNA.
OH, I LOVE LASAGNA.
WELL, WE'RE NOT HAVING IT.
THEN WHY DID YOU BRING IT UP?
YOU KNOW HOW HE LATCHES ON.
I KNOW THIS IS GOING TO SOUND UNBELIEVABLY SELFISH ON MY PART
BUT WERE YOU PLANNING ON BRINGING UP
THE WHOLE BABY- LESBIAN THING?
BECAUSE I THINK IT MIGHT TAKE
SOME OF THE HEAT OFF ME.
WHAT THAT RACHEL DID TO HER LIFE.
WE RAN INTO HER PARENTS AT THE CLUB.
THEY WERE NOT PLAYING VERY WELL.
I'M NOT GOING TO TELL YOU
WHAT THEY SPENT ON THAT WEDDING
BUT 40,000 DOLLARS IS A LOT OF MONEY.
WELL, AT LEAST SHE HAD THE CHANCE
TO LEAVE A MAN AT THE ALTAR.
WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
NOTHING.
IT'S AN EXPRESSION.
NO, IT'S NOT.
DON'T LISTEN TO YOUR MOTHER.
YOU'RE INDEPENDENT, AND YOU ALWAYS HAVE BEEN.
EVEN WHEN YOU WERE A KID
AND YOU WERE CHUBBY, AND YOU HAD NO FRIENDS
YOU WERE JUST FINE.
AND YOU WOULD READ ALONE IN YOUR ROOM-- AND YOUR PUZZLES.
LOOK, THERE ARE PEOPLE LIKE ROSS
WHO NEED TO SHOOT FOR THE STARS
WITH HIS MUSEUM AND HIS PAPERS GETTING PUBLISHED.
OTHER PEOPLE ARE SATISFIED WITH STAYING WHERE THEY ARE.
I'M TELLING YOU, THESE ARE THE PEOPLE
WHO NEVER GET CANCER.
THEY'RE HAPPY WITH WHAT THEY HAVE.
THEY'RE BASICALLY CONTENT, LIKE... COWS.
COWS, DAD?
SHE KNOWS HOW MUCH I LOVE COWS.
AND I READ ABOUT THESE WOMEN
TRYING TO HAVE IT ALL
AND I THANK GOD OUR LITTLE HARMONICA
DOESN'T SEEM TO HAVE THAT PROBLEM.
I'M TELLING YOU, SWEETHEART
YOU'RE GOING TO BE FINE.
THANK YOU, DADDY.
OH, SO THIS DOES WORK.
SO, ROSS, WHAT'S GOING ON WITH YOU?
ANY STORIES?
NO NEWS, NO LITTLE ANECDOTES
TO SHARE WITH THE FOLKS?
OKAY, OKAY.
LOOK, I REALIZE YOU GUYS HAVE BEEN WONDERING
WHAT EXACTLY HAPPENED
BETWEEN CAROL AND ME, AND SO, WELL...
HERE'S THE DEAL.
CAROL'S A LESBIAN.
SHE IS LIVING WITH A WOMAN NAMED SUSAN.
SHE'S PREGNANT WITH MY CHILD
AND SHE AND SUSAN ARE GOING TO RAISE THE BABY.
AND YOU KNEW ABOUT THIS?
FOLKS ARE REALLY THAT BAD, HUH?
WELL, YOU KNOW, THESE PEOPLE ARE PROS.
THEY KNOW WHAT THEY'RE DOING.
THEY TAKE THEIR TIME.
THEY GET THE JOB DONE.
I KNOW THEY SAY THAT YOU CAN'T CHANGE YOUR PARENTS.
BOY, IF YOU COULD
I'D WANT YOURS.
MUST PEE.
IT'S EVEN WORSE WHEN YOU'RE TWINS.
YOU'RE A TWIN?
YEAH. WE DON'T SPEAK.
SHE'S LIKE THIS HIGH POWERED, DRIVEN, CAREER TYPE.
WHAT DOES SHE DO?
SHE'S A WAITRESS.
IDENTICAL?
YEAH, PEOPLE SAY WE LOOK ALIKE, BUT I DON'T SEE IT.
ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
I'VE KIND OF GOT TO CLEAN UP NOW.
CHANDLER, YOU'RE AN ONLY CHILD, RIGHT?
YOU DON'T HAVE ANY OF THIS.
WELL, NO, ALTHOUGH I DID HAVE AN IMAGINARY FRIEND
WHO MY PARENTS ACTUALLY PREFERRED.
HIT THE LIGHTS, PLEASE.
HOW LONG WAS I IN THERE?
I'M JUST CLEANING UP.
OH, YOU, UH, DO YOU NEED ANY HELP?
UM, OKAY, SURE.
THANKS.
ANYWAY, UH, SO YOU
NERVOUS ABOUT BARRY TOMORROW?
UH, A LITTLE.
MM HMM.
A LOT.
SO, GOT ANY ADVICE--
YOU KNOW, AS SOMEONE WHO'S RECENTLY BEEN DUMPED?
WELL, YOU MAY WANT TO STEER CLEAR
OF THE WORD "DUMPED."
CHANCES ARE, HE'S GOING TO BE THIS
THIS BROKEN SHELL OF A MAN.
SO YOU SHOULD TRY NOT TO LOOK TOO TERRIFIC.
I KNOW IT'LL BE HARD.
UH, OR, YOU KNOW, I CAN, UH... HEY, I'LL GO DOWN THERE
AND GIVE BARRY BACK HIS RING
YOU CAN GO WITH CAROL AND SUSAN TO
THE OB GYN.
YOU'VE GOT CAROL TOMORROW.
UGH, WHEN DID IT GET SO COMPLICATED?
GOT ME.
REMEMBER WHEN WE WERE IN HIGH SCHOOL TOGETHER?
YEAH.
I MEAN, DIDN'T YOU THINK
YOU WERE JUST GOING TO MEET SOMEONE, FALL IN LOVE
AND THAT WOULD BE IT?
ROSS?
YES, YES.
UGH.
MAN, I NEVER THOUGHT I'D BE HERE.
HMM.
ME NEITHER.
HI. OH, SORRY I'M LATE.
I GOT STUCK AT WORK.
THERE WAS THIS BIG DINOSAUR THING.
ANYWAY.
HI.
ROSS, YOU REMEMBER SUSAN.
HOW COULD I FORGET?
ROSS.
HELLO, SUSAN.
GOOD SHAKE. GOOD SHAKE.
SO, UH, WE'RE JUST WAITING FOR...
DR. OBERMAN.
DR. OBERMAN. AND IS HE..?
SHE.
"SHE," OF COURSE.
SHE, UH, FAMILIAR
WITH OUR SPECIAL SITUATION?
YES, AND SHE'S VERY SUPPORTIVE.
GREAT. OKAY, THAT'S GREAT.
NO, I'M... OH.
THANKS.
QUACK, QUACK. QUACK, QUACK.
QUACK, QUACK, QUACK.
ROSS...
THAT OPENS MY CERVIX.
BARRY?
COME ON IN.
ARE YOU SURE?
IT'S FINE.
BOBBY'S GOING TO BE HERE FOR HOURS.
HUH?
SO...
HOW YOU DOING?
I'M...
I I'M OKAY.
YOU LOOK GREAT.
YEAH, WELL...
Dr. Farber
Jason Greenspan is gagging.
BE RIGHT THERE.
BE BACK IN A SECOND.
I DUMPED HIM.
OKAY.
SO, UH...
SO HOW'S THIS, UH...
HOW'S THIS ALL GOING TO WORK?
WELL, THE BABY GROWS IN A SPECIAL PLACE INSIDE MOMMY'S...
THANK YOU.
I MEAN, HOW'S THIS GOING TO WORK
YOU KNOW, WITH US?
YOU KNOW WHEN, LIKE
IMPORTANT DECISIONS HAVE TO BE MADE?
GIVE ME A "FOR INSTANCE."
WELL, I DON'T KNOW.
HOW ABOUT WITH THE BABY'S NAME?
MARLON.
OR "MINNIE" IF IT'S A GIRL.
AS IN "MOUSE"?
AS IN MY GRANDMOTHER.
STILL, YOU SAY "MINNIE," YOU HEAR "MOUSE."
UM, HOW ABOUT, UM...
HOW ABOUT "JULIA"?
JULIA.
WE AGREED ON MINNIE.
THAT'S FUNNY, UM, WE AGREED
WE'D SPEND THE REST OUR LIVES TOGETHER.
THINGS CHANGE--
ROLL WITH THE PUNCHES.
I BELIEVE JULIA'S ON THE TABLE.
OH.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
SO, WHAT HAVE YOU BEEN UP TO?
OH, NOT MUCH.
I GOT A JOB.
THAT'S GREAT.
WHY ARE YOU SO TAN?
OH, I, UH, I WENT TO ARUBA.
OH, NO.
YOU WENT ON OUR HONEYMOON ALONE?
NO.
NO, ACTUALLY, UH...
I WENT WITH, UH...
NOW THIS MAY HURT.
ME?
NO, NO.
I WENT WITH MINDY.
MINDY?
MY MAID OF HONOR, MINDY?
YEAH, WE'RE, UH...
KIND OF A THING NOW.
OH.
WELL, UM, I...
YOU GOT PLUGS.
CAREFUL THEY HAVEN'T QUITE TAKEN YET.
AND YOU GOT LENSES.
BUT YOU HATE STICKING YOUR FINGER IN YOUR EYE.
NOT FOR HER.
OH.
LISTEN, I REALLY WANTED TO THANK YOU.
OKAY.
SEE, ABOUT A MONTH AGO, I WANTED TO HURT YOU--
MORE THAN I'VE EVER WANTED TO HURT ANYONE IN MY LIFE.
AND I'M AN ORTHODONTIST.
WOW.
YOU KNOW, YOU WERE RIGHT.
I THOUGHT WE WERE HAPPY.
WE WEREN'T HAPPY.
BUT WITH MINDY...
NOW I'M HAPPY.
SPIT.
WHAT?
ME.
ANYWAY, UM...
I GUESS, UH...
I GUESS THIS BELONGS TOYOU.
OR, HEY, MAYBE SOMEDAY MINDY.
YEAH, LIKE SHE'D SETTLE FOR THAT.
OH... YEAH.
YEAH, THAT'S TRUE.
UH... BUT, UH...
I THINK IT'S, UH, I THINK IT'S A NICE RING
AND, UM, AND THANK YOU FOR GIVING IT TO ME.
WELL, THANK YOU FOR GIVING IT BACK.
HELLO?
OH, PLEASE. WHAT'S WRONG WITH HELEN?
"HELEN GELLER"?
I DON'T THINK SO.
HELLO? IT'S NOT GOING TO BE HELEN GELLER.
THANK YOU.
NO, I MEAN
IT'S NOT GELLER.
IT'S GOING TO BE "HELEN WILLICK?"
NO, ACTUALLY WE TALKED ABOUT
"HELEN WILLICK BUNCH."
WELL, WAIT A MINUTE.
WHY IS SHE IN THE TITLE?
BECAUSE IT'S MY BABY, TOO.
REALLY? I DON'T REMEMBER YOU MAKING ANY SPERM.
YEAH, AND WE ALL KNOW WHAT A CHALLENGE THAT IS.
SEE, SEE?
ALL RIGHT, YOU TWO STOP IT.
NO, SHE GETS A CREDIT, I'M IN THERE TOO.
ROSS, YOU'RE NOT ACTUALLY SUGGESTING
"HELEN WILLICK BUNCH GELLER?"
BECAUSE I THINK THAT BORDERS ON CHILD ABUSE.
UH, OF COURSE NOT.
I'M SUGGESTING "GELLER WILLICK BUNCH."
OH, NO. NO, NO, NO. SEE WHAT HE'S DOING?
HE KNOWS NO ONE'S GOING TO SAY ALL THOSE NAMES.
HE KNOWS THEY'LL WIND UP CALLING HER "GELLER."
THEN HE GETS HIS WAY.
MY WAY? YOU THINK THIS IS MY WAY?
BELIEVE ME, OF ALL THE WAYS I EVER IMAGINED
THIS MOMENT IN MY LIFE BEING-- THIS IS NOT MY WAY.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THIS IS TOO HARD-- I CAN'T...
HOW ARE WE?
ANY NAUSEA?
A LITTLE.
YEAH. JUST A LITTLE.
I WAS JUST WONDERING ABOUT THE MOTHER TO BE
BUT THANKS FOR SHARING.
UH, LIE BACK.
UH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M GOING TO GO.
I DON'T THINK I CAN BE INVOLVED IN THIS PARTICULAR FAMILY.
OH, MY GOD.
LOOK AT THAT.
I KNOW.
WELL, ISN'T THAT AMAZING?
WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSED TO BE SEEING HERE?
I DON'T KNOW, BUT I THINK IT'S ABOUT
TO ATTACK THE ENTERPRISE.
YOU KNOW, IF YOU TILT YOUR HEAD TO THE LEFT
AND RELAX YOUR EYES
IT KIND OF LOOKS LIKE AN OLD POTATO.
THEN DON'T DO THAT, ALL RIGHT?
OKAY.
MONICA.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
MM HMM.
ARE YOU WELLING UP?
NO.
YOU ARE.
YOU'RE WELLING UP.
NO, I'M NOT.
YOU'LL BE AN AUNT.
SHUT UP.
HI, MINDY.
HI, I IT'S RACHEL.
YEAH, I'M FINE.
I I SAW BARRY TODAY.
UH, YEAH, HE TOLD ME.
NO. NO, IT'S OKAY.
REALLY, IT'S OKAY.
I HOPE YOU TWO ARE VERY HAPPY, I REALLY DO.
UH, OH, AND MIN, YOU KNOW
IF EVERYTHING WORKS OUT AND YOU GUYS
END UP GETTING MARRIED
AND HAVING KIDS AND EVERYTHING...
I JUST HOPE THEY HAVE HIS OLD HAIRLINE AND YOUR OLD NOSE.
OKAY, I KNOW IT WAS A CHEAP SHOT
BUT I FEEL SO MUCH BETTER NOW.