TERRY, I I KNOW THAT I HAVEN'T WORKED HERE VERY LONG
BUT I WAS WONDERING, DO YOU THINK IT WOULD BE POSSIBLE
IF I GOT A HUNDRED DOLLAR ADVANCE ON MY SALARY?
AN ADVANCE?
IT'S SO THAT I CAN SPEND THANKSGIVING WITH MY FAMILY.
SEE, EVERY YEAR WE GO SKIING IN VAIL
AND, NORMALLY, MY FATHER PAYS FOR MY TICKET
BUT I'VE SORT OF STARTED THIS WHOLE INDEPENDENT THING, YOU KNOW
WHICH IS ACTUALLY WHY I TOOK THIS "JOB."
RACHEL, RACHEL.
SWEETHEART.
YOU'RE A TERRIBLE, TERRIBLE WAITRESS.
REALLY, REALLY AWFUL.
OKAY. I I HEAR WHAT YOU'RE SAYING.
I'M WITH YOU.
UM...
BUT BUT I'M TRYING REALLY HARD
AND AND I THINK I'M I'M DOING BETTER.
I REALLY DO.
DOES ANYBODY NEED COFFEE?
YEAH, OVER HERE. YEAH, I DO.
OH, LOOK AT THAT.
OH, EXCUSE ME, SIR. HI.
YOU COME IN HERE ALL THE TIME.
I WAS JUST WONDERING DO YOU THINK THERE'S A POSSIBILITY
THAT YOU COULD GIVE ME AN ADVANCE ON MY TIPS?
HUH?
OKAY, OKAY. THAT'S FINE. FINE.
HEY, I'M SORRY ABOUT THAT SPILL BEFORE.
ONLY $98.50 TO GO.
HEY. HEY.
ROSS, DID YOU KNOW THAT MOM AND DAD
ARE GOING TO PUERTO RICO FOR THANKSGIVING?
WHA..? NO, THEY'RE NOT.
YES, THEY ARE. THE BLYMANS INVITED THEM.
YOU'RE WRONG.
I AM NOT WRONG.
NO. I JUST TALKED TO THEM.
I'M CALLING MOM.
HEY, HEY.
HEY. HEY.
AND THIS
FROM THE CRY FOR HELP DEPARTMENT
ARE YOU WEARING MAKEUP?
YES, I AM.
AS OF TODAY, I AM OFFICIALLY JOEY TRIBBIANI
ACTOR SLASH MODEL. THANK YOU.
THAT'S SO FUNNY
BECAUSE I WAS THINKING YOU LOOK MORE LIKE
JOEY TRIBBIANI, MAN SLASH WOMAN.
WHAT WERE YOU MODELING FOR?
WELL, YOU KNOW THOSE POSTERS FOR THE CITY FREE CLINIC?
OH, WOW! SO YOU'RE GOING TO BE
ONE OF THOSE HEALTHY, HEALTHY, HEALTHY GUYS?
AH... YOU KNOW
THE ASTHMA GUY'S REALLY CUTE.
OH, HE IS, ISN'T HE?
DO YOU KNOW WHICH ONE YOU'RE GOING TO BE?
NO, NO, BUT I HEAR LYME DISEASE IS OPEN, SO, YOU KNOW...
GOOD LUCK, MAN.
I HOPE YOU GET IT.
THANKS.
WELL, YOU WERE RIGHT.
HOW CAN THEY DO THIS TO US, HUH?
IT'S THANKSGIVING.
OH. OKAY, I TELL YOU WHAT.
HOW ABOUT IF I COOK DINNER AT MY PLACE?
I'LL MAKE IT JUST LIKE MOM'S.
WILL YOU MAKE THE MASHED POTATOES
WITH THE LUMPS?
YOU KNOW, THEY'RE NOT
ACTUALLY SUPPOSED TO HAVE...
I'LL WORK ON THE LUMPS.
JOEY, YOU'RE GOING HOME, RIGHT?
YEAH.
AND I ASSUME, CHANDLER
YOU'RE STILL BOYCOTTING
ALL THE PILGRIM HOLIDAYS.
YES. EVERY SINGLE ONE OF THEM.
AND, PHOEBE, YOU'RE GOING TO BE WITH YOUR GRANDMA?
YEAH, AND AND HER BOYFRIEND
BUT WE'RE CELEBRATING THANKSGIVING IN DECEMBER
BECAUSE HE'S LUNAR.
S... SO YOU'RE FREE THURSDAY, THEN?
YEAH. OH! CAN I COME?
YEAH.
RACH, ARE YOU STILL THINKING
YOU'RE GOING TO MAKE IT TO VAIL?
ABSOLUTELY.
SHOOP, SHOOP, SHOOP.
ONLY $102 DOLLARS TO GO.
I THOUGHT IT WAS $98.50.
YEAH, WELL, IT WAS, BUT I I BROKE A CUP.
WELL, I'M OFF TO CAROL'S.
OOH! OOH! WHY DON'T WE INVITE HER?
"OOH! OOH!" BECAUSE SHE'S MY EX WIFE
AND WILL PROBABLY WANT TO BRING HER "OOH! OOH!"
LESBIAN LIFE PARTNER.
HI.
HI. IS, UH, IS CAROL HERE?
NO, SHE'S AT A FACULTY MEETING.
OH. WELL, I, UH, I JUST CAME BY TO PICK UP MY SKULL.
WELL, UH, WELL, NOT MINE, BUT...
COME IN.
THANKS.
YEAH, CAROL BORROWED IT FOR A CLASS
AND I HAVE TO GET IT BACK TO THE, UH, THE MUSEUM.
WHAT'S IT LOOK LIKE?
KIND OF LIKE A BIG FACE WITHOUT SKIN.
YES, I'M FAMILIAR WITH THE CONCEPT.
WE CAN JUST LOOK FOR IT.
OKAY.
WOW, YOU GUYS...
...SURE HAVE A LOT OF BOOKS ABOUT BEING A LESBIAN.
WELL, YOU KNOW, YOU HAVE... YOU HAVE TO TAKE A COURSE.
OTHERWISE, THEY DON'T LET YOU DO IT.
HEY.
HEY, YERTLE THE TURTLE.
A CLASSIC.
ACTUALLY, I'M READING IT TO THE BABY.
THE, UH, THE BABY THAT HASN'T BEEN BORN YET?
UH, WOULDN'T THAT MEAN YOU'RE... CRAZY?
WHAT, YOU DON'T THINK
THEY CAN HEAR SOUNDS IN THERE?
YOU'RE NOT SERIOUS.
I MEAN, YOU... YOU REALLY... YOU REALLY TALK TO IT?
YEAH. ALL THE TIME.
I WANT THE BABY TO KNOW MY VOICE.
WELL, THAT'S THAT'S JUST...
DO YOU, UH...
DO YOU TALK ABOUT ME?
YEAH, YEAH, ALL THE TIME.
REALLY?
BUT, UM...
WE JUST REFER TO YOU AS BOBO THE SPERM GUY.
LOOK, IF SHE'S TALKING TO IT
I JUST THINK I SHOULD GET SOME BELLY TIME, TOO, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, NOT THAT... NOT THAT I BELIEVE ANY OF THIS.
OH, I BELIEVE IT.
I THINK THE BABY CAN TOTALLY HEAR EVERYTHING.
REALLY?
I CAN SHOW YOU.
OKAY, THIS WILL SEEM A LITTLE WEIRD
BUT YOU PUT YOUR HEAD INSIDE THIS TURKEY
AND THEN WE'LL ALL TALK
AND YOU'LL HEAR EVERYTHING WE SAY.
I'D JUST LIKE TO SAY I'M...
I'M TOTALLY BEHIND
THIS EXPERIMENT.
IN FACT, I'D... I'D VERY MUCH LIKE
TO BUTTER YOUR HEAD.
HI.
HEY, RACH.
DID YOU MAKE YOUR MONEY?
NO, NOT EVEN CLOSE.
FORGET VAIL.
FORGET SEEING MY FAMILY.
FORGET SHOOP, SHOOP, SHOOP.
RACH?
HERE'S YOUR MAIL.
THANKS. YOU CAN JUST PUT IT ON THE TABLE.
NO. HERE'S YOUR MAIL.
WOULD YOU JUST OPEN IT?!
OH, MY GOD!
OH, YOU GUYS ARE GREAT.
OH...
WE ALL CHIPPED IN.
WE DID?
YOU OWE ME 20 BUCKS.
THANK YOU. THANK YOU SO MUCH.
CHANDLER, HERE YOU GO.
GOT YOUR TRADITIONAL HOLIDAY FEAST.
WE GOT YOUR TOMATO SOUP
YOUR GRILLED CHEESE FIXINS
AND YOUR FAMILY SIZED BAG OF FUNYUNS.
WAIT, WAIT, CHANDLER, THIS IS WHAT YOU'RE HAVING
FOR THANKSGIVING DINNER?
WH WHAT WHAT IS IT WITH YOU AND THIS HOLIDAY?
ALL RIGHT. I'M NINE YEARS OLD.
AW, I HATE THIS STORY.
WE'VE JUST FINISHED THIS MAGNIFICENT THANKSGIVING DINNER.
I HAVE AND I REMEMBER THIS PART VIVIDLY
A MOUTHFUL OF PUMPKIN PIE.
AND THIS IS THE MOMENT MY PARENTS CHOOSE TO TELL ME
THEY'RE GETTING DIVORCED.
OH, MY GOD.
YES, YES. VERY DIFFICULT TO ENJOY THANKSGIVING DINNER
ONCE YOU'VE SEEN IT
IN REVERSE.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
WHAT'S THIS?
I NEVER SAW THIS AT MOM'S.
IT'S A YAM.
HEL LO.
THIS ISN'T A YAM.
YAM COMES IN THE PURPLE CANS.
THEY DON'T, THEY DON'T, THEY DON'T COME IN THESE.
OKAY, ROSS, DON'T TAKE THIS THE WRONG WAY OR ANYTHING
BUT BACK OFF!
UH, HI.
WE, UH...
WE USED TO WORK TOGETHER.
WE DID?
YEAH. AT MACY'S.
YOU'RE THE "OBSESSION GIRL," RIGHT?
YES.
I WAS THE "ARAMIS GUY."
"ARAMIS...
ARAMIS."
YEAH, RIGHT.
I GOT TO TELL YOU
YOU'RE THE BEST IN THE BUSINESS.
GET OUT.
I'M SERIOUS.
YOU'RE AMAZING.
YOU KNOW WHEN TO SPRITZ.
YOU KNOW WHEN TO LAY BACK.
REALLY? YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS TO ME.
OOH. MMM.
YOU SMELL GREAT TONIGHT.
UH, WHAT ARE YOU WEARING?
NOTHING.
LISTEN, UH, DO YOU WANT TO GO GET A DRINK OR SOMETHING?
YEAH. THAT'D BE...
UH...
W WHAT'S WRONG?
I JUST REMEMBERED
I HAVE TO DO SOMETHING.
OH, WHAT?
UM...
LEAVE.
OH, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WA...!
? DON'T STAND ?
? DON'T STAND SO ?
? DON'T STAND SO CLOSE TO ME ?
? DON'T STAND ?
? DON'T STAND SO ?
? DON'T STAND SO CLOSE TO ME. ?
SO I GUESS YOU ALL SAW IT.
WHAT? SAW WHAT?
NO, WE'RE JUST LAUGHING.
YOU KNOW HOW LAUGHTER CAN BE INFECTIOUS. OH!
? DON'T STAND ?
? DON'T STAND SO ?
? DON'T STAND SO CLOSE TO ME ?
? DON'T STAND ?
? DON'T STAND SO ?
? DON'T STAND SO CLOSE TO ME ?
? DON'T STAND... ?
HEY.
SET ANOTHER PLACE FOR THANKSGIVING.
MY ENTIRE FAMILY THINKS
I HAVE V.D.
TONIGHT, ON A VERY SPECIAL BLOSSOM...
MMM, LOOKING GOOD. OKAY.
CIDER'S MULLING, TURKEY'S TURKING, YAMS ARE YAMMING.
WHAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S JUST NOT THE SAME WITHOUT MOM IN THE KITCHEN.
OH... ALL RIGHT, THAT'S IT.
YOU KNOW WHAT, JUST GET OUT OF MY WAY AND STOP ANNOYING ME.
OH, THAT'S CLOSER.
I GOT THE TICKET, I GOT THE TICKET!
FIVE HOURS FROM NOW...
SHOOP, SHOOP, SHOOP.
OH, YOU MUST STOP SHOOPING.
YEAH, I BETTER GET MY STUFF.
CHANDLER, WILL YOU JUST COME IN ALREADY?
OH, NO, THANK YOU.
I PREFER TO KEEP A SAFE DISTANCE FROM ALL THIS MERRIMENT.
LOOK OUT.
INCOMING PUMPKIN PIE.
OKAY, WE ALL LAUGHED WHEN YOU DID IT WITH THE STUFFING
BUT THAT'S NOT FUNNY ANYMORE.
HEY, MONICA, I GOT A QUESTION.
I DON'T SEE ANY TATER TOTS.
THAT'S NOT A QUESTION.
BUT MY MOM ALWAYS MAKES THEM.
IT'S LIKE A TRADITION.
YOU GET A LITTLE PIECE OF TURKEY ON YOUR FORK
A LITTLE CRANBERRY SAUCE
AND A TOT.
I MEAN, IT'S BAD ENOUGH
I CAN'T BE WITH MY FAMILY
BECAUSE OF MY DISEASE.
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
TONIGHT'S POTATOES WILL BE BOTH MASHED WITH LUMPS
AND IN THE FORM OF TOTS.
ALL RIGHT, I'M OFF TO TALK TO MY UNBORN CHILD.
AH!
OKAY, MOM NEVER HIT.
OKAY, ALL DONE.
WHAT, PHOEBE, DID YOU WHIP THE POT...?
ROSS NEEDS LUMPS.
OH, I'M SORRY.
OH, I JUST... I THOUGHT WE COULD HAVE THEM WHIPPED
AND THEN ADD SOME PEAS AND ONIONS.
WHY WOULD WE DO THAT?
WELL, BECAUSE THEN THEY'D BE
JUST LIKE THE WAY MY MOM USED TO MAKE IT YOU KNOW
BEFORE SHE DIED.
OKAY, THREE KINDS OF POTATOES COMING UP.
OKAY, GOOD BYE, YOU GUYS.
THANKS FOR EVERYTHING.
OH, LOOK.
OH, SORRY.
THE MOST UNBELIEVABLE THING HAS HAPPENED.
UNDERDOG HAS GOTTEN AWAY.
THE BALLOON?
NO, NO, THE ACTUAL CARTOON CHARACTER.
OF COURSE THE BALLOON.
IT'S ALL OVER THE NEWS.
RIGHT BEFORE HE REACHED MACY'S, HE BROKE FREE
AND WAS SPOTTED FLYING OVER WASHINGTON SQUARE PARK.
I'M GOING TO THE ROOF. WHO'S WITH ME?
WELL, I CAN'T. I GOT TO GO.
COME ON, AN 80 FOOT INFLATABLE DOG LOOSE OVER THE CITY?
HOW OFTEN DOES THAT HAPPEN?
ALMOST NEVER.
GOT THE KEYS?
OH, OKAY.
ANYTIME YOU'RE READY.
OKAY.
OKAY, HERE WE GO.
OKAY, WH WHERE AM I TALKING TO HERE?
I MEAN, UH, WELL, THERE IS ONE WAY
THAT SEEMS TO OFFER A CERTAIN ACOUSTICAL ADVANTAGE, BUT...
JUST AIM FOR THE BUMP.
OKAY.
OKAY, OKAY.
OKAY, HERE GOES.
YOU KNOW, I... YOU KNOW, I CAN'T DO THIS.
UH, THIS IS...
IT'S TOO WEIRD.
I I FEEL STUPID.
ALL RIGHT, SO DON'T DO IT. IT'S FINE.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO IT JUST BECAUSE SUSAN DOES IT.
HELLO, BABY.
HELLO. HELLO.
THAT MOMENT WHEN YOU FIRST SAW
THE GIANT DOG SHADOW FALL OVER THE PARK...
YEAH, BUT DID THEY HAVE TO SHOOT HIM DOWN?
I MEAN, THAT WAS JUST JUST MEAN.
OKAY. RIGHT ABOUT NOW
THE TURKEY SHOULD BE CRISPY ON THE OUTSIDE
JUICY ON THE INSIDE.
WHY ARE WE STANDING HERE?
WE'RE WAITING FOR YOU TO OPEN THE DOOR.
YOU'VE GOT THE KEYS.
NO, I DON'T.
YES, YOU DO.
WHEN WE LEFT, YOU SAID, "GOT THE KEYS."
NO, I DIDN'T. I ASKED, "GOT THE KE EYS?"
NO, NO, NO, YOU SAID, "GOT THE KE EYS."
EITHER OF YOU HAVE THE KE EYS?
THE OVEN IS ON.
OH, I'VE GOT TO GET MY TICKET.
OH, WAIT, WAIT-- WE HAVE A COPY OF YOUR KEY.
WELL, THEN, GET IT, GET IT!
HEY, HEY, THAT TONE WON'T MAKE ME GO ANY FASTER.
JOEY...
THAT ONE WILL.
AND EVERYONE'S TELLING ME, "YOU'VE GOT TO PICK A MAJOR."
"YOU'VE GOT TO PICK A MAJOR."
SO, ON A DARE, I PICKED PALEONTOLOGY.
AND YOU HAVE NO IDEA WHAT I'M SAYING
BECAUSE LET'S FACE IT, YOU'RE A FETUS.
YOU'RE JUST HAPPY YOU DON'T HAVE GILLS ANYMORE.
LOOK, YOU DON'T HAVE TO TALK TO IT.
YOU CAN SING TO IT IF YOU WANT TO.
OH, PLEASE, I AM NOT SINGING TO YOUR STOMACH, OKAY?
HOW'S IT GOING?
SHH SHH SHH.
? HERE WE COME ?
? WALKIN' DOWN THE STREET ?
? GET THE FUNNIEST LOOKS FROM EVERYONE WE MEET ?
? HEY, HEY... ?
HEY, UH, DID YOU JUST FEEL THAT?
I DID.
WELL, DOES IT ALWAYS...?
NO, NO, THAT WAS THE FIRST.
HEY, KEEP SINGING, KEEP SINGING.
? HEY, HEY, YOU'RE MY BABY ?
? UH, AND I CAN'T WAIT TO MEET YOU ?
? UH, WHEN YOU COME OUT I'LL BUY YOU A BAGEL ?
? AND THEN WE'LL GO TO THE ZOO... ?
I FELT IT.
? HEY, HEY, I'M YOUR DADDY ?
? I'M THE ONE WITHOUT ANY BREASTS. ?
OH, THIS IS REALLY GREAT!
IT'S 5:00, MY PLANE IS NOW PULLING AWAY FROM THE GATE.
MAYBE YOU CAN TAKE A LATER FLIGHT.
THERE IS NO LATER FLIGHT.
WELL, MAYBE YOU CAN GO TOMORROW.
TOMORROW IS NOT THANKSGIVING.
OKAY, LOOK, IF I'M GOING TO TRY TO CHEER YOU UP
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO MEET ME HALFWAY.
CAN YOU GO ANY FASTER WITH THAT?
HEY, I GOT ONE KEYHOLE AND ABOUT A ZILLION KEYS.
YOU DO THE MATH.
WHY DO YOU GUYS HAVE SO MANY KEYS IN THERE ANYWAY?
FOR AN EMERGENCY JUST LIKE THIS.
ALL RIGHT, LISTEN, SMIRKY, IF IT WASN'T FOR YOU
AND YOUR STUPID BALLOON, I WOULD BE ON A PLANE
WATCHING A WOMAN DO THIS RIGHT NOW
BUT I'M NOT.
I SWEAR YOU SAID YOU HAD THE KEYS.
NO, I DIDN'T. I WOULDN'T SAY
I HAD THE KEYS UNLESS I HAD THE KEYS
AND I OBVIOUSLY DID NOT HAVE THE KEYS!
OH, OKAY, ALL RIGHT, THAT'S IT-- ENOUGH WITH THE KEYS.
NO ONE SAY "KEYS."
WHY WOULD I HAVE THE KEYS?
OH!
ASIDE FROM THE FACT THAT YOU SAID YOU HAD THEM?
BUT I DIDN'T.
WELL, YOU SHOULD HAVE.
WHY? BECAUSE. WHY? BECAUSE.
BECAUSE EVERYTHING IS MY RESPONSIBILITY?
ISN'T IT ENOUGH THAT I'M MAKING
THANKSGIVING DINNER FOR EVERYONE?
YOU KNOW, EVERYONE WANTS A DIFFERENT KIND OF POTATO.
SO I'M MAKING DIFFERENT KINDS OF POTATOES.
AND DOES ANYBODY CARE WHAT KIND OF POTATOES I WANT?
NOOOO! NO! NO!
YOU KNOW, JUST AS LONG AS PHOEBE
GETS HER PEAS AND ONIONS
AND MARIO GETS HIS TOTS.
IT'S MY FIRST THANKSGIVING
AND IT'S... IT'S ALL BURNED AND...
AND I... I...
OKAY, MONICA, ONLY DOGS CAN HEAR YOU NOW, SO...
THE DOOR IS OPEN. HERE WE GO.
OH, GOD.
ALL RIGHT, CHANDLER, DON'T LOSE THIS.
OH, NO, NO!
GREAT. OH, WELL!
WELL, THE TURKEY'S BURNT.
POTATOES ARE RUINED.
? HERE WE COME ?
? WALKIN' DOWN THE... DO DO DO... ?
THIS DOESN'T SMELL LIKE MOM'S.
NO, IT DOESN'T, DOES IT?
BUT YOU WANTED LUMPS, ROSS?
WELL, HERE YOU GO, BUDDY. YOU GOT ONE.
DON'T YELL AT ME. YOU BURNT DINNER.
HEY! HEY, DON'T MAKE HER SQUEAK AGAIN.
OH! GOD, THIS IS GREAT.
THE PLANE IS GONE
SO I GUESS I'M STUCK HERE WITH YOU GUYS.
HEY, WE ALL HAD BETTER PLANS, OKAY.
THIS WAS NOBODY'S FIRST CHOICE.
OH, REALLY?
SO WHY WAS I BUSTING MY ASS
TO MAKE THIS DELICIOUS THANKSGIVING DINNER?
YOU CALL THAT DELICIOUS?
STOP IT! STOP IT! STOP IT!
NOW, THIS FEELS LIKE THANKSGIVING.
OH, SKIING...
SHOOP, SHOOP, SHOOP.
SHOOP.
EW!
WHAT?
UGLY NAKED GUY'S
TAKING HIS TURKEY OUT OF THE OVEN.
OH, HE JUST SAT IN GRAVY.
OH, MY GOD.
HE'S NOT ALONE.
UGLY NAKED GUY IS HAVING
THANKSGIVING DINNER WITH UGLY NAKED GAL.
I'VE GOT TO SEE THIS.
ALL RIGHT, UGLY NAKED GUY!
OOH, UGLY NAKED DANCING.
IT'S NICE THAT HE HAS SOMEONE.
SHALL I CARVE?
BY ALL MEANS.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY. WHO WANTS LIGHT CHEESE?
AND WHO WANTS DARK CHEESE?
I DON'T EVEN WANT TO KNOW
ABOUT THE DARK CHEESE.
DOES ANYBODY WANT TO SPLIT THIS WITH ME?  OH. I WILL.
MM, YOU GUYS HAVE TO MAKE A WISH.
MAKE A WISH?
COME ON. YOU KNOW  THANKSGIVING.
OOH! YOU GOT THE BIGGER HALF.
WHAT'D YOU WISH FOR?
THE BIGGER HALF.
ALL RIGHT.
I'D LIKE TO PROPOSE A TOAST.
LITTLE TOAST HERE. DING, DING, DING.
I KNOW THIS ISN'T EXACTLY
THE KIND OF THANKSGIVING THAT ALL OF YOU PLANNED
BUT FOR ME, THIS HAS BEEN REALLY GREAT. YOU KNOW?
I THINK BECAUSE IT DIDN'T INVOLVE DIVORCE
OR PROJECTILE VOMITING.
ANYWAY, I WAS JUST THINKING
I MEAN, IF YOU HAD GONE TO VAIL
OR IF YOU GUYS HAD BEEN WITH YOUR FAMILY
OR IF YOU DIDN'T HAVE SYPHILIS AND STUFF...
...WE WOULDN'T BE ALL TOGETHER, YOU KNOW?
SO I GUESS WHAT I'M TRYING TO SAY IS
THAT, UH, I'M VERY THANKFUL
THAT ALL OF YOUR THANKSGIVINGS SUCKED.
THAT'S SO SWEET. THANK YOU.
MM...
AND HEY...
HERE'S TO A LOUSY CHRISTMAS.
AND A CRAPPY NEW YEAR.
HEAR, HEAR.