HEY, GORGEOUS.
HOW'S IT GOING?
DEHYDRATED JAPANESE NOODLES UNDER FLUORESCENT LIGHTS.
DOES IT GET BETTER THAN THIS?
QUESTION YOU'RE NOT DATING ANYBODY, ARE YOU?
BECAUSE I MET SOMEBODY WHO WOULD BE PERFECT FOR YOU.
AH. YOU SEE, "PERFECT" MIGHT BE A PROBLEM.
HAD YOU SAID "CO DEPENDENT" OR "SELF DESTRUCTIVE"...
DO YOU WANT A DATE SATURDAY?
YES, PLEASE.
OKAY. HE IS CUTE
HE'S FUNNY, HE'S...
HE'S A HE?
WELL, YEAH.
OH, GOD.
I JUST... I THOUGHT...
YOU'RE NOT. SO.
GOOD, SHELLY. OKAY.
I'M JUST GOING TO GO FLUSH MYSELF DOWN THE TOILET NOW.
OKAY. BYE BYE.
HARD TO ENJOY A CUP OF RAMEN NOODLES AFTER THAT.
I MEAN, IS THAT RIDICULOUS?
CAN YOU BELIEVE SHE ACTUALLY THOUGHT THAT?
UM...
YEAH.
WELL, I MEAN, WHEN I FIRST MET YOU
YOU KNOW, I THOUGHT MAYBE... POSSIBLY YOU MIGHT BE.
YOU DID?
YEAH, BUT THEN YOU SPENT
PHOEBE'S ENTIRE BIRTHDAY PARTY
TALKING TO MY BREASTS
SO THEN I FIGURED MAYBE NOT.
HUH. DID ANY OF THE REST OF YOU GUYS THINK THAT
WHEN YOU FIRST MET ME?
I DID.
YEAH, I THINK SO.
NOT ME.
NO, NO. ME NEITHER.
ALTHOUGH, UH
YOU KNOW, BACK IN COLLEGE, SUSAN SALIDOR DID.
YOU'RE KIDDING.
DID YOU TELL HER
I WASN'T?
NO.
WELL, IT'S JUST BECAUSE
I KIND OF WANTED TO GO OUT WITH HER, TOO
SO I TOLD HER, ACTUALLY
YOU WERE SEEING BERNIE SPELLMAN
WHO ALSO LIKED HER, SO...
WELL, THIS IS FASCINATING.
SO, UH, WHAT IS IT ABOUT ME?
I DON'T KNOW.
BECAUSE YOU'RE SMART, YOU'RE FUNNY...
ROSS IS SMART AND FUNNY.
DID YOU EVER THINK THAT ABOUT HIM?
YEAH! RIGHT!
WHAT IS IT?!
OKAY, I DON'T KNOW.
YOU JUST... YOU HAVE A QUALITY.
YES. EXACTLY.
YEAH. A QUALITY.
OH, "A QUALITY." GOOD.
BECAUSE I WAS WORRIED
YOU GUYS WERE GOING TO BE VAGUE ABOUT THIS.
YOU KNOW, CHANDLER, I THINK THIS IS GOING TO WORK FOR YOU.
EXCUSE ME?
SURE, SURE.
WOMEN FIND YOU LESS THREATENING
THEY LET THEIR GUARDS DOWN, AND BOOM.
YOU'RE LIKE A... STEALTH HETEROSEXUAL.
HELLO?
OH. RACHEL.
IT'S PAOLO CALLING FROM ROME.
OH, MY GOD.
HE'S CALLING FROM ROME!
BUON GIORNO, CARO MIO.
SO HE'S CALLING FROM ROME.
I COULD DO THAT.
YOU JUST GOT TO GO TO ROME.
MONICA, YOUR DAD JUST BEEPED IN, BUT CAN YOU MAKE IT QUICK?
BECAUSE I'M TALKING TO ROME.
I'M TALKING TO ROME.
HEY, DAD.
WHAT'S UP?
OH, GOD.
ROSS. IT'S NANA.
HEY.
OH, HI.
OH, ROSS.
HI, AUNT LILLIAN.
HEY, DAD.
SO, UH...
HOW'S SHE DOING?
THE DOCTOR SAYS IT'S A MATTER OF HOURS.
HOW ARE YOU, MOM?
ME? I'M FINE. FINE.
I'M GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
WHAT'S WITH YOUR HAIR?
WHAT?
WHAT'S DIFFERENT?
NOTHING.
OH. MAYBE THAT'S IT.
SHE'S UNBELIEVABLE! HER MOTHER IS...
RELAX, RELAX.
OKAY, WE ARE GOING TO BE HERE FOR A WHILE
IT LOOKS LIKE
AND WE STILL HAVE BOYFRIENDS
AND YOUR CAREER TO COVER.
...THE FUZZY LITTLE MINTS
AT THE BOTTOM OF HER PURSE.
OH! YEAH. THEY WERE GROSS.
OH! YOU KNOW WHAT I LOVE?
HER SWEET 'N LOWs--
HOW SHE WAS ALWAYS STEALING THEM FROM RESTAURANTS.
NOT JUST RESTAURANTS
FROM OUR HOUSE.
MRS. GELLER?
SHE LOOKS SO SMALL.
I KNOW.
AT LEAST SHE'S WITH POP POP
AND AUNT PHYLLIS NOW.
AUNT PHYLLIS IS DEAD?
YEAH, FOR LIKE SIX YEARS.
WHERE WAS I?
WHERE WERE YOU?
CAN WE FOCUS, PLEASE?
GOOD BYE, NANA.
BYE, NANA.
ROSS!
WHAT IS GOING ON?
YOU KNOW HOW THE NURSE SAID THAT NANA HAD PASSED?
WELL, SHE'S NOT QUITE.
WHAT?
SHE'S NOT PASSED.
SHE'S PRESENT.
SHE'S BACK.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
SHE MAY HAVE DIED.
SHE MAY HAVE DIED?
WE'RE LOOKING INTO IT.
I'LL GO SEE.
THIS ALMOST NEVER HAPPENS.
NOW SHE'S PASSED.
I JUST HAVE TO KNOW, OKAY?
IS IT MY HAIR?
YES, CHANDLER, THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT IT IS.
IT'S YOUR HAIR.
YEAH. YOU HAVE HOMOSEXUAL HAIR.
HEY.
HI.
SO, UM, DID SHE..?
TWICE.
TWICE?
OH, THAT SUCKS.
ARE YOU GUYS OKAY?
I DON'T KNOW. IT'S WEIRD.
I MEAN, I KNOW SHE'S GONE
BUT I JUST DON'T FEEL, UH...
MAYBE THAT'S BECAUSE SHE'S NOT REALLY GONE.
NO, NO. SHE'S GONE.
WE CHECKED.
A LOT.
NO, I MEAN, MAYBE NO ONE EVER REALLY GOES, YOU KNOW?
EVER SINCE MY MOM DIED
EVERY NOW AND THEN, I GET THIS FEELING
THAT SHE'S, LIKE, RIGHT HERE, YOU KNOW?
OH! AND DEBBIE
MY BEST FRIEND FROM JUNIOR HIGH
GOT STRUCK BY LIGHTNING ON A MINIATURE GOLF COURSE.
I ALWAYS GET
THIS REALLY STRONG "DEBBIE" VIBE
WHENEVER I USE ONE OF THOSE LITTLE YELLOW PENCILS
YOU KNOW?
I MISS HER.
OH. HERE, PHEEBS.
WANT THIS?
OH. THANKS. SURE.
I JUST SHARPENED HER THIS MORNING.
NOW, SEE, I DON'T BELIEVE ANY OF THAT.
I THINK WHEN YOU'RE DEAD, YOU'RE DEAD.
YOU'RE GONE. YOU'RE WORM FOOD.
SO CHANDLER LOOKS GAY, HUH?
YOU KNOW, I DON'T KNOW WHO THIS IS
BUT IT'S NOT DEBBIE.
DAD, LET'S JUST MAKE A DECISION.
YOU'RE RIGHT. THIS IS CRAZY.
IT'S GOING INTO THE GROUND.
WE SHOULD JUST GET THE MOST BASIC THING.
RIGHT. OKAY, THAT WOULD BE
THE NONPROTECTIVE CORRUGATED FIBERBOARD WITH WHITE LAMINATE.
DAD, WE CAN'T BURY NANA IN A DRESSER FROM IKEA.
SEE, THIS IS WHY YOUR MOTHER BUYS ALL MY CLOTHES.
I HATE TO SHOP. I HATE IT.
DAD, DON'T YOU THINK THIS MIGHT BE MORE ABOUT THE FACT
THAT ONCE YOU MAKE THE DECISION
IT'S LIKE ACKNOWLEDGING NANA'S ACTUALLY GONE?
NO, I REALLY HATE TO SHOP.
I THOUGHT IT WAS GOING TO BE A CLOSED CASKET.
WELL, THAT DOESN'T MEAN SHE CAN'T LOOK NICE.
OH.
SWEETIE, YOU THINK YOU
CAN GET IN THERE?
I DON'T SEE WHY NOT.
HERE'S MY RETAINER!
I WAS JUST THINKING
WHEN MY TIME COMES...
DAD!
LISTEN TO ME!
WHEN MY TIME COMES...
I WANT TO BE BURIED AT SEA.
YOU WHAT?
IT LOOKS LIKE FUN.
DEFINE "FUN."
COME ON!
YOU'LL MAKE A DAY OF IT.
YOU'LL GET A BOAT, PACK A LUNCH...
AND THEN WE THROW YOUR BODY IN THE WATER.
GEE, THAT DOES SOUND FUN.
EVERYONE THINKS THEY KNOW ME.
EVERYONE SAYS, "JACK GELLER, SO PREDICTABLE."
MAYBE AFTER I'M GONE, THEY'LL SAY
"BURIED AT SEA. HUH."
THAT'S PROBABLY WHAT THEY'LL SAY.
I'D LIKE THAT.
HEY, GORGEOUS.
HEY.
LOOK, I'M SORRY ABOUT YESTERDAY. I, UH...
NO, NO, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT, BELIEVE ME.
APPARENTLY, OTHER PEOPLE HAVE MADE THE SAME MISTAKE, SO...
OH!
OKAY!
PHEW!
SO, UH, WHAT DO YOU THINK IT IS ABOUT ME?
I DON'T KNOW, UH, YOU JUST HAVE A...
A QUALITY. A QUALITY. RIGHT.
YOU KNOW, IT'S A SHAME
BECAUSE YOU AND LOWELL WOULD HAVE MADE
A GREAT COUPLE.
LOWELL? FINANCIAL SERVICES LOWELL?
THAT'S WHO YOU SAW ME WITH?
WHAT? HE'S CUTE.
WELL, YEAH.
HE'S NO BRIAN IN PAYROLL.
IS BRIAN...?
NO. I DON'T KNOW.
THE POINT IS THAT IF YOU WERE GOING TO SET ME UP WITH SOMEONE
I'D LIKE TO THINK YOU WOULD SET ME UP WITH SOMEBODY LIKE HIM.
WELL, I THINK BRIAN'S A LITTLE
OUT OF YOUR LEAGUE.
EXCUSE ME.
YOU DON'T THINK I COULD GET A BRIAN?
BECAUSE I COULD GET A BRIAN.
BELIEVE YOU ME.
I'M REALLY NOT.
THIS ONE?
NO.
I HAVE SHOWN YOU EVERY DRESS WE HAVE.
UNLESS YOU WANT YOUR MOTHER TO SPEND ETERNITY
IN A LEMON YELLOW PANTSUIT, GO WITH THE BURGUNDY.
YOU KNOW, WHATEVER WE PICK
SHE WOULD HAVE TOLD US IT'S THE WRONG ONE.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE'LL GO WITH THE BURGUNDY.
A FINE CHOICE.
I'M COMING OUT.
WAIT! WE NEED SHOES.
OKAY.
HOW ABOUT THESE?
THAT'S REALLY A DAY SHOE.
AND WHERE SHE'S GOING, EVERYONE ELSE WILL BE DRESSIER.
COULD WE SEE SOMETHING IN A SLIMMER HEEL?
OKAY. I HAVE NOTHING IN AN EVENING SHOE
IN THE BURGUNDY.
I CAN SHOW YOU SOMETHING IN A SILVER THAT MAY WORK.
NO. IT REALLY SHOULD BE BURGUNDY.
MM. UNLESS WE GO WITH A DIFFERENT DRESS.
YES.
NO, NO, NO, NO. WAIT!
WAIT. I MAY HAVE SOMETHING IN THE BACK.
AH.
MY GOD.
IS EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT, DEAR?
YEAH. YEAH. JUST...
JUST NANA STUFF.
HOW WE DOING? YOU GUYS READY?
SO MOM ALREADY CALLED THIS MORNING
TO REMIND ME NOT TO WEAR MY HAIR UP.
DID YOU KNOW MY EARS WERE NOT MY BEST FEATURE?
SOME DAYS IT'S ALL I CAN THINK ABOUT.
HI. I'M SORRY I'M LATE.
I COULDN'T FIND MY BEARINGS.
OH. YOU MEAN YOUR EARRINGS?
WHAT DID I SAY?
ARE THESE THE SHOES?
YES. PAOLO SENT THEM FROM ITALY.
WHAT? WE, UH...
WE DON'T HAVE SHOES HERE?
MORNING.
WE READY TO GO?
WELL, DON'T WE LOOK NICE ALL DRESSED UP?
IT'S STUFF LIKE THAT, ISN'T IT?
IT WAS A REALLY BEAUTIFUL SERVICE.
IT REALLY WAS.
OH... COME HERE, SWEETHEART.
YOU KNOW...
I THINK IT MIGHT BE TIME FOR YOU
TO START USING NIGHT CREAM.
WHAT?
NOTHING, NOTHING-- JUST YOUR OVERCOAT
SOUNDS REMARKABLY LIKE BRENT MUSBURGER.
CHECK IT OUT.
GIANTS/COWBOYS.
YOU'RE WATCHING A FOOTBALL GAME
AT A FUNERAL?
NO, IT'S THE PREGAME.
I'M GOING TO WATCH IT AT THE RECEPTION.
YOU ARE A FRIGHTENING, FRIGHTENING MAN.
OH, NO!
MY NEW PAOLO SHOES.
OH, I HOPE THEY'RE NOT RUINED.
GOD, WHAT A GREAT DAY.
WHAT? WEATHER WISE.
I KNOW.
THE AIR, THE TREES...
EVEN THOUGH NANA'S GONE, THERE'S SOMETHING ALMOST...
I DON'T KNOW...
ALMOST LIFE...
ARE YOU OKAY?
ROSS!
I'M FINE. I'M FINE.
OHH.
I'M JUST... JUST...
HAVING MY WORST FEAR REALIZED, BUT...
OKAY, DON'T WORRY.
I'M JUST CHECKING TO SEE IF THE MUSCLE'S IN SPASM.
HUH.
WHAT? WHAT IS IT?
YOU MISSED A BELT LOOP.
OH, N N NO.
OKAY, IT'S IN SPASM.
HERE, SWEETIE.
I TOOK THESE WHEN I HAD MY GOLFING ACCIDENT.
THANKS, MOM.
OH, GO.
SORRY.
HI, I'M ANDREA.
I'M DOROTHY'S DAUGHTER.
HI, I'M CHANDLER, AND...
I HAVE NO IDEA WHO DOROTHY IS.
HEY, LOOK WHO'S UP.
HEY.
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
I FEEL GREAT.
I FLEEL GREAT.
WOW, THOSE PILLS REALLY WORKED, HUH?
NOT THE FIRST TWO, BUT THE SECOND TWO WHOO...
I LOVE YOU GUYS.
YOU GUYS ARE THE GREATEST.
I LOVE MY SISTER.
I LOVE PHEEB.
THAT'S SO NICE.
CHANDLER...
HEY.
I LOVE YOU, MAN.
AND LISTEN, MAN.
IF YOU WANT TO BE GAY, BE GAY.
DOESN'T MATTER TO ME.
YOU WERE RIGHT.
RACHEL.
RACHEL...
I DO LOVE YOU.
OH, ROSS...
I LOVE YOU, TOO.
OH, NO, I REALLY LOVE YOU.
I REALLY LOVE YOU.
OHH...
YOU DON'T GET IT.
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT THERE?
UH... JUST A, UH... HEARING DISABILITY.
WHAT'S THE SCORE?
17-14, GIANTS.
THREE MINUTES TO GO IN THE THIRD.
BEAUTIFUL.
PHEEBS...
COULD YOU MAYBE HAND ME A CRACKER?
YOUR GRANDMOTHER WOULD HAVE HATED THIS.
WELL, SURE...
WHAT WITH IT BEING HER FUNERAL AND ALL.
NO, I'D BE HEARING ABOUT
WHY DIDN'T I GET THE HONEY GLAZED HAM?
OR I DIDN'T SPEND ENOUGH ON FLOWERS.
AND IF I SPENT MORE, SHE'D BE SAYING
"WHY ARE YOU WASTING YOUR MONEY?
I DON'T NEED FLOWERS. I'M DEAD."
THAT SOUNDS LIKE NANA.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE TO GROW UP
WITH SOMEONE WHO IS CRITICAL OF EVERY SINGLE THING YOU SAY?
I CAN IMAGINE.
I'M TELLING YOU.
IT'S A WONDER YOUR MOTHER TURNED OUT TO BE
THE POSITIVE, LIFE AFFIRMING PERSON SHE IS.
THAT IS A WONDER.
SO, TELL ME SOMETHING, MOM.
IF YOU HAD TO DO IT ALL OVER AGAIN
I MEAN, IF SHE WAS HERE RIGHT NOW
WOULD YOU TELL HER?
TELL HER WHAT?
HOW SHE DROVE YOU CRAZY?
PICKING ON EVERY LITTLE DETAIL
LIKE... YOUR HAIR, FOR EXAMPLE.
I'M NOT SURE I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE GETTING AT.
DO YOU THINK THINGS WOULD HAVE BEEN BETTER
IF YOU'D JUST TOLD HER THE TRUTH?
NO.
I THINK SOME THINGS ARE BETTER LEFT UNSAID.
I THINK IT'S NICER WHEN PEOPLE JUST GET ALONG.
HUH.
MORE WINE, DEAR?
OH, I THINK SO.
THOSE EARRINGS LOOK REALLY LOVELY ON YOU.
THANK YOU.
THEY'RE YOURS.
ACTUALLY, THEY WERE NANA'S.
NO!
OH, MY GOD!
NOW I'M DEPRESSED.
EVEN MORE THAN I WAS.
OH, LOOK, THIS IS MY FIRST GRADE PICTURE.
OH, PLEASE IGNORE THE "DYNOMITE" T-SHIRT.
HEY, WHO'S THIS LITTLE NAKED GUY?
OH, THAT NAKED GUY WOULD BE ME.
AW, LOOK AT THE LITTLE THING.
YES.
YES, FINE.
THAT IS MY PENIS.
CAN WE BE GROWN UPS NOW?
WHO ARE THOSE PEOPLE?
GOT ME.
OH, THAT'S NANA RIGHT THERE
IN THE MIDDLE.
LET'S SEE.
"ME AND THE GANG AT JAVA JOE'S."
WOW, MONICA, YOU LOOK JUST LIKE YOUR GRANDMOTHER.
HOW OLD WAS SHE THERE?
LET'S SEE...
1939.
24, 25.
HUH.
IT LOOKS LIKE A FUN GANG.
OOH, LOOK, LOOK, LOOK, LOOK, LOOK.
I GOT MONICA NAKED.
LET ME SEE!
NO, NO. THAT WOULD BE ME AGAIN.
I'M, UH... JUST TRYING SOMETHING.
HEY, LOWELL.
OH, HEY, CHANDLER.
SO, HOW'S IT GOING
DOWN THERE IN FINANCIAL SERVICES?
IT'S LIKE MARDI GRAS
WITHOUT THE PAPIER MACHE HEADS.
HOW ABOUT YOU?
GOOD, GOOD.
LISTEN, UM...
I DON'T KNOW WHAT SHELLY TOLD YOU
ABOUT ME, BUT, UH...
I'M NOT.
I KNOW.
THAT'S WHAT I TOLD HER.
REALLY?
YEAH.
SO, YOU CAN TELL?
PRETTY MUCH.
MOST OF THE TIME.
WE HAVE A KIND OF... RADAR.
SO YOU DON'T THINK I HAVE A...
A QUALITY?
SPEAKING FOR MY PEOPLE...
I'D HAVE TO SAY NO.
BY THE WAY, YOUR FRIEND BRIAN FROM PAYROLL...
HE IS.
HE IS?
YUP, AND WAY OUT OF YOUR LEAGUE.
OUT OF MY LEAGUE?
I COULD GET A BRIAN.
IF I WANTED TO GET A BRIAN, I COULD GET A BRIAN.
HEY, BRIAN.