COFFEE.
THANK YOU.
CAPPUCCINO.
GRAZIE.
A NICE HOT CIDER FOR MONICA.
AW, THANK YOU.
RACH?
YEAH?
WHY DOES MY CINNAMON STICK HAVE AN ERASER?
OH...
OH... THAT'S WHY.
I'M SORRY.
CHANDLER...
MISS TEDLOCK
YOU'RE LOOKING LOVELY TODAY.
AND MAY I SAY
THAT IS A VERY FLATTERING SLEEVE LENGTH ON YOU.
YES. WELL... MR. KOSTELIC WOULD LIKE YOU
TO STOP BY HIS OFFICE AT THE END OF THE DAY.
OH, LISTEN, IF THIS IS ABOUT THOSE PRANK MEMOS
I HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH THEM--
REALLY, NOTHING AT ALL. REALLY.
AND, FRANKLY, I DON'T THINK THAT THOSE KIND OF SHENANIGANS
HAVE A PLACE IN AN OFFICE ENVIRONMENT.
HEY, YOU GUYS--
CHANDLER'S COMING, AND HE SAYS
HE HAS THIS, LIKE, INCREDIBLE NEWS.
SO WHEN HE GETS HERE, LET'S ALL ACT LIKE...
HEY.
NEVER MIND, BUT IT WAS GOING
TO BE REALLY GOOD.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT'S UP?
SO IT'S A TYPICAL DAY AT WORK--
I'M PUTTING MY NUMBERS--
AND BIG AL CALLS ME INTO HIS OFFICE
AND TELLS ME HE WANTS TO MAKE ME PROCESSING SUPERVISOR.
THAT IS GREAT!
CONGRATULATIONS.
SO... I QUIT.
WHY? WHY?
WHY? THIS WAS SUPPOSED TO BE A TEMP JOB.
CHANDLER, YOU'VE BEEN THERE FOR FIVE YEARS.
BUT IF I TOOK THIS PROMOTION
IT'D BE LIKE ADMITTING THAT THIS IS WHAT I ACTUALLY DO.
OH, MAN, DOES THAT MEAN
WE GOT TO START BUYING OUR OWN TOILET PAPER?
THAT WAS JOEY TRIBBIANI
WITH THE BIG PICTURE. DAN?
SO IS IT A LOT MORE MONEY?
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO BE ONE OF THOSE GUYS
THAT'S IN HIS OFFICE UNTIL 12:00 AT NIGHT
WORRYING ABOUT THE WEENUS.
THE... THE WEENUS?
"WEEKLY ESTIMATED NET USAGE SYSTEMS."
IT'S A PROCESSING TERM.
OH... THAT WEENUS.
SO WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I WANT TO DO
BUT I'M NOT GOING TO FIGURE IT OUT WORKING THERE.
OH! I HAVE SOMETHING YOU CAN DO.
I HAVE THIS NEW
MASSAGE CLIENT-- STEVE.
ANYWAY, HE'S OPENING UP A RESTAURANT
AND HE'S LOOKING FOR A HEAD CHEF.
UM... HI, THERE.
HI.
OH, YEAH, I KNOW, YOU'RE A CHEF
AND I THOUGHT OF YOU FIRST
BUT CHANDLER'S THE ONE
WHO NEEDS A JOB RIGHT NOW, SO...
I JUST DON'T HAVE A LOT OF CHEFFING EXPERIENCE.
UNLESS IT'S AN ALL TOAST RESTAURANT.
YEAH, YEAH.
WHAT KIND OF FOOD IS HE LOOKING FOR?
HE WANTS TO DO SOMETHING ECLECTIC
SO HE'S LOOKING FOR SOMEONE
WHO CAN CREATE THE ENTIRE MENU.
OH, MY GOD!
YEAH, I KNOW.
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK?
THANKS, PHEEB.
I JUST DON'T REALLY SEE MYSELF IN A BIG WHITE HAT.
OKAY.
OH, MONICA, GUESS WHAT!
A big run up, and there he goes!
A perfect heave!
YOU WATCH SOMETHING LIKE THIS
AND YOU REALIZE WHY EVOLUTION IS JUST A THEORY.
CAN YOU SEE MY NIPPLES THROUGH THIS SHIRT?
N NO.
BUT DON'T WORRY-- I'M SURE THEY'RE STILL THERE.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING
MR. SUITY MAN?
WELL, I HAVE AN APPOINTMENT TO SEE DR. ROBERT PILLMAN--
CAREER COUNSELOR A GO GO.
I ADDED THE "A GO GO."
CAREER COUNSELOR?
HEY, YOU GUYS ALL KNOW WHAT YOU WANT TO DO.
I DON'T.
HEY, YOU GUYS IN THE LIVING ROOM ALL KNOW
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO.
YOU HAVE GOALS, YOU HAVE DREAMS.
I DON'T HAVE A DREAM.
AH, THE LESSER KNOWN "I DON'T HAVE A DREAM" SPEECH.
OH, I LOVE MY LIFE! I LOVE MY LIFE!
BRIAN'S SONG!
THE MEETING
WITH THAT GUY WENT GREAT?
IT WAS SO GREAT.
HE SHOWED ME WHERE THE RESTAURANT'S GOING TO BE.
IT'S THIS CUTE LITTLE PLACE ON 10th STREET.
IT'S NOT TOO BIG, IT'S NOT TOO SMALL.
IT'S JUST RIGHT.
WAS IT FORMERLY OWNED
BY A BLOND WOMAN AND SOME BEARS?
SO, ANYWAY, I'M COOKING DINNER FOR HIM MONDAY NIGHT.
KIND OF LIKE AN AUDITION.
PHOEBE, HE REALLY WANTS YOU TO BE HERE.
WHICH WOULD BE GREAT FOR ME
BECAUSE YOU CAN MAKE YUMMY NOISES.
WHAT ARE YOU MAKING?
YUMMY NOISES.
AND, MONICA, WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO MAKE?
I DON'T KNOW. IT'S JUST GOT TO BE SO GREAT.
OH! I KNOW WHAT YOU COULD MAKE.
YOU SHOULD MAKE THAT THING WITH THE STUFF.
YOU KNOW THAT... THING.
WITH THE STUFF.
OKAY, I DON'T KNOW.
HEY, GUYS, DOES ANYONE KNOW
A GOOD DATE PLACE IN THE NEIGHBORHOOD?
UH... HOW ABOUT TONY'S?
IF YOU CAN FINISH A 32 OUNCE STEAK, IT'S FREE.
OKAY.
HEY, DOES ANYONE KNOW A GOOD PLACE
IF YOU'RE NOT DATING A PUMA?
WHO ARE YOU GOING OUT WITH?
OH! IS THIS THE BUG LADY?
"I LOVE YOU, ROSS."
HER NAME IS CELIA.
SHE'S NOT A BUG LADY.
SHE'S CURATOR OF INSECTS AT THE MUSEUM.
SO WHAT ARE YOU GUYS GOING TO DO?
I JUST THOUGHT WE'D GO OUT TO DINNER
AND THEN MAYBE BRING HER BACK TO MY PLACE
AND I'D INTRODUCE HER
TO MY MONKEY.
AND HE'S NOT SPEAKING METAPHORICALLY.
SOOO... BACK TO YOUR PLACE.
YOU'RE THINKIN' MAYBE... HEH HEH?
WELL, I DON'T KNOW, HEH HEH.
I'M HOPING, HEH HEH.
I'M TELLING YOU-- THAT MONKEY IS A CHICK MAGNET.
SHE'S GOING TO TAKE ONE LOOK AT HIS FURRY, CUTE LITTLE FACE
AND IT'LL SEAL THE DEAL.
HE'S NOT GOING TO HURT YOU.
SOOTHING TONES, CELIA. SOOTHING TONES.
MARCEL, MARCEL, 'NANA...
I CAN'T STAND THIS.
HE'S GOT HIS CLAWS ON MY...
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY. TRY THIS SALMON MOUSSE.
MMM. GOOD.
YEAH? IS IT BETTER THAN THE OTHER SALMON MOUSSE?
IT'S CREAMIER.
YEAH. WELL, IS THAT BETTER?
I DON'T KNOW.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT WHIPPED FISH, MONICA.
I'M JUST HAPPY I'M KEEPING IT DOWN.
OH, MY GOD!
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU?
EIGHT AND A HALF HOURS OF APTITUDE TESTS
INTELLIGENCE TESTS, PERSONALITY TESTS
AND WHAT DO I LEARN?
"YOU ARE IDEALLY SUITED FOR A CAREER IN DATA PROCESSING
FOR A LARGE MULTINATIONAL COOPERATION."
THAT'S SO GREAT
BECAUSE YOU ALREADY KNOW HOW TO DO THAT.
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
DON'T I SEEM LIKE SOMEBODY
WHO SHOULD BE DOING SOMETHING REALLY COOL?
I JUST ALWAYS PICTURED MYSELF DOING SOMETHING...
SOMETHING.
OH, CHANDLER, I KNOW.
I KNOW.
OH, HEY!
YOU CAN SEE YOUR NIPPLES
THROUGH THIS SHIRT.
HERE YOU GO.
MAYBE THIS WILL CHEER YOU UP.
I HAD A GRAPE ABOUT FIVE HOURS AGO
SO I BETTER SPLIT THIS WITH YOU.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE THAT SMALL.
IT'S A PRE APPETIZER.
THE FRENCH CALL IT ANAMUSE BOUCHE.
WELL, IT... IT IS "AMOOZING."
HELLO.
OH, HI, WENDY.
YEAH, 8:00.
WHAT DID WE SAY, TEN DOLLARS AN HOUR?
OKAY, GREAT.
ALL RIGHT. I'LL SEE YOU THEN. BYE.
TEN DOLLARS AN HOUR FOR WHAT?
I ASKED ONE OF THE WAITRESSES AT WORK
IF SHE WOULD HELP ME OUT.
WAITRESSING?
UH OH.
WELL, OF COURSE I THOUGHT OF YOU.
BUT... BUT...
BUT BUT?
BUT, YOU SEE
THIS NIGHT HAS TO GO JUST PERFECT, YOU KNOW.
WELL, WENDY'S MORE OF A... PROFESSIONAL WAITRESS.
OH. I SEE.
YES, AND I'VE SORT OF BEEN
MAINTAINING MY AMATEUR STATUS
SO THAT I CAN WAITRESS IN THE OLYMPICS.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T MEAN TO BRAG
BUT I WAITED TABLES AT INNSBRUCK IN '76.
TOOK HOME A BRONZE.
AMUSE BOUCHE?
? YOU'LL BE ALL ALONE SOMEDAY. ?
TALK TO ME.
OKAY, UH...
A WEIRD THING HAPPENED TO ME
ON THE TRAIN THIS MORNING.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
TALK DIRTY.
WELL... HERE?
AH...
SAY SOMETHING... HOT.
UH...
UM...
WHAT?
WH...
UM...
WHAT?
VULVA.
"VULVA"?
ALL RIGHT, I PANICKED, ALL RIGHT?
SHE... SHE TOOK ME BY SURPRISE.
BUT IT WASN'T A TOTAL LOSS.
I MEAN, UH, WE ENDED UP CUDDLING.
WHOA, YOU CUDDLED?
HOW MANY TIMES?
SHUT UP. IT WAS NICE.
I DIDN'T... I JUST DON'T THINK
I'M THE DIRTY TALKING KIND OF GUY, YOU KNOW?
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
YOU JUST SAY WHAT YOU WANT TO DO TO HER
OR WHAT YOU WANT HER TO DO TO YOU
OR WHAT YOU THINK OTHER PEOPLE MIGHT
BE DOING TO EACH OTHER.
LOOK. I TELL YOU WHAT.
TRY SOMETHING ON ME.
PLEASE BE KIDDING.
WHY NOT? COME ON.
JUST... JUST CLOSE YOUR EYES
AND TELL ME WHAT YOU'D LIKE
TO BE DOING RIGHT NOW.
OKAY. I'M, UH... I'M IN MY APARTMENT...
YEAH... WHAT ELSE?
THAT'S IT.
I'M IN MY APARTMENT. YOU'RE NOT THERE.
WE'RE NOT HAVING THIS CONVERSATION.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, I'LL START, OKAY?
JOEY, PLEASE.
COME ON, COME ON. READY? LOOK.
OH, ROSS...
YOU GET ME SO HOT.
I WANT YOUR LIPS
ON ME NOW.
HUH?
HMM.
ALL RIGHT.
NOW YOU SAY SOMETHING.
I, UH, I REALLY DON'T THINK SO.
YOU LIKE THIS WOMAN, RIGHT?
WELL, YEAH.
YOU WANT TO SEE HER AGAIN, RIGHT?
SURE.
IF YOU CAN'T TALK DIRTY TO ME
HOW YOU GOING TO TALK DIRTY TO HER?
NOW TELL ME YOU WANT TO CARESS MY BUTT.
OKAY. TURN AROUND.
I JUST DON'T WANT YOU STARING AT ME
WHEN I'M DOING THIS.
ALL RIGHT, I'M NOT LOOKING.
GO AHEAD.
OKAY, OKAY.
I WANT...
OKAY, I WANT TO... FEEL YOUR...
HOT, SOFT SKIN WITH MY LIPS.
THERE YOU GO.
KEEP GOING. KEEP GOING.
I, UH... I WANT TO TAKE MY TONGUE, AND...
AND, AND...
SAY IT.
SAY IT!
RUN IT ALL OVER YOUR BODY UNTIL YOU'RE...
...TREMBLING WITH... WITH...
WITH...?
FUNNY STORY.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO BELIEVE THIS.
NO, NO, NO. SHH! IT'S OKAY.
I WAS ROOTING FOR YOU TWO KIDS TO GET TOGETHER.
THE TREMBLING THING WAS NICE.
SHUT UP.
HEY, CHANDLER, WHILE YOU WERE SLEEPING
THAT GUY FROM YOUR OLD JOB CALLED AGAIN.
OH, AGAIN?
AND AGAIN AND AGAIN
AND AGAIN. AND AGAIN.
HELLO.
AND AGAIN.
HI, MR. KOSTELIC.
HOW'S LIFE ON THE 15th FLOOR?
YEAH. I MISS YOU, TOO.
IT'S A LOT LESS SATISFYING
TO STEAL PENS FROM YOUR OWN HOME, YOU KNOW?
WELL, THAT'S VERY GENEROUS.
BUT LOOK.
THIS ISN'T ABOUT THE MONEY.
I NEED SOMETHING MORE THAN A JOB.
I NEED SOMETHING I REALLY CARE ABOUT.
AND THAT'S ON TOP OF THE YEAR END BONUS STRUCTURE
YOU MENTIONED EARLIER?
DREAM. DREAM.
LOOK, AL. AL...
I'M NOT PLAYING HARDBALL HERE.
THIS IS NOT A NEGOTIATION.
THIS IS AREJECTION.
NO... NO. NO. NO. STOP SAYING... STOP SAYING NUMBERS.
I'M TELLING YOU, YOU'VE GOT THE WRONG GUY.
YOU'VE GOT THE WRONG GUY!
I'LL SEE YOU MONDAY!
NYAH.
HUH?
OH, WOW!
IT'S HUGE!
THIS IS SO MUCH BIGGER THAN THE CUBICLE.
OH, THIS IS A CUBE.
LOOK AT THIS.
YOU HAVE A WINDOW!
YES, INDEEDY.
WITH A BEAUTIFUL VIEW OF...
OH, LOOK. THAT GUY'S PEEING.
OKAY. THAT'S ENOUGH OF THE VIEW.
CHECK THIS OUT. LOOK AT THIS.
OKAY. SIT DOWN HERE.
OKAY.
THIS IS GOOD. THIS IS GREAT.
NOW?
HELEN, COULD YOU COME IN HERE FOR A MOMENT?
THANK YOU, HELEN.
THAT'LL BE ALL.
LAST TIME I DO THAT, I PROMISE.
SHE DOESN'T SEEM VERY WARM.
I KNOW. SHE HAS, LIKE, NO PERSONALITY.
Uh-uh!
WENDY, DON'T DO THIS TO ME.
WENDY, WE HAD A DEAL.
YEAH. YOU PROMISED.
WENDY... WENDY...
WENDY!
WHO WAS THAT?
WENDY BAILED.
I... I HAVE NO WAITRESS.
OH, THAT'S TOO BAD.
BYE BYE.
TEN DOLLARS AN HOUR.
NO.
$12 DOLLARS AN HOUR.
MON, I WISH I COULD, BUT I'VE MADE PLANS TO WALK AROUND.
RACHEL, WHEN YOU RAN OUT ON YOUR WEDDING
I WAS THERE FOR YOU.
I PUT A ROOF OVER YOUR HEAD
AND IF THAT MEANS NOTHING TO YOU...
...$20 DOLLARS AN HOUR.
DONE.
WELL, HELLO. WELCOME TO MONICA'S.
MAY I TAKE YOUR COAT?
HI, STEVE.
HELLO, MONICA.
HELLO, GREETER GIRL.
THIS IS RACHEL.
YEAH. OKAY.
MMM! MMM!
EVERYTHING SMELLS SO DELICIOUS.
I CAN'T REMEMBER A TIME I SMELLED SUCH A DELICIOUS
COMBINATION OF, OF...
OKAY. SMELLS.
WELL, IT'S A LOVELY APARTMENT.
OH, THANK YOU.
WOULD YOU LIKE A TOUR?
I WAS JUST BEING POLITE, BUT ALL RIGHT.
WHAT?
WHAT'S UP?
I... IN THE CAB, ON THE WAY OVER
STEVE BLAZED UP A DOOBIE.
WHAT?!
HE SMOKED A JOINT.
YOU KNOW, LIT A BONE-- WEED, HEMP, GANJA...
OKAY, OKAY. OKAY, I'M WITH YOU, CHEECH.
OKAY. DO YOU THINK HE'S GOING TO BE COOL?
IS IT DRY IN HERE?
LET ME... LET ME GET YOU SOME WINE.
I THINK WE'RE READY FOR OUR FIRST COURSE.
OKAY, UM, THESE ARE ROCK SHRIMP RAVIOLI
IN CILANTRO PONZU SAUCE
WITH JUST A TOUCH OF MINCED...
GINGER.
WELL, SMACK MY ASS AND CALL ME JUDY.
THESE ARE FANTASTIC.
OH, GOSH, I'M SO GLAD YOU LIKE THEM.
LIKE THEM? I COULD EAT 100 OF THEM.
OH. WELL, THAT'S ALL THERE IS OF THESE
BUT IN ABOUT EIGHT AND A HALF MINUTES
WE'LL BE SERVING SOME DELICIOUS ONION TARTLETS.
TARTLETS? MM, UH HUH.
TARTLETS?
THE WORD HAS LOST ALL MEANING.
EXCUSE ME.
CAN I HELP YOU WITH ANYTHING?
YOU KNOW, I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M LOOKING FOR.
OH, COOL! TACO SHELLS!
THESE ARE LIKE A LITTLE CORN ENVELOPE, YOU KNOW?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU DON'T WANT TO SPOIL YOUR APPETITE.
HEY, SUGAR Os!
YOU KNOW, IF YOU JUST WAIT ANOTHER SIX AND A HALF MINUTES...
OH! MACARONI AND CHEESE!
WE GOT TO MAKE THIS.
NO, WE DON'T.
OH, OKAY.
HEY...
OOP! SORRY.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST HAVE A SEAT HERE.
OKAY...
OKAY.
GIVE ME THE GUMMI BEARS.
I... NO.
GIVE THEM TO ME.
WE'LL SHARE.
NO.
GIVE ME THE BEARS.
THEN YOU CAN'T HAVE ANY!
OH! OH!
BEARS OVERBOARD!
THEY'RE DROWNING.
DON'T JUST STAND THERE.
CALL 911.
HEY, FELLAS!
GRAB ON TO A SUGAR O.
SAVE YOURSELVES.
HELP! HELP! WE'RE DROWNING!
HELP! HELP!
THAT'S IT! DINNER IS OVER.
WHAT? WHY?
"WHAT"? "WHY"?
WONDER IF I CAME INTO YOUR OFFICE
AND I STARTED... AND...
I CAN'T THINK OF AN EXAMPLE, OKAY?
IT'S JUST I'VE WAITED SEVEN YEARS
FOR AN OPPORTUNITY LIKE THIS
AND YOU CAN'T WAIT FOUR AND A HALF MINUTES
FOR A STUPID ONION TARTLET?
HEY!
SO I TOLD HIM
I'M SORRY.
THAT'S JUST HOW I FEEL.
AND HE TOLD ME I HARSHED HIS BUZZ.
AND THEN I SAID
"DON'T EAT THAT.
IT'S A KITCHEN MAGNET."
AND HE DIDN'T LISTEN
SO WE LEFT HIM IN THE EMERGENCY ROOM.
OH, MON, I'M SORRY.
WHAT A TOOL.
YOU DID THE RIGHT THING.
YOU DON'T WANT TO WORK FOR A GUY LIKE THAT.
I KNOW. IT'S JUST...
I JUST THOUGHT THAT THIS WAS, YOU KNOW, IT.
YOU'LL GET THERE.
YOU'RE AN AMAZING CHEF.
YEAH. YOU KNOW ALL THOSE YUMMY NOISES?
I WASN'T FAKING.
OH, BY THE WAY
AM I GOING TO GET PAID
FOR THE FULL THREE HOURS?
JUST A QUESTION.
TALK ABOUT IT LATER.
SO, UH, HOW DID IT GO WITH CELIA?
OH, UH, I WAS UNBELIEVABLE.
ALL RIGHT,ROSS!
I WAS THE JAMES MICHENER OF DIRTY TALK.
IT WAS THE MOST ELABORATE FILTH YOU HAVE EVER HEARD.
I MEAN, THERE WERE CHARACTERS, PLOT LINES
THEMES, A MOTIF...
AT ONE POINT, THERE WERE VILLAGERS.
OH, HO HO, AND, UH, HUH...?
WELL, BY THE TIME WE FINISHED WITH ALL THE DIRTY TALK
IT WAS KIND OF LATE
AND WE WERE BOTH KIND OF EXHAUSTED, SO, UM...
YOU CUDDLED.
WHICH WAS NICE.
YOU GUYS WANT TO TRY
TO CATCH A LATE MOVIE OR SOMETHING?
SHOULDN'T WE
WAIT FOR CHANDLER?
WHOA. WHERE THE HELL IS HE?
YES, FRAN, I KNOW WHAT TIME IT IS
BUT I'M LOOKING AT THE WEENUS, AND I'M NOT HAPPY.
LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING.
YOU WILL CARE ABOUT IT BECAUSE I CARE ABOUT IT.
YOU GOT IT? GOOD!
WHOA...
HOW'S THIS?
SORRY.
HOW ABOUT OVER HERE?
SEE? THAT JUST MEANS IT'S WORKING.
DOES THIS HURT?
NO.
HOW ABOUT THIS?
THERE YOU GO.
AH, OOH, AH... OH, I'M GOING TO THROW UP.