IS JUST ONCE COULD WE GO TO LUNCH AND NOT TALK
ABOUT WHAT I'M WEARING OR HOW I'M DOING MY HAIR
OR WHERE MY CAREER IS GOING?
OR WHO I'M DATING.
OH...
WELL, ARE WE READY FOR THE CHECK? YES!
GOD, YES! NO, I'LL TAKE IT.
OH, NO, DARLING, DON'T BE SILLY.
I SAID I'LL TAKE IT.
HERE, TAKE IT.
GO. RUN!
THAT'S VERY SWEET.
AND ON WHAT THEY PAY YOU...
CAREER...
MOM, YOU DON'T HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT ME, OKAY?
I'M DOING FINE.
I'M AFRAID THIS HAS BEEN DENIED.
WELL, THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
THAT'S ALL RIGHT, DEAR.
I HAVE NO IDEA, BUT LOOK HOW MUCH THEY SPENT.
MONICA, WOULD YOU CALM DOWN?
THE CREDIT CARD PEOPLE SAID
YOU ONLY HAVE TO PAY FOR THE STUFF THAT YOU BOUGHT.
STILL... IT'S JUST SUCH RECKLESS SPENDING.
I THINK WHEN SOMEBODY STEALS YOUR CREDIT CARD
THEY'VE KIND OF ALREADY THROWN CAUTION TO THE WIND.
WOW, WHAT A GEEK.
THEY SPENT 69.95 ON A WONDER MOP.
THAT'S ME.
YOU SEE, WHEN I SAY "GEEK," I MEAN...
OH, THE HELL WITH IT.
YOU BOUGHT A $70 DOLLARS MOP-- YOU'RE A GEEK.
OH, YUCK.
ROSS, HE'S DOING IT AGAIN.
MARCEL, STOP HUMPING THE LAMP.
STOP HUMPING.
NOW, MARCEL, COME BACK... COME HERE, MARCEL.
NO, NO. NOT IN MY ROOM.
I'LL GET HIM.
ROSS, YOU'VE GOT TO DO SOMETHING
ABOUT THE HUMPING.
WHAT? IT'S IT'S JUST A PHASE.
WELL, THAT'S WHAT WE SAID ABOUT JOEY.
YOU THINK YOU GUYS WOULD BE
JUST A LITTLE MORE UNDERSTANDING, YOU KNOW?
I KNOW, BUT WE'RE NOT.
HEY, WOULD YOU ALL RELAX?
IT'S NOT THAT BIG A DEAL.
MARCEL, STOP IT!
MARCEL... BAD MONKEY!
WHAT?
LET'S JUST SAY MY CURIOUS GEORGE DOLL IS NO LONGER CURIOUS.
OH, MONICA, YOU ARE NOT STILL GOING OVER THAT THING?
THIS WOMAN'S LIVING MY LIFE.
WHAT?
SHE'S LIVING MY LIFE
AND SHE'S DOING IT BETTER THAN ME.
LOOK AT THIS.
LOOK. SHE BUYS TICKETS TO PLAYS THAT I WANT TO SEE.
SHE BUYS CLOTHES AT STORES
THAT I'M INTIMIDATED BY THE SALES PEOPLE.
SHE SPENT $300 ON ART SUPPLIES.
YOU'RE NOT AN ARTIST.
YEAH, WELL, I MIGHT BE IF I HAD THE SUPPLIES.
I MEAN, I COULD DO ALL THIS STUFF
ONLY I DON'T.
MONICA, COME ON.
YOU DO COOL THINGS.
OH, REALLY? OKAY.
LET'S COMPARE, SHALL WE?
OH, IT'S SO LATE FOR "SHALL WE."
DO I GO HORSEBACK RIDING IN THE PARK? HMM?
DO I TAKE CLASSES AT THE NEW SCHOOL?
NO.
THIS IS SO UNFAIR.
SHE'S GOT EVERYTHING I WANT AND SHE DOESN'T HAVE MY MOTHER.
HOW ABOUT "JOEY PEPPONI"?
NO. STILL TOO ETHNIC.
MY AGENT THINKS
I SHOULD HAVE A NAME THAT'S MORE NEUTRAL.
"JOEY.... SWITZERLAND?"
PLUS, YOU KNOW, I THINK IT SHOULD BE "JOE."
"JOEY" MAKES ME SOUND LIKE I'M...
I DON'T KNOW-- THIS BIG.
WHICH I'M NOT.
JOE, JOE, JOE... STALIN?
"STALIN... STALIN."
DO I KNOW THAT NAME?
THAT SOUNDS FAMILIAR.
WELL, IT DOES NOT RING A BELL WITH ME.
BUT YOU'RE MORE PLUGGED INTO THAT WHOLE SHOW BUSINESS THING.
JOE STALIN.
YOU KNOW THAT'S PRETTY GOOD.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO TRY "JOSEPH."
OH!
JOSEPH STALIN.
I THINK YOU'D
REMEMBER THAT.
OH, YES.
"BYE BYE BIRDIE, STARRING JOSEPH STALIN."
"JOSEPH STALINIS THE FIDDLER ON THE ROOF."
HEY.
HI.
HI, UH, YES. THIS IS MONICA GELLER.
UM, I BELIEVE I'M TAKING SOME CLASSES WITH YOU
AND I WAS WONDERING
WHAT THEY WERE.
WELL, I'VE HAD A RECENT HEAD INJURY
AND CERTAIN NUMBERS AND DATES ARE... BARBECUE?!
OH, DID I?
SEE? THERE YOU GO.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
ALL RIGHT. GREAT.
GREAT. THANKS A LOT.
I'M GOING TO TAP CLASS.
SO THAT YOU CAN DANCE WITH THE WOMAN
THAT STOLE YOUR CREDIT CARD.
I WANT TO SEE WHAT SHE LOOKS LIKE.
WELL, THEN JUST GO TO THE POST OFFICE.
I'M SURE THEY'VE GOT HER PICTURE UP.
THIS WOMAN'S GOT MY LIFE.
I SHOULD GET TO SEE WHO SHE IS.
OKAY, MONICA, YOU KNOW WHAT, HONEY?
YOU'RE KINDA LOSING IT HERE.
I MEAN, THIS IS REALLY BECOMING
LIKE, A WEIRD OBSESSION THING.
THIS IS MADNESS. IT'S MADNESS, I TELL YOU!
FOR THE LOVE OF GOD, MONICA
DON'T DO IT!
THANK YOU.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
LOTS OF THINGS.
WHICH ONE DO YOU THINK SHE IS?
MAY I HELP YOU?
NO, THANKS. WE'RE JUST HERE TO OBSERVE.
YOU DON'T OBSERVE A DANCE CLASS.
YOU DANCE A DANCE CLASS.
SPARE SHOES ARE OVER THERE.
WHAT DOES SHE MEAN?
I THINK SHE MEANS YOU DANCE... A DANCE CLASS.
COME ON. COME ON.
OKAY. YOU SEE ANYBODY YOU THINK COULD BE ME?
PEOPLE, LAST TIME, THERE WERE SOME EMPTY YOGURT CONTAINERS
LYING AROUND AFTER CLASS.
LET'S NOT HAVE THAT HAPPEN AGAIN.
SHE COULD BE YOU.
LET'S GET STARTED.
FIVE, SIX...
A FIVE, SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT--
OKAY. I'M NOT GETTING THIS.
I'M TOTALLY GETTING IT.
DO YOU EVER JUST FEEL LIKE SOMETIMES YOU ARE
SO UNBELIEVABLY UNCOORDINATED?
WHAT?
YOU JUST CLICK WHEN THEY CLICK.
ALL RIGHT, PEOPLE.
NOW EVERYONE GRAB A PARTNER.
OH... UM, ALL RIGHT.
AND MY DEAD MOTHER SAID YOU ARE IT.
I'M WITH RACHEL.
WAIT. IT'S GYM CLASS ALL OVER AGAIN.
OH... OH...
OH, THAT'S ALL RIGHT, YOU CAN COME UP TO THE FRONT
AND DANCE WITH ME.
WHY DON'T I JUST TAKE OFF MY CLOTHES
AND HAVE A NIGHTMARE?
IT'S OKAY. IT'S OKAY.
I'M HERE. I'M HERE.
I'M SO SORRY I'M LATE.
OKAY, HERE I AM.
SO, WHO'S THE NEW TENSE GIRL?
SHE'S YOUR PARTNER.
HI. I'M MONICA.
OH... MONICA.
HI. I'M MON... NANA.
MONANA?
YES.
IT'S DUTCH.
YOU'RE KIDDING?
I SPENT THREE YEARS IN AMSTERDAM.
MAG IK DEZE DANS VAN U?
UM, PENNSYLVANIA DUTCH.
OH.
AND WE'RE DANCING.
A FIVE, SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT--
HI.
HEY. HEY.
WHERE'VE YOU BEEN?
I JUST GOT BACK FROM THE VET.
SHE'S NOT GOING TO MAKE YOU WEAR
ONE OF THOSE BIG PLASTIC CONES, IS SHE?
SHE SAYS MARCEL'S HUMPING THING'S NOT A PHASE.
APPARENTLY, HE'S REACHED SEXUAL MATURITY.
HEY, HE BEAT YOU.
SHE SAYS AS TIME GOES ON
HE'S GOING TO START GETTING AGGRESSIVE AND VIOLENT.
SO WHAT DOES THIS MEAN?
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO GIVE HIM UP.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT, ROSS.
THIS SUCKS!
I MEAN, I DON'T GET IT. YOU JUST GOT HIM.
HOW COULD HE BE AN ADULT ALREADY?
I KNOW, I KNOW.
I MEAN, ONE DAY HE'S THIS LITTLE THING
AND THEN BEFORE YOU KNOW IT
HE'S THIS LITTLE THING I CAN'T GET OFF MY LEG.
ISN'T THERE ANY WAY YOU CAN KEEP HIM?
NO. NO, THE VET SAID THAT UNLESS HE'S IN A PLACE
WHERE HE HAS REGULAR ACCESS TO SOME...
MONKEY LOVING...
HE'S JUST GOING TO GET VICIOUS.
I'VE... I'VE JUST GOT TO GET HIM INTO A ZOO.
HOW DO YOU GET A MONKEY INTO A ZOO?
I KNOW THAT ONE.
NO, THAT'S "POPES INTO A VOLKSWAGEN."
WELL, WE'RE APPLYING TO A LOT OF THEM
AND NATURALLY, OUR FIRST CHOICE
WOULD BE ONE OF THE BIGGER STATE ZOOS--
YOU KNOW, LIKE SAN DIEGO.
OH... RIGHT?
BUT THAT MAY BE JUST A PIPE DREAM
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, HE'S OUT OF STATE.
UH, MY VET KNOWS SOMEONE AT MIAMI
SO THAT'S A POSSIBILITY.
YEAH, BUT THAT'S, LIKE, TWO BLOCKS AWAY FROM THE BEACH.
I MEAN, IT'S A TOTAL PARTY ZOO.
HEY. WE FOUND HER, WE FOUND THE GIRL.
DID YOU CALL THE COPS?
NOPE. WE TOOK HER TO LUNCH.
AH, YOUR OWN BRAND OF VIGILANTE JUSTICE.
ARE YOU INSANE?
THIS WOMAN STOLE FROM YOU!
SHE... SHE STOLE! SHE'S A STEALER!
YOU KNOW WHAT? AFTER YOU'RE WITH THIS WOMAN
FOR, LIKE, TEN MINUTES
YOU FORGET ALL THAT.
I MEAN, SHE'S THIS ASTOUNDING PERSON
WITH THIS AMAZING SPIRIT.
YEAH, WHICH SHE PROBABLY STOLE FROM SOME CHEERLEADER.
"TAKE OFF THEIR HATS."
"POPES IN
A VOLKSWAGEN."
I LOVE THAT JOKE.
NO WAY... NO WAY DID YOU DO THIS.
MONANA WAS VERY BRAVE.
IT WAS SO WILD.
WE TOLD THEM WE WERE THE GUNDERSONS IN ROOM 615
ONLY TO FIND OUT THAT THE BOSTON CELTICS
HAD TAKEN OVER THE ENTIRE SIXTH FLOOR.
WHEN THEY CAUGHT ON TO THE FACT
THAT WE'RE, YOU KNOW, SHORT AND HAVE BREASTS...
THEY THREW US OUT.
I WAS THROWN OUT OF A HOTEL-- ME!
GO, MONANA!
WELL, YOU LADIES ARE NOT THE ONLY ONES LIVING THE DREAM.
I GET TO GO POUR COFFEE FOR PEOPLE I DON'T KNOW.
DON'T WAIT UP.
OH, BY THE WAY-- TOMORROW, WE'RE AUDITIONING FOR A BROADWAY SHOW.
EXCUSE ME?
THERE'S AN OPEN CALL FOR CATS.
I'M THINKING WE GO DOWN THERE, SING "MEMORIES"
AND MAKE COMPLETE FOOLS OF OURSELVES.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
REMEMBER WHO YOU'RE DEALING WITH HERE.
I'M NOT LIKE YOU.
I CAN'T EVEN STAND IN FRONT OF A TAP CLASS.
THAT'S JUST PROBABLY BECAUSE
OF YOUR AMISH BACKGROUND.
WHAT?
WELL, YOU'RE PENNSYLVANIA DUTCH, RIGHT?
RIGHT... TILL I BOUGHT A BLOW DRYER
AND THEN I WAS SHUNNED.
I USED TO BE JUST LIKE YOU
AND THEN ONE DAY I SAW A MOVIE THAT CHANGED MY LIFE.
DID YOU EVER SEE DEAD POETS SOCIETY?
UH HUH.
I THOUGHT THAT MOVIE WAS SO INCREDIBLY... BORING.
I MEAN, THAT THING AT THE END
WHERE THE KID KILLS HIMSELF BECAUSE HE CAN'T BE IN THE PLAY?
WHAT WAS THAT?
IT'S LIKE, "KID, WAIT A YEAR, LEAVE HOME.
DO SOME COMMUNITY THEATER."
I WALKED OUT OF THERE AND I THOUGHT
"NOW, THAT'S TWO HOURS OF MY LIFE
THAT I'M NEVER GETTING BACK."
AND THAT THOUGHT SCARED ME MORE THAN ALL THE OTHER CRAP
I WAS AFRAID TO DO.
WOW. THEN I WOULD DEFINITELY
NOT RECOMMEND MRS. DOUBTFIRE.
OH, GOD.
WE DIDN'T GET INTO SCRANTON.
THAT WAS, LIKE, OUR SAFETY ZOO.
THEY TAKE, LIKE, DOGS AND COWS.
SEE? I DON'T KNOW WHO THIS IS HARDER ON--
ME OR HIM.
I'D SAY THAT CHAIR'S TAKING THE BRUNT OF IT.
MARCEL! MARCEL!
MARCEL, NO!
GOOD BOY.
SEE? HOW CAN NOBODY WANT HIM?
OH, SOMEBODY WILL.
YOU KNOW THERE ALREADY IS A JOSEPH STALIN?
YOU'RE KIDDING.
APPARENTLY, HE WAS THIS RUSSIAN DICTATOR
WHO SLAUGHTERED ALL THESE PEOPLE.
YOU'D THINK YOU WOULD HAVE KNOWN THAT.
YOU KNOW, YOU'D THINK I WOULD'VE.
HEY, HOW ABOUT JOEY HEATHERTON?
COME ON, SERIOUSLY.
I TOLD YOU, I DON'T WANT TO GO BACK TO JOEY.
PHOEBE, WHAT DO YOU THINK
A GOOD STAGE NAME FOR ME WOULD BE?
FLAME BOY.
WHERE EXACTLY IS YOUR ZOO?
WELL, IT'S TECHNICALLY NOT A ZOO, PER SE.
IT'S MORE OF AN INTERACTIVE WILDLIFE EXPERIENCE.
LET ME ASK YOU
SOME QUESTIONS ABOUT-- IS IT "MARCEL"?
YES.
DOES HE, UH, FIGHT WITH OTHER ANIMALS?
NO, NO. HE'S VERY DOCILE.
MMM. EVEN IF HE WERE... CORNERED?
WELL, I DON'T KNOW. WHY?
UM... HOW IS HE AT HANDLING SMALL OBJECTS?
HE CAN HOLD A BANANA, IF THAT'S WHAT YOU MEAN.
WHAT ABOUT A HAMMER OR A SMALL BLADE?
WHY... WHY... WHY... WHY WOULD HE NEED A BLADE?
WELL, IF HE'S UP AGAINST A JUNGLE CAT
OR AN ANIMAL WITH HORNS
YOU GOT TO GIVE THE LITTLE GUY
SOMETHING.
OTHERWISE, IT'S JUST CRUEL.
HE GOT INTO SAN DIEGO.
WHAT?
WE CAME BACK FROM OUR WALK.
THE PHONE WAS RINGING.
HE'S IN!
AH, DID YOU HEAR THAT, MARCEL?
OH! SAN DIEGO! SAN DIEGO!
YOU'RE MAKING A BIG MISTAKE HERE.
I MEAN, SAN DIEGO'S ALL VERY WELL AND GOOD, BUT IF YOU GIVE HIM TO ME
I'LL START HIM OFF AGAINST A BLIND RABBIT AND GIVE YOU
20% OF THE GATE.
? YO HO! ?
WHERE THE HELL HAVE YOU BEEN?
MONICA AND I JUST CRASHED AN EMBASSY PARTY.
I THINK I KISSED AN ARCHBISHOP.
BUT OF COURSE, IT COULD'VE BEEN A CHEF.
ARE YOU DRUNK?
NO!
I'M LYING. I AM SO DRUNK...
OH, GOD.
GREAT, MONICA. YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU COULD HAVE CALLED.
I'VE BEEN UP HERE, I'VE BEEN WORRIED...
MONICA!
MONICA?
AH...
WATER RULES!
YES, YES, IT DOES.
OKAY, LOOK. THE RESTAURANT CALLED AGAIN TODAY.
THEY WANT TO KNOW IF YOU'LL BE SHOWING UP FOR WORK?
NOPE. I'M GOING TO THE BIG APPLE CIRCUS TODAY.
OKAY, MONICA, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU'RE GOING TO LOSE YOUR JOB.
THIS IS NOT YOU.
NO, IT IS ME.
I'M NOT JUST THE PERSON WHO NEEDS TO FLUFF THE PILLOWS
AND PAY THE BILLS AS SOON AS THEY COME IN.
YOU KNOW, WHEN I'M WITH HER, I AM SO MUCH MORE THAN THAT.
I'M...
I'M MONANA.
HELLO?
YES, SHE IS.
HOLD ON A SECOND, PLEASE.
"MONANA..." IT'S FOR YOU.
THE CREDIT CARD PEOPLE.
HELLO.
YES?
OH, MY GOD.
THANKS.
WHAT?
THEY'VE ARRESTED MONICA.
HI.
HEY.
HOW ARE YOU?
I'M NOT TOO BAD.
FORTUNATELY, BLUE'S MY COLOR.
HOW DID YOU KNOW
I WAS HERE?
BECAUSE... I'M MONICA GELLER.
IT WAS MY CREDIT CARD YOU WERE USING.
THAT, I WAS NOT EXPECTING.
I WANT YOU TO KNOW IT WASN'T ME
WHO TURNED YOU IN.
OH... THANKS.
NO... THANK YOU.
YOU HAVE GIVEN ME SO MUCH.
IF IT WASN'T FOR YOU
I WOULD HAVE NEVER GOTTEN TO SING "MEMORIES" ON THE STAGE
AT THE WINTERGARDEN THEATER.
WELL, ACTUALLY, YOU ONLY GOT
TO SING "MEMO..."
I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE IN HERE.
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO WITHOUT YOU?
WHO'S GOING TO CRASH THE EMBASSY PARTIES WITH ME
OR WHO'S GOING TO TAKE ME TO THE BIG APPLE CIRCUS?
MONICA, I STARTED MY DAY
BY PEEING IN FRONT OF 25 OTHER WOMEN
AND YOU'RE WORRIED ABOUT WHO'S GOING TO TAKE YOU
TO THE BIG APPLE CIRCUS?
WELL, NOT WORRIED... YOU KNOW, JUST WONDERING.
THERE'S NOTHING TO WONDER ABOUT, MONICA.
YOU'RE GOING TO GO BACK TO BEING EXACTLY WHO YOU WERE
BECAUSE THAT'S WHO YOU ARE.
NOT NECESSARILY.
YES, NECESSARILY.
I MEAN, I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS.
MAYBE IT'S THE AMISH THING.
UM... I'M NOT ACTUALLY AMISH.
REALLY? THEN WHY ARE YOU LIKE THAT?
YOU BY THE DOOR, IN OR OUT?
IN.
YOU IN THE BACK, YOU'RE GETTING IT ALL WRONG.
BUT AT LEAST I'M DOING IT.
This is the final boarding call for flight 67 to San Diego
boarding at Gate 42A.
OKAY, GOOD BYE, LITTLE MONKEY GUY.
I WROTE YOU THIS POEM.
OH...
OKAY, BUT DON'T EAT IT TILL YOU GET ON THE PLANE.
"THANK YOU, AUNT PHOEBE."
OH...
OKAY, BYE, CHAMP.
NOW, I KNOW THERE'S GOING TO BE A LOT OF BABES IN SAN DIEGO
BUT REMEMBER, THERE'S ALSO A LOT TO LEARN.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY, ROSS.
IT'S A MONKEY.
OH, JUST... JUST SAY WHAT YOU FEEL, JOEY.
MARCEL, I'M HUNGRY.
THAT WAS GOOD.
MARCEL, THIS IS FOR YOU.
IT'S, UH...
JUST, YOU KNOW, SOMETHING TO, UH... DO ON THE PLANE.
IF YOU GUYS DON'T MIND
I'D LIKE TO TAKE A MOMENT-- JUST ME AND HIM.
OH, SURE. OF COURSE. ABSOLUTELY.
YEAH, GO AHEAD.
OH! UH...
MARCEL, COME HERE, COME HERE.
COME HERE.
WELL, BUDDY... THIS IS IT.
THERE'S JUST A COUPLE OF THINGS I WANTED TO SAY.
I'M REALLY GOING TO MISS YOU
AND I'M NEVER GOING TO FORGET ABOUT YOU.
YOU'VE BEEN MORE THAN JUST A PET TO ME.
YOU'VE BEEN... YOU'VE BEEN...
MORE LIKE A...
MARCEL, WOULD YOU LEAVE MY LEG ALONE?
WOULD YOU JUST STOP HUMPING ME FOR TWO SECONDS?
MARCEL... OKAY, WOULD YOU...? JUST TAKE HIM AWAY.
JUST TAKE HIM.
? AND I DON'T KNOW HOW ?
? BUT YOU'RE A BIG BOY NOW ?
? BUT YOU'RE BIG BOY NOW ?
? MM MM... ?
OH, THAT I WERE A GLOVE UPON THAT HAND
THAT I MIGHT... TOUCH THY CHEEK.
THAT'S FINE. THANK YOU.
NEXT.
HI. I'LL BE READING
FOR THE ROLE OF MERCUTIO.
NAME?
HOLDEN McGROIN.