HI, GUYS!
HEY, PHOEBE!
HEY, OH, HOW DID IT GO?
UM, NOT SO GOOD.
HE SAID, "WE SHOULD DO THIS AGAIN."
WHAT? "WE SHOULD DO IT AGAIN."
THAT'S GOOD, RIGHT?
NO, LOOSELY TRANSLATED
"WE SHOULD DO THIS AGAIN" MEANS
"YOU WILL NEVER SEE ME NAKED."
SINCE WHEN?
SINCE ALWAYS.
IT'S LIKE DATING LANGUAGE.
YOU KNOW, LIKE, "IT'S NOT YOU" MEANS "IT IS YOU."
OR "YOU'RE SUCH A NICE GUY" MEANS:
"I'LL BE DATING LEATHER WEARING ALCOHOLICS
"AND COMPLAINING
ABOUT THEM TO YOU."
OR "I THINK WE SHOULD SEE OTHER PEOPLE"
MEANS "HA, HA, I ALREADY AM."
AND EVERYBODY KNOWS THIS.
OH, YEAH... CUSHIONS THE BLOW.
LIKE WHEN YOU'RE A KID AND YOUR PARENTS PUT YOUR DOG TO SLEEP
AND THEY TELL YOU IT WENT OFF TO LIVE ON SOME FARM.
THAT'S FUNNY.
NO, BECAUSE OUR PARENTS ACTUALLY DID
SEND OUR DOG UP TO LIVE ON A FARM.
UH... ROSS?
WHAT, HELLO? THE MILNERS' FARM IN CONNECTICUT?
THE MILNERS HAD THIS UNBELIEVABLE FARM.
THEY HAD HORSES
AND RABBITS TO CHASE
AND...
OH, MY GOD, CHI CHI!
"SO HOW DOES IT FEEL KNOWING YOU'RE ABOUT TO DIE?"
"WARDEN, IN FIVE MINUTES MY PAIN WILL BE OVER
"BUT YOU'LL HAVE TO LIVE
WITH THE KNOWLEDGE THAT YOU SENT AN HONEST MAN TO DIE."
HEY, THAT WAS REALLY GOOD.
YEAH? THANKS, LET'S KEEP GOING.
OKAY.
"SO, WHAT DO YOU WANT FROM ME, DIMONE... HUH?"
"I JUST WANT TO GO BACK TO MY CELL
BECAUSE IN MY CELL I CAN SMOKE."
"SMOKE AWAY!"
I THINK THIS IS PROBABLY WHY
DIMONE SMOKES IN HIS CELL, ALONE.
WHAT?
RELAX YOUR HAND.
LET YOUR WRIST GO.
NOT SO MUCH.
WHOA.
HEY.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, TRY TAKING A PUFF.
RIGHT.
OKAY, NO, GIVE IT TO ME.
NO, NO, I'M NOT GIVING YOU A CIGARETTE.
DO YOU WANT TO GET THIS PART
OR NOT? HERE.
ALL RIGHT, NOW
DON'T THINK OF IT AS A CIGARETTE.
THINK OF IT AS THE THING
THAT HAS BEEN MISSING
FROM YOUR HAND.
WHEN YOU'RE HOLDING IT, YOU FEEL RIGHT, YOU FEEL COMPLETE.
DO YOU MISS IT?
NO, NOT SO MUCH.
ALL RIGHT, NOW WE SMOKE.
OH, MY GOD!
CHANDLER, GIVE ME THAT.
NO, NO, NO. YOU GOT YOUR OPTIONS.
YOU CAN SMOKE IT LIKE THIS...
CHANDLER...
OR YOU CAN JUST HOLD IT IN YOUR MOUTH AND SMOKE IT LIKE THIS.
CHANDLER, GIVE ME THE CIGARETTE.
GIMME, GIMME.
ALL RIGHT, YOU TRY.
THANK YOU. OKAY, HOW'S THIS?
OKAY, THAT'S NOT BAD.
YEAH?
ALL RIGHT, NOW, WHEN YOU'RE FINISHED
IT'S REALLY COOL IF YOU FLICK IT.
YOU KIND OF FLICK IT.
YOU FLICK IT.
THAT'S GOOD.
ALL RIGHT, YOU KEEP PRACTICING
AND, UH... I'LL GO PUT OUT THE SOFA.
I THOUGHT IT HAD TO DO WITH THE SIZE OF A GUY'S FEET.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
THEY SAY IT'S THE SAME AS THE DISTANCE
FROM THE TIP OF A GUY'S THUMB TO THE TIP OF HIS INDEX FINGER.
THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
CAN I USE EITHER THUMB?
I'D RATHER GO WITH THE FOOT THEORY.
ALL RIGHT, DON'T TELL ME, DON'T TELL ME.
DECAF CAPPUCCINO FOR JOEY.
COFFEE BLACK.
LATTE.
AND AN ICED TEA.
I'M GETTING PRETTY GOOD AT THIS.
EXCELLENT!
VERY GOOD.
GOOD FOR ME!
YOU OKAY, PHOEBE?
YEAH, NO, I'M...
IT'S NOT EVEN WORTH IT-- IT'S MY BANK.
WHAT DID THEY DO TO YOU?
IT'S JUST... OKAY.
I'M GOING THROUGH MY MAIL
AND I OPEN UP THEIR MONTHLY STATEMENT!
EASY!
OKAY, I KNOW.
AND THERE'S 500 DOLLARS EXTRA IN MY ACCOUNT.
OH, SATAN'S MINIONS AT WORK AGAIN.
YES, BECAUSE NOW I HAVE TO GO DOWN THERE AND DEAL WITH THEM.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT? KEEP IT!
IT'S NOT MINE. I DIDN'T EARN IT.
IF I KEPT IT, IT WOULD BE LIKE STEALING.
YEAH, BUT IF YOU SPENT IT, IT WOULD BE LIKE SHOPPING.
OKAY, OKAY, LET'S SAY I BOUGHT A REALLY GREAT PAIR OF SHOES.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT I'D HEAR WITH EVERY STEP I TOOK?
"NOT MINE, NOT MINE, NOT MINE."
EVEN IF I WAS HAPPY, AND SKIPPING, I'D HEAR
"NOT, NOT MINE, NOT, NOT MINE..."
WE'RE WITH YOU, WE GOT IT.
OKAY. I'D NEVER BE ABLE ENJOY IT.
IT WOULD BE LIKE THIS GIANT KARMIC DEBT.
CHANDLER, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
HEY! WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
OH, GROSS!
WHAT IS THIS?
I'M SMOKING, I'M SMOKING.
OH, I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU!
YOU'VE BEEN SO GOOD FOR THREE YEARS.
AND THIS IS MY REWARD.
HOLD ON A SECOND, ALL RIGHT?
JUST THINK ABOUT WHAT YOU WENT THROUGH THE LAST TIME YOU QUIT.
YOU KNOW WHAT? FORGET ABOUT YOU.
THINK ABOUT WHAT WE WENT THROUGH THE LAST TIME YOU QUIT.
OKAY, SO THIS TIME I WON'T QUIT.
PUT IT OUT!
I'M PUTTING IT OUT.
OH, NO! I CAN'T DRINK THIS NOW.
ALL RIGHT, I'M GOING TO GO CHANGE.
I'VE GOT A DATE.
WITH ALAN AGAIN?
HOW'S IT GOING?
IT'S GOING PRETTY GOOD, YOU KNOW.
HE'S NICE, WE'RE HAVING FUN.
SO WHEN DO WE GET TO MEET THE GUY?
LET'S SEE, TODAY IS MONDAY.
NEVER.
NO, NOT AFTER WHAT HAPPENED WITH STEVE.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
WE LOVED SCHTEVE.
SCHTEVE WAS SCHEXY.
SORRY.
LOOK, I DON'T EVEN KNOW HOW I FEEL ABOUT HIM YET.
JUST GIVE ME A CHANCE TO FIGURE THAT OUT.
WELL, THEN CAN WE MEET HIM?
MMM... NO... SCHORRY.
JOEY, JOEY...
LET IT GO.
I MEAN, WHY SHOULD I LET THEM MEET HIM?
I MEAN, I BRING A GUY HOME
AND WITHIN FIVE MINUTES THEY'RE ALL OVER HIM.
THEY'RE LIKE COYOTES PICKING OFF THE WEAK MEMBERS OF THE HERD.
LISTEN, AS SOMEONE WHO'S SEEN MORE THAN HER SHARE OF BAD BEEF
THAT IS NOT SUCH A TERRIBLE THING.
COME ON, NOW, THEY'RE YOUR FRIENDS
THEY'RE JUST LOOKING OUT AFTER YOU.
JUST WISH THAT ONCE I'D BRING A GUY HOME THEY ACTUALLY LIKED.
WELL, YOU DO REALIZE THAT THE ODDS OF THAT HAPPENING
ARE A LITTLE SLIMMER IF THEY NEVER GET TO MEET THE GUY.
I KNOW, I KNOW.
DO YOU MIND IF I WHIMPER A LITTLE BIT?
WHIMPER.
OKAY, I'M DONE.
LET IT GO, ROSS.
YEAH, WELL, YOU DIDN'T KNOW CHI CHI.
DO YOU ALL PROMISE?
YEAH, WE PROMISE.
WE'LL BE GOOD.
CHANDLER, DO YOU PROMISE TO BE GOOD?
YOU CAN COME IN
BUT YOUR FILTER TIPPED LITTLE BUDDY HAS TO STAY OUTSIDE.
HEY, PHEEBS.
"DEAR MS. BUFFAY:
"THANK YOU FOR CALLING ATTENTION TO OUR ERROR.
"WE HAVE CREDITED YOUR ACCOUNT 500 DOLLARS.
"WE'RE SORRY FOR THE INCONVENIENCE
"AND HOPE YOU'LL ACCEPT
"THIS FOOTBALL PHONE...
AS OUR FREE GIFT."
DO YOU BELIEVE THIS?
NOW I HAVE 1,000 DOLLARS AND A FOOTBALL PHONE.
WHAT BANK IS THIS?
OKAY, IT'S HIM.
WHO IS IT?
Alan.
CHANDLER, HE'S HERE!
DO I LOOK OKAY?
UH, ONE MORE BUTTON
OKAY.
CLOSED.
HOW ABOUT CLOSED. YEAH.
I DIDN'T KNOW.
YEAH.
OH, OKAY.
ALL RIGHT,PLEASE BE GOOD, OKAY?
DO YOU REMEMBER HOW MUCH YOU ALL LIKE ME?
HI, ALAN, THIS IS EVERYBODY.
EVERYBODY, THIS IS ALAN.
HI.
HI, ALAN.
I'VE HEARD SCHO MUSCH ABOUT ALL YOU GUYS.
I'LL CALL YOU TOMORROW. THANKS.
OKAY... OKAY, LET'S LET THE ALAN BASHING BEGIN.
WHO'S GOING TO TAKE THE FIRST SHOT? HMM?
COME ON!
I'LL GO.
LET'S START WITH THE WAY HE KEPT PICKING AT...
YOU KNOW, I'M SORRY, I CAN'T DO THIS.
WE LOVED HIM.
WE LOVED HIM!
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT SOMEONE
THAT I'M GOING OUT WITH?
YES!
THAT PIMENTO TRICK?
I WILL NEVER LOOK AT AN OLIVE THE SAME WAY AGAIN.
AND DID YOU NOTICE?
YOU KNOW WHAT WAS GREAT?
THE WAY HIS SMILE WAS KIND OF CROOKED.
YES, YES, LIKE THE MAN IN THE SHOE.
WHAT SHOE?
FROM THE NURSERY RHYME:
"THERE WAS A CROOKED MAN WHO HAD A CROOKED SMILE
"WHO LIVED IN A SHOE FOR A... WHILE."
SO I THINK ALAN... WILL BECOME THE YARDSTICK
AGAINST WHICH ALL FUTURE BOYFRIENDS WILL BE MEASURED.
WHAT FUTURE BOYFRIENDS?
NO, I THINK THIS COULD BE...
REALLY?
OH, YEAH. I'D MARRY HIM
JUST FOR HIS DAVID HASSELHOFF IMPRESSION ALONE.
YOU KNOW I'M GOING TO BE
DOING THAT AT PARTIES, RIGHT?
YOU KNOW WHAT I LIKE MOST ABOUT HIM?
WHAT?
THE WAY HE MAKES ME FEEL ABOUT MYSELF.
YEAH. YEAH. YEAH. YEAH.
HI.
HOW WAS THE GAME?
WELL...
WE WON!
THANK YOU! YES!
FANTASTIC! I HAVE ONE QUESTION.
HOW IS THAT POSSIBLE?
ALAN.
HE WAS UNBELIEVABLE.
HE WAS LIKE THAT BUGS BUNNY CARTOON
WHERE BUGS IS PLAYING ALL THE POSITIONS
BUT INSTEAD OF BUGS IT WAS FIRST BASE, ALAN;
SECOND BASE, ALAN; THIRD BASE, ALAN.
I MEAN, IT WAS LIKE HE MADE US INTO A TEAM.
YEP, WE SURE SHOWED THOSE HASIDIC JEWELERS
A THING OR TWO ABOUT SOFTBALL.
CAN I ASK YOU GUYS A QUESTION?
DO YOU EVER THINK THAT ALAN IS MAYBE SOMETIMES...
WHAT?
I DON'T KNOW, A LITTLE TOO ALAN?
OH, NO, THAT'S NOT POSSIBLE.
ONE CAN NEVER BE TOO ALAN.
YEAH, IT'S HIS INNATE ALAN NESS THAT WE ADORE.
I PERSONALLY COULD HAVE A GALLON OF ALAN.
HEY, LIZZY.
HEY, WEIRD GIRL.
I BROUGHT YOU ALPHABET SOUP.
DID YOU PICK OUT THE VOWELS?
YES, BUT I LEFT IN THE "Y"s
BECAUSE YOU KNOW, "SOMETIMES Y..."
UM, I ALSO HAVE SOMETHING ELSE FOR YOU.
SALTINES?
NO, BUT WOULD YOU LIKE 1,000 DOLLARS AND A FOOTBALL PHONE?
WHAT?
OH, MY GOD!
OH, MY GOD, THERE'S REALLY MONEY IN HERE.
I KNOW.
WEIRD GIRL, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I WANT YOU TO HAVE IT. I DON'T WANT IT.
NO, NO, I HAVE TO GIVE YOU SOMETHING.
NO, IT'S FINE, YOU DON'T...
DO YOU WANT MY TINFOIL HAT?
NO, BECAUSE YOU NEED THAT.
NO, IT'S OKAY.
PLEASE, LET ME DO SOMETHING.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT, I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
YOU BUY ME A SODA, AND THEN WE'RE EVEN, OKAY?
OKAY.
KEEP THE CHANGE.
THANKS, LIZZY.
SURE YOU DON'T WANT A PRETZEL?
NO, I'M FINE, THANKS.
SEE YOU.
HUH!
A THUMB?
EWW!
I KNOW, I KNOW, I OPENED IT UP
AND THERE IT WAS JUST FLOATING IN THERE
LIKE THIS TINY LITTLE HITCHHIKER.
MAYBE IT'S A CONTEST, LIKE, COLLECT ALL FIVE.
DOES ANYONE WANT TO SEE?
NO!
OH, HEY, DON'T DO THAT.
PUT THAT OUT.
COME ON!
IT'S WORSE THAN THE THUMB.
HEY, THIS IS SO UNFAIR.
WHY IS IT UNFAIR?
SO I HAVE A FLAW.
BIG DEAL!
LIKE JOEY'S CONSTANT KNUCKLE CRACKING
ISN'T ANNOYING?
AND ROSS WITH HIS OVER PRONOUNCING EVERY SINGLE WORD;
AND MONICA WITH THAT SNORT WHEN SHE LAUGHS.
I MEAN
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT THING?
I ACCEPT ALL THOSE FLAWS.
WHY CAN'T YOU ACCEPT ME FOR THIS?
DOES THE KNUCKLE CRACKING BOTHER EVERYBODY OR JUST HIM?
WELL, I COULD LIVE WITHOUT IT.
OH, WELL, IS IT, LIKE, A LITTLE ANNOYING
OR IS IT LIKE WHEN PHOEBE CHEWS HER HAIR?
NOW, DON'T LISTEN TO HIM, PHEEBS.
I THINK IT'S END EARING.
OH, YOU DO, DO YOU?
YOU KNOW, THERE'S NOTHING WRONG WITH SPEAKING CORRECTLY.
INDEED, THERE ISN'T.
I SHOULD REALLY GET BACK TO WORK.
YEAH, OTHERWISE SOMEONE MIGHT GET
WHAT THEY ACTUALLY ORDERED.
OOH, WELL!
OH, HO, HO, THE HAIR COMES OUT AND THE GLOVES COME OFF.
DID YOU EVER GO OUT WITH A GUY
YOUR FRIENDS ALL REALLY LIKED?
NO.
OKAY. WELL, I'M GOING OUT
WITH A GUY MY FRIENDS ALL REALLY LIKE.
WERE WE TALKING ABOUT THE COYOTES HERE?
ALL RIGHT!
A COW GOT THROUGH!
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
IT'S JUST... YOU KNOW WHAT?
I JUST DON'T FEEL THE THING.
I MEAN, THEY FEEL THE THING, I DON'T FEEL THE THING.
HONEY, YOU SHOULD ALWAYS FEEL THE THING.
LISTEN, IF THAT'S HOW YOU FEEL ABOUT THE GUY, MONICA, DUMP HIM.
I KNOW, IT'S JUST GOING TO BE REALLY HARD.
YEAH, HE'S A BIG BOY, HE'LL GET OVER IT.
NO, HE'LL BE FINE.
IT'S THE OTHER FIVE I'M WORRIED ABOUT.
DO YOU HAVE ANY RESPECT FOR YOUR BODY?
DON'T YOU REALIZE WHAT YOU'RE DOING TO YOURSELF?
I'VE HAD IT WITH YOU GUYS AND YOUR CANCER
AND YOUR EMPHYSEMA AND YOUR HEART DISEASE.
THE BOTTOM LINE IS SMOKING IS COOL AND YOU KNOW IT.
CHANDLER... IT'S ALAN, HE WANTS TO SPEAK TO YOU.
REALLY, HE DOES?
HEY, BUDDY, WHAT'S UP?
OH, SHE TOLD YOU ABOUT THAT, HUH?
WELL, YEAH, I HAVE ONE NOW AND THEN.
WELL, YEAH, NOW.
WELL, IT'S NOT THAT...
WELL, THAT'S TRUE.
GEE, YOU KNOW, NO ONE'S EVER PUT IT LIKE THAT BEFORE.
SO, WELL, OKAY, THANKS.
GOD, HE'S GOOD.
IF ONLY HE WERE A WOMAN.
YEAH.
And Lamb Chop and Hush Puppy...
HOW OLD IS THAT SOCK?
IF I HAD A SOCK ON MY HAND FOR 30 YEARS
IT'D BE TALKING, TOO.
OKAY, I THINK IT'S TIME TO CHANGE
SOMEBODY'S NICOTINE PATCH.
HEY!
WHERE'S JOEY?
JOEY ATE MY LAST STICK OF GUM
SO I KILLED HIM.
DO YOU THINK THAT WAS WRONG?
I THINK HE'S ACROSS THE HALL.
THANKS.
THERE YOU GO.
OOH, I'M ALIVE WITH PLEASURE NOW.
HEY, PHEEBS, YOU GOING TO HAVE
THE REST OF THAT POP TART? PHEEBS?
DOES ANYONE WANT
THE REST OF THIS POP TART?
HEY, I MIGHT.
SORRY.
YOU KNOW, THOSE STUPID SODA PEOPLE GAVE ME
7,000 DOLLARS FOR THE THUMB.
7,000 DOLLARS?
AND ON MY WAY OVER HERE
I STEPPED IN GUM.
WHAT IS UP WITH THE UNIVERSE?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
NOTHING, I JUST THINK IT'S NICE
WHEN WE'RE ALL HERE TOGETHER.
EVEN NICER WHEN EVERYONE GETS TO WEAR THEIR UNDERWEAR.
UH, JOEY.
OH.
OH, OKAY.
PLEASE, GUYS
WE HAVE TO TALK.
WAIT, WAIT.
I'M GETTING A DEJA VU.
NO, I'M NOT.
ALL RIGHT, WE HAVE TO TALK.
THERE IT IS!
OKAY, IT'S ABOUT ALAN.
OH! SPEAKING OF WHICH, WOULD YOU TELL HIM WE'RE ON
FOR THE RENAISSANCE FAIRE NEXT WEEKEND.
GUYS, BEFORE YOU GET INTO THAT, THERE'S SOMETHING
THAT YOU SHOULD KNOW.
I MEAN, THERE'S REALLY NO EASY WAY TO SAY THIS.
I'VE DECIDED TO BREAK UP WITH ALAN.
IS THERE SOMEBODY ELSE?
NO, NO, NO, NO, IT'S JUST...
YOU KNOW, THINGS CHANGE, PEOPLE CHANGE.
WE DIDN'T CHANGE.
SO THAT'S IT? IT'S OVER?
JUST LIKE THAT?
YOU KNOW, YOU LET YOUR GUARD DOWN
YOU KNOW, YOU START TO REALLY CARE ABOUT SOMEONE
AND I JUST... I...
LOOK, I CAN GO ON PRETENDING...
OKAY.
NO.
THAT WOULDN'T BE FAIR TO ME
IT WOULDN'T BE FAIR TO ALAN, IT WOULDN'T BE FAIR TO YOU.
YEAH, WELL, WHO WANTS FAIR?
I MEAN, I JUST WANT THINGS BACK
YOU KNOW, THE WAY THEY WERE.
I'M SORRY.
OH, SHE'S SORRY.
I FEEL BETTER.
I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
I MEAN, WITH THE HOLIDAYS COMING UP.
I WANTED HIM TO MEET MY FAMILY.
I'LL MEET SOMEONE ELSE.
THERE'LL BE OTHER ALANS.
OH, YEAH, RIGHT.
ARE YOU GUYS GONNA BE OKAY?
HEY, HEY, WE'LL BE FINE.
WE'RE JUST GOING TO NEED A LITTLE TIME.
I UNDERSTAND.
WOW!
I'M REALLY SORRY.
YEAH. I'M SORRY, TOO.
BUT I GOT TO TELL YOU, I AM A LITTLE RELIEVED.
RELIEVED?
WELL, I MEAN, I HAD A GREAT TIME WITH YOU...
I JUST CAN'T STAND YOUR FRIENDS.
REMEMBER WHEN WE WENT TO CENTRAL PARK AND RENTED BOATS?
THAT WAS FUN.
YEAH.
HE COULD ROW LIKE A VIKING.
HI.
SO HOW'D IT GO?
UH... YOU KNOW.
DID... DID HE MENTION US?
HE SAYS HE'S REALLY GOING TO MISS YOU GUYS.
YOU HAD A ROUGH DAY, HUH?
YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
COME HERE.
THAT'S IT, I'M GETTING CIGARETTES.
NO, NO, NO!
I DON'T CARE.
GAME'S OVER, I'M WEAK. I'VE GOTTA SMOKE.
I'VE GOTTA HAVE THE SMOKE!
IF YOU NEVER SMOKE AGAIN
I'LL GIVE YOU $7,000.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.