WHAT AM I SITTING ON?
TOP OF THE WORLD?
DOCK OF THE BAY?
I'M OUT.
EW, UNDIES, OH!
ALL RIGHT.
WHOSE ARE THEY?
NOT MINE.
WELL, THEY'RE JOEY'S.
THEY GOT TO BE JOEY'S.
YEAH, THEY'RE MINE.
SEE, JOEY'S.
THEY'RE J J J J JOEY'S.
WHY ARE THEY HERE?
I DON'T KNOW, UH...
WELL, I'M JOEY.
YEAH, I'M DISGUSTING.
I TAKE MY UNDERWEAR OFF IN OTHER PEOPLE'S HOMES.
WELL, GET THEM OUT OF HERE.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
YEAH. YEAH.
TAKE THEM.
OH, I GOT...
JOEY, YOU CAN TOUCH THE EM.
THEY'RE YOUR UNDERWEAR.
CHANDLER, A WORD?
YEAH.
THAT'S IT.
I'M TIRED OF COVER ING FOR YOU TWO.
THIS HAS GOT TO STOP.
UGH!
AND TIGHTY WHITEYS?
WHAT ARE YOU, EIGHT?
THANK YOU, JOEY. THANK YOU SO MUCH.
WELL, HEY, NO, YOU'RE NOT WELCOME, OKAY?
LOOK, I HATE THIS.
YOU GUYS KEEP EMBARRASSING ME.
YESTERDAY, RACHEL FOUND YOUR RAZOR IN OUR BATHROOM.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY
SO I SAID IT WAS MINE AND... AND...
AND THAT I WAS PLAYING A WOMAN IN A PLAY.
AND, WELL, ONE THING LED TO ANOTHER AND...
WOW, AND AROUND THE ANKLES.
YOU KNOW, THAT IS A TOUGH SPOT.
YEAH, IT WAS.
ALL RIGHT, LISTEN, I CAN'T...
ALL THIS LYING HAS BEEN HARD ON US, TOO.
OH, YEAH, I BET ALL THE SEX MAKES IT EASIER.
WELL, YEAH, ACTUALLY.
MEANWHILE, I GET RACHEL SHOVING YOUR UNDERWEAR IN MY FACE
AND ASKING WHEN SHE COME SEE ME STAR IN UGLY WOMAN.
WE'LL TRY TO BE MORE CAREFUL, OKAY?
IT'S JUST THAT...
WE DON'T WANT EVERYONE TO KNOW
BECAUSE THIS IS GOING REALLY WELL.
AND MAYBE THE REASON
IT'S GOING REALLY WELL IS... IS BECAUSE IT'S A SECRET.
I KNOW IT SOUNDS REALLY WEIRD
BUT WE'RE JUST BOTH SO BAD AT RELATIONSHIPS.
WE ARE. HELP US.
ALL RIGHT.
BUT YOU DO IT WITH ME ONCE.
JOEY.
DIDN'T THINK SO.
CAN WE PLEASE JUST DROP THIS?
BUT I DON'T GET IT.
I MEAN, DOES ANYBODY ELSE
JUST TAKE OFF THEIR UNDERWEAR WHEN THEY'RE HOT?
HEY, PHOEBE.
HI, PHEEBS.
WHAT ARE YOU READING?
WUTHERING HEIGHTS.
I'M TAKING A LITERATURE CLASS AT THE NEW SCHOOL
AND I HAVE TO FINISH IT FOR THE FIRST SESSION TOMORROW.
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU WERE TAKING A CLASS. THAT'S SO COOL.
YEAH, WELL, I REALLY LIKED THAT LAMAZE CLASS I TOOK
YOU KNOW, AND I JUST THOUGHT THIS TIME
I'D GO FOR SOMETHING, YOU KNOW, A LITTLE MORE INTELLECTUAL
WITH A LESS PAINFUL FINAL EXAM.
HONEY, THAT SOUNDS LIKE FUN.
YEAH.
OH, YOU SHOULD COME WITH ME.
OH, YEAH, THEN I'LL HAVE SOMEONE TO SIT WITH.
OKAY.
YAY! OKAY.
BUT ARE YOU GOING TO HAVE TIME TO READ IT?
I READ THAT IN HIGH SCHOOL.
OH, THIS IS GOING TO BE SO MUCH FUN.
OKAY, SHH. I HAVE TO FINISH.
UH, W WAIT. WHAT TIME DOES THE CLASS START?
SH SH SHH!
HI.
WHAT'S WRONG, BUDDY?
SOMEONE AT WORK ATE MY SANDWICH.
WELL, WHAT DID THE POLICE SAY?
MY THANKSGIVING LEFTOVER SANDWICH.
I CAN'T BELIEVE SOMEONE JUST ATE IT.
ROSS, IT'S JUST A SANDWICH.
JUST A SANDWICH?
LOOK, I AM 30 YEARS OLD, OKAY?
I'M GOING BE DIVORCED TWICE, AND I JUST GOT EVICTED.
THAT SANDWICH WAS THE ONLY GOOD THING GOING ON IN MY LIFE.
SOMEONE ATE THE ONLY GOOD THING GOING ON IN MY LIFE.
THAT'S A NICE SWEATER VEST.
OKAY, LOOK, I HAVE ENOUGH STUFF
FOR ONE MORE SANDWICH.
I MEAN, I WAS GOING TO EAT IT MYSELF, BUT...
MON, TH THAT WOULD BE INCREDIBLE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
BUT I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE SOMEONE ATE IT.
I MEAN, LOOK, I LEFT A NOTE AND EVERYTHING.
"KNOCK KNOCK.
"WHO'S THERE?
"ROSS GELLER'S LUNCH.
"ROSS GELLER'S LUNCH, WHO?
ROSS GELLER'S LUNCH, PLEASE DON'T TAKE ME, OKAY?"
I'M SURPRISED YOU DIDN'T GO HOME WEARING YOUR LUNCH.
OKAY, LOOK
YOU WANT TO HOLD ON TO YOUR FOOD?
YOU'VE GOT TO SCARE PEOPLE OFF.
I LEARNED THAT LIVING ON THE STREET.
REALLY?
SO, WHAT WOULD YOU SAY, PHEEBS?
STUFF LIKE, UH, "KEEP YOUR MITTS OFF MY GRUB"?
SAY, ROSS, WHEN YOU PICTURE PHOEBE LIVING ON THE STREET
IS SHE SURROUNDED BY THE ENTIRE CAST OF ANNIE?
OKAY, THIS'LL KEEP THEM AWAY FROM YOUR STUFF.
OH. WHOA. JEEZ.
WHOA.
PHOEBE, YOU ARE A BADASS.
SOMEDAY, I'LL TELL YOU ABOUT THE TIME I STABBED A COP.
PHOEBE?
WHAT? HE STABBED ME FIRST.
SEE, THE BRONTE SISTERS WERE REALLY REMARKABLE WOMEN
FOR THEIR TIME.
THEY LIVED IN A PATRIARCHAL SOCIETY...
SORRY I'M LATE, BUT I LEFT LATE.
OKAY.
PHEEBS, WHAT IS THE BOOK ABOUT?
I THOUGHT YOU SAID YOU READ IT IN HIGH SCHOOL.
WELL, YEAH, BUT THEN I REMEMBERED I STARTED IT
BUT THEN THERE WAS THIS PEP RALLY
AND I WAS ON TOP OF THE PYRAMID.
ANYWAY, WHAT'S THE BOOK ABOUT?
OKAY, IT'S THIS TRAGIC LOVE STORY
BETWEEN CATHY AND HEATHCLIFF.
AND IT TAKES PLACE ON THESE REALLY CREEPY MOORS IN ENGLAND.
WHICH I THINK REPRESENT THE WILDNESS
OF HEATHCLIFF'S CHARACTER.
I TOTALLY GET SYMBOLISM.
HOW WOULD YOU CHARACTERIZE THE THEME OF THIS BOOK?
UH, LET'S SEE... RACHEL GREEN?
UH, WELL, I WOULD HAVE TO SAY
THAT IT'S A TRAGIC LOVE STORY
WELL, THAT'S SORT OF A GIVEN, BUT... YES.
ANYONE ELSE?
OH, OH, OH.
SYMBOLISM, A ND THE, UH...
WILDNESS OF THE MOORS
WHICH I THINK IS MIRRORED IN THE WILDNESS
OF HEATHCLIFF'S CHARACTER.
EXCELLENT.
WHAT RACHEL HAS SHREWDLY OBSERVED HERE
IS AT THE HEART...
YOU COMPLETELY STOLE MY ANSWER.
I THOUGHT IT WAS PRETTY OBVIOUS.
HOW WOULD YOU KNOW?
YOU DIDN'T EVEN READ IT.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
UH, YOU, IN THE BLUE SHIRT.
I THINK THAT YOURS IS A QUESTION
WITH MANY POSSIBLE ANSWERS.
WOULD YOU CARE TO VENTURE ONE?
ARE YOU JUST REPEATING WHAT I'M SAYING?
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S MOVE ON.
OKAY, THEN.
WHY DIDN'T YOU JUST SAY THAT YOU HADN'T READ THE BOOK?
BECAUSE I DIDN'T WANT HIM
TO THINK I WAS STUP ID.
I MEAN, THAT WAS REALLY EMBARRASSING.
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU.
PHOEBE?
YEAH?
PHOEBE, YOUR NOTE... AMAZING.
NOT ONLY DID NO ONE TOUCH MY SANDWICH
BUT PEOPLE AT WORK ARE ACTUALLY AFRAID OF ME.
A GUY CALLED ME "MENTAL."
"MENTAL" GELLER. YEAH.
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED A COOL NICKNAME LIKE THAT.
YEAH, THE BEST YOU GOT IN HIGH SCHOOL
WAS "WET PANTS GELLER."
IT WAS THE WATER FOUNTAIN, OKAY?!
ANYWAY...
PEOPLE ARE WRITING REPORTS FOR ME.
UH, PUSHING BACK DEADLINES TO FIT MY SCHEDULE.
I'M TELLING YOU, YOU GET TOUGH WITH PEOPLE
AND YOU CAN GET ANYTHING YOU WANT.
HEY, TRIBBIANI, GIVE ME THAT COFFEE, NOW.
THIS WAS REALLY FUN.
I'VE BEEN WONDERING IF YOU WERE EVER GOING TO ASK ME OUT.
SO YOU, UH, STILL WONDERING?
NO.
WE JUST WENT OUT.
YOU'RE SMART.
I LIKE THAT.
OH, CANDLES.
WHAT IS THAT, A BLANKET?
A VIDEO CAMERA?
OH, MY GOD!
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU THOUGHT
YOU WERE GOING TO VIDEOTAPE US HAVING SEX ON THE FIRST DATE.
HI.
JOEY, IS WHAT  SHE JUST SAID, UM...
OH, MY GOD.
YOU WERE ACTUALLY GOING TO...
WHAT IS GOING ON HERE?
AND WITH CHANDLER IN THE NEXT ROOM?
WHAT, ARE YOU SICK?
I'M JOEY.
I MEAN, I'M DISGUSTING.
I MAKE LOW BUDGET ADULT FILMS.
HUH.
YOU GUYS PROMISED
YOU'D BE MORE CAREFUL.
I MEAN, COME ON, THE GOOD JOEY NAME
IS BEING DRAGGED THROUGH THE MUD HERE.
WE'RE SO SORRY.
YEAH.
WELL, I'M TELLING EVERYONE ABOUT YOU.
IT'S THE ONLY  WAY
TO EXPLAIN THE UNDERWEAR, AND THE VIDEO CAMERA
THAT DOESN'T MAKE ME LOOK LIKE A PIG.
NO, WAIT. THERE'S GOT TO BE A BETTER EXPLANATION.
YOU... YOU COULD TELL THEM
THAT YOU HAD TO MAKE AN ADULT FILM
FOR YOUR... ADULT FILM CLASS.
YEAH, I LIKE THAT.
BUT, NO, HOW DOES THAT EXPLAIN
WHY RACHEL FOUND MY UNDERWEAR AT YOUR PLACE?
I DON'T KNOW.
WELL, GET READY TO COME OUT OF THE NON GAY CLOSET.
JUST WAIT, PLEASE--
I PROMISE WE'LL COME UP WITH SOMETHING.
JUST GIVE US A LITTLE MORE TIME.
ALL RIGHT.
HEY, BUT IT BETTER MAKE  ME LOOK REALLY, REALLY GOOD.
OH, AND ANOTHER THING.
THE VIDEO CAMERA?
NICE.
UM, ROSS, MAY I HAVE A WORD WITH YOU?
OH, OF COURSE, DONALD.
WE'VE BEEN GETTING REPORTS
OF SOME VERY ANGRY BEHAVIOR ON YOUR PART.
WHAT?
THREATENING LETTERS
REFUSAL TO MEET DEADLINES.
APPARENTLY PEOPLE NOW CALL YOU "MENTAL."
YEAH.
WE WANT YOU TO SPEAK TO A PSYCHIATRIST.
OH, NO, YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
UH, THIS IS SO SILLY.
UM, THIS IS ALL JUST BECAUSE OF A SANDWICH.
A SANDWICH?
YEAH. YOU SEE, MY...
MY SISTER MAKES THESE AMAZING TURKEY SANDWICHES.
HER SECRET IS, SHE PUTS AN EXTRA SLICE
OF GRAVY SOAKED BREAD IN THE MIDDLE.
I CALL IT THE "MOIST MAKER."
ANYWAY, I I PUT MY SANDWICH
IN THE FRIDGE OVER HERE, AND...
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I I I'M SORRY.
I I I BELIEVE I ATE THAT.
YOU ATE MY SANDWICH?
IT WAS A SIMPLE MISTAKE.
IT COULD HAPPEN TO ANYONE.
OH, OH, REALLY?
DID YOU CONFUSE IT WITH YOUR OWN TURKEY SANDWICH
WITH A MOIST MAKER?
NO, I...
DO YOU PERHAPS REMEMBER SEEING.
A NOTE ON TOP OF IT?
THERE MAY HAVE BEEN A JOKE
OR... LIMERICK OF SOME KIND...
THAT SAID IT WAS MY SANDWICH.
NOW, NOW, CALM DOWN.
COME LOOK IN MY OFFICE.
SOME OF IT MAY STILL BE IN THE TRASH.
WHAT?
WELL, IT WAS QUITE LARGE.
I HAD TO THROW MOST OF IT AWAY.
YOU, YOU, YOU...
YOU THREW MY SANDWICH AWAY?
MY SANDWICH?
MY SANDWICH?!
HI.
SO, UM WHAT'S THIS BOOK ABOUT?
YOU DIDN'T READ THIS ONE EITHER?
WELL, I WAS GOING TO
BUT I ACCIDENTALLY READ SOMETHING ELSE.
WHAT?
VOGUE.
OKAY, SO TELL ME ABOUT THIS JANE EYRE WOMAN.
NO, YOU SHOULD HAVE READ IT YOURSELF.
OH, COME ON, PHOEBE
DON'T BE SUCH A GOODY GOODY.
FINE.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
SO, JANE EYRE?
FIRST OF ALL, YOU'D THINK SHE'S A WOMAN
BUT SHE'S NOT.
SHE'S A CYBORG.
A CYBORG?
ISN'T THAT LIKE A ROBOT?
YEAH. THIS BOOK WAS LIGHT YEARS AHEAD OF ITS TIME.
SORRY, I'M LATE.
LET'S GET STARTED.
SO, WHAT DID EVERYBODY THINK OF JANE EYRE?
UM, RACHEL AND I WERE JUST DISCUSSING IT
AND SHE ACTUALLY HAD SOME VERY INTERESTING INSIGHTS.
WELL, GO AHEAD, RACHEL.
UM, THANK YOU, PHOEBE.
UM, WELL, WHAT STRUCK ME MOST
WHEN READING JANE EYRE WAS
UH, HOW THE BOOK WAS SO AHEAD OF ITS TIME.
IF YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT FEMINISM, I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT.
YEAH, WELL, FEMINISM, YES.
BUT ALSO, THE ROBOTS.
HEY.
HEY. OKAY...
SO, UM, SINCE THAT VIDEO CAMERA THING DIDN'T WORK OUT...
UM, I THOUGHT THAT I WOULD GIVE YOU JUST A LITTLE PREVIEW.
YOU'RE NAKED IN THIS PICTURE.
I KNOW.
OH, THAT'S ROSS.
ROSS?
HEY, CHANDLER.
MONICA?
ROSS, ARE YOU OKAY?
I'M FINE.
I SAW A PSYCHIATRIST AT WORK TODAY.
WHY?
ON ACCOUNT OF MY RAGE.
WHICH, IF I MAY SAY RIGHT NOW, IS OUT OF CONTROL.
HE GAVE ME A PILL FOR IT.
A PILL?
MM HMM.
WELL, WHEN THE PSYCHIATRIST TOLD ME
THAT I HAD TO TAKE A LEAVE OF ABSENCE
BECAUSE I YELLED AT MY BOSS
I STARTED TO GET WORKED UP AGAIN.
SO, HE OFFERED ME A TRANQUILIZER
AND I THOUGHT IT WAS A GOOD IDEA
SO I TOOK IT.
WAIT A MINUTE.
THEY'RE MAKING YOU TAKE TIME OFF WORK?
AND YOU'RE OKAY WITH THAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S GOING TO BE WEIRD NOT HAVING A JOB FOR A WHILE
BUT I... I DEFINITELY DON'T CARE ABOUT MY SANDWICH.
YEAH, YOU KNOW, I HATE IT
WHEN THEY MAKE ME SEE THE SHRINK AT MY OFFICE.
YOU KNOW, HE'S ALWAYS LIKE, "WHOA, MAYBE YOUR COLLEAGUES
WILL LIKE YOU BETTER IF YOU LIKE YOURSELF BETTER."
WHO NEEDS THAT?
YOU DO.
I KNOW.
UH, IT WAS JUST SO EMBARRASSING
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU JUST LET ME GO ON  AND ON AND ON LIKE THAT.
I'M SORRY.
IT WAS JUST SO FUNNY
WHEN YOU STARTED COMPARING JANE EYRE TO ROBOCOP.
THAT WAS NOT FUNNY.
WELL, I SNAPPED, OKAY?
YOU WEREN'T TAKING THE CLASS SERIOUSLY.
PHOEBE, COME ON, WHAT IS THE BIG DEAL?
I THOUGHT THIS WAS GOING TO BE SOMETHING WE COULD DO TOGETHER.
YOU KNOW, I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE FUN.
WELL, YEAH, FUN IS GOOD
BUT, YOU KNOW, I ALSO WANTED TO LEARN.
YOU KNOW, PEOPLE ARE ALWAYS
TALKING ABOUT WHAT THEY LEARNED IN HIGH SCHOOL
AND I NEVER WENT TO HIGH SCHOOL.
OH.
OH, SO YOU REALLY WANTED TO LEARN?
YEAH, YOU KNOW, PHEEBS, I JUST WANTED TO HAVE FUN.
YOU KNOW WHO YOU SHOULD GO WITH?
I KNOW! I KNOW! I KNOW!
MONICA, YOU ASKED THE QUESTION.
OH, YEAH.
AH, OH MY GOD! THAT'S MONICA!
OH, NO, NO.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
YOU GET AWAY FROM ME, YOU SICK, SICK, SICKO.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
JOEY HAS GOT A SECRET PEEPHOLE.
OH, NO, NO, NO.
YES. HE HAS A NAKED PICTURE OF MONICA.
HE TAKES NAKED PICTURES OF US.
THEN HE EATS CHICKEN AND THEN HE LOOKS AT THEM.
LOOK.
DUDE, THAT'S MY SISTER.
GIVE ME THAT.
ALL RIGHT, WAIT, JUST WAIT.
EVERYBODY JUST CALM DOWN, OKAY?
LET'S GIVE OUR FRIEND JOEY A CHANCE TO EXPLAIN
WHY HE'S SUCH A BIG PERVERT.
NO, I AM NOT A PERVERT, OKAY?
IT'S JUST, I JUST KIND OF...
OH LOOK, LOOK, I THINK I CAN EXPLAIN THIS.
THANK YOU.
JOEY'S A SEX ADDICT.
WHAT?! NO, I'M NOT.
IT'S OKAY. IT'S GOOD.
IT'S GOOD. IT'S A DISEASE.
NO, NO, I AM NOT A SEX ADDICT.
YES, YOU ARE.
THAT'S THE ONLY WAY TO EXPLAIN
ALL THIS STUFF.
NO, IT ISN'T. NO, IT'S NOT.
BECAUSE YOU COULD ALSO EXPLAIN IT WITH THE TRUTH.
WELL, WHAT  IS THE TRUTH?
YEAH.
YEAH, WHAT'S GOING ON?
I SLEPT WITH MONICA.
WELL, LET'S...
LET'S SEE WHAT EVERYBODY THINKS OF THAT.
OH, NO.
YOU SLEPT WITH MY SISTER?
UH, YES... BUT IT WAS...
WE JUST DID IT ONCE... IN LONDON.
THIS IS NOT GOOD FOR MY RAGE.
MONICA, IS THIS TRUE?
OF COURSE IT'S TRUE.
HOW ELSE WOULD YOU EXPLAIN ALL THE WEIRD STUFF
THAT'S BEEN GOING ON?
YES, IT'S TRUE.
OKAY, BUT IF IT ONLY HAPPENED
THAT ONE TIME, HOW COME WE FOUND
YOUR UNDERWEAR IN OUR APARTMENT THE OTHER DAY?
UH... OY.
THAT WAS THE UNDERWEAR
I WAS WEARING THAT NIGHT IN LONDON.
RIGHT, MONICA?
I GUESS I WANTED TO KEEP IT...
AS A SOUVENIR.
MY GOD, MONICA.
ARE YOU SURE, JOE?
ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE NOT JUST A SEX ADDICT?
NO, AND IF ANYONE'S
A SEX ADDICT HERE, IT'S MONICA.
YEAH, YEAH.
SHE HAS BEEN TRYING TO GET ME BACK IN THE SACK
EVER SINCE LONDON.
SO THAT'S  WHY SHE GAVE YOU
A NAKED PICTURE OF HERSELF.
THAT MAKES SENSE.
AND THE VIDEO CAMERA?
UH, MONICA?
I GUESS I SET UP THE VIDEO CAMERA
TO TRY AND ENTICE JOEY.
BUT, SADLY, I COULD NOT BE ENTICED.
OH, MONICA, THIS HAS TO STOP NOW.
I KNOW, I KNOW.
I KNOW. I WILL.
AND I WOULD APPRECIATE IT IF WE ALL COULD JUST, YOU KNOW
JUST DROP IT IMMEDIATELY. AND FOREVER.
OKAY.
THAT IS... IF YOU CAN RESIST ME.
I'LL GIVE  IT MY BEST SHOT.
WELL, GOOD LUCK.
THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE.
I MEAN, YOU REALLY KEPT JOEY'S UNDERWEAR?
WHY?
WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT?
I'M MONICA.
I'M DISGUSTING.
I STALK GUYS AND KEEP THEIR UNDERPANTS.
WELL, I THINK WE'VE ALL LEARNED SOMETHING
ABOUT WHO'S DISGUSTING AND WHO'S NOT.
HUH?
ALL RIGHT.
NOW... I'M GOING TO GET BACK TO MY BUCKET.
I'M ONLY EATING THE SKIN
SO THE CHICKEN'S UP FOR GRABS.
I REALLY THOUGHT YOU WERE MAKING A GOOD POINT
I MEAN, YOU KNOW, UNTIL YOU GOT CUT OFF.
I KNOW. WHAT'S UP WITH THAT GIRL MONICA?
I DON'T KNOW. I DIDN'T COME WITH HER.
HEY, EVERYBODY.
EVERYBODY, GUESS WHAT?
I JUST CONVINCED CARL TO GIVE US A TEST NEXT WEEK.
A TEST?!
OH, COME ON, TESTS MAKE US ALL BETTER LEARNERS.
OH, YEAH! WE SHOULD HAVE ESSAY QUESTIONS!