PHEEBS, COULD YOU GET THAT, PLEASE?
WHY? JUST BECAUSE YOU'RE TOO LAZY TO GET UP OFF YOUR TUSHY?
NO. NO, IT'S JUST THAT ALL THE PEOPLE
IN THE ENTIRE WORLD THAT I WOULD WANT TO TALK TO
ARE RIGHT HERE.
SUCKER.
HELLO.
HEY, JOEY.
Hey, Pheebs.
LISTEN, UH, CAN YOU DO ME A FAVOR?
I FORGOT THE PIN NUMBER TO MY ATM CARD.
CAN YOU GET IT FOR ME?
Sure. Where is it?
UH, I SCRATCHED IT ON THE ATM MACHINE DOWN ON THE CORNER.
OH, SO YOU'RE 5639?
THAT'S IT. THANKS, PHEEBS.
HEY.
OH, DO YOU WANT  TO TALK TO CHANDLER? IS THAT JOEY?
LET ME TALK TO HIM.
No.
BECAUSE HE DIDN'T BELIEVE IN MY MOVIE
WHICH IS A BIG MISTAKE, BECAUSE IT IS REAL. REAL.
HEY, TRIBBIANI, GET BACK TO WORK.
BREAK TIME'S OVER.
OKAY.
WHO WAS THAT?
UH, MY STUNT DOUBLE. YEAH, AND, YOU KNOW
HE'S GETTING A LITTLE TOO FAMILIAR FOR MY TASTE.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'VE BEEN TRYING TO APOLOGIZE TO HIM ALL WEEK.
IF HE'S NOT GOING TO LET ME DO IT ON THE PHONE
I'M GOING DOWN THERE. I'M GOING TO DO IT IN PERSON.
UH, PHEEBS, I HEARD THAT.
UH, CAN YOU PUT HIM ON?
YEAH.
HEY.
DON'T COME OUT HERE.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
I SUPPORT YOU 100%
AND I WANT TO PROVE THAT TO YOU IN PERSON.
I GOT THAT. I FORGIVE YOU.
DON'T COME OUT HERE.
YOU FORGIVE ME? YOU HAVEN'T BEEN TAKING MY CALLS FOR A WEEK.
WELL, I'M TOTALLY OVER IT, CHANDLER.
FRIENDS FOREVER.
DON'T COME OUT HERE.
WOULD YOU MIND DOING A PICTURE WITH US?
WH WHAT WAS THAT?
UH, ENTERTAINMENT TONIGHT.
Yeah. Okay, so...
GOOD TALKING TO YOU
AND DON'T COME OUT HERE. ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
MONICA?
I'M SORRY I'M LATE.
PHOEBE?
OH, PHOEBE
I'M SO SORRY. HAVE YOU BEEN HERE LONG?
IT'S OKAY.
WHAT THE HELL TOOK YOU SO LONG?
OKAY, YOU CANNOT TELL CHANDLER, OKAY?
BUT I RAN INTO RICHARD.
WHICH RICHARD?
THE RICHARD.
RICHARD SIMMONS? OH, MY GOD.
NO. MY EX BOYFRIEND, RICHARD.
YOU KNOW, THE TALL GUY, MUSTACHE?
OH, OKAY. THAT ACTUALLY MAKES MORE SENSE.
SO HOW WAS IT?
IT WAS REALLY NICE.
I MEAN, WE STARTED TALKING
AND I I ENDED UP HAVING LUNCH WITH HIM.
THAT IS SO WEIRD. I HAD A DREAM
YOU HAD LUNCH WITH RICHARD.
REALLY?
BUT AGAIN, RICHARD SIMMONS.
SO, GO ON.
ALL RIGHT, THE STRANGE PART WAS, HE WAS... HE WAS REALLY NICE
UM, AND HE LOOKS GREAT
BUT I DIDN'T FEEL ANYTHING AT ALL.
OOH. SO NOW, WHY CAN'T WE TELL CHANDLER?
OH, BECAUSE IT'LL TOTALLY FREAK HIM OUT
AND TOMORROW'S OUR ANNIVERSARY.
I JUST DON'T WANT ANYTHING TO SPOIL THAT.
OH. I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU GUYS HAVE LASTED A WHOLE YEAR. GOD! I KNOW.
WOW, I OWE RACHEL 20 BUCKS.
WHAT?
ON A TOTALLY DIFFERENT BET.
HEY.
IT'S ALMOST OUR ANNIVERSARY.
I KNOW.
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT? ONE YEAR AGO TODAY
I WAS JUST YOUR ANNOYING FRIEND, CHANDLER.
AW... NOW YOU'RE JUST MY ANNOYING FRIEND, CHANDLER.
HUH.
I GOT YOU A PRESENT.
OH, BUT IT'S NOT TILL TOMORROW.
I KNOW, BUT YOU HAVE TO OPEN IT TODAY.
OKAY.
OKAY! THERE YOU GO!
IT'S TWO TICKETS TO VEGAS!
WOW!
YEAH, FOR THIS WEEKEND!
OH, GOSH, IT'LL BE PERFECT.
YOU GET TO SEE JOEY.
PLUS, WE GET TO START OUR ANNIVERSARY CELEBRATION
ON THE PLANE.
WE CAN CALL IT OUR "PLANEIVERSARY."
DO WE HAVE TO?
NO.
OKAY, BUT THIS IS GREAT
BUT JOEY SAID HE DIDN'T WANT ANY OF US OUT THERE.
OH, HE JUST DOESN'T WANT US TO GO THROUGH ANY TROUBLE.
THINK HOW EXCITED HE'S GOING TO BE
WHEN WE GO OUT AND SURPRISE HIM.
PLUS, WE GET TO HAVE OUR OWN "ANNI VEGAS RY."
"ANNEVADA VERSARY"!
YEAH, I THINK WE SHOULD SEE OTHER PEOPLE.
BUT WE CAN GO, RIG YES.
OKAY. IT'S A GREAT IDEA.
OKAY, I'M GOING TO GO, TOO.
YOU KNOW WHAT, PHEEBS, IT'S KIND OF OUR ANNIVERSARY.
OH, PLEASE. YOU ARE NOT GOING TO DITCH ME AGAIN
LIKE YOU DID WITH LONDON.
DITCH YOU? PHOEBE, YOU WERE PREGNANT WITH TRIPLETS.
UH HUH, GREAT STORY. I'M GOING.
HI.
HEY. HEY!
HEY, YOU GUYS, LISTEN.
THIS WEEKEND WE'RE ALL GOING TO GO TO LAS VEGAS
TO SURPRISE JOEY--
INCLUDING ME!
DO YOU WANT TO GO?
WELL, I GUESS I COULD TAKE A COUPLE DAYS OFF WORK.
OF COURSE YOU COULD TAKE A COUPLE DAYS OFF WORK
BECAUSE THIS TRIP INCLUDES ME!
OH, NO. WAIT A MINUTE.
WAIT, I'VE GOT A PRESENTATION TOMORROW.
I CAN'T MISS THAT.
OH, I'VE GOT TICKETS TO THE VAN GOGH EXHIBIT.
I'VE BEEN WAITING, LIKE, A YEAR FOR THIS.
ART LOVER.
WHAT'D YOU SAY?
I SAID, "ART LOVER."
IS THAT SUPPOSED TO BE AN INSULT?
I DON'T KNOW. I'M VERY TIRED.
SO, RACH, MAYBE YOU AND I CAN FLY OUT TOGETHER SATURDAY.
THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
HUH? ALL RIGHT, I'LL CALL THE AIRLINES. OKAY. YEAH.
YEAH, YOU KNOW, THAT'LL BE NICE, ACTUALLY
TO HAVE THE APARTMENT TO MYSELF FOR A NIGHT.
OH, YEAH, SO YOU CAN WALK AROUND NAKED.
NO. SO I CAN BE BY MYSELF.
YOU KNOW, HAVE A LITTLE ALONE TIME.
UH HUH, NAKED ALONE TIME.
NO, PHOEBE. JUST BECAUSE I'M ALONE DOESN'T MEAN
I WANT TO WALK AROUND NAKED.
I MEAN, YOU LIVE ALONE.
YOU DON'T WALK AROUND NAKED.
UH HUH. WHY DO YOU THINK
IT TAKES ME SO LONG TO ANSWER THE DOOR?
SO, SO FAR, IS THIS TRIP TO LAS VEGAS BETTER OR WORSE
THAN THE TRIP TO LONDON?
SO FAR, IT'S PRETTY MUCH THE SAME, PHEEBS.
OKAY. WHAT ABOUT AFTER I GIVE YOU THESE CANDIES?
YEAH, I GUESS IT'S A LITTLE BETTER NOW.
HA HA.
OKAY, LAS VEGAS-- ONE; LONDON-- ZERO.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
OOH.
HAPPY "PLANEIVERSARY."
AW... I LOVE YOU.
CAN I GIVE YOU YOUR PRESENT NOW?
OKAY. OKAY.
OH, MAN. DON'T TELL ME I DID THIS.
I LOVE THE "I FORGOT THE PRESENT" FAKE OUT!
HOW DO YOU FEEL ABOUT THE "I REALLY DID FORGET THE PRESENT.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME" NOT FAKE OUT?
OH, HONEY, THAT'S OKAY. DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
YOU CAN GIVE IT TO ME WHEN WE GET BACK.
NO, THIS IS THE WORST THING
THAT CAN HAPPEN ON AN ANNIVERSARY EVER.
OH, GOOD, ALL RIGHT.
YOU DECIDED TO TELL HIM ABOUT THE RICHARD THING.
WHAT... WHAT "RICHARD THING"?
OH, NO.
WHAT "RICHARD THING"?
SIMMONS. GO WITH SIMMONS.
OKAY. I, UM... I RAN INTO RICHARD YESTERDAY
AND HE ASKED ME IF I WANTED TO GO FOR A BITE AND I DID.
AND THE ONLY REASON WHY I DIDN'T TELL YOU
IS BECAUSE I I KNEW YOU'D GET MAD
AND I DIDN'T WANT TO SPOIL OUR ANNIVERSARY.
I'M NOT MAD.
REALLY?
OH, YEAH. YEAH , SO YOU YOU BUM PED INTO RICHARD.
YOU GRABBED A BITE.
NO BIG DEAL.
GREAT.
OKAY, LONDON-- ONE.
THIS IS GOING TO BE A REAL HORSE RACE.
OOH!
HMM.
OH, LOOK WHAT HAPPENED.
HA, CHECK ME OUT.
I'M IN MY KITCHEN... NAKED.
I'M PICKING UP AN ORANGE.
I'M NAKED.
I'M LIGHTING THE CANDLES NAKED
AND CAREFULLY...
OH, MY GOD, THAT'S RACHEL NAKED!
I CAN'T LOOK AT THAT.
I AM LOOKING AT THIS.
OKAY, VIVID COLORS, EXPRESSIVE BRUSH STROKES...
UNLESS SHE WANTS ME TO BE LOOKING AT THAT.
SHE KNOWS I'M HOME.
SHE KNOWS I CAN SEE HER.
WHAT KIND OF GAME IS SHE PLAYING?
I THINK MAYBE SOMEONE'S LONELY TONIGHT.
OH, DR. GELLER, STOP IT.
YOU'RE BEING SILLY.
OR AM I?
?? I... Love to love you, baby ??
OW!
OW.
?? I... Love to love you, baby ??
??
?? Don't tell me again...
?? MMM... LOVE TO LOVE YOU, BABY ??
OW. DARN IT.
HEY.
MAY I COME IN?
UH, YEAH, IF YOU WANT TO.
DO YOU WANT ME TO?
YEAH, SURE?
SO DO I.
OKAY, RACH, BEFO RE ANYTHING HAPPENS
I JUST WANT TO LAY DOWN A COUPLE OF GROUND RULES.
THIS IS JUST ABOUT TONIGHT.
I DON'T WANT TO GO THROUGH WITH THIS
IF IT'S GOING TO RAISE THE QUESTION OF "US."
OKAY? I JUST WANT
THIS TO BE...
ABOUT WHAT IT IS.
AND, UM...
... W WHAT IS THAT, ROSS?
THE PHYSICAL ACT OF LOVE.
WHAT? ARE YOU CRAZY?
OH, SO SO YOU WEREN'T TRYING TO ENTICE ME JUST NOW
WITH YOUR, YOUR NAKEDNESS?
OH... GOD.
YOU SAW ME?
OH...
YOU WEREN'T TRYING TO ENTICE ME WITH YOUR NAKEDNESS.
NO, NO!
YOU THOUGHT... YOU ACTUALLY THOUGHT
I WANTED TO HAVE SEX WITH YOU?
OH, MY...
NO.
NO. NO...
NO, NO, NO, NO.
OH, WOW, I'M SORRY
BUT, ROSS, YOU KICKED OFF YOUR SHOES.
LOOK, C CAN WE JUST FORGET THIS EVER HAPPENED?
YES, OF COURSE , ABSOLUTELY.
YOU'RE RIGHT. I'M SORRY.
THANK YOU. YES.
ALL RIGHT, I GUESS I'M GOING TO GO PACK.
OKAY.
OH, WAIT, ONE MORE THING, UM... YES?
DO DO WE STILL NEED TO, UH, SETTLE THE QUESTION OF "US"?
??
?? MONEY, MONEY, MONEY, MONEY
?? MONEY ??
??
?? MONEY, MONEY, MONEY, MONEY
?? MONEY ??
?? MONEY, MONEY, MONEY, MONEY... ??
HEY, YOU GUYS, WAIT! YOU GUYS!
THIS PLACE IS SO MUCH BETTER THAN LONDON, OKAY?
THIS LADY, DRESSED LIKE CLEOPATRA
GAVE ME THIS COUPON--
99 CENT STEAK AND LOBSTER DINNER. HUH.
PHOEBE, YOU DON'T EAT ANIMALS.
FOR 99 CENTS I'D EAT YOU.
OKAY
I COULD TOTALLY SETTLE DOWN HERE.
IT'S GOT EVERYTHING I COULD EVER WANT.
INCLUDING JOEY. LOOK!
OH, LOOK. HEY!
OH, MY GOD.
HEY, JOEY!
HEY!
WOW. HI.
LOVE YOUR CONDOMS, MY MAN.
W WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING HERE?
I I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU NOT TO COME.
WHY ARE YOU DRESSED AS A GLADIATOR?
UH... BECAUSE...
I'M SHOOTING A SCENE RIGHT NOW.
YEAH, I, UH... I PLAY A GLADIATOR.
UH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
H HOLD ON A SECOND.
CAN WE CUT?!
YEAH, MY MY FRIENDS ARE HERE.
I'M GOING TO TAKE A LITTLE BREAK.
WHO WHO ARE YOU TALKING TO?
THE, UH...
DIRECTOR.
UH... HER.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
IT'S NOT A GLADIATOR MOVIE.
I WORK HERE.
WHY? WHAT HAPPENED?
WELL, THE MOVIE GOT SHUT DOWN
BECAUSE THEY RAN OUT OF MONEY
SO I'M WORKING HERE TILL IT STARTS UP AGAIN
IF IT EVER DOES.
OH, SUCH A DRAG. SWEETIE.
LOOK, I I'M SORRY I DIDN'T TELL YOU.
I'M SORRY, MAN.
NO, NO, IT'S OKAY. APPARENTLY THERE'S A NEW POLICY
WHERE WE DON'T HAVE TO SHARE EVERYTHING WITH EVERYBODY.
I KNEW YOU WERE NOT OKAY WITH THAT.
SO YOU'RE A GLADIATOR?
YEAH, WHAT WHAT'S GOING ON?
MONICA HAD LUNCH WITH RICHARD.
DAWSON?!
NO...
BUT THAT WOULD HAVE BEEN SO COOL.
NO, HER BOYFRIEND, RICHARD.
IT MEANT NOTHING, OKAY?
I MEAN, AFTER ALL THIS TIME
HOW CAN YOU NOT TRUST ME?
WHEN YOU GO LUNCHING WITH HUNKY MUSTACHE MEN
AND DON'T TELL ME ABOUT IT.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'M SORRY, I SHOULD HAVE TOLD YOU.
THANKS.
AW, THERE WE GO.
I LOVE VEGAS.
I PROMISE YOU, NEXT TIME
I ABSOLUTELY WILL TELL YOU.
NEXT TIME?
OOH, SO CLOSE. MM. MM.
THERE'S NOT GOING TO BE A NEXT TIME.
YOU CANNOT SEE HIM EVER AGAIN.
I CANNOT SEE HIM?
I MEAN, Y YOU CAN'T TELL ME WHAT TO DO.
OH, THAT'S SO FUNNY, BECAUSE I THINK I JUST DID.
OH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
IF YOU'RE GOING TO BE ACTING LIKE THIS ALL NIGHT?
I DON'T EVEN WANT TO BE AROUND YOU.
FINE WITH ME.
FINE. HAPPY ANNIVERSARY.
WHOA, GUYS, GUYS, PLEASE.
COME ON, COME ON, THIS IS OBVIOUSLY
JUST A BIG MISUNDERSTANDING.
NO, IT IS NOT.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
HEY, HEY! DON'T LOOK AT ME.
I JUST WORK HERE.
OKAY, UM... ROSS?
I'M I'M A LITTLE WARM
SO I'M GOING TO BE TAKING OFF MY SWEATER.
NOW, I'M I'M JUST LETTING YOU KNOW
THIS IS NOT AN INVITATION
TO THE PHYSICAL ACT OF LOVE.
YEP, THAT'S HILARIOUS.
I'M SORRY, I'M DONE. I'M DONE.
YOU KNOW, LAST NIGHT
WAS EMBARRASSING FOR YOU, TOO.
NO, NOT REALLY.
I MEAN, YOU'VE SEEN ME NAKED HUNDREDS OF TIMES.
UH HUH, BUT IT WAS A FIRST
FOR THE REST OF MY BUILDING.
I I JUST DON'T EMBARRASS THAT EASILY.
WHAT? YOU TOTALLY GET EMBARRASSED.
NO, I DON'T.
ROSS, I THINK I'M JUST A MORE SECURE PERSON
THAN YOU ARE.
IS THAT SO?
YEAH.
HEY, LADY!
I DON'T CARE HOW MUCH YOU WANT IT, OKAY?!
I AM NOT GOING TO HAVE SEX WITH YOU
IN THE BATHROOM!
HEY, YOU KNOW, IN ROMAN TIMES.
THIS WAS MORE THAN JUST A HAT.
REALLY?
YEAH, SURE, SURE.
THEY WOULD, UH, THEY WOULD SCRUB THE FLOORS WITH IT.
THEY WOULD, UH, USE IT TO GET THE MUD OFF THEIR SHOE
AND, UH, SOMETIMES
UNDERNEATH THE HORSE WOULD GET DIRTY
SO THEY WOULD STICK IT RIGHT IN THERE...
JOEY!
I CANNOT BELIEVE THIS IS HOW
I'M SPENDING MY ANNIVERSARY.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, I'LL TAKE YOU SOMEPLACE NICE THEN.
LOOK, A GUY TIPPED ME A HUNDRED BUCKS TODAY.
WHOA! YEAH, YEAH.
HE WAS PLAYING BLACKJACK
FOR, LIKE, AN HOUR , AND HE WON 5,000 DOLLARS.
DO YOU BELIEVE THAT? 5,000 DOLLARS.
YOU KNOW, IF I WON 5,000 DOLLARS, I'D JOIN A GYM.
YOU KNOW, BUILD UP MY UPPER BODY
AND HIT RICHARD FROM BEHIND WITH A STICK.
WAIT A MINUTE.
WHY DON'T I JUST DO WHAT THAT GUY DID?
I'LL TAKE THIS HUNDRED DOLLARS, TURN IT INTO 5,000 DOLLARS
AND THEN I'LL TURN THAT INTO ENOUGH MONEY
TO GET MY MOVIE GOING AGAIN.
GOOD LUCK.
CHANDLER, I DON'T NEED LUCK.
I HAVE THOUGHT THIS THROUGH.
I SEE.
?? Danke schoen ??
??
?? Darling, danke schoen...
THANK YOU.
THANKS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
THIS IS, LIKE, THE WORST NIGHT EVER.
YOU KNOW, MONICA, YOU'VE HAD A MINOR SETBACK
IN YOUR RELATIONSHIP WITH CHANDLER.
BIG DEAL. IT'S ONLY CHANDLER.
I AM SO SORRY.
THIS IS CRAZY.
I MEAN, IT WAS SUCH A STUPID ARGUMENT.
I DON'T EVEN WANT TO SEE RICHARD AGAIN.
SO GO FIX IT.
GO FIND CHANDLER.
HE'S PROBABLY UP IN YOUR ROOM.
TELL HIM THAT YOU'RE SORRY AND THAT YOU LOVE HIM.
YOU KNOW WHAT? YOU'RE RIGHT, PHOEBE. YOU'RE RIGHT.
THANK YOU.
SURE.
YEAH! LAS VEGAS-- NUMBER ONE!
?? ...DANKE SCHOEN ??
?? THANK YOU FOR SEEING ME AGAIN... ??
DID ANYBODY LOSE THIS?
COMING OUT.
PLACE YOUR BET.
DICE ARE OUT.
YO, 11.
PAY THE FRONT LINE.
?? DANKE SCHOEN ??
?
?? DANKE SCHOEN, MY DARLING... ?
HMM.
SO, UH...
I'M ON MY WAY BA CK TO THE BATHROOM.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT, JUST KEEP WALKING, ALL RIGHT?
OOH...
ROSS, WHAT ARE YOU...?
I'M SORRY, SIR.
I JUST... I THINK HE JUST REALLY LIKES YOU.
OH!
HEY, YOU KNOW
THAT TEACHER WHO HAD A BABY WITH HER STUDENT?
HEY, WHAT THE...?! WHAT...?
HI.
YES, MAY I HELP YOU?
YES, I'M SORRY.
DO YOU HAVE ANY EXTRA PANTS?
UH, MY FRIEND SEEMS TO HAVE HAD A LITTLE "ACCIDENT."
CAN I CHANGE 100 DOLLARS
CHANGING 100 DOLLARS
GOOD LUCK, SIR.
THANKS.
THAT'S RIGHT.
THIRTEEN.
HIT ME.
OH, MAN!
WAIT.
CHANDLER, YOU ARE NOT GOING TO BELIEVE THIS.
I HAVE FOUND MY IDENTICAL HAND TWIN.
WHAT?
MY IDENTICAL HAND TWIN.
WHAT'S AN IDENTICAL HAND TWIN?
WHAT DOES IT SOUND LIKE?
IT'S A GUY WITH MY IDENTICAL HANDS.
IT WAS INCREDIBLE.
CHANDLER, THE DEALER'S HANDS WERE EXACTLY LIKE MINE.
IT WAS LIKE LOOKING AT MY HANDS IN A MIRROR.
ARE YOU SURE YOU WEREN'T
LOOKING AT YOUR HANDS IN A MIRROR?
DON'T YOU SEE WHAT THIS MEANS?
I CAN FORGET ABOUT THAT STUPID MOVIE.
I'M GOING TO BE A MILLIONAIRE.
HOW?
WELL, LOOK, I DON'T HAVE IT ALL WORKED OUT YET
BUT IT'S GOT TO MEAN BIG MONEY.
COME ON, IDENTICAL HANDS!
AGAIN I MUST GO BACK TO...
HOW?
THIS IS VEGAS, MAN.
PEOPLE WILL PAY TO SEE FREAKY STUFF.
OKAY...
HOW MUCH WOULD YOU PAY TO SEE THIS HAND TWICE?
HUH?
YOU KNOW, I I CAN'T REALLY PUT A PRICE ON THAT, JOE.
HEY, ARE YOU UNSUPPORTING ME AGAIN?
NO, NO.
I SUPPORT YOU 100% PERCENT.
I JUST DIDN'T... I DID N'T GET IT RIGHT AWAY.
YOU KNOW, NOW I'M CAUGHT UP.
IDENTICAL HAND TWINS.
IT'S A MILLION DOLLAR IDEA.
RIGHT?!
I KNOW, OKAY, ALL RIGHT!
WHAT'S THAT FOR?
OH, WELL, I GOT TO DOCUMENT THIS
BEFORE THAT DEALER GETS OFF HIS BREAK. I SEE.
HEY.
PHEEBS... YEAH?
I FOUND MY IDENTICAL HAND TWIN!
OH, YOU'RE SO LUCKY.
HEY.
SO, WHERE'S MONICA?