OKAY, GUYS, LISTEN.
DON'T FORGET THAT TOMORROW
IS THE DAY EMILY GETS MARRIED AGAIN
SO, WHATEVER WE DO
JUST TRY TO REALLY KEEP ROSS' MIND OFF OF IT.
OH, YEAH, GOOD IDEA.
HEY, MAN, WHAT'S UP?
OH, JUST THINKING ABOUT EMILY GETTING MARRIED TOMORROW.
OH, ROSS, LOOK! LOOK!
WHAT? WHERE?
RIGHT OVER THERE. RIGHT THERE.
LOOK, LOOK, LOOK.
WHAT AM I LOOKING AT?
SOMEBODY HELP ME OUT HERE.
HEY. HELLO.
HI. HOW ARE YOU?
MONICA, SORRY I DIDN'T COME BY LAST NIGHT.
I WAS OUT WITH GARY.
HE LET ME RIDE AROUND WITH HIM IN HIS COP CAR.
WE SAW AND PREVENTED CRIMES.
YOU GOT TO GO ON A RIDE ALONG?
UH HUH.
I WANT TO GO ON A RIDE ALONG.
ME, TOO.
OKAY.
YEAH, ME, TOO.
REALLY? YOU?
YEAH.
I MEAN, IT'S KIND OF DANGEROUS.
WELL, I LIKE DANGER.
OKAY, YOU GUYS FREE TONIGHT?
YEAH. YEAH.
TONIGHT? Y YOU DIDN'T SAY
IT WAS GOING TO BE AT NIGHT TIME.
HEY. HEY.
OH, I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE HOME. I THOUGHT TONIGHT
WE COULD FINALLY ORGANIZE THESE PHOTOS.
OH, THANK GOD!
FINALLY!
OKAY.
I'VE BROKEN THEM DOWN INTO CATEGORIES, OKAY?
WE HAVE, UH, WE GOT HOLIDAYS, BIRTHDAYS, CANDIDS.
AND THEN WHAT I'VE DONE  IS
I'VE CROSS REFERENCED THEM BY SUBJECT, RIGHT?
SO IF YOU'RE LOOKING UP
LET'S SAY, "BIRTHDAYS" AND "DOGS"
YOU GET PHOTO 152. SEE?
OH, IT'S ME AND LAPOOH.
WOW, I MISS THAT DOG.
YOU CAN ALSO FIND HIM UNDER "DOG" AND "DEAD."
GREAT. THANKS.
ALL RIGHT.
HAND ME THAT OTHER BOX OF PHOTOS.
THAT'S THE VERY LAST ONE.
OKAY.
OOPS.
SORRY.
WELL, GOOD THING YOU NUMBERED ALL OF THEM, HUH?
I HADN'T. PHOTO 152 WAS A PROTOTYPE.
OH, HONEY, HONEY, HONEY, IT'S OKAY, IT'S OKAY.
HONEY, HOW ABOUT I FIX YOU A DRINK, HUH?
MAYBE A MARGARITA?
ROSS HAS THE BLENDER.
OH, EVERYTHING IS JUST FALLING APART.
NO, HONEY, IT'S OKAY.
LISTEN, I'LL GO TO ROSS', GET THE BLENDER.
YOU GET ALL THE MARGARITA STUFF READY.
HIS KEYS ARE IN THE DRAWER.
YOU KNOW WHAT? ALSO, I NEED SOME CASH.
YOU WANT ME TO STOP AT THE A.T.M.?
NO. WHILE YOU'RE AT ROSS', IF YOU SEE ANY LYING AROUND.
WHAT?
WHAT? I I I DON'T... I DON'T DO THAT.
THAT WAS SO COOL, MAN, THAT WAY YOU LEANED ON THAT GUY.
IT IS STARTING TO GET DARK OUT THERE.
HE TOLD YOU EVERYTHING.
I MEAN, YOU TOTALLY CRACKED HIM.
YEAH, WELL, BEING TH AT HE WAS THE VICTIM--
THEY'RE USUALLY PRETTY TALKATIVE.
OKAY, BUT IT IS OFFICIALLY NIGHTTIME.
ALL RIGHT, GARY, DO YOU WANT ME TO GRAB THE BERRY FOR YOU?
IT'S CALLED A CHERRY.
CHANDLER!
OKAY.
I GOT IT.
THIS PLACE MAKES THE BEST SANDWICH IN THE WORLD.
HEY, JOE, DOES IT HAVE MEATBALLS ON IT?
OH, YEAH.
YEAH? DOES IT HAVE MELTED CHEESE AND MARINARA SAUCY?
YUP.
YEAH, YOU CAN'T EAT THAT IN MY CAR.
YEAH, OKAY.
EVEN THOUGH MY TAX DOLLARS PAID FOR THIS CAR.
YOUR TAX DOLLARS?
YEAH, OKAY.
WOW, THAT SANDWICH REALLY DOES SMELL GOOD.
DID I SAY YOU COULD SMELL IT?
I CAN'T SMELL YOUR SANDWICH?
HALF THE TASTE IS IN THE SMELL.
YOU'RE SUCKING UP ALL THE TASTE UNITS.
OKAY, I'LL GIVE THEM BACK.
WHAT IS SO GREAT ABOUT THAT SANDWICH?
OKAY, IMAGINE THE BEST SEX YOU EVER HAD.
OKAY.
ARE YOU THINKING ABOUT MONICA?
YEAH.
YEAH? WHAT'S THAT LIKE?
OH, PLEASE DON'T BE FROM A REAL DINOSAUR.
PLEASE, PLEASE.
PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE. PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE.
"MADE IN MEXICO." YES!
OH. WHO WOULD BUY THIS?
OH.
Rach, it's me. Pick up.
HEY, WHAT'S UP?
I need a few more things to make the margaritas.
UM, I NEED SOME, UH, SOME SALT, SOME MARGARITA MIX, AND TEQUILA.
SO ALL WE HAD WAS ICE?
SEE IF HE HAS ICE.
OKAY.
Hello, Ross?
It's Emily here.
I know this is out of the blue, but, um
I'm getting married tomorrow.
Well... maybe I am.
I keep thinking about you
and I'm wondering if we made a mistake
giving up so fast.
Are you thinking about me?
No, of course you're not.
But if you are, call me tonight.
Okay, bye.
OH! OH!
SO, WHERE WE GOING NEXT?
THIS WITNESS WON'T RETURN MY CALLS
SO WE'RE GOING TO SEE
IF WE CAN SURPRISE HIM COMING HOME.
S SURPRISE HIM?
WE'RE NOT GOING TO MAKE ANYBODY MAD, ARE WE?
COME ON, MAN.
SO, YOU GOING TO SQUEEZE THE PERP'S SHOES A LITTLE BIT
BEFORE HE LAWYERS UP?
IT'S A WITNESS, NOT A PERP , AND NO ONE TALKS LIKE THAT.
YEAH, NO ONE TALKS LIKE THAT.
OH, WHAT? LIKE YOU'RE MR. COP?
HEY, I'M MORE COP THAN YOU TWO.
HOW DO YOU FIGURE THAT?
HELLO.
I'M IN THE FRONT SEAT, OKAY.
I'M GARY'S PARTNER.
YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU SAY "PARTNER"
IT DOESN'T SOUND COP.
IT SOUNDS GAY.
UM... JEALOUS.
HEY, DO YOU MIND?
WE'RE UNDERCOVER HERE.
OH, YEAH. NO PROBLEM.
ROSS.
SORRY, SORRY.
THERE.
HEY, GARY, WHO AM I?
PHONE HOME.
LOOK AT OFFICER ROSS
RIDING BACK HERE WITH THE VISITORS.
YEAH, WHAT'S UP WITH THAT, SERPICO?
WHAT'S UP WITH THAT, SERPICO?
Are you thinking about me?
No, of course you're not.
But if you are, call me tonight.
Okay, bye.
NO!
I KNOW.
WELL, THANK GOD YOU WERE HERE.
I MEAN, WE HAVE TO ERASE THAT.
WHAT? WE CAN'T DO THAT.
WE HAVE TO.
WHAT IF ROSS HEARS THAT, AND THEN CALLS HER BACK
AND THEN THEY  GET BACK TOGETHER?
IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT--
ROSS BACK WITH THAT CONTROLLING
NEUROTIC, CRAZY EMILY?
THE EMILY THAT WOULDN'T LET HIM SEE YOU?
NO! OH, NO. NO. GOD, NO.
HE SHOULD NOT GET BACK TOGETHER WITH HER.
I MEAN, I KNOW THAT, YOU KNOW THAT
EVEN ROSS KNOWS THAT.
BUT THAT STILL DOESN'T GIVE US THE RIGHT TO ERASE HIS MESSAGE.
LOOK, I'M HIS SISTER, OKAY? AND I LOVE HIM.
I DON'T WANT TO SEE HIM GET HURT.
COME ON, DOESN'T THAT
GIVE ME THE RIGHT TO CONTROL HIM...?
HELP HIM?
I DON'T THINK HE'S THE ONE WHO NEEDS HELP.
LOOK. SHE'S OBVIOUSLY UNSTABLE, OKAY?
SHE'S THINKING ABOUT RUNNING OUT ON HER WEDDING DAY.
OKAY, FINE.
BUT LOOK AT THE POSITION SHE'S PUTTING HIM IN.
WHAT'S HE'S GOING TO DO?
ROSS IS GOING TO RUN OVER THERE ON THE WEDDING DAY
AND BREAK  UP THE MARRIAGE?
WHO WOULD DO THAT?
OKAY, FINE. ALL RIGHT?
BUT, THAT'S, YOU KNOW, THAT WAS DIFFERENT.
ALTHOUGH IT DID INVOLVE A LOT OF THE SAME PEOPLE.
OH...!
THIS IS OBVIOUSLY
SOME TWISTED JOKE SHE'S TRYING TO PLAY ON HIM.
OKAY, YOU ARE CRAZY.
I'M SORRY, BUT SHE SOUNDED GENUINELY UPSET.
I MEAN, LISTEN.
Your messages have been erased.
NO!
WELL, THAT WORKED OUT WELL.
MARGARITA?
OKAY, BUT, YOU KNOW, W WE'RE SAFE, RIGHT?
I MEAN, NOTHING BAD IS GOING TOGO DOWN?
NO.
BUT THAT REMINDS ME-- SIGN THIS.
WHAT IS IT?
IT'S NOTHING.
IT SAYS YOU CAN'T SUE THE CITY
IF YOU SCRAPE YOUR KNEE
OR, YOU KNOW, GET YOUR HEAD BLOWN OFF.
OH, HURRY UP.
I WANT TO SIGN THAT.
OKAY, HERE HE COMES.
WHAT IS HE DOING?
WHAT THE HELL IS HE DOING?
WHAT IS IT? IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
OKAY, HE SEES US. DON'T MOVE.
AND DON'T LOOK AT HIM.
HEY, IT'S OKAY.
IT WAS JUST A CAR BACKFIRE.
HEY, LOOK AT THAT.
YOU TRIED TO SAVE YOUR BUDDY.
YOU SEE THAT?
YOU SEE WHAT HE DID?
YOU OKAY, MAN?
UH HUH.
THANKS, JOEY.
UH, HELLO!
WHAT?
YOU ALL RIGHT?
I GUESS WE SHOULD GO.
NO. WAIT, WAIT.
OH, YEAH, RIGHT.
NO. MONICA...
MONICA, WE HAVE TO FIX THIS.
THERE'S NOTHING WE CAN DO.
YOU'VE ERASED THE MESSAGE.
YEAH, BUT MAYBE I COULD CALL HIS MACHINE
AND RE CREATE THE MESSAGE.
RIGHT? OKAY. UM...
HELLO, ROSS. THIS IS RACHEL... EMILY!
WOW. GOD!
WHAT IS IT WITH THOSE TWO NAMES?
UH... I JUST WANTED TO SAY
THAT I'M GOING TO BE GETTING MARRIED
TO... ANOTHER BRITISH PERSON...
AND, UM... I'M... I'M HAVING DOUBTS
AND SCONES AND...
OH, STOP IT!
I CAN'T REMEMBER WHAT SHE SAID.
YEAH,THAT'S THE PROBLEM WITH THIS PLAN.
ALL RIGHT, RACHEL, COME ON . THE MESSAGE IS ERASED.
THERE'S NOTHING WE CAN DO.
HE'S NEVER GOING TO FIND OUT ABOUT IT.
I COULD TELL HIM ABOUT IT.
LOOK, IF YOU'RE GOING TO BE TOTALLY RATIONAL ABOUT THIS
I CAN'T ARGUE WITH YOU.
ALL RIGHT?
FINE. IF YOU WANT TO TELL HIM, TELL HIM.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO BE A PART OF IT.
OH! MAYBE THAT'S EMILY CALLING BACK
TO LEAVE THE EXACT SAME MESSAGE.
Hey, Ross, it's you.
I just want you to remember this feeling.
You are lucky to be alive
so live every day to the fullest.
Love yourself, okay? Okay.
Oh, and also, get stamps. Bye.
WOW. PLAY THAT MESSAGE FOR EMILY
AND THIS WHOLE PROBLEM GOES AWAY.
OH, RIGHT.
HEY, ANYBODY WANT TO MEET A HERO?
JOHN GLENN IS HERE?
NO. JOEY.
JOEY'S NEVER BEEN IN OUTER SPACE.
PHEEBS, WE HAD THE MOST INCREDIBLE NIGHT.
OKAY, SO, WE'RE IN THE CAR...
WAIT, HOLD ON.
HI. HI.
OKAY, GO AHEAD.
OKAY, OKAY
SO WE'RE IN THE CAR, RIGHT?
AND BANG! A SHOT WAS FIRED
AND JOEY, WITH NO REGARD FOR HIS OWN SAFETY
THROWS HIMSELF ON ME.
MY GOD, JOEY.
IT WAS A CAR BACKFIRE.
YEAH, BUT HE DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
YEAH, I DIDN'T KNOW THAT.
AND IT COULD HAVE JUST AS EASILY HAVE BEEN A BULLET.
HEY, JOEY, EVER THINK ABOUT JOINING THE FORCE?
WE COULD USE A GUY LIKE YOU.
WHO JUMPS AT LOUD NOISES.
WOW.
I COULD HAVE DIED TONIGHT.
YEAH, IF THE CAR THAT BACKFIRED HAD RUN OVER YOU.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M GOING TO GO HOME BEFORE ROSS STARTS RAMBLING
ABOUT HIS NEWFOUND RESPECT FOR LIFE.
I DO HAVE A NEWFOUND RESPECT FOR LIFE.
OH, MY GOD.
ROSS, I COULD HAVE TOLD YOU
YOU WEREN'T GO ING TO DIE TODAY.
WHAT? YOU KNOW WHEN I'M GOING TO DIE?
SWEETHEART, YOU WANT TO GET SOME DINNER?
SURE. YEAH.
OH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
IF I HEARD A SHOT RIGHT NOW, I'D THROW MY BODY ON YOU.
OH, YEAH? WELL , MAYBE YOU AND I
SHOULD TAKE A WALK IN A BAD NEIGHBORHOOD.
OKAY. ALL RIGHT.
BYE.
BYE. BYE.
CUT IT OUT, ROSS.
I'D HATE TO HAVE TO SAVE YOUR LIFE
AND KICK YOUR  ASS IN THE SAME DAY.
DUDE?
HOW COME YOU TOOK OFF?
OH, JUST GOING FOR A WALK.
AROUND THE LIVING ROOM. WHATEVER.
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
NO. NO, I'M JUST TIRED.
YOU KNOW, FROM THE WALK.
OH. OKAY.
YOU DOVE IN FRONT OF ROSS.
ROSS.
THAT'S WHAT THIS IS ABOUT.
OH, MY GOD. YOU HATE ROSS.
I DON'T HATE ROSS.
OF COURSE YOU DO.
I SAVED HIM. YOU'RE MAD AT ME.
IT ALL ADDS UP.
YOU WANT ROSS  OUT OF THE PICTURE.
WHAT PICTURE?
I DON'T KNOW, BUT I DON'T LIKE WHAT I'M HEARING.
LOOK, I'M VERY GLAD THAT YOU SAVED ROSS FROM THE CAR BACKFIRE
BUT IT COULD HAVE BEEN A BULLET
AND, YOU KNOW, YOU DIDN'T TRY TO SAVE ME.
OH.
YOU'RE UPSET BECAUSE YOU THINK I CHOSE ROSS OVER YOU.
NO. I KNEW YOU COULD TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF.
YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, ROSS, HE NEEDS HELP.
HE'S NOT STREET LIKE US.
WHAT IT COMES DOWN TO
IS YOU WOULD RISK YOUR LIFE FOR ROSS
BEFORE YOU WOULD FOR ME.
THAT'S THE BOTTOM LINE.
N NO, NOT EXACTLY.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK. I...
I WASN'T TRYING TO SAVE ROSS
OKAY?
MY SANDWICH WAS NEXT TO ROSS.
ALL RIGHT?
I WA... I WAS TRYING TO SAVE MY SANDWICH.
FROM A BULLET?
I KNOW IT DOESN'T MAKE MUCH SENSE.
MUCH SENSE?
CHANDLER, IT WAS INSTINCT, OKAY?
I JUST WENT FOR IT.
SO YOU RISKED YOUR LIFE FOR A SANDWICH?
I KNOW IT SOUNDS CRAZY, BUT, CHANDLER
THIS IS THE GREATEST SANDWICH  IN THE WORLD.
SO YOU DIDN'T, UH, CHOOSE ROSS BEFORE ME?
NO. I WOULD NEVER DO THAT.
YOU'RE LIKE MY BROTHER.
REALLY?
YEAH. IN FACT
TO PROVE HOW MUCH YOU MEAN TO ME...
HERE.
THANKS.
WHOA! EASY. IT'S NOT A HOT DOG.
HOW GOOD IS THAT?
OH, YEAH.
SEE? MM HMM.
OH, DUDE, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I THOUGHT YOU WERE SHOWING ME HOW MUCH I MEAN TO YOU.
YEAH. WITH A BITE.
GEEZ!
HEY, HI.
RACH, WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU ARE IN OUR APARTMENT ALL THE TIME, OKAY?
THIS IS JUST A DROP IN THE BUCKET, MISTER.
YOU KNOW, IT DOESN'T MATTER.
THE IMPORTANT THING IS THAT YOU'RE HERE.
YOU'RE MY FRIEND, AND YOU'RE HERE.
HUH. OKAY. JUST A LITTLE SCARED.
WHAT'S GOING ON, ROSS?
THE MOST AMAZING THING HAPPENED TONIGHT.
I THOUGHT MY NUMBER WAS UP.
I HAD AN ACTUAL NEAR DEATH EXPERIENCE.
WHAT?! WHAT HAPPENED?
OKAY, OKAY, WE WERE ON THE RIDE- ALONG WITH GARY, RIGHT?
AND SOMEBODY TOOK A SHOT AT ME.
REALLY?
NO, A CAR BACKFIRED, BUT...
I THOUGHT SOMEBODY WAS TAKING A SHOT AT ME
AND, RACH, I, I SURVIVED.
AND I WAS FILLED WITH
THIS, THIS GREAT RESPECT FOR LIFE.
YOU KNOW, I WANT TO EXPERIENCE EVERY MOMENT.
I WANT TO SEIZE EVERY OPPORTUNITY.
I AM SEEING EVERYTHING SO, SO CLEARLY NOW.
BECAUSE A CAR BACKFIRED?
OKAY, WHY ARE YOU HERE?
WELL, I DON'T KNOW HOW THIS FITS INTO YOUR WHOLE SEIZING THING
BUT, UM, EMILY CALLED YOU TODAY.
YOU TALKED TO HER?
NO, SHE LEFT A MESSAGE.
BUT IT KIND OF GOT ERASED.
I MEAN, THERE'S...
SOMETHING WRONG WITH YOUR MACHINE.
OKAY, WHAT DID SHE SAY?
WELL, UM, SOMETHING
ABOUT HAVING SECOND THOUGHTS ABOUT THE WEDDING
AND DID YOU GUYS MAKE A MISTAKE BREAKING UP, AND, UH...
SHE WANTS YOU TO CALL HER.
WOW.
NOW THAT WAS A GOOD THING THAT I TOLD YOU, RIGHT?
HUH? YEAH. YES.
OF COURSE.
OKAY, THANK YOU.
THANK YOU, BECAUSE
I'M GOING TO JUST GO TELL MONICA THAT I WAS RIGHT.
BECAUSE YOU KNOW WHAT?
SHE DIDN'T WANT... NOT IMPORTANT.
THE POINT IS, I WAS RIGHT.
YOUR DECISION.
OKAY? I WAS RIGHT.
RIGHT.
I GUESS I SHOULD CALL EMILY.
OKAY. NO, THAT'S NOT THE RIGHT DECISION.
THAT'S NOT RIGHT.
ROSS, COME ON.
I MEAN, THAT WOMAN MADE YOU MISERABLE.
OKAY, ROSS
DO YOU REALLY WANT  TO GET BACK INTO THAT?
OKAY, LOOK, YESTERDAY
I WOULDN'T HAVE EVEN CONSIDERED CALLING HER BACK
BUT MY EX WIFE CALLS
ON THE SAME DAY I HAVE A NEAR DEATH EXPERIENCE?
I MEAN, THAT'S GOT TO MEAN SOMETHING, RIGHT?
ROSS, THAT WAS NOT A NEAR DEATH EXPERIENCE.
THAT WAS BARELY AN EXPERIENCE.
YOU WEREN'T THERE.
OKAY, MAYBE THIS IS SOMETHING
THAT I AM... I'M SUPPOSED TO SEIZE, YOU KNOW?
OKAY. YOU KNOW WHAT?
MAYBE THIS IS NOT ABOUT SEIZING STUFF.
MAYBE THIS IS ABOUT ESCAPING STUFF.
OKAY, I MEAN , LOOK AT TODAY.
I MEAN, YOU ESCAPED...
DEATH...
YOU KNOW?
AND MAYBE THIS IS A CHANCE FOR YOU TO ESCAPE
GETTING BACK TOGETHER WITH EMILY.
THAT DOES MAKE SENSE.
BECAUSE I DO
WANT TO SEIZE SOME OPPORTUNITY
BUT I REALLY DON'T WANT TO SEE OR TALK TO HER.
WELL, THEN THERE YOU GO.
YEAH.
YEAH, MAYBE TODAY'S JUST...
CLOSE CALL DAY.
HEY, THANKS, RACH.
OH, HONEY, NO PROBLEM.
OKAY. WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
THE MESSAGE IS BLINKING.
MAYBE YOU DIDN'T ERASE IT.
OH?
Hey, Ross, it's you.
OH, YEAH.
THAT'S AN OLD MESSAGE.
NOBODY NEEDS TO HEAR THAT.
HEY, UM, WAS MONICA HERE?
YEAH.
YEAH, I WANT MY MONEY BACK.
YEAH, UM, YOU PROBABLY NEED THAT FOR STAMPS, RIGHT?
HEY, PHEEBS...
HAS GARY EVER BEEN SHOT AT FOR REAL?
YES, ONCE.
YEAH.
A LITTLE.
HE KIND OF DID IT TO HIMSELF.
IT'S NOT REALLY A GOOD STORY.
I WONDER HOW I'D REACT UNDER FIRE, YOU KNOW?
AND NOT BACKFIRE, BUT HEAVY FIRE.
LIKE IF I WAS IN A WAR OR SOMETHING.
MAN, I WOULD BE GREAT IN A WAR.
I MEAN, I THINK I WOULD MAKE A FANTASTIC MILITARY LEADER.
I MEAN, I KNOW I WOULD MAKE GENERAL
BEFORE ANY OF YOU GUYS.
BEFORE OR AFTER YOU WERE SHOT BY YOUR OWN TROOPS?
I KNOW WHERE JOEY WOULD BE.
HE'D BE DOWN IN THE FOXHOLE
PROTECTING ALL OF US.
YES, IF THE FOXHOLE WAS LINED WITH SANDWICHES.
YEAH, HERO SANDWICHES.
YOU ALL KNOW THAT I'M A PACIFIST
SO I'M NOT INTERESTED IN WAR IN ANY WAY.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
WHEN THE REVOLUTION COMES, I WILL HAVE TO DESTROY YOU ALL.
NOT YOU, JOEY.