ALL RIGHT, HERE WE GO.
1999. THE YEAR OF JOEY.
YEAH.
WE'RE VERY HAPPY FOR YOU.
WHAT'S T HE MATTER?
WE WANTED TO KISS AT MIDNIGHT, BUT NOBODY ELSE IS GOING TO
.
SO, YOU KNOW..
ALL RIGHT. I'LL TAKE CARE OF IT.
JOEY... IT'S 30 SECONDS TO MIDNIGHT.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
WILL YOU JUST TRUST ME?
33... 32... 31...
ROSS! ROSS ! ROSS, LISTEN.
WHO ARE YOU KISSING AT MIDNIGHT, HUH, RACHEL OR PHOEBE?
WHAT? WELL, YOU GOT TO KISS SOMEONE. CAN'T KISS YOUR SISTER.
WELL, WHO'S GOING TO KISS MY SISTER?
CHANDLER. OH, MAN. REALLY?
DUDE, DUDE, WHO WOULD  YOU RATHER HAVE KISS YOUR SISTER, ME OR CHANDLER?
THAT'S A GOOD POINT. YEAH.
UH, WELL SINCE I HAVE THAT WHOLE HISTORY
WITH RACHEL, I GUESS PHOEBE.
OKAY. GREAT.
PHEEBS! PHEEBS! LISTEN--
ROSS WANTS TO KISS YOU AT MIDNIGHT.
IT'S SO OBVIOUS.
WHY DOESN'T HE JUST ASK?
RACH... RACH, LISTEN.
I'M GOING TO KISS YOU AT MIDNIGHT.
00:00:53,053 -> 00:00:54,054
WHAT? EVERYONE'S GOT TO KISS SOMEONE.
CAN'T KISS ROSS. YOU GOT THE HISTORY.
SO? SO, WHO WOULD YOU RATHER
HAVE KISSING YOU, ME OR CHANDLER?
OH, GOOD POINT.
YEAH.
THREE... TWO... ONE...
HAPPY NEW YEAR!
HAPPY NEW YEAR.
HAPPY NEW YEAR, PHEEBS. YOU, TOO.
HAPPY NEW YEAR, JOEY.
SO, THAT DO ANYTHING FOR YOU?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M GOING TO GO OUT ON A LIMB
AND SAY NO DIVORCES IN '99!
YEAH, BABY!
BUT YOU'RE DIVORCE ISN'T EVEN FINAL YET.
JUST THE ONE DIVORCE IN 99S!
YEAH, BABY!
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I AM GOING TO BE HAPPY THIS YEAR.
I AM GOING TO MAKE MYSELF HAPPY.
DO YOU WANT US TO LEAVE THE ROOM OR...?
EVERY DAY, I AM GOING TO DO ONE THING
I HAVE NEVER DONE BEFORE.
THAT, MY FRIENDS, IS MY NEW YEAR'S RESOLUTION.
OOH! THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
YEAH.
MINE IS TO PILOT A COMMERCIAL JET.
OH...
THAT'S A GOOD ONE, TOO, PHEEBS.
NOW ALL YOU HAVE TO DO IS FIND A PLANELOAD OF PEOPLE
WHOSE RESOLUTION IS TO PLUMMET TO THEIR DEATHS.
MAYBE YOUR RESOLUTION SHOULD BE NOT TO MAKE FUN OF YOUR FRIENDS
ESPECIALLY THE ONES WHO MAY SOON
BE FLYING YOU TO EUROPE FOR FREE ON THEIR OWN PLANE.
SHE HAS A BETTER CHANCE OF SPROUTING WINGS
AND FLYING UP YOUR NOSE
THAN YOU DO OF NOT MAKING FUN OF US.
IN FACT, I'LL BET YOU 50 BUCKS YOU CAN'T GO THE WHOLE YEAR
WITHOUT MAKING FUN OF US.
YOU KNOW WHAT? BETTER YET-- A WEEK.
I'LL TAKE THAT BET, MY FRIEND.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
PAYING ME THE 50 BUCKS CAN BE THE "NEW THING" YOU DO THAT DAY.
AND IT STARTS RIGHT NOW.
ALL RIGHT, MY NEW YEAR'S RESOLUTION
IS TO LEARN HOW TO PLAY GUITAR.
REALLY? HOW COME?
WELL, YOU KNOW THOSE, UH, SPECIAL SKILLS
I HAVE LISTED ON MY RESUME?
WELL, I WOULD LOVE IT IF ONE OF THOSE WAS TRUE.
DO YOU WANT ME TO TEACH YOU? I'M A GREAT TEACHER.
OH, REALLY? WHO HAVE YOU TAUGHT?
WELL, I TAUGHT  ME AND I LOVED ME.
OH, THAT'D BE GREAT.
YEAH. THANKS, PHEEBS.
MY RESOLUTION IS TO BE LESS OBSESSED
WITH BEING NEAT AND CLEAN.
REALLY?
HUH...
NO!
OR SOMETHING ELSE.
OH, LOOK-- BLAIR FORGOT HER GLASSES
AND SHE'S GOING TO REALLY BE NEEDING THESE
TO KEEP AN EYE ON THAT BOYFRIEND
WHO, FROM WHAT I HEAR
NEEDS TO KEEP HIS STAPLER IN HIS DESK DRAWER
IF YOU KNOW WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
HEY, RACH, MAYBE YOUR RESOLUTION SHOULD BE
TO, UM... GOSSIP LESS.
I DON'T GOSSIP.
MAYBE SOMETIMES I FIND OUT THINGS
OR I HEAR SOMETHING AND I PASS THAT INFORMATION ON.
YOU KNOW, KIND OF LIKE A PUBLIC SERVICE.
DOESN'T MEAN I'M A GOSSIP.
I MEAN, WOULD YOU CALL TED KOPPEL A GOSSIP?
WELL, IF TED KOPPEL TALKED ABOUT
HIS COWORKER'S BOTCHED BOOB JOBS, YEAH, I WOULD.
THEY WERE LIKE THIS!
ALL RIGHT, OKAY, FINE.
FINE. MY NEW YEAR'S RESOLUTION WILL BE NOT TO GOSSIP.
IT'S EASY.
OH, EASY?
YOU HAVE NEVER KEPT A RESOLUTION.
YES, I HAVE.
OKAY, LET'S SEE HOW YOU DID LAST YEAR.
NO. NO, NOT MY DIARY.
NO, YOU CANNOT READ MY DIARY.
"DEAR DIARY, I'M SO EXCITED.
"MY RESOLUTION IS TO WRITE  IN YOU EVERY DAY.
I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW!"
NOTHING.
YOU KNOW, NOT A LOT HAPPENED LAST YEAR.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT, I WILL PROVE TO YOU
THAT I CAN KEEP IT THIS TIME.
NO MORE GOSSIPING.
I HATE GOSSIP.
IN JUNIOR HIGH, THIS GIRL SAID
A LOT OF MEAN STUFF ABOUT ME, AND I SET HER BIKE ON FIRE.
WOW, WHAT DID  SHE SAY ABOUT YOU?
SHE SAID I WAS CRAZY.
BUT I GUESS SHE GOT HERS, HUH? YAH HA!
I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW.
OKAY.
HEY.
HEY HEY.
I JUST ASKED THAT GIRL OUT.
NICE.
NICE... YEAH.
IS THAT PART OF YOUR RESOLUTION?
YOUR "NEW THING" FOR TODAY?
YES, IT IS.
SEE?
"ELIZABETH...
...HORNSWOGGLE"?
THAT'S RIGHT.
ELIZABETH... HORNSWOGGLE.
HORN... SWOGGLE?
YOU OKAY, CHANDLER?
IS THERE SOMETHING...?
SOMETHING FUNNY ABOUT THAT NAME?
NO. NO. I JUST THINK THAT MAYBE I'VE...
I'VE HEARD IT SOMEWHERE BEFORE.
OH, REALLY? WHERE?
SOMEWHERE FUNNY, I'LL BET.
HEY...
GUESS WHAT?
I HAVE A DATE WITH, UH...
ELIZABETH HORNSWOGGLE.
HORNSWOGGLE?
OH, THIS MUST BE KILLING YOU.
ALL RIGHT, SEE YOU LATER.
NOT REALLY.
I HAVEN'T TOLD YOU HER MIDDLE NAME.
WELL, DON'T-- JUST DON'T.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
SEE YOU.
ALL RIGHT, PHEEBS, I AM READY FOR MY FIRST LESSON.
OKAY.
OH, NO, NO.
YOU DON'T TOUCH THE GUITAR.
NO. NO. FIRST, YOU LEARN HERE.
THEN YOU LEARN HERE.
OH... OKAY.
OKAY--
LESSON ONE.
CHORDS.
NOW, UM, I DON'T KNOW THE ACTUAL NAMES OF THE CHORDS
UM, BUT I I I
MADE UP NAMES FOR THE WAY MY HAND LOOKS
WHILE I'M DOING THEM.
SO, THEN
THIS IS "BEAR CLAW."
"OKAY. UM, "TURKEY LEG...
AND "OLD LADY."
WHAT AN INTERESTING APPROACH TO GUITAR INSTRUCTION.
YOU KNOW, SOME MIGHT FIND IT AMUSING.
I, MYSELF, FIND IT REGULAR.
HEY, EVERYBODY. RACHEL WAS SO GOOD TODAY.
SHE DIDN'T GOSSIP AT ALL.
I DIDN'T. EVEN WHEN I FOUND OUT...
UM... ALL RIGHT...
WELL, LET'S JUST SAY
I FOUND OUT SOMETHING ABOUT SOMEONE
AND LET'S JUST SAY... SHE'S GOING TO KEEP IT.
HEY, PHEEBS.
CHECK THIS OUT.
OOH! YOU YOU NAILED THE "OLD LADY."
OH!
YEAH...
YEAH. LISTEN, SO--
I THOUGHT I WAS GETTING BETTER
SO, ON MY WAY HOME TODAY
I STOPPED BY THIS GUITAR STORE AND...
DID YOU DID YOU TOUCH ANY OF THE GUITARS
WHILE YOU WERE THERE?
DID YOU?
NO.
GIVE ME YOUR HANDS.
STRINGS.
GIVE IT.
PICK.
OH!
DO YOU WANT TO LEARN TO PLAY GUITAR?
YES.
THEN DON'T TOUCH ONE!
HI.
HI!
HI, BEN!
AUNTIE MONKIE!
ROSS IS WEARING LEATHER PANTS!
DOES NOBODY ELSE SEE THAT ROSS IS WEARING LEATHER PANTS?
SOMEONE! COMMENT ON THE PANTS!
I THINK THEY'RE VERY NICE.
I REALLY LIKE THEM.
YEAH. NICE STUFF.
NOT WHAT I HAD IN MIND.
SEE, PEOPLE LIKE ROSS
DON'T GENERALLY WE AR THESE TYPES OF PANTS.
YOU SEE, THEY'RE VERY TIGHT.
MAYBE THERE'S  SOMETHING IN THAT AREA.
THEY LOOK GOOD. I LIKE THEM.
WAY TO GO.
THEY LOOK GREAT.
WHERE DID  YOU GET THEM?
DAY SEE, I... I NEEDED A NEW THING FOR TO
BY AND THERE'S THIS LEATHER STORE I GO
THAT ALWAYS SMELLS SO GOOD.
AND I THOUGHT TO MYSELF, WOW.
YOU KNOW, I'VE NEVER OWNED
A REALLY GOOD SMELLING PAIR OF PANTS BEFORE.
OH, COME ON!
OKAY, SERIOUSLY, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
AWFUL. ABSOLUTELY AWFUL.
YEAH. AWFUL.
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
IT'S MY NEW YEAR'S RESOLUTION.
TO BLIND MY CHILD?
NO. TO TAKE MORE PICTURES OF ALL OF US TOGETHER.
I MEAN, I REALLY THINK IT'S THE BEST RESOLUTION
BECAUSE EVERYONE CAN ENJOY THE PICTURES.
WELL, EVERYONE WILL ENJOY MY MUSIC AS WELL.
OH, MY GOD.
THESE PANTS-- I'M BURNING UP.
SHE WANTS TO SNUGGLE NOW?
WHAT? IS SHE TRYING TO KILL ME?
IT'S LIKE A VOLCANO IN HERE.
ARE YOU HOT?
NO.
OKAY. MUST JUST BE ME, THEN.
THAT WAS JUST THE PANTS ON THE COUCH.
UM, HEY, DO YOU DO YOU MIND IF I USE YOUR BATHROOM?
OH, GO AHEAD.
THANKS.
AH...
HEY!
MY FAVORITE PART'S COMING UP!
OKAY.
OH, MY GOD!
"TIGER."
"DRAGON."
"ICEBERG."
JOSEPH, DID YOU EVEN STUDY AT ALL LAST NIGHT?
YES. YES, I DID.
THEN DO "ICEBERG."
"G" SHARP.
"G" SHARP?
HAVE YOU BEEN STUDYING THE REAL NAMES OF THE CHORDS?
HAVE YOU?
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT? I I DIDN'T TOUCH A GUITAR!
NO, BUT YOU'RE QUESTIONING MY METHOD.
NO. I'M NOT QUESTIONING IT, PHOEBE.
I'M SAYING IT'S STUPID!
WHAT?
THANK YOU.
YOU KNOW, NONE OF MY OTHER STUDENT
THOUGHT I WAS STUPID!
YOUR OTHER STUDENT WAS YOU!
YEAH, WELL, YOU KNOW, MAYBE YOU JUST NEED  TO TRY A LITTLE HARDER.
MAYBE I NEED TO TRY A REAL TEACHER!
RIGHT HERE. HERE. ANDY COOPER.
HE TEACHES GUITAR.
AND LOOK. OOH, THERE'S A NICE PICTURE OF HIM
WITH A LITTLE KID, YEAH.
AND THE KID'S GOT A GUITAR!
FINE!
YOU GO LEARN FROM YOUR... QUALIFIED INSTRUCTOR!
BUT DON'T COME CRYING TO ME
WHEN EVERYONE IS SICK AND TIRED
OF HEARING YOU PLAY "BAD, BAD, LEROY BROWN."
?? BADDEST MAN IN THE WHOLE DAMN TOWN... ??
OH, FINE. TAKE HIS SIDE!
I can't wait to be with you.
I'll sneak over as soon as Ross picks up Ben.
I'll just tell Rachel
I'm going to be doing laundry for a couple of hours.
Laundry? Huh. Is that my new nickname?
You know what your nickname is, Mr. Big...
WOULD YOU STOP LOOKING AT ME LIKE THAT?
PHOEBE WAS A TERRIBLE TEACHER.
I WASN'T LEARNING ANYTHING FROM HER.
LOOK, I FEEL BAD... AW, FORGET IT.
WE'RE GOING AROUND IN CIRCLES.
AW, GO ON, ON.
HELLO.
JOEY, IT'S ROSS. I NEED SOME HELP.
UH, CHANDLER'S NOT HERE.
WELL, YOU CAN HELP ME.
OKAY.
LISTEN, I'M IN ELIZABETH'S BATHROOM...
NICE.
NO, I GOT REALLY HOT IN MY LEATHER PANTS
SO I TOOK THEM OFF
BUT THEY MUST HAVE SHRUNK FROM THE SWEAT OR SOMETHING
OR MY LEGS EXPANDED FROM THE HEAT.
BUT I CAN'T GET THEM BACK ON, JOEY.
I CAN'T!
OH, THAT IS QUITE A SITUATION.
UH, DO YOU SEE ANY, LIKE, POWDER?
POWDER, YEAH, YEAH.
I HAVE POWDER.
Good, good, okay.
SPRINKLE SOME OF THAT ON YOUR LEGS.
IT WILL ABSORB SOME OF THE MOISTURE
AND THEN YOU CAN GET YOUR PANTS ON.
OKAY, HOLD ON.
THEY'RE NOT COMING ON, MAN.
UH... OH! OH! OKAY, CUT SLITS IN THE PANTS, RIGHT?
THEN PUT THEM BACK ON, GO OUT THERE
AND TELL HER YOU'RE THE INCREDIBLE HULK.
CHANDLER'S NOT THERE, HUH?
WELL, THAT WOULD HAVE WORKED, BUT ALL RIGHT, FINE.
UM, YOU SEE ANY... OH, VASELINE?
I... I SEE LOTION.
I HAVE LOTION.
WILL THAT WORK?
YEAH, SURE. THROW SOME OF THAT ON THERE.
Hold on.
SOUNDS LIKE IT'S WORKING.
THEY'RE STILL...
THEY'RE STILL NOT COMING ON, MAN.
AND THE LOTION AND THE POWDER HAVE MADE A PASTE.
REALLY?
UH, WHAT COLOR IS IT?
WHAT DIFFERENCE DOES THAT MAKE?
WELL, IF THE PASTE MATCHES THE PANTS
YOU CAN MAKE YOURSELF A PAIR OF PASTE PANTS
AND SHE WON'T KNOW THE DIFFERENCE.
JOEY, DO YOU HAVE A MINUTE?
DUDE, WHAT AM I...?
RACHEL'S HERE. SO GOOD LUCK, MAN.
LET ME KNOW HOW IT WORKS OUT.
OH, JOEY, I HAVE SUCH A PROBLEM.
WELL, YOUR TIMING COULDN'T BE BETTER.
I AM PUTTING OUT FIRES ALL OVER THE PLACE TODAY.
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY.
JOEY, I HAVE GOT TO TELL YOU SOMETHING.
WHAT? WHAT IS IT? WHAT IS IT?
OH, MY GOD, IT'S SO HUGE.
BUT YOU JUST HAVE TO PROMISE ME-
YOU CANNOT TELL ANYONE.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO. I DON'T WANT TO KNOW.
WHAT?
YES, YES, YES.
YOU DO WANT TO KNOW. THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE.
I DON'T CARE, RACH.
LOOK, I AM TIRED OF BEING THE GUY
WHO KNOWS ALL THE SECRETS AND CAN'T TELL ANYONE.
WHAT SECRETS? YOU KNOW SECRETS? WHAT ARE THEY?
AND YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO BE GOSSIPING.
I KNOW, I JUST CAN'T KEEP THIS ONE IN.
SO I PICK UP THE PHONE...
?? LA LA LA LA LA! ??
I'M NOT LISTENING TO YOU.
?? AH AH AH AH! ??
?? AH! ??
?? AH... LA LA LA LA! ??
ROSS, UM, YOU'VE BEEN IN THERE FOR A LONG TIME.
I'M STARTING TO GET KIND OF FREAKED OUT.
ALL RIGHT, I'M COMING OUT.
HEY, CAN YOU TURN THE LIGHTS OFF?
NO.
LET'S JUST LEAVE THE LIGHTS ON.
OH, MY GOD.
I HAD A PROBLEM.
HEY, PHEEBS.
OH, I CAN'T TALK TO YOU.
I DON'T HAVE A FANCY AD IN THE YELLOW PAGES.
LOOK, PHEEBS, I JUST...
I WANT TO APOLOGIZE.
FOR SAYING YOUR METHOD WAS STUPID
AND MAYBE...
ASK YOU TO BE MY TEACHER AGAIN?
AND AND I PROMISE I WON'T TOUCH A GUITAR
UNTIL YOU SAY I'M READY.
YOU REALLY THINK I'M READY?
UH HUH.
WOW. COOL!
OKAY.
WAS THE CHORD AT LEAST RIGHT BEFORE...?
NO.
OH, MY GOD!
WE HEARD ABOUT YOUR PANTS.
I'M SO SORRY.
THIS YEAR WAS SUPPOSED TO BE GREAT.
WELL, IT'S ONLY THE SECOND DAY
AND I'M A LOSER WITH STUPID LEATHER PANTS
THAT DON'T EVEN FIT!
NO, YOU'RE NOT A LOSER.
LOOK AT ME!
HEY, HEY, LOOK. LOOK, ROSS.
BEN DREW A PICTURE OF YOU.
HUH? YOU'RE A COWBOY.
OH.
BE BECAUSE OF THE LEATHER PANTS?
SEE? BEN DOESN'T THINK YOU'RE A LOSER.
HE THINKS YOU'RE A COWBOY.
I MEAN, THAT'S SOMETHING.
HOWDY, PARTNER. HEY HEY.
MAYBE I SHOULD GET ANOTHER PAIR.
OOH! YOU KNOW, THEY HAD SOME WITH, UH...
WITH FRINGE ALL DOWN THE SIDES.
PHEEBS, YOU MAY KNOW THIS-- YOU KNOW STRANGE THINGS--
WHAT IS THE BOILING POINT OF BRAIN?
I USED TO KNOW THIS.
I'M GOING TO GO KISS BEN GOOD NIGHT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HE THINKS I'M A COWBOY.
I WOULD MAKE A GOOD COWBOY.
OKAY, NOW THAT EVERYTHING'S WRAPPED UP HERE
I THINK I'M GOING TO GO DO MY LAUNDRY.
ME, TOO, YOU KNOW,  IF THIS SHIRT IS DIRTY.
YEP.
HEY, I'M GOING TO GO, TOO.
I'M GOING TO GO TO THE AIRPORT.
I FIGURE IF I HANG AROUND THERE LONG ENOUGH
SOMEONE'S BOUND TO LEAVE ONE OF THOSE PLANES UNATTENDED.
GOOD LUCK, HONEY. BYE.
WOW.
HEY, UH, JOEY, REMEMBER THAT BIG THING
I WAS GOING TO TELL YOU ABOUT?
OH, NO.
I'M NOT GOING TO TELL YOU
BUT IF YOU FOUND OUT ON YOUR OWN
THAT WOULD BE OKAY, AND THEN WE COULD TALK ABOUT IT, RIGHT?
WELL, THEN IT WOULDN'T BE A SECRET
SO, YEAH, THAT WOULD BE OKAY.
YEAH, YEAH.
YEAH.
HEY, UH, JOE, WOULD YOU MIND GOING OVER
INTO CHANDLER'S BEDROOM AND GETTING THAT BOOK BACK
THAT HE BORROWED FROM ME?
NOW? YOU WANT ME TO GO OVER THERE NOW?
HMM.
DO YOU KNOW SOMETHING?
I MIGHT KNOW SOMETHING.
I MIGHT KNOW SOMETHING, TOO.
WHAT'S THE THING YOU KNOW?
OH, NO, I CAN'T TELL YOU UNTIL YOU TELL  ME WHAT YOU KNOW.
I CAN'T TELL YOU WHAT I KNOW.
WELL, THEN, I CAN'T TELL YOU WHAT I KNOW.
OKAY, FINE.
YOU DON'T KNOW.
ALL RIGHT, HOW ABOUT I GO OVER THERE
AND I WILL WALK INTO CHANDLER'S BEDROOM
AND I WILL SEE THE THING THAT I THINK THAT I KNOW
IS ACTUALLY THE THING THAT I THINK THAT I KNOW.
YOU KNOW!
AND YOU KNOW!
YEAH, I KNOW!
CHANDLER AND MONICA?!
OH, THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE!
HOW LONG HAVE YOU KNOWN?!
TOO LONG!  OH, MY GOD, RACH!
I'VE BEEN DYING TO TALK TO SOMEONE ABOUT THIS
FOR SO LONG!
BUT LISTEN, LISTEN.
YOU CAN'T SAY ANYTHING TO ANYBODY.
THEY'RE SO WEIRD ABOUT THAT.
LISTEN...
HEY, PHOEBE!
HEY. IT'S RAINING.
I DON'T LIKE TO FLY IN THE RAIN, SO...
OH!
I AM GOING TO GO FOR A WALK IN THE RAIN.
OH, YEAH, ME, TOO.
THAT'S WEIRD.
I BET THEY'RE DOING IT.
OH, GOOD. OKAY, LOOK, I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE.
I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE, SO YOU WIN, OKAY? HERE.
PHEEBS, FLYING A JET?
BETTER MAKE IT A SPACESHIP
SO YOU CAN GET BACK TO YOUR HOME PLANET.
AND ROSS, PHONE CALL FOR YOU TODAY.
TOM JONES-- HE WANTS HIS PANTS BACK!
AND "HORNSWOGGLE"?
WHAT ARE YOU-- DATING A CHARACTER FROM FRAGGLE ROCK?
AHHHH!