OH, MONICA, THAT WAS THE BEST
THANKSGIVING DINNER EVER.
IT WAS SO GOOD.
I THINK YOU KILLED US.
I COULDN'T POSSIBLY EAT ANOTHER BITE.
I NEED SOMETHING SWEET.
DOES ANYONE WANT TO WATCH TV?
YEAH.
MONICA, YOUR REMOTE DOESN'T WORK.
PHOEBE, YOU HAVE TO LIFT IT AND POINT.
OH.
OH, FORGET IT.
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT WE SHOULD ALL DO?
WE SHOULD PLAY THAT GAME
WHERE EVERYONE SAYS ONE THING THAT THEY'RE THANKFUL FOR.
OH, I... I AM THANKFUL
FOR THIS BEAUTIFUL FALL WE'VE BEEN HAVING.
THAT'S SWEET, JOEY. VERY NICE.
YEAH, THE OTHER DAY I WAS AT THE BUS STOP
AND THIS LOVELY FALL BREEZE CAME IN OUT OF NOWHERE
AND BLEW THIS CHICK'S SKIRT RIGHT UP.
OH, WHICH REMINDS ME
I'M ALSO THANKFUL FOR THONGS.
I MEAN, IT'S NOT
SO MUCH AN UNDERPANT AS IT IS A FEAT OF ENGINEERING.
IT'S AMAZING
HOW MUCH THEY CAN DO WITH SO LITTLE MATERIAL
YOU KNOW, AND THE WAY THEY PLAY WITH YOUR MIND.
I MEAN, IS IT THERE? IS IT NOT THERE?
ARE YOU AWARE THAT YOU'RE STILL TALKING?
IS ANYONE THANKFUL FOR ANYTHING ELSE
BESIDES A THONG?
HUH, I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO PICK.
AM I MORE THANKFUL
FOR MY DIVORCE OR MY EVICTION?
WOW. SEE, AND I DIDN'T THINK
YOU'D BE ABLE TO COME UP WITH ANYTHING.
I'M SORRY, IT'S JUST THIS IS THE WORST THANKSGIVING EVER.
NO, NO, NO, NO. I AM THE KING OF BAD THANKSGIVINGS.
YOU CAN'T JUST SWOOP IN HERE WITH YOUR BAD MARRIAGE
AND TAKE THAT AWAY FROM ME.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO TELL THE WHOLE STORY
ABOUT HOW YOUR PARENTS GOT DIVORCED AGAIN, ARE YOU?
OH, GOD NO.
NO, NO, COME ON, I WANT TO HEAR IT.
IT WOULDN'T BE THANKSGIVING WITHOUT CHANDLER BUMMING US OUT.
SEE, IT'S A TRADITION LIKE THE PARADE...
IF THE PARADE DECIDED IT WAS GAY, MOVED OUT
AND ABANDONED ITS ENTIRE FAMILY.
NOW, CHANDLER, DEAR
JUST BECAUSE YOUR FATHER AND I
ARE GETTING A DIVORCE
DOESN'T MEAN WE DON'T LOVE YOU.
IT JUST MEANS
HE WOULD RATHER SLEEP WITH THE HOUSEBOY THAN WITH ME.
MORE TURKEY, MR. CHANDLER?
EVERY TIME YOU TELL THAT STORY
THAT GUY'S ACCENT GETS THICKER AND THICKER.
SO, ARE HE AND YOUR DAD STILL TOGETHER?
NO, NO, NO, AFTER THEY GOT THEIR OWN PLACE
THE HOUSEBOY GOT HIS OWN HOUSEBOY.
YOU SHOULD'VE HEARD HIS ACCENT.
YOU'RE RIGHT, YOURS IS WORSE.
YOU ARE THE KING OF BAD THANKSGIVINGS.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT.
I'VE GOT ONE THAT'S WORSE.
REALLY? WORSE THAN "MORE TURKEY, MR. CHANDLER?"
OH, DID THE LITTLE RICH BOY
HAVE A PROBLEM WITH THE BUTLER?
YES, MINE'S WORSE.
MORE BANDAGES! MORE BANDAGES!
PLEASE, CAN I GET SOME MORE BANDAGES IN HERE?!
THIS MAN IS DYING!
OH, NO.
IN THIS LIFE, PHOEBE.
OH, THIS LIFE.
OH, OKAY. NO, CHANDLER'S IS WORSE.
MAN, IT MUST BE SO COOL
REMEMBERING STUFF LIKE THAT.
I DON'T HAVE ANY PAST LIFE MEMORIES.
OF COURSE YOU DON'T, SWEETIE.
YOU'RE BRAND NEW.
I KNOW MONICA'S WORST THANKSGIVING.
LET'S NOT TELL THIS STORY.
OH, COME ON.
OH, NO. I KNOW, I KNOW.
IT'S THE ONE WHERE JOEY
GOT MONICA'S TURKEY STUCK ON HIS HEAD.
WHAT?
WHAT?!
JOEY GOT A TURKEY STUCK ON HIS HEAD?
HEY, IT'S NOT LIKE IT SOUNDS.
IT'S EXACTLY LIKE IT SOUNDS.
HELLO?
PHOEBE?
JOEY?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
OH, MY GOD!
I KNOW.
IT'S STUCK!
WELL... STEP.
HOW DID IT GET ONE?
I PUT IT ON TO SCARE CHANDLER.
OH, MY GOD!
MONICA'S GOING TO TOTALLY FREAK OUT.
WELL, THEN HELP ME GET IT OFF.
PLUS, IT SMELLS REALLY BAD IN HERE.
WELL, OF COURSE IT SMELLS BAD.
YOU HAVE YOUR HEAD UP A DEAD ANIMAL'S ASS.
OOH, OH. MONICA. OOH!
HEY.
HEY, DID YOU GET THE TURKEY BASTE...?
OH. OH, MY GOD!
OH, MY GOD!
WHO IS THAT?
IT'S JOEY.
WHAT? WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
AND IS THIS SUPPOSED TO BE FUNNY?
NO, IT'S NOT SUPPOSED TO BE FUNNY.
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE SCARY.
WELL, GET THAT OFF NOW.
I CAN'T. IT'S STUCK.
I DON'T CARE. THAT HAS TO FEED 20 PEOPLE AT MY PARENTS' HOUSE
AND THEY'RE NOT GOING TO EAT IT OFF YOUR HEAD!
HOLD ON, OKAY?
LET'S JUST ALL THINK.
OKAY, I GOT IT.
PHOEBE, YOU PULL.
I'M GOING TO SPREAD THE LEGS AS WIDE AS I CAN.
JOEY? YEAH.
NOW IS NOT THE TIME.
SORRY. RIGHT. SORRY.
OKAY, NOW COUNT TO THREE.
ONE, TWO, THREE.
IT WORKED.
I SCARED YOU.
I KNEW IT.
HA HA!
I'M OVER HERE, BIG GUY.
YEAH, YOU ARE.
YEAH, HA HA!
I SCARED YOU.
YOU YOU DID LOOK LIKE AN IDIOT.
HEY, I WASN'T THE ONLY ONE
WHO LOOKED LIKE AN IDIOT, ALL RIGHT?
REMEMBER WHEN ROSS TRIED TO SAY "BUTTERNUT SQUASH"
AND IT CAME OUT... "SQUATTER NUTBOSH"?
YEAH, THAT'S THE SAME.
WELL, THAT'S IT.
THAT'S MY WORST THANKSGIVING.
OH, WAIT. THAT CAN'T BE THE ONE
THAT RACHEL WAS TALKING ABOUT
BECAUSE SHE DIDN'T EVEN KNOW THAT THAT HAPPENED.
SO WHAT WAS IT?
YEAH, WHAT WAS IT?
I I REALLY DON'T WANT TO TELL THIS STORY.
OH, COME ON, MONICA.
RELIVING PAST PAIN AND GETTING DEPRESSED
IS WHAT THANKSGIVING'S ALL ABOUT.
YOU KNOW, FOR ME ANYWAY.
AND, OF COURSE, THE INDIANS.
LOOK, UM, OF ALL PEOPLE
YOU DO NOT WANT ME TO TELL THIS STORY.
WHAT IS THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
MONICA! I THINK RACHEL IS HERE.
I'LL GET IT!
HAPPY THANKSGIVING.
NOT FOR ME.
CHIP AND I BROKE UP.
WHY? WHY? WELL, WHAT HAPPENED?
OH, YOU KNOW HOW MY PARENTS ARE OUT OF TOWN
AND CHIP WAS GOING TO COME OVER.
YEAH, YEAH, AND YOU WERE GOING
TO GIVE HIM, YOU KNOW...
YOUR FLOWER.
OKAY, MONICA, CAN YOU JUST CALL IT "SEX"?
IT REALLY CREEPS ME OUT WHEN YOU CALL IT THAT.
OKAY, AND BY THE WAY, WHILE WE'RE AT IT
A GUY'S THING IS NOT CALLED HIS "TENDERNESS."
BELIEVE ME.
HI.
HI, RACHEL.
HAPPY THANKSGIVING.
HEY.
OH, HI.
UH... EVERYONE
THIS IS CHANDLER, MY ROOMMATE
AND LEAD SINGER OF OUR BAND.
ROSS.
OH, THIS IS MONICA.
HI, I'M ROSS'S LITTLE SISTER.
OKAY.
I'M SO GLAD YOU COULD COME, CHANDLER.
WE GOT PLENTY OF FOOD, SO I HOPE YOU'RE HUNGRY.
OH, MOM, CHANDLER HATES THANKSGIVING
AND DOESN'T EAT ANY THANKSGIVING FOOD.
OH, I'M SO GLAD YOU BROUGHT HIM HERE, THEN.
HEY, CHANDLER, UM... IF YOU WANT, I CAN MAKE YOU
SOME MACARONI AND CHEESE FOR DINNER.
WELL, AS LONG AS THE PILGRIMS DIDN'T EAT IT, I'M IN.
DAMN IT.
SO, UH... RACH...
DOES IT... DOES IT FEEL WEIRD AROUND HERE NOW?
YOU KNOW, SINCE I'VE BEEN AWAY AT COLLEGE?
OH. NO, NOT REALLY.
WELL, THAT'S COOL.
SO, DO...?
SO THAT'S RACHEL, HUH?
THE GIRL YOU'VE BEEN WRITING ALL THOSE SONGS ABOUT.
YEAH.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO RETHINK
THE LYRICS TO "SHE FEELS WEIRD SINCE I'VE BEEN GONE."
OH!
I CANNOT BELIEVE CHIP DUMPED ME
FOR THAT SLUT NANCY BRANSON.
I AM NEVER GOING OUT WITH HIM AGAIN, YOU KNOW.
I DON'T CARE HOW MUCH HE BEGS.
I THINK HIS BEGGING DAYS ARE OVER
NOW HE'S GOING OUT WITH NANCY BRANSON.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'VE JUST HAD IT WITH HIGH SCHOOL BOYS.
THEY'RE JUST... SILLY.
THEY'RE JUST SILLY, STUPID BOYS.
I'M GOING TO START DATING MEN.
UH, I'M SORRY, JUDY.
I COULDN'T FIND THAT BOWL YOU AND JACK WERE LOOKING FOR.
CALL THEM "MOM AND DAD," YOU LOSER.
MONICA!
HEY, CHANDLER...
DID YOU LIKE THE MACARONI AND CHEESE?
OH, YEAH. IT WAS GREAT.
YOU SHOULD BE A CHEF.
OKAY.
GUESS WHAT? ALL THAT STUFF
ABOUT NANCY BRANSON BEING A SLUT
WAS ALL A RUMOR, SO CHIP DUMPED HER
AND HE WANTS TO COME OVER TO MY HOUSE TONIGHT.
OH, THAT IS SO GREAT!
OH, GOSH, LIST EN.
IF YOU AND CHIP DO IT TONIGHT
PROMISE ME YOU'LL TELL ME EVERYTHING.
OH, TOTALLY, TOTALLY. YOU KNOW, IT'S NOT THAT BIG A DEAL.
WE ALREADY KIND OF DID IT ONCE, YOU KNOW.
I KNOW, BUT THIS TIME YOU'RE GOING.
TO DEFINITELY KNOW WHETHER OR NOT YOU DID IT.
I KNOW. OH, AND CHIP PROMISED
THAT THAT THIS TIME IT WOULD LAST
AT LEAST FOR AN ENTIRE SONG.
SO I'M THINKING OF ASK ING RACHEL OUT TONIGHT
YOU KNOW, MAYBE PLAYING HER THAT SONG
WE WROTE LAST WEEK.
"EMOTIONAL KNAPSACK"?
YEAH.
RIGHT ON.
OH, BUT DON'T TAKE TOO LONG, OKAY?
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, WE'RE GOING TO TEST OUT
OUR FAKE I.D.s TONIGHT, RIGHT, CLIFFORD ALVAREZ?
LISTEN, ROWLAND CHANG
IF THINGS GO WELL, I MAY BE OUT WITH HER ALL NIGHT.
DUDE, DON'T DO THAT TO ME.
NO, IT'S COOL.
YOU CAN STAY HERE.
MY PARENTS WON'T MIND.
NO, IT'S NOT THAT. I JUST DON'T WANT
TO BE STUCK HERE ALL NIGHT WITH YOUR FAT SISTER.
HEY.
MONICA, WHY DON'T YOU FINISH OFF THESE PIES?
I DON'T HAVE ANY MORE ROOM IN THE FRIDGE.
NO.
NO, THANK YOU.
WELL, JUDY, YOU DID IT.
SHE'S FINALLY FULL.
I CALLED YOU FAT?
I DON'T EVEN REMEMBER THAT.
MAYBE IT'D JOG YOUR MEMORY
IF YOU GUYS PLAYED A LITTLE BIT OF "EMOTIONAL KNAPSACK."
I'M SO SORRY.
I REALLY AM.
BUT, COME ON, I WAS AN IDIOT BACK THEN
I RUSHED THE STAGE AT A WHAM! CONCERT, FOR CRYING OUT LOUD.
OH, I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU CALLED HER FAT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU LET GEORGE MICHAELS SLAP YOU.
I AM REALLY SORRY.
THAT IS SO TERRIBLE.
I'M SO, SO SORRY.
ACTUALLY, YOU KNOW, THAT'S NOT
THE THANKSGIVING I WAS TALKING ABOUT.
YES, IT WAS.
NO, IT WASN'T. IT...
THANKSGIVING'S OVER.
LET'S GET READY FOR CHRISTMAS.
WHO WANTS TO GO GET
A CHRISTMAS TREE?
OOH, NO. I HAVE THE CUTEST CHRISTMAS STORY.
BUT WE WANT TO HEAR MONICA'S THANKSGIVING STORY.
FINE. ALL RIGHT.
MINE HAD A DWARF THAT GOT BROKE IN HALF
BUT, YOU KNOW, WHATEVER.
SO, RACHEL, YOUR MOM TELLS ME
YOU CHANGED YOUR MAJOR AGAIN.
WELL, YEAH, I HAD TO.
THERE WAS NEVER ANY PARKING BY THE PSYCHOLOGY BUILDING.
HI, RACHEL.
OH, HI.
WOW, LOVE YOUR NEW NOSE.
JACK...
WHAT? DR. WILSON'S AN ARTIST.
HE REMOVED MY MOLE CLUSTER.
WANT TO SEE?
I'LL GET IT.
NO. PLEASE LET ME.
HEY.
HEY. HEY.
HAPPY THANKSGIVING
HELLO.
GOD, YOUR HAIR SURE IS DIFFERENT.
YEAH, WE WERE JUST TALKING ABOUT THAT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HOW STUPID WE USED TO LOOK.
YEAH.
SO, UH, WHERE'S MONICA?
SHE'S UPSTAIRS.
MONICA, COME DOWN.
EVERYONE'S HERE--
ROSS, RACHEL AND THE BOY WHO HATES THANKSGIVING.
HI, CHANDLER.
OH, MY GOD.
W W WHAT'S THE MATTER
IS THERE... IS THERE SOMETHING ON MY DRESS?
YOU LOOK SO DIFFERENT, TERRIFIC.
THAT DRESS, THAT BODY.
DUDE.
SORRY.
YES, YES.
MONICA IS THIN. IT'S WONDERFUL
BUT WHAT WE REALLY WANT TO HEAR ABOUT
IS ROSS'S NEW GIRLFRIEND.
OH, MOM.
OKAY. UM, HER NAME IS CAROL
AND SHE'S REALLY PRETTY AND SMART
AND, UH, SHE'S... SHE'S ON THE LACROSSE TEAM
AND THE GOLF TEAM, CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
SHE PLAYS FOR BOTH TEAMS.
SO, CHANDLER, I GUESS I'LL SEE YOU AT DINNER.
DUDE.
SORRY.
OH, MY GOD. THAT WAS SO AWESOME.
YOU TOTALLY GOT HIM BACK FOR CALLING YOU FAT.
HE WAS JUST DROOLING ALL OVER YOU.
THAT MUST HAVE FELT SO GREAT.
WELL, IT DIDN'T.
WHAT?
YEAH. I MEAN, YEAH, I LOOK GREAT
AND, YEAH, I FEEL GREAT, AND, YEAH, MY HEART'S
NOT IN TROUBLE ANYMORE, BLAH, BLAH, BLAH.
I STILL DON'T FEEL LIKE I GOT HIM BACK, YOU KNOW?
I JUST WANT TO HUMILIATE HIM.
I WANT HIM TO BE LIKE NAKED AND I WANT TO POINT AT HIM
AND I WANT TO LAUGH.
OKAY.THAT WE MAY BE ABLE TO DO.
HOW?
WELL, GUYS TEND TO GET NAKED
BEFORE THEY'RE GOING TO HAVE SEX.
WHAT?!
I DIDN'T WORK THIS HARD A A AND LOSE ALL THIS WEIGHT
JUST SO I COULD GIVE MY FLOWER TO SOMEONE LIKE HIM.
OKAY, FIRST OF ALL, IF YOU KEEP CALLING IT THAT
NO ONE'S EVER GOING TO TAKE IT.
ALL AND THEN, SECOND OF
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO ACTUALLY HAVE SEX WITH HIM.
YOU'RE JUST GO ING TO MAKE HIM THINK THAT YOU ARE.
YEAH.
YEAH, AND THEN WHEN HE'S NAKED
I CAN THROW HIM OUT IN THE FRONT YARD
AND LOCK THE DOOR, AND THEN ALL THE NEIGHBORS
WILL JUST HUMILIATE HIM.
YEAH, AND THEN YOU WILL DEFINITELY GET HIM BACK.
HOW DO I MAKE HIM THINK I WANT TO HAVE SEX WITH HIM?
UH, HERE'S WHAT YOU DO.
JUST ACT LIKE EVERYTHING AROUND YOU TURNS YOU ON.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WELL, LIKE ANYTHING CAN BE SEXY, LIKE, UM...
OKAY, LIKE THIS... LIKE THIS DISH TOWEL.
OOH... OOH...
THIS FEELS SO GOOD AGAINST MY CHEEK.
AND IF I GET A LITTLE HOT, I CAN JUST DAB MYSELF WITH IT.
OR I CAN BRING IT DOWN TO MY SIDE
AND MAYBE RUN IT THROUGH MY FINGERS
WHILE I TALK TO HIM.
I CAN DO THAT. YEAH.
OKAY, GOOD, GOOD, GOOD.
HE'S COMING. HE'S COMING.
HEY, WHAT'S UP?
MONICA, I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU COULD MAKE ME
SOME OF THAT RIGHT EO US MAC 'N' CHEESE
LIKE LAST YEAR.
UH, I'D LOVE TO.
OOH... I LOVE MACARONI AND CHEESE.
I LOVE... I LOVE THE WAY THIS BOX FEELS
AGAINST MY CHEEK.
OKAY.
OH, AND I LOVE CARROTS.
OH...
SOMETIMES I LIKE TO PUT THEM BETWEEN MY FINGERS...
LIKE THIS, AND... AND... AND HOLD THEM DOWN HERE
WHILE I TALK TO YOU.
UM, AN AN AND YOU KNOW, IF I GET REALLY HOT?
UM, I I LIKE TO... PICK UP THIS KNIFE
AND... AND, UM, I PUT
THE... THE COOL STEEL AGAINST, UM... MY BODY.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
OH, YEAH, YEAH. I'M FINE. IT'S...
WHAT HAVE WE GOT HERE?
20 YEAR OLD MALE.
HE'S GOT A SEVERED TOE ON HIS RIGHT FOOT.
OW! OW!
COULD YOU PLEASE NOT DO THAT FEET FIRST?
YOU KNOW WHERE HIS INJURY IS.
SEVERED TOE. YOU JUST SAID IT.
SAYS HERE THE KNIFE WENT RIGHT THROUGH YOUR SHOE.
OF COURSE IT DID.
THEY'RE MADE OF WICKER.
DID YOU BRING THE TOE?
YES. I HAVE IT RIGHT HERE ON ICE.
"TOES ON ICE": COMING SOON
TO MADISON SQUARE GARDEN.
SAVE YOUR STRENGTH, MAN.
DON'T WORRY, SON, WE'LL JUST REATTACH IT AND THEN...
WHAT? WHAT IS IT?
YOU BROUGHT A CARROT.
WHAT?
THIS ISN'T YOUR TOE.
THIS IS A SMALL, VERY COLD PIECE OF CARROT.
YOU BROUGHT A CARROT?
OH, MY GOD.
THERE'S A TOE IN MY KITCHEN.
OH, I'M SORRY! I'LL GO BACK AND GET IT!
IT'S TOO LATE. ALL WE CAN DO IS SEW UP THE WOUND.
WITHOUT MY TOE?
I NEED MY TOE.
I CAN GO REALLY FAST.
DAD, GIVE ME THE KEYS TO YOUR PORSCHE.
OH, I'M NOT FALLING FOR THAT ONE.
THAT'S WHY I LOST MY TOE?
BECAUSE I CALLED YOU FAT?
I DIDN'T MEAN TO CUT IT OFF. IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
THAT'S WHY, FOR AN ENTIRE YEAR
PEOPLE CALLED ME SIR LIMPS A LOT?
I'M SORRY.
IT WASN'T YOUR WHOLE TOE.
YEAH, WELL, I MISS THE TIP.
IT'S THE BEST PART.
IT HAS THE NAIL.
CHANDLER...
SIR LIMPS A LOT-- I CAME UP WITH THAT.
YOU'RE A DORK.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
CHANDLER, I SAID I WAS SORRY.
WELL, SORRY DOESN'T BRING BACK
THE LITTLE PIGGY THAT CRIED ALL THE WAY HOME.
YOU KNOW, IT JUST FIGURES
THAT SOMETHING LIKE THIS WOULD HAPPEN TODAY.
I HATE THIS STUPID DAY AND EVERYTHING ABOUT IT.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
OH, WAIT, CHANDLER.
COME HERE. IS THERE ANYTHING I CAN DO?
ANYTHING?
YEAH, JUST... LEAVE ME ALONE FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
OH, OH, I'M A DUCK.
I GO, "QUACK, QUACK."
I'M HAPPY ALL THE TIME.
NICE TRY.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
LOOK, MONICA...
THIS IS NOT GOING TO WORK.
I BET THIS WILL WORK.
YOU ARE SO GREAT.
I LOVE YOU.
WHAT?
NOTHING. I SAID...
I SAID, "YOU'RE SO GREAT," AND THEN I JUST...
I JUST STOPPED TALKING.
YOU SAID YOU LOVED ME.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS IS.
NO, I DIDN'T.
YES, YOU DID.
YOU LOVE ME.
NO, I DON'T!
STOP IT! STOP IT!
GAUZE!
I NEED TO GET SOME GAUZE IN HERE!
CAN I PLEASE GET SOME MORE GAUZE?!
PHEW!
THIS IS GETTING RIDICULOUS, HUH?
OKAY. ALORS.