HEY. HEY.
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING UP?
OH, WE WANTED TO FINISH THE CROSSWORD
BEFORE WE WENT TO BED.
HEY, DO YOU KNOW A SIX LETTER WORD FOR RED?
DARK RED.
YEAH, I THINK THAT'S WRONG
BUT THERE'S A CONNECT THE DOTS IN HERE FOR YOU LATER.
OKAY.
HEY, HOW ABOUT MAROON?
YOU ARE SO SMART.
AH.
YOU GUYS ARE SO CUTE.
I KNOW.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL SEE YOU IN THE MORNING.
OKAY. OKAY.
YOU KNOW, I LOVE DOI NG CROSSWORD PUZZLES WITH YOU, HONEY.
AH. ME, TOO.
LET'S FINISH THIS AND GO TO BED.
OKAY.
THERE'S ONLY ONE LEFT.
THREE LETTER WORD...
NOT DOG, BUT..
CAT.
YES!
YOU ARE SO SMART.
I LOVE YOU.
I LOVE YOU, TOO.
THANKS.
UH...
WE STILL NEED A TIP.
ALL RIGHT.
HOLD ON.
I GOT IT.
NICKEL.
HOW MUCH MORE DO WE NEED?
COUPLE OF BUCKS.
OKAY, DIME.
YOU GUYS SHOULD PROBABLY KEEP TALKING.
THIS COULD TAKE AWHILE.
OH, NO, WAIT! LOOK IT!
WHOA!
OH, MY GOD.
THIS IS A POLICE BADGE.
OH, THAT'S SO COOL.
WHY WOULD A COP COME IN HERE, THOUGH?
THEY DON'T SERVE DOUGHNUTS.
YOU KNOW WHAT, ACTUALLY?
COULD YOU DISCOVER THE BADGE AGAIN?
I THINK I CAN COME UP WITH SOMETHING BETTER THAN THAT.
PHOEBE
I BET SOMEBODY'S MISSING THAT BADGE.
YEAH. I SHOULD PROBABLY TAKE IT BACK.
OOH, BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
WHILE I'M AT THE POLICE STATION
I COULD CHECK THEIR TEN MOST WANTED LIST.
BECAUSE MY FRIEND FRITZY'S BEEN NUMBER 11 FOR, LIKE, EVER
SO THIS COULD BE HER YEAR.
HEY, YOU GUYS.
HEY, JOEY.
HEY.
HI.
IS THAT, UH... IS THAT MY SWEATSHIRT?
OH, YES, IT IS.
I'M SORRY. I BORROWED IT.
I WAS COLD. I I HOPE IT'S OKAY.
UH, WELL, IT'S JUST THAT, UH...
YOU KNOW, IF YOU'RE GOING TO BE WEARING SOMEONE'S SWEATSHIRT
SHOULDN'T IT BE YOUR BOYFRIEND'S?
AND I'M NOT HIM.
I'M SORRY. I'LL GIVE IT BACK TO YOU.
NO, NO.
NO. IT'S GOING TO BE
ALL SMELLING LIKE MONICA.
ARE YOU SAYING I SMELL BAD?
NO, NO. YOU SMELL LIKE A MEADOW.
I'M SORRY. I...
WHAT'S WITH HIM?
OH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
THE LAST TIME THAT JOEY WENT TO A MEADOW
HIS MOTHER WAS SHOT BY A HUNTER.
HEY.
HEY, LOOK IT! LOOK WHAT I FOUND.
IT'S A POLICE BADGE.
WHAT'S THAT DOING HERE?
I DON'T SEE ANY DOUGHNUTS.
COPS AND DOUGHNUTS? COME ON.
OH, OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
IF CHANDLER HAD SAID IT, YOU'D ALL BE ON THE FLOOR.
COPS? DOUGHNUTS? ME?
OH!
YEAH, I STILL DON'T KNOW.
I'M SORRY. I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE I BOUGHT THE RIGHT COUCH.
I NEED A COUCH THAT SAYS
"KIDS WELCOME HERE"
BUT THAT ALSO SAYS...
"COME HERE TO ME."
WHAT?
YOU SAY THAT TO KIDS?
NO, NO, NO.
THE "COME HERE TO ME" IS...
YOU KNOW, FOR THE LADIES.
ROSS, HONEY, IT'S A NICE COUCH.
IT'S NOT A MAGIC COUCH.
YOU PICKED A GREAT COUCH.
YEAH?
YEAH. COULD YOU JUST SIGN RIGHT HERE, PLEASE?
OH, SURE. WHOA, WHOA. WHAT'S...?
THE DELIVERY CHARGE IS ALMOST AS MUCH AS THE COUCH.
WAIT, NO. THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
COME ON, HE LIVES THREE BLOCKS AWAY.
YEAH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'LL TAKE IT MYSELF, THANK YOU.
ALL RIGHT, RACH, COME ON. LET'S GO.
YEAH.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
NO, COME ON. IT'S ONLY THREE BLOCKS.
IT'S NOT VERY HEAVY.
TRY IT. COME ON.
OH! OH, I CAN DO IT.
YEAH.
YOU TWO WILL REALLY ENJOY THAT COUCH.
OH, YEAH, WE'RE, UH...
YEAH, WE'RE NOT TOGETHER.
OH. OKAY.
SOMETHING DIDN'T QUITE ADD UP THERE.
ROSS...
WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
WELL, YOU... HER...
I MEAN, SHE'S VERY...
YOU KNOW...
AND YOU'RE, LIKE...
NOT THAT IT'S ANY OF YOUR BUSINESS, BUT WE DID GO OUT.
REALLY? YOU TWO?
YEAH. RACH?
I REALLY DON'T WANT TO BE DOING THIS RIGHT NOW.
I'M CARRYING A VERY HEAVY COUCH.
THEN TELL HIM QUICKLY.
FINE. WE WENT OUT.
NOT ONLY DID WE GO OUT.
WE DID IT... 298 TIMES.
ROSS!
OH, MY...
OH! YOU KEPT COUNT?!
YOU ARE SUCH A LOSER.
A LOSER YOU DID IT WITH 298 TIMES!
OH! OH!
MA'AM! EXCUSE ME, MA'AM?
YES?
YOU CAN'T PUT YOUR CIGARETTE OUT ON A TREE.
YEAH, I CAN. IT WORKED REAL WELL.
NO, BUT YOU SHOULDN'T.
SO DON'T EVER DO THAT AGAIN.
I WON'T...
TILL I HAVE MY NEXT CIGARETTE.
HOLD IT.
N.Y.P.D. FREEZE, PUNK.
WHAT?
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU ARE SO BUSTED.
UH, BOOK THEM.
WHO ARE YOU TALKING TO?
SAVE IT, RED!
UNLESS YOU WANT TO SPEND THE NIGHT IN THE SLAMMER
YOU'LL APOLOGIZE TO THE TREE.
I AM NOT GOING TO APOLOGIZE TO A TREE.
YOU APOLOGIZE TO THE TREE RIGHT NOW
OR I AM CALLING FOR BACKUP.
BACKUP! BACKUP!
I I'M SORRY! SORRY!
OKAY, CANCEL BACKUP!
CANCEL BACKUP!
OKAY.
ROSS, DIDN'T YOU SAY
THAT THERE WAS  AN ELEVATOR IN HERE?
UH, YES, I DID, BUT THERE ISN'T. OKAY.
WELL, THEN, WAIT. DON'T YOU THINK WE SHOULD
MAYBE RETHINK THE WHOLE HIRING MOVERS THING?
NO WAY! THEY'RE A RIP OFF.
AND YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE?
THEY CHECK OUT YOUR STUFF
AND COME BACK LATER AND STEAL IT.
IT'S TRUE. I SAW IT ON DATE LINE.
OH, I LOVE DATELINE.
JANE PAULEY IS THE ONE WOMAN I WOULD KISS.
OW. I DON'T KN
THERE'S JUST SOMETHING ABOUT HER.
RACH, CAN WE CONCENTRATE.
YEAH. FINE.
I LISTENED TO YOUR DUMB STORY.
OKAY, GO LEFT. LEFT.
OKAY.
LEFT!
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
THERE'S NO MORE LEFT LEFT.
OH, OKAY.
YOU KNOW, LIFT IT STRAIGHT UP OVER YOUR HEAD.
STRAIGHT UP OVER YOUR HEAD.
YOU CAN DO IT.
OKAY. YOU GOT IT?
GO. YEAH. GO.
OKAY, YOU GOT IT, RIGHT? YOU GOT IT, RIGHT?
RIGHT. YEAH.
ANY CHANCE YOU THINK THE COUCH LOOKS GOOD THERE?
SO THIS GUY WAS ALL...
AND I'M ALL, "BUFFAY-- HOMICIDE."
IT WAS JUST SO COOL.
PHOEBE, YOU WERE SUPPOSED TO TAKE THAT BACK.
I KNOW, BUT I'M HAVING SO MUCH FUN DOING GOOD DEEDS.
OKAY, BUT IMPERSONATING A POLICE OFFICER'S A SERIOUS THING.
YOU COULD GET ARRESTED.
YOU COULD GET ARRESTED RIGHT NOW!
ALL RIGHT, YEAH, I BETTER TAKE IT BACK.
I'M TOTALLY DRUNK WITH POWER.
HEY.
OH, I...
HI, JOE.
YEAH... I DIDN'T KNOW YOU GUYS
WERE GOING TO BE HERE.
HEY, JOEY?
DO ME A FAVOR, SWEETIE. TASTE THIS.
WHAT? WHY?
IT'S OKAY, JOE.
SHE'S A TRAINED CHEF.
UH... ACTUALLY, I  WAS LOOKING FOR PHOEBE.
YOU JUST MISSED HER.
OH, WAS THAT HER?
UH HUH.
OH. I GOT TO GO.
JOEY, WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT IS GOING ON WITH YOU?
NOTHING.
OH, COME ON, YOU'VE BEEN ACTING STRANGE ALL DAY.
ALL RIGHT.
THERE IS SOMETHING.
I, UH...
I KIND OF HAD A DREAM...
BUT I DON'T WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA!
WHAT IF MARTIN LUTHER KING HAD SAID THAT?
I... KIND OF HAVE A DREAM.
I DON'T WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT.
IT INVOLVED MONICA.
YOU HAD A DREAM ABOUT A GIRL THAT I'M SEEING? OH, THAT IS SO COOL.
I CAN'T TELL YOU HOW MANY TIMES
I DREAMT ABOUT A GIRL THAT HE WAS SEEING.
ANYWAY, WE'RE TALK ING ABOUT YOUR DREAM.
I LOVE YOU. YOUR DREAM?
DON'T WORRY, THERE WASN'T ANY SEX IN IT OR ANYTHING.
I HAVEN'T DREAMT ABOUT HER LIKE THAT
SINCE I FOUND OUT ABOUT YOU TWO... ISH.
WHAT WAS THE DREAM ABOUT?
WELL... OKAY.
YOU WERE MY GIRLFRIEND
AND WE WERE DOING THE CROSSWORD PUZZLE--
YOU KNOW, LIKE YOU GUYS WERE DOING LAST NIGHT.
SO, THAT'S IT.
I'M IN LOVE WITH MONICA, AND I'LL BE MOVING OUT.
WAIT, JOEY, JOEY.
THAT DOESN'T MEAN THAT THAT YOU'RE IN LOVE WITH ME.
IT... IT DOESN'T?
NO, IT CAN MEAN ANYTHING...
LIKE ALL OF A SUDDEN YOU'RE JEALOUS
THAT I'VE BECOME THE APARTMENT STUD.
KIND OF SOUNDS LIKE YOUR DREAM, DUDE.
OR IT COULD MEAN THAT YOU SAW CHANDLER AND ME TOGETHER
AND WE WERE BEING CLOSE AND STUFF
AND AND YOU JUST WANT TO HAVE THAT WITH SOMEONE, TOO.
WELL, IN THE DREAM, I DID ENJOY THE CLOSENESS.
WELL, IF THAT'S WHAT IT WAS, THAT WOULD BE GREAT.
I WOULDN'T HAVE TO MOVE.
OKAY, LOOK, LOOK.
ARE YOU ATTRACTED TO MONICA?
RIGHT HERE, RIGHT NOW
ARE YOU ATTRACTED TO HER?
NOT REALLY.
WELL, THERE YOU HAVE IT.
WELL, SURE. I'M JUST WEARING SWEATS.
BUT THAT'S GOOD...
THAT YOU'RE NOT IN LOVE WITH ME
BECAUSE YOU JUST WANT A GIRLFRIEND.
NO, I DON'T THINK IT'S JUST ABOUT
JUST GETTING A GIRLFRIEND, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, YEAH, I COULD GET A GIRLFRIEND.
YEAH, WE COULD SIT IN THE CHAIR AND DO CROSSWORD PUZZLES
BUT, YOU KNOW, ARE WE EVER GOING TO HAVE
THE CLOSENESS LIKE YOU GUYS HAVE?
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT?
MONICA AND I WERE FRIENDS BEFORE WE STARTED DATING
SO MAYBE THAT'S IT.
FRIENDS FIRST?
THAT'S INTERESTING.
YOU BECOME FRIENDS AFTER?
NO. NEVER DONE THAT EITHER.
HEY... UM, DO YOU GUYS HAVE A TAPE MEASURE?
OH, YEAH, IT'S ACTUALLY IN MY BEDROOM.
THAT'S RIGHT.
WHAT'S UP, JOEY?
HOW YOU DOING?
OH... EXCUSE ME.
IS THIS YOUR CAR?
YEAH.
I DON'T THINK IT'S VERY NICE OF YOU TO PARK HERE.
YOU'RE BLOCKING THE ENTRANCE.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
IT'S NOT A PROBLEM.
WELL, IT'S A PROBLEM FOR ME
WHICH MEANS IT'S A PROBLEM FOR YOU
BECAUSE I'M A COP.
SO AM I.
OH, NO.
OH, OKAY, SO YOU'RE A COP
WHICH MEANS YOU CAN PARK ANYWHERE.
I KNOW THAT, BECAUSE I'M A COP, TOO.
SORRY. KEEP UP THE GOOD WORK. TEN FOUR.
HEY, WAIT A SECOND.
SO WHAT PRECINCT ARE YOU WITH?
I I'M WITH THE, UM, THE 57th.
OH, I KNOW A GUY IN HOMICIDE UP THERE.
I'M IN VICE.
YEAH, IN FACT, I'M UNDERCOVER RIGHT NOW.
I'M A WHORE.
WHO ELSE IS  IN VICE UP THERE?
UM, DO YOU KNOW, UM, SIPOWITZ?
SIPOWITZ? NO, I DON'T THINK SO.
YEAH, SIPOWITZ, YEAH.
BIG GUY, KIND OF BALD.
NAH, I DON'T KNOW HIM.
OKAY.
DON'T TRY TO CALL HIM OR ANYTHING
BECAUSE HE'S NOT THERE.
HE'S OUT.
HIS, UM... HIS PARTNER JUST DIED.
WOW. WELL, TELL SIPOWITZ I'M REAL SORRY FOR HIS LOSS.
I I SURE WILL.
TAKE CARE.
OKAY.
HEY, BY THE WAY
I'M SURE SIPOWITZ IS GOING TO BE ALL RIGHT
I HEARD THAT KID FROM SILVER SPOONS
IS REALLY GOOD.
AND WHERE'D YOU FIND MY BADGE?
OH.
HEY, JOEY, WOULD YOU MIND
GIVING ME AND ROSS A HAND MOVING HIS COUCH?
OH, I'D LOVE TO, BUT I GOT ACTING CLASS.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
I GUESS I COULD BLOW THAT OFF...
FOR YOU.
THANKS.
UH, SAY, RACHEL, LET ME ASK YOU SOMETHING.
UH, I WAS JUST OVER THERE
TALKING TO MONICA AND CHANDLER
AND, BOY, THEY ARE REALLY TIGHT.
I KNOW.
THAT'S NOT A BAD SITUATION THEY GOT GOING OVER THERE.
UH UH.
THINKING OF GETTING ME ONE OF THOSE.
WHAT'S UP, JOE?
WELL, THE REASON I THINK MONICA AND CHANDLER
ARE SO GREAT IS BECAUSE THEY WERE FRIENDS FIRST, YOU KNOW?
SO I ASKED MYSELF, WHO ARE MY FRIENDS?
YOU AND PHOEBE.
I SAW YOU FIRST, SO...
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
I'M SAYING, MAYBE YOU AND I CRANK IT UP A NOTCH.
YOU KNOW, HONEY, UM, AS, UH... AS FLATTERED AS I AM
THAT YOU SAW ME FIRST, UH, I JUST...
I DON'T THINK WE SHOULD BE CRANKING ANYTHING UP.
WELL, I'LL TREAT YOU REAL NICE.
OH HO.
YEAH, WELL, YOU KNOW, UM...
NO, HONEY, LISTEN, I THINK IT'S A GREAT IDEA TO BECOME
FRIENDS WITH SOMEONE BEFORE YOU DATE THEM
BUT THE WAY YOU DO IT IS, YOU KNOW, YOU MEET SOMEONE
BECOME THEIR FRIEND, BUILD A FOUNDATION
THEN ASK THEM OUT ON A DATE.
DON'T HIT ON YOUR EXISTING FRIENDS.
WELL, WON'T THAT TAKE LONGER?
YEAH. YEAH.
OH, BUT ONCE YOU FIND IT, OH, IT'S SO WORTH THE WAIT.
YEAH.
WELL, I UNDERSTAND.
I UNDERSTAND, YOU KNOW.
MAN, I WISH I SAW PHOEBE FIRST.
COME HERE TO ME.
NO, NO. YOU COME HERE TO ME.
HEY, ROSS.
I BROUGHT REINFORCEMENTS.
OH, GREAT. WHAT, YOU BROUGHT JOEY?
WELL, I BROUGHT THE NEXT BEST THING.
HEY.
CHANDLER? YOU BROUGHT CHANDLER?
THE NEXT BEST THING WOULD BE MONICA.
YOU KNOW, I WOULD BE OFFENDED
BUT MONICA IS FREAKISHLY STRONG, SO...
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, I I DREW A SKETCH
OF HOW WE'RE GOING TO DO IT, OKAY?
RACH, THAT'S YOU.
THAT'S THE COUCH.
MM HMM. OOH, WHAT'S THAT?
OH, THAT'S ME.
WOW.
YOU CERTAINLY THINK A LOT OF YOURSELF.
NO, THAT'S... THAT'S MY ARM.
OH, I SEE.
I THOUGHT YOU JUST REALLY, REALLY LIKED YOUR NEW COUCH.
YOU KNOW, JUST... JUST FOLLOW MY LEAD.
OKAY. OKAY.
COME ON, CHANDLER.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
HERE WE GO.
ALL RIGHT, READY, SET, TURN.
OKAY.
TURN.
I DON'T THINK WE CAN TURN ANY MORE.
ROSS, I JUST DON'T THINK
IT'S GOING TO FIT.
OH, YEAH, IT WILL.
COME ON, UP. UP, UP, UP.
UP!
HERE WE GO, PIVOT.
PIVOT!
PIVOT.
SHUT UP! SHUT UP! SHUT UP!
OKAY, I... I DON'T THINK IT'S GOING TO PIVOT ANYMORE.
YOU THINK? YOU THINK?
ALL RIGHT, LET'S, UH...
LET'S BRING IT BACK DOWN AND TRY AGAIN.
OKAY. OH...
OKAY, YEAH. I THINK IT'S REALLY STUCK NOW.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT DIDN'T WORK.
I KNOW. ME NEITHER.
I MEAN, YOU HAD A SKETCH.
OH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
WHAT DID YOU MEAN WHEN YOU SAID "PIVOT"?
MAN, I CANNOT FIGURE THIS OUT.
YEAH, BECAUSE IT'S NOT 1985.
YOU GUYS, GUESS WHAT.
I... I DITCHED A COP.
WHAT? WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WELL, HE CAUGHT ME USING HIS BADGE
AND HE TRIED TO BUST ME.
DAMN REAL COPS!
HOW FAR DID HE CHASE YOU?
WELL, HE DIDN'T REALLY...
HE JUST PICKED UP HIS BADGE AND... AND STOOD THERE.
WOW. MAYBE WE'LL SEE YOU
ON WORLD'S MOST BORING POLICE CHASES.
WHY DID YOU RUN?
I HAD TO.
I MEAN, IMPERSONATING A COP
IS, LIKE, A CLASS E FELONY.
THAT'S TWO TO FOUR YEARS MINI MUM
AND I AM NOT GOING BACK TO THAT HELLHOLE.
IF I CAN JUST... GET IT... TO PIVOT
WE'LL BE BACK ON TRACK.
RACH... RACH, CAN I GET SOME HELP, PLEASE?
YEAH.
TURN IT OFF! TURN IT OFF!
OH! ROSS! OH!
MAYBE THE FIREMEN CAN HELP US MOVE THE COUCH
WHEN THEY GET HERE.
WAIT! WAIT!
NOT THE NEW COUCH!
IT'S A NEW COUCH! IT'S A NEW...
HEY.
HOW'S IT GOING?
DID YOU MAKE ANY NEW FRIENDS?
YEAH. YEAH, I MET THIS WOMAN.
OKAY, WHOA, WHOA.
WHAT'S SHE LIKE?
UH, WELL...
SHE'S REALLY GOOD IN BED.
JOEY, I THOUGHT YOU WERE GOING TO TRY
TO BE FRIENDS FIRST.
WELL, HEY, IT'S ALL YOUR FAULT.
WHAT? WHY?
BECAUSE YOU DIDN'T GIVE ME ADVICE.
NO, YOU GAVE ME A PICKUP LINE.
AS SOON AS I TOLD HER
I WANTED TO BUILD A FOUNDATION AND BE FRIENDS FIRST
I SUDDENLY-- THROUGH NO FAULT OF MY OWN--
BECAME IRRESISTIBLE TO HER.
AND HER ROOMMATE.
WHAT ABOUT THE CLOSENESS?
CLOSENESS, SCHMOSENESS.
THERE WAS THREE OF US, FOR CRYING OUT LOUD.
ALL RIGHT, HEY, WHO WANTS PIZZA?
I DO. I DO. I DO.
OH, THIS IS GREAT.
CAN YOU BELIEVE I FOUND THIS ON THE SECOND FLOOR?
WHO IS IT?
N.Y.P.D.
OH, MY GOD.
UH... JUST A MINUTE, OFFICER!
I'M LOOKING FOR PHOEBE BUFFAY.
OH, MY GOD, IT'S HIM.
IT'S THAT COP.
GOD, I CAN'T BELIEVE IT. HE FOUND ME.
MY GOD, PHOEBE.
ARE YOU GOING TO GO TO JAIL?
WELL, IF I'M GOING DOWN, YOU GUYS ARE GOING DOWN WITH ME.
WHAT?
HARBORING A FUGITIVE?
THAT'S ONE TO THREE YEARS MINIMUM.
GOOD LUCK, CHANDLER.
OKAY, YOU CAN ARREST ME, FINE, BUT YOU'LL
NEVER MAKE IT STICK, AND YOU KNOW IT.
YEAH, BUT I KIND OF DON'T HAVE A CHOICE.
IT'S MY JOB. I MEAN, YOU UNDERSTAND, RIGHT?
YEAH, AS LONG AS YOU UNDERSTAND THAT I'M GOING TO CALL MY LAWYER
AND, ONCE HE PUTS YOU ON THE STAND
HE'S GOING TO MAKE YOU LOOK LIKE A FOOL-- LIKE A FOOL.
MM HMM. I DON'T LIKE LOOKING FOOLISH.
YOU KNOW WHAT? MAYBE, UH, I DON'T ARREST YOU TODAY.
MAYBE I CAME BY AND YOU WEREN'T HERE.
I WOULD LOVE IT IF I WEREN'T HERE.
OKAY, SINCE, UM, YOU'RE NOT GOING TO JAIL TONIGHT
I WAS WONDERING IF YOU WOULD LIKE
TO GO TO DINNER WITH ME.
ME?
YEAH.
EVER SINCE YOU FLASHED MY BADGE AT ME
I KIND OF CAN'T STOP THINKING ABOUT YOU.
YOU'RE THE PRETTIEST FAKE UNDERCOVER WHORE I'VE EVER SEEN.
NICE. NICE.
WOW, I DIDN'T SEE THAT COMING.
YOU'RE ASKING ME OUT.
YEAH, AND I COULD
HAVE DONE IT BETTER
BUT THESE PEOPLE KEEP STARING AT ME.
UM... YEAH.
I I'D LIKE TO GO OUT WITH YOU, OFFICER.
GARY.
OKAY, SO IT'S A DATE?
YEAH. OOH, I GOT TO ASK YOU, THOUGH--
HOW DID YOU KNOW WHERE TO FIND ME?
WELL, YOUR FINGERPRINTS WERE ALL OVER MY BADGE
SO I JUST RAN THEM THROUGH THE COMPUTER
AND THIS IS LISTED AS YOUR LAST KNOWN ADDRESS
SO I JUST CHECKED IT OUT.
OH, IMPRESSIVE.
NOT AS IMPRESSIVE AS YOU.
I GOT TO TELL YOU, I LOOKED AT YOUR RECORD
AND YOU'VE DONE SOME PRETTY WEIRD STUFF.
YEAH, WE'LL TALK AT DINNER.
OKAY. SO I'LL COME BY IN A COUPLE HOURS
AND PICK YOU UP?
ALL RIGHT. I CAN'T WAIT.
OH, AND DON'T WORRY. I'M NOT GOING TO JUST TAKE YOU OUT FOR DOUGHNUTS.
HE HAS A GUN.
I'D LIKE TO RETURN THIS COUCH.
I'M NOT SATISFIED WITH IT.
YOU WANT TO RETURN
THIS COUCH?
IT'S CUT IN HALF.
THAT'S WHAT I'M TELLING YOU.
DID YOU CUT THIS COUCH IN HALF?
IT'S CRAZY.
IT IS CUT IN HALF.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
THIS COUCH IS CUT IN HALF.
I WOULD LIKE TO EXCHANGE IT FOR ONE THAT IS NOT CUT IN HALF.
WE CAN'T ACCEPT  IT IN THIS CONDITION.
WELL,I CAN'T ACCEPT IT IN THIS CONDITION.
YOU'RE TELLING ME THIS COUCH
WAS DELIVERED TO YOU LIKE THIS?
LOOK, I'M A REASONABLE MAN.
I WILL ACCEPT STORE CREDIT.
I'LL GIVE  YOU STORE CREDIT
IN THE AMOUNT OF FOUR DOLLARS.
I WILL TAKE IT.