HEY. HEY.
WOW. YOU LOOK NICE; WHAT'S THE OCCASION?
MONICA AND I ARE CELEBRATING OUR TEN MONTH ANNIVERSARY.
GOT RESERVATIONS AT JEAN GEORGES.
WOW. HOW'D YOU GET IN THERE?
OH, MADE A FEW CALLS, PULLED SOME STRINGS
AND THEY AGREED TO SEAT US AT 11:30
IF WE BOTH HAD THE CHICKEN AND DIDN'T GET DESSERT.
I SEE.
HI, CHANDLER.
HEY, CAITLIN.
SOMEBODY GOT A HAIRCUT.
UGH. I HATE IT.
I LOOK LIKE AN EIGHT YEAR OLD BOY.
YEAH, WELL, IF THAT WAS TRUE
GYM CLASS WOULD HAVE BEEN A LOT MORE INTERESTING.
IT'S, UH, $27 EVEN.
OH, OKAY.
HEY, WHERE'S YOUR CHICKEN?
OH, HE'S IN THE BACK.
THE DUCK PISSED HIM OFF-- SAID THAT EGGS CAME FIRST.
THANKS. I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
OKAY, BYE.
WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?
WHAT?
THE FLIRTING.
AREN'T YOU SUPPOSED TO BE GOING OUT WITH--
UH, I DON'T KNOW-- MY SISTER?
I WAS NOT FLIRTING.
IT WAS TOTALLY FLIRTING.
"SOMEBODY GOT A HAIRCUT."
OKAY, FIRST OF ALL, THE IMPRESSION? UNCANNY.
AND, SECOND, THAT WAS NOT FLIRTING.
THAT WAS JUST CASUAL CONVERSATION
BETWEEN TWO PEOPLE; THAT IS ALL.
YEAH, RIGHT.
YOU WANT TO SEE FLIRTING? I'LL SHOW YOU FLIRTING.
I'M GOOD. I'M GOOD.
I AM SO PROUD OF JOEY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HE'S GOING TO BE ONLAW & ORDER.
I KNOW, BUT DON'T YOU THINK
THAT IT SHOULD BE CALLED ORDER & LAW?
NO, BECAUSE FIRST THEY ARREST THE GUY, AND THEN THEY TRY HIM.
YEAH, DON'T GET  ME STARTED ON THAT.
I WAS NOT FLIRTING.
AND ON YOUR ANNIVERSARY-- FOR SHAME.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
CHANDLER WAS HITTING ON THE HOT DELIVERY GIRL.
I WAS NOT AND, OH, GOD, SHH!
WELL, I'M SORRY, BUT YOU WERE, OKAY?
AND BESIDES, IF ANYONE SHOULD BE HITTING ON HER
IT'S THE GUY WHO'S SINGLE, OKAY?
THE GUY WHO CAN DO SOMETHING ABOUT IT.
SOUNDS LIKE SOMEONE WANTS TO BEMR. PIZZA DELIVERY GIRL.
WELL...
IS THAT WHAT THIS IS ABOUT?
YOU LIKE CAITLIN?
ROSS, WE BROKE  UP TWO YEARS AGO.
YOU'VE BEEN MARRIED SINCE THEN.
I THINK IT'S OKAY THAT WE SEE OTHER PEOPLE.
WELL, I WAS WATCHING HER THE OTHER DAY
AT THE PIZZA PLACE, AND SHE WAS JUST SO SEXY
AND FUNNY AND HAS THE CUTEST LITTLE...
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
WE DON'T NEED HER MEASUREMENTS.
OKAY, PEPPERONI, PEPPERONI, PEPPERONI.
ROSS, I KNOW SHE'S PRETTY AND YOU LOVE HER
BUT IS SHE STUPID?
SHE FORGOT MY VEGETARIAN.
THIS IS PERFECT.
SHE'LL HAVE TO COME BACK HERE WITH YOUR PIZZA
AND WHEN SHE DOES, I WILL TURN ON THE CHARM O'-ROSS.
OH, I AM SO GLAD YOU DON'T EAT MEAT.
SEE? VEGETARIANISM BENEFITS EVERYONE.
HEY, EVERYBODY, LOOK WHO'S HERE.
YOU REMEMBER MY GRANDMOTHER?
HI!
BIG NIGHT.
YEAH, IT'S SO COOL.
SO, JOEY ONLAW AND ORDER-- YOU MUST BE VERY PROUD.
CHANDLER, SHE DOESN'T UNDERSTAND A WORD OF ENGLISH.
I'M SORRY. I THOUGHT YOU WERE JOEY'S OTHER GRANDMOTHER.
I'VE DONE IT AGAIN.
NO, NONNI-- NONNI'S MY BIGGEST FAN.
YEAH, SHE'S THE ONLY ONE IN THE FAMILY
WHO'S ALWAYS BELIEVED IN ME.
SI, NONNI?
IO SONO NUMERON UNO, NO?
SI,BIG STAR.
MY BIG FAT JOEY STAR.
YEAH, I WEIGHED, LIKE, 27 POUNDS WHEN I WAS BORN.
HEY, HAPPY ANNIVERSARY.
HAPPY ANNIVERSARY, TEN MONTHS.
SO, UM, WHEN I WAS IN THE SHOWER
I WAS THINKING ABOUT OUR FIRST NIGHT IN LONDON.
OH, JOEY'S GRANDMOTHER'S RIGHT THERE.
IS THAT THE ONE WHO SPEAKS ENGLISH OR THE ONE WHO DOESN'T?
THE ONE WHO DOESN'T. THAT WAS SOME HOT LOVE YOU GAVE ME.
I'M GOING TO GO GET READY.
HEY, WHY DON'T YOU WEAR THOSE EARRINGS I GOT YOU?
OH, THAT'S A GREAT IDEA.
I WAS SAVING THEM FOR SOMETHING SPECIAL. OKAY.
YOU'VE GOT TO GO HOME.
BUT I LIKE IT HERE.
YOU GOT TO GO HOME AND GET THE EARRINGS
YOU BORROWED FROM ME, OKAY?
CHANDLER WANTS ME TO WEAR THEM TONIGHT.
OKAY. I THINK THEY'RE IN MY PURSE.
GOT GET DRESSED AND I'LL LOOK FOR THEM.
GREAT. OKAY.
RACH, HI.
I NEED THOSE EARRINGS YOU BORROWED.
OH, UM... OKAY.
YEAH. I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
OKAY.
SCUSA, SIGNORA.
NIENTE, GRAZIE.
WOW, PHEEBS, YOU SPEAK ITALIAN?
I GUESS SO.
THERE YOU GO.
THANK YOU. WAIT, RACH.
WHERE'S THE OTHER ONE?
OH, WHAT? YOU WANT BOTH OF THEM?
GETTING A LITTLE GREEDY, DON'T YOU THINK?
RACHEL KAREN GREEN, WHERE IS THE OTHER EARRING?
OKAY, OKAY, OKAY, LOOK, JUST DON'T FREAK OUT
BUT I KIND OF LOST IT.
I KNOW IT'S IN THE APARTMENT
BUT I DEFINITELY LOST IT.
WHAT AM I GOING TO TELL MONICA?
SHE WANTS TO WEAR THEM TONIGHT.
I DON'T KNOW.
TELL HER TO WEAR HER OWN EARRINGS.
THESE ARE HER EARRINGS.
NO, NO!
YOU LENT ME MONICA'S EARRINGS?!
I'M NOT ALLOWED TO BORROW HER STUFF!
WHY NOT?
BECAUSE I LOSE HER STUFF!
He left a little after 2:00.
OKAY, NOW, YOU SEE THAT BLIND GUY RIGHT THERE?
I'M GOING TO BASH HIS HEAD IN LATER.
DOV'E, JOEY? DOV'E, JOEY?
MY BIG SCENE'S COMING UP.
THE BIG SCENE COMING UP.
IF YOU SAID, "BIG LIMA BEAN BUBBLING UP"
WOULD SHE UNDERSTAND THE DIFFERENCE?
RACH, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
OH, I I JUST CAN'T WATCH.
IT'S TOO SCARY.
IT'S A DIAPER COMMERCIAL.
OH, YEAH, WELL, YOU KNOW ME AND BABIES... RESPONSIBILITIES.
PIZZA DELIVERY!
I'LL GET IT!
I WILL GET THAT!
HOW DOES MY HAIR LOOK?
ROSS, IT HASN'T MOVED SINCE 1996.
HEY. HI.
ONE VEGETARIAN PIZZA.
IT'S $12.50.
OH. UH, BY THE WAY
IF IT MAKES YOU FEEL ANY BETTER
I HAPPEN TO LIKE EIGHT YEAR OLD BOYS.
WHAT?
OH, I MEAN...
THE, UH... YOUR HAIR... BEFORE...
YOUR HAIR... YOU SAID YOU THOUGHT
THAT YOUR HAIR LOOKED LIKE AN EIGHT YEAR OLD BOY'S
AND I'M, I'M JUST SAYING, I LIKE IT--
THE THE HAIR.
OH. THANKS.
YOU UNDERSTAND
I DON'T ACTUALLY LIKE EIGHT YEAR OLD BOYS...
YOU KNOW, ALL I'M LOOKING FOR IS THE MONEY.
HERE YOU GO.
NOW, STOP BRINGING US PIZZAS, YOU.
I'M GOING TO TRY.
BYE.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
YOU COULDN'T LET ME HAVE HER, COULD YOU?
WHAT?
THIS IS A GIRL I REALLY LIKE
AND YOU, YOU HAD TO SWOOP IN THERE!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
CHANDLER WAS TOTALLY FLIRTING
WITH THE HOT DELIVERY GIRL.
THANK YOU FOR THAT.
I WAS NOT FLIRTING.
IT'S OKAY. I DON'T CARE.
IT'S FINE.
REALLY? REALLY?
IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
I DO IT ALL THE TIME.
SO, UH...
YOU YOU YOU FLIRT WITH GUYS ALL THE TIME?
SURE. IT DOESN'T MEAN ANYTHING.
JUST LIKE I KNOW IT DOESN'T MEAN ANYTHING WITH YOU.
OKAY, BUT THERE'S A BIG DIFFERENCE.
YOU ARE A LOT HOTTER THAN I AM.
TRUE STORY.
CHANDLER, THIS ACTUALLY BOTHERS YOU?
YES, IT DOES BOTHER ME.
I THINK IT'D BOTHER A LOT OF PEOPLE.
RACHEL, WHEN YOU WERE GOING OUT WITH ROSS
DID IT BOTHER YOU WHEN HE FLIRTED WITH OTHER WOMEN?
UH, NO. NO, IT BOTHERED ME
WHEN HE SLEPT WITH OTHER WOMEN.
AND THANK YOU FOR THAT.
BUT, YOU KNOW, I NEVER REALLY HAD
ANYTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
ROSS WAS NEVER VERY GOOD AT THE FLIRTING THING.
WHA WHA...?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
IT WORKED WITH YOU.
OH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
NO, YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE MET, YOU FLIRTED AND THEN, BAM!
NINE YEARS LATER, YOU HAD ME.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M GOING TO DO?
I AM GOING TO ORDER ANOTHER PIZZA.
AND WHEN CAITLIN GETS HERE
I WILL SHOW YOU HOW WELL I FLIRT.
IN FACT, I WILL...
RIGHT. I WILL GET HER PHONE NUMBER--
AND NOT THE ONE ON THE MENU.
I FOUND IT.
OH, THANK GOD! WHERE WAS IT?
ON YOUR DRESSER.
OKAY, THAT IS THE ONE WE ALREADY HAVE.
OH!
OKAY, HERE'S MY BIG SCENE.
MY BIG SCENE'S HERE.
What do you bet, nobody heard anything?
No bet.
Anybody home?
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT?
OKAY, EVERYBODY JUST KEEP SMILING.
IT'LL KILL MY GRANDMOTHER IF SHE FINDS OUT.
WHAT IS IT?
THEY CUT ME OUT OF THE SHOW.
WHAT?
ARE YOU SURE?
MAYBE YOUR SCENE'S COMING UP.
NOT LIKELY
BECAUSE YOU SEE THAT BODY BAG RIGHT THERE?
YEAH. I'M IN IT.
THIS IS TERRIBLE.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
I DON'T KNOW.
THIS LITTLE OLD LADY LIVES FOR MY CAREER.
WHEN THEY DUMPED ME OFF DAYS OF OUR LIVES,SHE ALMOST DIED.
THAT'S NOT GOOD.
NO. WE HAD TO GET HER A HOME NURSE.
OH, MY GOD.
SHE ALMOST DIED, AND GOT REALLY EXPENSIVE.
YOU'RE NOT SMILING. NOT THAT FACE.
SMILE. EVERYBODY SMILE!
JOEY, WHY DON'T YOU JUST TELL HER WHAT HAPPENED?
I MEAN, IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
IF WE KEEP TALKING THIS WAY
AREN'T WE GOING TO FREAK HER OUT SOON?
OH, UH, UH, SOON. SOON.
I'M GOING TO BE ON SOON.
I... THERE I AM!
I'll let you know.
NO!
SAM WATERSTON.
NO, NO, NO. THAT'S... THAT'S ME. THAT'S ME.
NO. SAM WATERSTON.
CRIME MISDEMEANOR, CAPRICORN ONE...
SHE DOESN'T KNOW "HELLO"
BUT SHE KNOWS CAPRICORN ONE.
PHOEBE? HMM?
I HAVE TO HAVE THOSE EARRINGS.
WE'RE LEAVING AS SOON AS THE SHOW'S OVER.
BUT I ALREADY GAVE THEM BACK TO YOU.
NO, YOU DIDN'T.
ALL RIGHT, I ALREADY DIDN'T GAVE THEM BACK TO YOU.
THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
RACHEL, WHERE IS THAT OTHER EARRING?
IT'S NOT HERE, PHEEBS. IT'S NOT HERE.
OH! I WENT TO JOEY
AND CHANDLER'S LAST NIGHT.
OKAY. MAKE SURE YOU CHECK CHANDLER'S JEWELRY BOX.
WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT? CHANDLER HAS A JEWELRY BOX?
OKAY, WE HAVE, LIKE, TEN MINUTES.
DO YOU WANT ME TO GET INTO THAT NOW?
HEY, PHEEBS.
HOW'S THAT, UH...
VEGETARIAN PIZZA WORKING OUT FOR YOU, HUH?
YOU AND THOSE VEGETABLES
HAVE A REAL THING GOING ON, HUH?
WHY ARE YOU BEING WEIRD?
DO YOU LIKE IT?
NO. THAT WOULD BE, "WHY ARE YOU BEING CUTE?"
OKAY, I'M WORKING ON MY FLIRTING.
OH! I DID NOT GET THAT.
SO, MONICA, DO YOU... DO YOU LIKE THE LAW & ORDER?
YEAH. IT'S GOOD.
SEE, I'M FINDING OUT ALL THIS STUFF ABOUT YOU TODAY--
LIKE YOU LIKE THE LAW & ORDER
AND AND YOU FLIRTED WITH EVERY GUY IN THE TRISTATE AREA.
SHH! SHH!
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, LET ME GET THIS STRAIGHT.
IT'S OKAY FOR YOU TO FLIRT, BUT NOT FOR ME.
OH, I'M SO GLAD WE CLEARED THAT UP.
LOOK, I'M SORRY
BUT SOME THINGS ARE DIFFERENT
FOR MEN AND FOR WOMEN.
GO ON, TEACH ME SOMETHING ABOUT MEN AND WOMEN.
OKAY, I'VE ALREADY TAUGHT YOU SO MUCH ALREADY, BUT WHATEVER...
SEE, WHEN YOU FLIRT WITH A GUY
YOU THINK, "I'M JUST FLIRTING. NO BIG DEAL."
BUT THE GUY IS THINKING
"FINALLY, SOMEBODY WHO WANTS TO SLEEP WITH ME."
NO WAY!
IT'S TRUE.
THAT'S PATHETIC.
AGAIN, TRUE.
AND THIS GOES FOR ALL GUYS?
ALL GUYS THAT ARE AWAKE.
THEN WE GO TO SLEEP.
THEN ALL GUYS FROM THE OTHER END OF THE WORLD WAKE UP
AND BEHAVE THE EXACT SAME WAY.
ALL RIGHT, IT'S ANOTHER COMMERCIAL
AND I STILL HAVEN'T TOLD HER.
JOEY, THIS IS, LIKE, THE LAST COMMERCIAL.
YOU GOT, LIKE, TEN MINUTES LEFT.
I KNOW, I KNOW.
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO? OH!
NO, YOU ARE NOT GOING TO RUN OUT
AND LEAVE HER HERE.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
OH!
JOEY?
UH... JOEY'S GOING TO BE RIGHT BACK.
RIGHT... BACK.
MEANWHILE, LET'S, LET'S, LET'S TALK ABOUT YOU.
SO...
YOU'RE OLD AND SMALL.
DID YOU FIND IT?
THE EARRING? NO. BUT, LOOK--
I FOUND MY SUNGLASSES UNDER THE COUCH.
I'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR THESE SINCE, LIKE, LAST SUMMER.
OKAY, THOSE ARE MY SUNGLASSES.
YOU BORROWED THEM FROM ME.
ALL RIGHT. OKAY. CALM DOWN.
HERE THEY ARE.
PHOEBE?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I DON'T KNOW. I DON'T KNOW.
ALL RIGHT. WELL...
WE'RE JUST GOING TO HAVE
TO TELL MONICA, THAT'S ALL.
OH, GOD, SHE'S GOING TO KILL ME.
I SUPPOSE I COULD TELL HER
IT WAS JUST ALL MY FAULT.
OH, THAT WOULD BE GREAT.
MON, CAN I TALK TO YOU FOR A SEC?
YEAH. WHAT IS IT?
UM... I LOST ONE OF YOUR EARRINGS.
I'M SORRY. I AM SO, SO SORRY.
WOW...
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, I MEAN, WHAT CAN YOU DO?
IF YOU LOST IT, YOU LOST IT.
I'LL REPLACE IT, I PROMISE.
I FEEL SO TERRIBLE.
YOU DIDN'T DO IT ON PURPOSE.
NO.
LOOK AT YOU. COME HERE.
AW...
IS THAT BETTER?
YEAH. YOU'RE THE BEST.
OKAY, WAIT A MINUTE.
WAIT A MINUTE.
I I I... I CAN'T DO THIS.
LISTEN, HONEY, THIS IS...
IT'S NOT PHOEBE'S FAULT.
SHE LENT ME THE EARRINGS.
I LOST IT.  I'M SO SORRY, HONEY.
I FEEL TERRIBLE, TOO.
THAT IS EXACTLY WHY I DO NOT LEND YOU STUFF!
OKAY? I MEAN, FIRST, IT'S MY JEWELRY!
IF IT'S NOT MY JEWELRY, IT'S MY BLUE SWEATER!
IF IT'S NOT MY BLUE SWEATER, IT'S MY SUNGLASSES!
YOUR SUNGLASSES?
YES!
OH, RIGHT.
PIZZA!
MINE! MINE! MINE!
OKAY, HERE GOES.
PREPARE YOURSELVES FOR SOME CLASS "A" FLIRTING.
OKAY, HOLD ON.
OKAY.
ROSS, YOU HAVE NOTHING TO PROVE.
AND IF YOU REALLY LIKE THIS GIRL
I DON'T THINK FLIRTING'S THE RIGHT WAY TO...
UH! UH! UH! UH! UH!
YOU'LL SEE.
OKAY.
WH WHAT'S HER NAME? WHAT'S...?
CAITLIN.
HEY!
OH, WE... WE CAN'T KEEP EATING LIKE THIS.
IT'S, UH.... $12.50.
OKAY. UM...
SO...
DO YOU... MAKE THE PIZZAS
IN ONE OF THOSE, UH... WOOD BURNING OVENS?
NO. ACTUALLY, UM... I THINK THEY'RE GAS.
GAS? WOW!
INTENSE.
IF THIS IS THE WAY ALL THE GELLERS FLIRT
WE DON'T HAVE A PROBLEM.
HEY, UH... YOU KNOW THAT SMELL GAS HAS?
YEAH.
THEY PUT THAT IN.
WHAT?
THE GAS IS ODORLESS
BUT THEY ADD THE SMELL
SO YOU KNOW WHEN THERE'S A LEAK.
WELL, OKAY.
A LOT OF OTHER GAS SMELLS.
OH, THE HUMANITY.
ME METHANE SMELLS.
YOU KNOW WHAT? UM...
ACTUALLY, I... I REALLY... I SHOULD GO.
OH, BUT I I... I HAVEN'T PAID YOU YET.
YOU KNOW WHAT? THAT'S OKAY.
YOU GUYS HAVE ORDERED SO MANY
THAT THIS ONE'S ON ME.
WAS I TALKING TO HER ABOUT GAS?
MORE SO THAN ANYTHING ELSE.
I I... I FOUND IT INTERESTING.
I'M SORRY.
HEY, HEY, REALLY, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
IN NINE YEARS, SHE AND I WILL BE RIGHT THERE.
OKAY, WELL
I'M GOING TO CLEAR OUT SOME OF THESE BOXES.
ROSS?
YEAH?
WHAT ELSE DO THEY ADD SMELL TO?
CAITLIN.
CAITLIN, HI.
HI, HI, HI. I'M RACHEL. FROM UPSTAIRS?
THE PEOPLE WITH ALL THE PIZZA?
OH, WAS THERE A PROBLEM?
NO, NO, NO. EVERYTHING... THEY'RE FINE. GREAT PIZZA.
BUT IT'S ACTUALLY, UM, MY FRIEND, ROSS.
HE, UH, HE JUST GETS REALLY NERVOUS WHEN HE'S FLIRTING.
OH, MY GOD. THAT WAS FLIRTING?
YEAH. I KNOW. WOW.
I KNOW. I KNOW.
BUT, UH, JUST... I'M TELLING YOU
ONCE... ONCE YOU GET PAST THAT PART
WHERE IT JUST FEELS LIKE YOU WANT TO DIE
UM, HE'S... HE'S A REALLY GOOD PERSON.
THE GUY WITH THE GAS?
YEAH. I I... I'M TELLING YOU
HE'S REALLY SWEET AND HE'S REALLY FUNNY
AND HE'S JUST... OH, HE'S GOT A GOOD HEART.
ACTUALLY, I DID THINK THAT HE WAS CUTE
AND THEN HE STARTED TALKING.
SEE? THERE YOU GO.
AND BESIDES, I THINK HE REALLY LIKES YOU.
REALLY?
YOU KNOW, WE HAVE SEVEN PEOPLE
AND, LIKE, TEN PIZZAS.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I JUST... I THOUGHT JOEY WAS THERE.
YEAH... NO... BUT JUST...
I'M TELLING YOU, HE'S WORTH A SHOT.
IF HE'S SO GREAT, WHY DON'T YOU
GO OUT WITH HIM?
HMM.
WELL, YOU KNOW, AT SOME POINT
YOU AND I MAY NEED TO HAVE A LONGER CONVERSATION.
We have till Monday
then I move to dismiss.
HEY, ROSS?
UM... I JUST RAN INTO CAITLIN IN THE HALLWAY
AND AND, UH... YOU MUST BE GETTING BETTER
AT THIS FLIRTING STUFF THAN I THOUGHT.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WELL, I DON'T GET IT
BUT SHE WANTED ME TO GIVE YOU HER PHONE NUMBER.
AND SHE JUST GAVE YOU THIS?
YEAH.
RACH, THANKS
BUT I DON'T NEED YOU DOING ME ANY FAVORS.
I DIDN'T. I DIDN'T.
SHE THOUGHT YOU WERE CUTE.
WELL,THAT I CAN BELIEVE.
YEAH.
HEY! IS THE SHOW STILL ON?
ALMOST OVER, MAN.
HEY, NONNI.
OH! IS THAT THE POPE?
WHY AM I LOOKING?
OH, NONNI, HERE I AM!
LOOK! THIS IS MY BIG SCENE.
All right, back off!
I got a gun.
I'm not afraid to use it!
OH, JOEY!
THAT'S RIGHT,NONNI.
YOU COULDN'T HAVE AT LEAST CHANGED YOUR SHIRT?
Now...
I want a suitcase filled with 100,000 DOLLARS...
Shoo! Shoo! Shoo!
...filled with 100,000 DOLLARS in small bills.
And if I don't get...
Shoo!
And if I don't get it...
I'm going to shoot this duck!
OH, NO!
I'm coming out.
AND SHE'S SUPPOSED TO BUY THIS?
JOEY, BRAVO! BELLISSIMO! OH!
Ground Control to Major Tom.
Commencing...
countdown.
Engines...
on.
THAT'S, UH, SCENES FROM NEXT WEEK'S SHOW.
NEXT WEEK.
I AM DEFINITELY GOING TO WATCH THAT.
WHAT ABOUT THESE? DO THESE LOOK THE SAME?
DEFINITELY.
NOT AS EACH OTHER.
OH. THEN, NO.
HEY, YOU READY?
HI. I GUESS.
YOU LOOK AMAZING.
I'M THE LUCKIEST MAN IN THE WORLD.
OH, YOU'RE ABOUT TO GET A LITTLE LUCKIER.
LET ME SEE THE EARRINGS.
OH, RIGHT. THE EARRINGS.
THEY LOOK GREAT.
DOES YOUR BOYFRIEND HAVE THE BEST TASTE, OR WHAT?
MY BOYFRIEND REALLY DOES HAVE GREAT TASTE.
THANKS FOR PICKING OUT THE EARRINGS, MAN.