CHANDLER! CHANDLER!
CHANDLER, I SAW WHAT YOU WERE DOING
THROUGH THE WINDOW!
I SAW WHAT YOU WERE DOING TO MY SISTER!
NOW, GET OUT HERE!
WELL, LISTEN, WE HAD A GOOD RUN.
YOU KNOW, WHAT WAS IT- - FOUR, FIVE MONTHS?
I MEAN, THAT'S MORE THAN MOST PEOPLE HAVE
IN A LIFETIME.
SO, GOOD BYE, TAKE CARE, BYE BYE, DEAR.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
OH, I'M GOING ON THE LAM.
COME ON, CHANDLER, COME ON.
I CAN HANDLE ROSS.
HOLD ON.
HEY, ROSS. WHAT'S UP, BRO?
WHAT...
THE HELL...
ARE YOU DOING?!
HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
WELL, I THINK...
I THINK ROSS KNOWS ABOUT ME AND MONICA?
DUDE, HE'S RIGHT THERE...
I THOUGHT YOU WERE MY BEST FRIEND.
THIS IS MY SISTER!
MY BEST FRIEND AND MY SISTER.
I CANNOT BELIEVE THIS!
LOOK, WE'RE NOT JUST MESSING AROUND.
I LOVE HER, OKAY?
I'M IN LOVE WITH HER.
I'M SO SORRY THAT YOU HAD TO FIND OUT THIS WAY.
I'M SORRY, BUT IT IT'S TRUE.
I I LOVE HIM, TOO.
MY BEST FRIEND AND MY SISTER!
I'M SO HAPPY!
I CANNOT BELIEVE THIS!
OH, I'M SORRY, YOU GUYS WANT
TO PROBABLY GET SOME HUGS IN, TOO, HUH?
BIG NEWS!
OH, NO, THAT'S OKAY.
WE'VE ACTUALLY KNOWN FOR A WHILE.
WHAT WHAT?
YOU GUYS KNEW?
YOU ALL KNEW
AND YOU DIDN'T TELL ME?!
WELL, ROSS, WE WERE WORRIED ABOUT YOU, OKAY?
WE DIDN'T KNOW HOW YOU WERE GOING TO REACT.
MMM.
YOU WERE WORRIED ABOUT SME?
YOU DIDN'T KNOW HOW I WAS GOING TO REACT?
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
WHEW!
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE ALL, UH, CLEAR OUT OF HERE
AND LET THESE TWO LOVEBIRDS GET BACK DOWN TO BUSINESS?
HEY, HEY, HEY, I I'M JUST TALKING HERE.
HE'S THE ONE DOING YOUR SISTER.
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT I JUST REALIZED?
IF YOU GUYS EVER HAVE KIDS...
WHOA, WHOA, WE'RE HAVING KIDS?
I CALL GODFATHER.
YOU CAN'T JUST CALL GODFATHER.
DON'T YOU THINK HER BROTHER SHOULD BE GODFATHER?
SURE, IF YOU CARED ENOUGH TO CALL IT FIRST.
YOU GUYS...
I THINK YOU'RE A FEW STEPS AHEAD OF US.
YEAH. BIG ZERO GRAVITY MOON STEPS.
OH, I JUST THOUGHT
OF THE GREATEST WEDDING GIFT TO GET YOU.
OOH, I'LL GO I N ON THAT WITH YOU.
I COULDN'T THINK OF ANYTHING.
OH. HI, KATIE.
HEY, EVERYONE, THIS IS KATIE. HI.
SO, ARE YOU READY TO GO?
I JUST GOT TO RUN TO THE BATHROOM. BACK THERE.
HEY, WHERE WE GOING TO LUNCH?
I WAS THINKING MAYBE CHINESE FOOD.
OH, I LOVE CHINESE!
HOW'D YOU KNOW I LOVE CHINESE?!
SHE IS SO CUTE.
YOU COULD FIT HER RIGHT IN YOUR LITTLE POCKET.
SHE COULD  FIT
IN THAT LITTLE POCKET INSIDE THE POCKET.
I DON'T KNOW...
I MEAN, I LIKE HER A LOT, AND SHE'S REALLY NICE, BUT...
BUT WHAT?
SHE KEEPS PUNCHING ME.
IN THAT CUTE, LITTLE SWEET WAY SHE JUST DID?
HEY, IT'S A LOT HARDER THAN IT LOOKS, OKAY?
SHE SHE... SHE'S HURTING ME.
OH, SEE, I KNOW WHAT YOU NEED.
YOU NEED A BODYGUARD.
ROSS, WHAT IS BEN DOING AFTER PRESCHOOL?
OKAY, LISTEN-- JOEY IS HAVING A PROBLEM...
WITH A LITTLE GIRL WHO'S BEATING HIM UP.
AW... JOEY, COME HERE.
LOOK-- HONEY, I KNOW THIS MUST BE
REALLY, REALLY DIFFICULT FOR YOU...
OH, I'M SORRY. AM I HURTING YOU?
HEY!
HEY! I BROUGHT YOU SOME HOUSEWARMING GIFTS.
OH...
YEAH-- SALT, SO YOUR LIFE ALWAYS HAS FLAVOR...
OH.
BREAD, SO YOU NEVER GO HUNGRY...
OH...
AND A SCENTED CANDLE FOR THE BATHROOM
BECAUSE, WELL, YOU KNOW.
WELL, THANKS, THANKS, AND... THANKS, I GUESS.
AH! YE
HI. HI.
WELCOME TO THE BUILDING.
I'M STEVE SERRA, PRESIDE NT OF THE TENANTS COMMITTEE.
OH, HI. ROSS GELLER.
AND THIS IS MY FRIEND, PHOEBE.
HI, PHOEBE.
MR. PRESIDENT.
I, UH, CAME TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT HOWARD.
HOWARD?
YEAH. HE'S THE HANDYMAN.
HE'S GOING TO RETIRING NEXT WEEK, AND EVERYONE WHO LIVES HERE
IS KICKING IN A HUNDRED BUCKS
AS A "THANK YOU FOR ALL OF THE HARD WORK" TYPE OF THING.
OH, THAT'S NICE.
YEAH. YOU WANT TO GIVE ME A CHECK OR...?
OH! UH...
LOOK, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO GIVE IT TO ME RIGHT NOW.
YOU CAN SLIP IT UNDER MY DOOR...
NO, NO, IT'S NOT THAT.
IT'S JUST, I... I I JUST MOVED IN.
WELL, THE GUY'S WORKED HERE FOR 25 YEARS.
YES, BUT I'VE LIVED HERE FOR 25 MINUTES.
OH.
OKAY. I GET IT.
NO, WAIT. LOOK, LOOK...
I'M SORRY, IT'S JUST I'VE NEVER EVEN MET... HOWARD.
I MEAN, I DON'T KNOW HOWARD.
HOWARD'S THE HANDYMAN?
YES, BUT TO ME HE'S JUST...
MAN.
OKAY, FINE.
WHATEVER.
WELCOME TO THE BUILDING.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT GUY?
YEAH. I REALLY LIKE HIS GLASSES.
...SO THEN PRESIDENT STEVE TOLD EVERYONE
I WAS A CHEAPSKATE
AND NOW THE WHOLE BUILDING HATES ME.
YOU KNOW, A LITTLE KID SPIT ON MY KNEE.
AND TOLD ME TO WIPE IT OFF WITH MY HUNDRED DOLLAR BILL.
WELL, YOU REALLY SHOULD WIPE IT OFF WITH SOMETHING.
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M GOING TO DO?
I'M GOING TO THROW A PARTY--
THAT'S RIGHT, FOR EVERYONE IN THE BUILDING.
I'M GOING TO SIT THEM ALL DOWN
AND EXPLAIN TO THEM THAT I AM NOT A BAD GUY.
I AM NOT A CHEAP GUY.
I'M JUST A GUY WHO WHO STANDS UP
FOR WHAT HE BELIEVES IN, A MAN...
WITH PRINCIPLES.
SOUNDS LIKE A FUN PARTY.
LOOK, ROSS, IF YOU WANT YOUR NEIGHBORS TO LIKE YOU
WHY DON'T YOU JUST PAY THE HUNDRED BUCKS?
A PARTY'S GOING TO COST YOU WAY MORE THAN THAT.
THAT DOESN'T MATTER.
IT'S MY PRINCIPLES.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT MY PRINCIPLES!
OKAY.
I THOUGHT IT WAS ABOUT YOUR NEIGHBORS LIKING YOU.
OH, THEY'LL LIKE ME ONCE THEY COME TO MY AWESOME PARTAY.
OKAY, I GOT TO RUN.
I GOT TO GO GET SOME NAME TAGS.
AND THAT CRAZY PARTY ANIMAL WILL BE YOUR BROTHER IN LAW.
OH, YEAH. VERY, VERY FUNNY.
BUT DON'T SAY THINGS LIKE THAT IN FRONT OF MONICA.
I DON'T WANT YOU PUTTING ANY IDEAS IN HER HEAD.
UM, CHANDLER, YOU YOU DO REALIZE
THAT THOSE IDEAS ARE PROBABLY ALREADY IN MONICA'S HEAD?
WH WHY?
WELL, BECAUSE SHE LOVES YOU AND BECAUSE YOU LOVE HER.
YEAH? SO? WHAT'S THAT'S SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
HEY, CHANDLER, DON'T FREAK OUT.
I'M TELLING YOU SOMETHING YOU ALREADY KNOW.
COME ON, SHE BROKE UP WITH RICHARD
BECAUSE HE DIDN'T WANT TO HAVE BABIES
AND SHE'S A WOMAN, AND SHE'S ALMOST 30, AND, YOU KNOW...
IT'S MONICA.
I DON'T SEE IT THAT WAY, OKAY? BECAUSE I SEE TWO MONICAS--
THE ONE THAT WAS MY FRIEND WHO LIVES ACROSS THE HALL
AND WANTED TO HAVE A LOT OF BABIES...
AND THEN THE NEW MONICA, WHO I JUST STARTED TO DATE.
OKAY, NOW, WHO'S TO SAY WHAT SHE WANTS?
I'M RIGHT. I'M RIGHT.
AM I RIGHT?
OH... ABSOLUTELY.
OKAY, AND YOU KNOW
I'M COMPLETELY DIFFERENT THAN RICHARD ANYWAY
BECAUSE HE'S AN EYE DOCTOR AND I DON'T WEAR GLASSES.
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT, YOU ARE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
I MEAN, THAT MAKES EVERYTHING DIFFERENT.
OKAY.
IT'S NOT DIFFERENT AT ALL, IS IT?
NOT UNLESS "DIFFERENT" MEANS "THE SAME."
YOU WERE SO FUNNY WITH THAT WAITER.
YOU'RE SUCH ANUT!
WELL, YOU KNOW, BREAD STICK FANGS
ARE ALWAYS FUNNY, SO...
NO, YOU MAKE THEM FUNNY.
YOU'RE THE FUNNY ONE!
THANKS.
UH, LOOK, KATIE, UH...
LISTEN, WE WE NEED TO TALK, OKAY?
UM, LOOK, I LIKE YOU -- I I REALLY DO.
I LIKE YOU A LOT, OKAY?
BUT SOMETIMES WHEN YOU PLAYFULLY PUNCH ME LIKE THAT
IT IT FEELS LIKE SOMEONE'S HITTING ME
WITH A VERY TINY, BUT A VERY REAL BAT.
OH... LIKE I COULD HURT YOU.
ARE YOU MAKING FUN OF MY SIZE?
NO.
DON'T MAKE FUN OF ME BECAUSE OF MY SIZE!
YEAH, OKAY.
OH...
HMM...
ISN'T THIS GREAT?
MMM.
COULDN'T YOU JUST STAY LIKE THIS FOREVER?
CHANDLER?
COULDN'T YOU JUST STAY HERE FOREVER?
YEAH, HERE, SOMEWHERE ELSE... YOU KNOW, WHERE WHEREVER.
ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH. I'M COOL.
CASUAL.
WHAT WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
OH, JUST HANGING OUT, YOU KNOW, HAVING FUN...
YOU KNOW, WITH THE GIRL THAT I'M SEEING CASUALLY
OH... MAN, I KNEW IT.
I KNEW YOU WERE GOING TO DO THIS.
WHAT? GET ALL FREAKED OUT
BECAUSE EVERYBODY WAS TALKING AND JUST JOKING AROUND
ABOUT MARRIAGE AND STUFF.
WELL, YOU YOU DO WANT ALL THAT STUFF, RIGHT?
OH, AND YOU KNOW WHAT I WANT.
YES. YOU WANT BABIES.
YOU HAVE BABY FEVER.
I DO NOT HAVE BABY FEVER.
OH, PLEASE. YOU ARE OBSESSED WITH BABIES AND MARRIAGE
AND EVERYTHING THAT'S RELATED TO BABIES
AND AND... MARRIAGE.
YOU KNOW WHAT? I GOT A GOOD IDEA.
WHY DON'T WE TURN THE HEAT DOWN
ON THIS PRESSURE COOKER?!
HAVE YOU LOST YOUR MIND?
CHANDLER, THIS ISN'T ABOUT ME; THIS IS ABOUT YOU
AND ALL YOUR WEIRD RELATIONSHIP COMMITMENT CRAP.
NUH UH. I KNOW YOU, OKAY?
I KNOW THE THOUGHTS
THAT YOU HAVE IN THE HEAD-- IN YOUR HEAD.
WELL, YOU DON'T KNOW EVERYTHING.
DID YOU KNOW THAT I'M GOING OUT WITH RACHEL TONIGHT
INSTEAD OF YOU, HMM?
AND DID YOU KNOW THAT THE ONLY BABY AROUND HERE IS YOU?
AND DID YOU KNOW
THAT I CAN'T EVEN LOOK AT YOU RIGHT NOW?
YEAH, WELL, I DID NOT KNOW THAT.
THIS IS GOING TO BE OKAY, RIGHT?
I MEAN, SHE'S NOT GOING TO LEAVE ME.
THIS IS FIXABLE.
SURE. ABSOLUTELY.
BY ME.
OH, NO.
NO, NO, NO.
WELL, UNLESS YOU MAKE SOME KIND OF BIG GESTURE.
YEAH, BIG, THOUGH.
UH OH! SHH! THE MISSUS.
GUNTHER, CAN  I GET A COFFEE?
TO GO?
LOOK, MONICA...
I'M STILL NOT DONE NOT WANTING TO TALK TO YOU.
JUST TELL ME WHAT I NEED TO DO
TO MAKE THINGS RIGHT.
WHAT?
WELL, THAT'S WHAT WE DO.
YOU KNOW, I MESS UP, AND THEN YOU TELL ME HOW TO FIX IT
AND THEN I DO, AND THEN YOU THINK I'M ALL CUTE AGAIN.
I'M REALLY TIRED OF BEING YOUR RELATIONSHIP TUTOR.
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO FIGURE THIS ONE OUT
FOR YOURSELF, ALL RIGHT?
IF YOU'RE TOO AFRAID TO BE IN A REAL RELATIONSHIP
THEN DON'T BE IN ONE.
?? RIGHT ABOUT NOW ??
?
?? THE FUNK SOUL BROTHER ?
?? CHECK IT OUT NOW ??
?
?? THE FUNK SOUL BROTHER ?
?? RIGHT ABOUT NOW ??
?
?? THE FUNK SOUL BROTHER ?
?? RIGHT ABOUT NOW ??
?
?? THE FUNK SOUL BROTHER ?
?? CHECK IT OUT... ??
!
HOWARD! HOWARD ! HOWARD! HOWARD
HOWARD! HOWARD
HOWARD! HOWARD! HOWARD! HOWARD!
PHOEBE?
HOWARD! PHOEBE?
HOWARD! YAY! OH, HI, ROSS!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
OH, I THOUGHT THIS WAS YOUR PARTY
AND IT TURNS OUT, IT'S A PARTY FOR HOWARD.
HE'S THE SWEETEST LITTLE MAN.
SEE YA, PHOEBE.
OH, AND, HEY, THANKS FOR CHIPPING IN.
OH, SURE.
YOU CHIPPED IN?
YEAH, UH HUH. $100.
PHOEBE, I I CAN'T BELI EVE YOU GAVE HIM MONEY.
I THOUGHT YOU AGREED IT WAS TOTALLY UNREASONABLE
THAT THEY ASKED  ME FOR THAT MONEY.
YEAH, BUT THEY DIDN'T ASK ME, YOU KNOW
AND THIS WAY I'M JUST THE EXOTIC, GENEROUS STRANGER
AND THAT'S ALWAYS FUN TO BE.
YEAH, BUT YOU'RE MAKING ME LOOK BAD.
NO, I'M NOT. NO.
IF ANYTHING, I'M MAKING YOU LOOK BETTER.
THEY'LL SEE YOU TALKING TO ME, AND THAT'S, YOU KNOW.
I'M A HIT.
HEY, PHEEBS.
HEY.
OH, HEY, ROSS.
UM, SAY, I WAS THINKING
MAYBE YOU TWO COULD SWITCH APARTMENTS
BECAUSE PHOEBE'S MORE OUR KIND OF PEOPLE.
SOMETHING TO THINK ABOUT.
YEAH, OKAY, MY BAD.
HEY.
HI.
WOW, YOU LOOK... YOU LOOK BIG.
THANKS. I'VE BEEN WORKING OUT.
HEY, LISTEN, IS IT OBVIOUS I'M WEARING SIX SWEATERS?
UH, YEAH. BUT IT'S NOT OBVIOUS WHY.
WELL, LOOK, I'M BREAKING UP WITH KATIE.
SO I HAD TO PUT ON SOME EXTRA PADDING.
I MEAN, IF SHE HITS ME WHEN SHE'S HAPPY
CAN YOU IMAGINE HOW HARD SHE'S GOING TO HIT ME
WHEN I TELL HER I'M TAKING AWAY THE JOEY LOVE?
OH... OH, RIGHT.
I FORGOT THAT  YOU CALL IT THAT.
YEAH.
HEY. HEY.
HOW ARE YOU?
HEY, CUTE JACKET.
OH, THANKS.
THAT'S SO SWEET. WHOA.
OW!
OH, "OW." DID JOEY TELL YOU TO SAY THAT?
YOU GUYS ARE TOO MUCH.
WHOA.
YOU KNOW WHAT, KATIE?
I GOT TO TELL YOU.
I I I THINK YOU'RE THE ONE THAT IS TOO MUCH.
OH, JOEY HAS THE NICEST FRIENDS.
OH, AND THE NICEST GIRLFRIEND.
OH...
YOU'RE SO SWEET.
WELL, YOU'RE SO SWEET.
OW!
JOEY... SHE JUST KICKED ME.
HUH.
WELL?
AREN'T YOU GOING TO DO SOMETHING?
UH...
YOU'D BETTER DO SOMETHING
OR I'M GOING TO WALK OUT THAT DOOR RIGHT NOW.
WELL?
ARE YOU GONNA?
NAH.
PHOEBE?
THAT'S WHAT I WAS SAYING.
PHOEBE, PHOEBE...
OOH.
LOOK, THIS IS A DISASTER.
CAN'T I PLEA SE JUST GO?
NO, NO. I'M TALKING YOU UP TO PEOPLE.
JUST GIVE IT A LITTLE TIME, ALL RIGHT?
RELAX. GET SOMETHING TO EAT.
OKAY?
SO, UH, WHAT
DID YOU TELL THEM ABOUT ME?
UM, OH, I WAS TELLING THEM ABOUT YOU AND EMILY.
YOU KNOW, TRY TO GET SOME SYMPATHY?
BUT SOMEHOW YOU CAME OFF AS THE BAD GUY.
WHAT?
YEAH. I THINK I TOLD IT WRONG.
YOU KNOW, WE SHOULD TALK ABOUT THAT
BECAUSE I DON'T TOTALLY UNDERSTAND
WHAT HAPPENED THERE.
OOH, THIS CAKE IS REALLY GOOD.
SEE? THINGS ARE LOOKING UP ALREADY.
OH, MY GOD, SOMEONE CUT HOWARD'S CAKE.
WHO WOULD DO A THING LIKE THAT?
3 B.
OH, YEAH. AW, COME ON.
OKAY, YOU GOT YOUR FREE FOOD, YOU RUINED EVERYONE'S FUN.
DON'T YOU THINK IT'S TIME YOU WENT HOME?
HEY, GO HOME.
GO BACK TO 3 B, 3 B.
OKAY, EVERYONE?
EVERYONE CALM DOWN.
I HAVE SOMETHING THAT I WOULD LIKE TO SAY.
WHO HERE LIKES ROSS?
WELL, OF COURSE YOU DON'T LIKE HIM.
HE DIDN'T GIVE YOU ANY MONEY.
HE RAISED HIS OWN HAND WHEN I ASKED, "WHO HERE LIKES ROSS?"
AND HE'S WEARING TWO NAME TAGS.
I'LL BE HONEST WITH YOU GUYS.
WHEN I FIRST MET ROSS, I DIDN'T LIKE HIM AT ALL.
BUT THEN, ONCE I GOT TO KNOW HIM
I SAW THAT HE'S REALLY SWEET AND CARING
AND VERY GENEROUS.
I MEAN, ALL I'M SAYING IS DON'T JUDGE ROSS
BEFORE YOU GET TO KNOW HIM, ALL RIGHT?
I MEAN, YOU KNOW, I LIKE ALL YOU GUYS NOW
BUT WHEN I FIRST MET YOU, YOU KNOW... CURT--
I THOUGHT, YOU KNOW
"ABRASIVE DRUNK."
UM, LOLA--
"MIND NUMBINGLY STUPID."
YOU KNOW, AND...
OKAY, YOU GUYS
"GOLD DIGGER," "CRADLE ROBBING PERV."
SO I THINK YOU ALL KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
OBVIOUSLY, I DIDN'T THINK
THEY WERE GOING TO START THROWING THINGS.
I JUST THOUGHT
IF I KEPT INSULTING THEM
YOU WOULD JUMP IN AND DEFEND EVERYONE
AND THEN YOU COULD LOOK LIKE THE HERO.
OH, WOW, YEAH.
SEE, I DID NOT GET THAT.
WHERE'S MONICA?
I NEED TO TALK TO HER.
IT'S URGENT. IS SHE HERE?
I'M MONICA.
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU. IT'S URGENT.
OKAY.
OKAY, I'VE BEEN DOING A LOT OF THINKING
ABOUT US, YOU KNOW, A LOT OF, UH, "US" THINKING
AND, UH... WELL, I GUESS THERE'S ONLY ONE...
ONE WAY TO DO THIS.
NO, NO, NO.
WH WHAT...? WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
MONICA...
NO, NO, NO. DON'T... DON'T DO IT.
WILL YOU MARRY ME?
OH, NO, NO, NO, NO.
WHAT A BAD IDEA.
OH, I CAN'T NOT LOOK AT IT.
CHANDLER, WHY  ARE YOU DOING THIS?
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT I KNOW I'M NOT AFRAID TO DO THIS.
CHANDLER...
I'M DOING THIS BECAUSE I'M SORRY?
D DO YOU, UM, YOU REALLY THINK
THE BEST REASON TO GET MARRIED
IS BECAUSE YOU'RE SORRY?
WELL, NO. THE BEST REASON TO GET MARRIED
IS PREGNANCY.
BUT "SORRY" IS PRETTY MUCH FOURTH
YOU KNOW, BEHIND "BEING READY"
AND "ACTUALLY WANTING TO GET MARRIED."
WILL YOU BE MY WIFE?
CHANDLER, UM, I WANT YOU TO TAKE JUST A MINUTE
AND I WANT YOU TO THINK ABOUT
HOW RIDICULOUS THIS SOUNDS.
YEAH, I'M KIND OF WISHING EVERYONE WASN'T HERE RIGHT NOW.
OH, HONEY, DO YOU KNOW
THAT NONE OF THAT STUFF CAME FROM ME?
I MEAN, I NEVER SAID THAT I WANTED
TO HAVE BABIES AND GET MARRIED RIGHT NOW.
YEAH, I KNOW, BUT I WAS REALLY CONFUSED
AND THEN I TALKED TO THESE GUYS
WHO, TWO DIVORCES AND JOEY?
HEY.
SHE'S RIGHT, YOU KNOW.
YEAH, BUT STILL, CHEAP SHOT.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU WHEN I WHEN I SAID THAT I WANT YOU TO DEAL
WITH THIS RELATIONSHIP STUFF ALL ON YOUR OWN
WELL, YOU'RE NOT READY FOR THAT.
I DIDN'T THINK I WAS.
COME HERE.
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT WOULD YOU HAVE DONE IF I HAD SAID YES?
WELL, I WOULD HAVE BEEN HAPPY
BECAUSE I WOULD HAVE BEEN ABLE TO SPEND THE REST OF MY LIFE
WITH THE WOMAN THAT I LOVE.
OR YOU WOULD HAVE SEEN A CHANDLER SHAPED HOLE
IN THAT DOOR.
HEY, ROSS, YOU PASS ME THAT KNIFE?
NO, I WILL NOT.
OH, IT'S OKAY. YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE SO MEAN ABOUT IT.
YOU'RE RIGHT. I'M SORRY.
WILL YOU MARRY ME?
OH, AND I WAS GOING TO ASK YOU TO MARRY ME
BECAUSE I FORGOT TO SAY HELLO TO YOU LAST WEEK.
OH, NO, WAIT, PHEEBS, I THINK
WITH SOMETHING LIKE THAT, YOU JUST ASK THEM
TO MOVE IN WITH YOU, BUT I'M NOT SURE.
CHANDLER?
OKAY, HOW LONG IS THIS GOING TO GO ON?
WELL, I THINK THE LENGTH OF TEASING
IS DIRECTLY RELATED TO HOW INSANE YOU WERE
SO A LONG TIME.
THIS IS FUN.
HEY, RACH, REMEMBER THAT WHOLE "WE WERE ON A BREAK" THING?
WELL, I'M SORRY. WILL YOU MARRY ME?
THAT'S NOT FUNNY.