YOU LOOK CUTE IN BUBBLES.
AH, YOU'RE JUST ALL LIQUORED UP.
HEY, IT'S ME.
I'M COMING IN.
I'VE HAD A VERY LONG, HARD DAY.
YOU'RE HOME EARLY.
YEAH, MY DATE THREW UP.
I'M GOING TO GO GET SOME CHICKEN. YOU WANT SOME?
NO, THANKS. NO CHICKEN.
BYE BYE THEN.
OKAY.
YOU SURE? SOME EXTRA CRISPY?
DIRTY RICE? BEANS?
FOR THE LAST TIME, NO.
GET OUT. GET OUT, JOEY.
ALL RIGHT.
ARE YOU OKAY?
I'M SO SORRY. HE WOULDN'T LEAVE.
HE KEPT ASKING ME
IF I WANTED CHICKEN.
CHICKEN?
I COULD EAT SOME CHICKEN.
HEY, JOE!
YEAH, COULD I GET A THREE PIECE, SOME COLE SLAW
AND SOME BEANS AND A COKE...
...DIET COKE.
??  ? ?
??  ??
HEY!
HEY! HEY, PHEEBS!
OH, I HAVE TO TELL YOU THIS STORY.
I WAS COMING OVER HERE AND THIS CAB DRIVER...
WAS HIS NAME ANGUS?
WHAT?
HE WAS THIS CAB DRIVER WE HAD IN LONDON.
OH. HA HA HA.
ALL RIGHT, ANYWAY...
WHAT WAS THAT PLACE
THAT PUB HE TOOK US TO?
THE WHEAT SHEAF.
AND THEY HAD THAT BEER, THAT, UH...
BODDINGTON'S.
BODDINGTON'S. BODDINGTON'S.
THAT'S IT, BABY.
OH, PHEEBS WAS GOING TO TELL A STORY.
OKAY, SO, HE HAD A REALLY FUNNY HAT.
I DON'T WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT.
HEY.
HEY, ROSS.
BODDINGTON'S.
YEAH! YEAH!
OH, MAN.
THAT WAS GOOD BEER.
YOU KNOW, I'D WALK BACK TO LONDON
FOR ANOTHER FROSTY ONE OF THOSE BAD BOYS.
YOU KNOW, I THINK THEY HAVE THOSE
AT THAT BRITISH PUB BY THE TRADE CENTER.
LATER.
ISN'T RACHEL SUPPOSED TO BE BACK BY NOW?
HER PLANE GOT DELAYED IN ATHENS
BUT, ACTUALLY, SHE SHOULD BE HERE BY NOW.
S SO YOU TALKED TO HER?
DID SHE... DID SHE SOUND MAD?
NO, BUT SHE LIKES ME.
YOU ABANDONED HER ON A PLANE TO GREECE.
OKAY, I DID NOT ABANDON RACHEL, OKAY?
EMILY SHOWED UP AT THE AIRPORT.
I HAD TO GO AFTER HER.
I MEAN, I DID WHAT I HAD TO DO.
SHE'S MY WIFE.
RACHEL IS MY WIFE, YOU KNOW.
EMILY!
EMILY IS MY WIFE.
MAN, WHAT IS THAT?
SO YOU STILL HAVEN'T HEARD FROM EMILY?
NO, NOT SINCE I LOST HER AT THE AIRPORT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE SHE CAN OUTRUN YOU, MAN.
HEY, SHE'S FAST, OKAY?
OH, YOU THINK YOU CAN BEAT ME?
LET'S GO, OUTSIDE!
I'M SORRY. I'M I'M JUST A LITTLE...
SLOW?
OH, YOU WANT SOME?!
HUH?! OKAY, GET THE SHOES ON.
LET'S GO, MAN.
IT'S COOL, OKAY?
YOU'RE THE FASTEST.
HI.
RACHEL! HI!
RACH, RACH, I AM SO SORRY.
I AM SO, SO SORRY.
OH, ROSS, COME ON.
YOU JUST DID WHAT YOU HAD TO DO.
THAT'S IT?
YOU'RE NOT MAD?
I MEAN, IT MUST HAVE BEEN TERRIBLE.
TERRIBLE? HELL, I WAS IN GREECE.
THAT WAS A NICE HOTEL.
NICE BEACH.
MET THE NICE PEOPLE.
NOT TOO SHABBY FOR RACHEL.
SO, WHAT? THAT'S IT?
WELL, YEAH.
WE'RE COOL. TOTALLY COOL.
THANKS, RACH.
OH, YOU'RE THE BEST.
OH, NO, YOU'RE THE BEST.
OH, I GOT TO GO TO THE FLOWER STORE.
CHECK IT OUT.
NO ONE WILL TELL ME WHERE EMILY IS.
SO I'M GOING TO SEND 72 LONG STEMMED RED ROSES
TO HER PARENTS' HOUSE.
ONE FOR EACH DAY THAT I'VE KNOWN AND LOVED HER.
THAT OUGHT TO GET HER TALKING TO ME AGAIN.
OH, ROSS, WHEN YOU MAKE OUT THE CARD
BE SURE TO MAKE IT OUT TO EMILY.
RACH, THAT'S GREAT.
IT'S SO GOOD YOU HAD SUCH A GOOD TIME IN GREECE.
WHAT?
I DIDN'T HAVE A GOOD TIME IN GREECE.
ROSS ABANDONED ME, OKAY?
I COULDN'T GET A PLANE OUT
SO I HAD TO STAY IN THEIR HONEYMOON SUITE
WITH PEOPLE COMING UP TO ME ALL THE TIME, GOING
"OH, MRS. GELLER, WHY YOU CRY?"
I MEAN, IT WAS SO HUMILIATING.
I FELT LIKE SUCH AN IDIOT.
I MEAN, IT'S ALL MY FAULT.
AND YOU KNOW WHY?
BECAUSE I MAKE VERY BAD DECISIONS.
OH, THAT'S NOT TRUE.
YES, IT IS. IT IS TRUE.
I WENT AFTER ROSS IN STUPID LONDON.
LONDON IS STUPID. STUPID.
I PUT ON A CHEERLEADING OUTFIT TO SEDUCE JOSHUA
THEN I LOST HIM BECAUSE I ASKED HIM TO MARRY ME AFTER FOUR DATES
AND THEN I WENT TO GREECE
ON SOMEBODY ELSE'S HONEYMOON, OKAY?
DO THOSE SOUND LIKE VERY GOOD DECISIONS TO YOU?
I LIKE YOUR LITTLE BRAID.
ALL RIGHT, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I JUST SHOULDN'T BE ALLOWED TO MAKE DECISIONS ANYMORE.
PHOEBE, YOU WERE RIGHT.
I SHOULD HAVE NEVER GONE TO LONDON
AND FROM NOW ON
YOU MAKE ALL OF MY DECISIONS FOR ME.
OH, NO, I DID THAT FOR SOMEONE ONCE.
I'M NOT COMFORTABLE HAVING THAT KIND OF POWER
AND CONTROL OVER SOMEONE'S LIFE.
I'LL DO IT.
THAT'S FINE.
SO, MONICA, YOU ARE NOW IN CHARGE OF MY LOVE LIFE.
OKAY, I GOT TO GO TO WORK.
AND RACHEL, GREAT TO HAVE YOU BACK.
PHEEBS!
ALWAYS A PLEASURE.
OH, RACHEL, SWEETIE, LOOK.
HERE'S A REALLY CUTE PICTURE
OF YOU AND JOEY AT THE RECEPTION.
OH, HE'S MARRIED.
ROSS IS MARRIED.
I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
HONEY, SWEETIE, BY THE EDGES.
I MEAN, I'M JUST GOING TO HAVE TO ACCEPT IT.
OH!
IT'S MY FAULT.
SWEETIE... EDGES...
FINGERS... SMUDGY...
OH, MY GOD! AH!
THAT'S OKAY. THAT'S OKAY.
I KNOW THAT YOU'RE VERY UPSET RIGHT NOW.
I KNOW THAT WASN'T ABOUT ME.
I BET IT WAS ABOUT HER A LITTLE.
IF YOU WOULD STOP THINKING ABOUT ROSS FOR ONE MINUTE
YOU WOULD NOTICE THERE WERE GREAT GUYS EVERYWHERE.
NOW, LOOK...
GUNTHER.
I MEAN...
HE'S NICE. HE'S CUTE.
YEAH, I GUESS GUNTHER IS...
OR HOW ABOUT
THAT GUY OVER THERE?
REMEMBER? THAT IS THE GUY THAT YOU FLIRTED WITH
AT THE COUNTER THAT TIME.
OH, I DON'T KNOW, I DON'T KNOW.
YOU'RE GOING TO TALK TO HIM.
WE MADE A DEAL.
I MAKE YOUR DECISIONS
AND I SAY YOU'RE GOING TO TALK TO HIM.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE THE BOSS.
I GUESS I GOT TO DO WHAT YOU TELL ME.
SAY THAT TO HIM AND YOU'RE GOLDEN.
HEY. HEY.
HEY, PHEEBS. HEY, PHEEBS.
WE GOT OUR PICTURES BACK FROM LONDON.
HERE'S ALL OF US AT THE TOWER OF LONDON...
OH, YEAH, THERE WE ALL ARE.
YEAH, THERE'S ROSS AND JOEY AND YOU AND...
AND ME.
WE'VE BEEN TALKING ABOUT LONDON TOO MUCH, HAVEN'T WE?
NO, I'M SORRY.
IT'S JUST BECAUSE I COULDN'T BE THERE
BECAUSE ALL I EVER GET TO DO NOW IS PREGNANT STUFF.
IT JUST BUMS ME OUT.
SORRY, PHEEBS. OH, WE'RE SORRY.
YOU KNOW WHAT I LIKE TO DO?
IT SOUNDS A LITTLE CORNY
BUT SOMETIMES WHEN I'M BUMMED OUT
I LIKE TO JUST CLOSE MY EYES
AND THINK ABOUT WHAT A WONDERFUL GIFT LIFE IS.
OH!
SEE?
UH HUH.
WHAT HAPPENED?
WELL, YOU KNOW, A LITTLE OF THIS
A LITTLE OF THAT.
I GOT MYSELF A DATE TOMORROW NIGHT.
SEE? DIDN'T I TELL YOU?
YOU'RE GETTING OVER ROSS ALREADY.
GET OUT.
WHAT TOOK YOU SO LONG?
I GOT CAUGHT UP AT WORK
BUT I'M QUITTING TOMORROW.
SO, THANKS FOR HAVING ME OVER.
RACH.
PHEEBS.
SEE YA!
WHAT THE HELL WAS THAT?
PROBABLY SOME EUROPEAN GOOD BYE THING
HE PICKED UP IN LONDON.
I DON'T...
IT'S NOT EUROPEAN.
WELL, IT FELT FRENCH.
WELL, I GUESS IT'S TIME
FOR ME TO SAY GOOD BYE, TOO... MON FRERE.
COME HERE. GIVE ME A LITTLE SUGAR.
OH, GOD, I REALLY HAD A GOOD TIME.
YEAH, ME, TOO.
SO, I GUESS THIS IS IT.
YEAH, UM...
UNLESS YOU WANT TO COME INSIDE.
YEAH.
OKAY... OH, UH...
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I, UH... I CAN'T DECIDE THIS.
UM...
OKAY, JUST HOLD ON A SECOND.
YEAH.
UH, HI.
HI.
IS MONICA AROUND?
I HAVE TO ASK HER SOMETHING.
DOING HER LAUNDRY.
WHAT'S THAT?
IT CAME IN THE MAIL TODAY.
IT'S 72 LONG STEMMED RED ROSES
ONE FOR EACH DAY I'VE KNOWN AND LOVED EMILY
CUT UP INTO MULCH.
OH, HONEY, THAT'S AWFUL.
OH, IT'S NOT SO BAD.
MONICA'S GOING TO MAKE POTPOURRI.
I THINK I'M GOING TO GO WANDER OUT
IN THE RAIN FOR A WHILE.
BUT IT'S NOT RAINING.
I CAN'T CATCH A BREAK.
YOU KNOW WHAT, ROSS?
YOU'RE NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
YOU'RE GOING TO SIT RIGHT HERE.
I'M GOING TO MAKE YOU A CUP OF TEA
AND WE'RE GOING TO TALK THIS WHOLE THING OUT.
ALL RIGHT?
HEY, DAVE.
YEAH.
LISTEN, I'M GOING TO NEED TO TAKE A RAIN CHECK.
MY ROOMMATE IS JUST REALLY SICK.
OKAY? BYE.
HONEY, LISTEN...
I KNOW...
GOD, I KNOW THINGS SEEM SO BAD...
RACH?
COULD I TALK TO YOU JUST FOR A MINUTE?
I DROPPED SOME SOCKS.
YEAH.
WHAT IS THE MATTER WITH YOU?
DO YOU WANT TO FALL INTO THE TRAP?
YOU DID NOT DROP ANY SOCKS!
I JUST RAN INTO DAVE
AND HE TOLD ME YOU BLEW HIM OFF.
YOU LISTEN TO ME.
I'M CALLING THE SHOTS.
I SAY YOU LEAVE ROSS ALONE AND GO GET DAVE.
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU TRYING TO DO?
WELL, ULTIMATELY, I WAS TRYING...
YOU KNOW, I WANTED...
TO TELL HIM I'M STILL IN LOVE WITH HIM.
WHAT?
YOU CANNOT TELL HIM THAT.
WHY? WHY NOT?
PEOPLE LOVE TO HEAR THAT.
COME ON. I LOVE YOU.
THERE. WASN'T THAT NICE?
NO. I MAKE THE DECISIONS AND I SAY "NO."
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT?
NO, YOU DON'T MAKE MY DECISIONS
BECAUSE... YOU'RE FIRED.
YOU CAN'T FIRE ME.
I MAKE YOUR DECISIONS AND I SAY I'M NOT FIRED. HA!
WELL...
RACHEL!
COME ON, LET ME IN.
HAVING SOME TROUBLE?
RACHEL LOCKED THE DOOR.
I'LL KICK THAT DOOR IN IF YOU GIVE ME A LITTLE SUGAR.
ROSS, THERE'S SOMETHING I WANT TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT.
I JUST NEED TO...
RACHEL, OPEN THIS DOOR!
WHAT, IS IT LOCKED?
SHE SHE'S FINE. LISTEN, UM...
RACHEL, I CAN DO THIS ALL NIGHT IF I HAVE TO.
DO YOU WANT ME TO GET THAT?
NO. YOU KNOW WHAT?
JUST JUST LET HER DO HER THING AND WE'LL DO OUR THING
BECAUSE I REALLY NEED TO TELL YOU...
THANK YOU.
RACHEL... CAN I TALK TO YOU OUTSIDE FOR A SEC?
NO.
I REALLY NEED TO TALK TO YOU.
WELL, THEN, TALK.
OKAY, I WILL.
REMEMBER THAT THING THAT WE JUST DISCUSSED
THAT YOU WANTED TO DO?
YES.
WHAT THING?
WELL...
RACHEL WANTS TO TAKE SWING DANCE LESSONS...
WHICH I THINK IS A REALLY STUPID IDEA.
IT'S DANGEROUS.
SHE'S NEVER GOING TO GET WHAT SHE WANTS
AND WHO KNOWS WHO SHE MIGHT
END UP HURTING?
MONICA'S RIGHT, SWING DANCING CAN BE TRICKY.
I'M GOING TO USE THE PHONE.
I GOT TO CANCEL
THOSE FIVE GIANT TEDDY BEARS I SENT TO EMILY.
MY GOD, THINK OF THE MASSACRE.
I'M GOING TO DO IT.
ALL RIGHT... RACHEL...
OKAY, I KNOW YOU THINK I'M CRAZY
BUT BEFORE YOU TELL HIM YOU LOVE HIM
JUST TRY TO FIND ONE PERSON WHO THINKS THIS IS A GOOD IDEA
BECAUSE I BET YOU CAN'T.
BUT I R...
PLEASE!
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
JOEY, I'M IN!
ALL RIGHT, GOOD DEAL.
HI.
HEY, RACH. HEY.
SO, DID YOU FIND ANYONE WHO AGREES WITH YOU YET?
NO, BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK... I THINK I NEED A MALE POINT OF VIEW.
HMM.
JOEY?
YOU'RE A MAN.
YOU GOT THAT RIGHT.
NOW, DO YOU THINK IT WOULD BE A GOOD IDEA
IF I TOLD ROSS THAT I WAS STILL IN LOVE WITH HIM?
NOPE.
HEY...
PHEEBS! PHOEBE!
HEY, PHEEBS.
UH...
OKAY... PHEEBS?
YEAH? UM...
YOU KNOW HOW THE OTHER DAY YOU WERE TALKING
ABOUT HOW YOU DIDN'T GET TO GO TO LONDON
AND YOU WERE KIND OF FEELING LEFT OUT?
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, WELL
WE ALL FELT REALLY BAD ABOUT THAT
SO... WE DECIDED
THAT WE SHOULD ALL TAKE A LITTLE TRIP TOGETHER.
OH, THAT'S SO NICE!
HOW GREAT! WHERE?
WHERE'S THE TRIP?
WELL...
WE THOUGHT WE WOULD ALL GO TO A PICNIC...
IN CENTRAL PARK!
CENTRAL PARK?
YEAH, ALL OF US, ALL DAY.
THAT SUCKS.
THAT'S NOT A TRIP.
I JUST CAME FROM THE PARK.
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO HIGH FIVE ABOUT
AT THE STUPID CENTRAL PARK?
WELL, IT'S RIGHT BY MY HOUSE.
ALL RIGHT!
WELL, I'M GOING TO GO HOME
AND BASK IN THE TRIUMPH OF MY CENTRAL PARK IDEA.
HEY, WHOA!
HOLD ON A SEC THERE, MR. KISSY.
YOU KNOW
I'VE BEEN MEANING TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT THIS WHOLE, LITTLE, NEW EUROPEAN THING
YOU'VE GOT GOING ON
AND I JUST NEED TO TELL YOU IT MAKES ME VERY UNCOMFORTABLE
AND I JUST... YOU KNOW, JUST STOP IT.
WELL, I WAS JUST TRYING
TO BRING A LITTLE CULTURE TO THE GROUP.
THAT'S FINE, JUST DON'T BRING IT IN MY MOUTH.
IT MAKES ME WANT TO PUKE.
HEY, EVERYBODY, PHEEBS IS HERE.
PHOEBE! HEY, PHOEBE!
HEY, PHEEBS!
HEY, PHOEBE, WHOO!
OKAY, WHOO, HI.
OKAY, PHEEBS... WE DECIDED
THAT THE PICNIC IDEA WAS A LITTLE...
YOU KNOW, IT DIDN'T HAVE ANY...
WELL, IT BLEW.
SO...
WE THOUGHT THAT THIS AFTERNOON
WE WOULD ALL GO AWAY FOR THE WHOLE WEEKEND
TO ATLANTIC CITY.
OOH, ATLANTIC CITY!
OH, THAT'S A GREAT PLAN.
WHOSE PLAN WAS THAT?
MINE.
WAIT.
IT WAS MY PLAN.
NO...
I SAID WE NEEDED  A NEW PLAN.
AND I CAME UP WITH ATLANTIC CITY.
WHICH IS THE NEW PLAN.
OKAY, WELL, WHY DON'T WE, UM
ALL MEET UPSTAIRS IN AN HOUR?
OKAY. OOH, ALL RIGHT, I'M GOING TO GO PACK.
I'M GOING TO GO PACK MY ASS OFF.
WHOO!
WELL, I THINK I'M GOING TO GRAB SOME COFFEE
BECAUSE MY ASS IS ALREADY PACKED.
ALL RIGHT, COME ON, RACH, LET'S GO.
YEAH, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M GOING TO MEET YOU UPSTAIRS IN A MINUTE.
NO.
RACHEL, YOU DIDN'T FIND ANYONE
SO YOU CAN'T TELL HIM.
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT?
THAT DOESN'T MATTER.
OKAY, RACHEL, DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW PAINFUL IT IS TO TELL SOMEONE THAT YOU LOVE THEM
AND NOT HAVE THEM SAY IT BACK?
I I DON'T CARE.
OKAY.
I I CAN'T WATCH.
WHATCHA READING?
PAPER.
YEAH? WHAT'S IT ABOUT?
EVENTS... FROM AROUND THE GLOBE.
OKAY.
UH... ROSS, YOU KNOW WHAT?
THERE'S SOMETHING THAT I...
THAT I HAVE TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT
AND EVERYBODY'S BEEN SAYING THAT I SHOULDN'T TELL YOU
BUT I I THINK THEY'RE WRONG.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW HOW PEOPLE CAN BE WRONG.
SURE.
ONCE, AT WORK, I...
I THOUGHT CARBON DATING OF FOSSILIZED...
OKAY, ROSS, I'M REALLY TRYING
TO TELL YOU SOMETHING HERE.
OH, UH...
YEAH.
OKAY.
GO AHEAD.
UM... OKAY.
I THINK I'M I'M JUST GO... I'M JUST GOING TO SAY IT.
I'M JUST GOING TO SAY IT.
UH...
I'M STILL IN LOVE WITH YOU... ROSS.
WOW.
UH...
HUH, I'M I'M...
WOW, I'M NOT SURE WHAT TO DO WITH THAT RIGHT NOW.
WH WHAT? WAS THAT A JOKE?
BECAUSE IT'S MEAN.
I'M SO DEAD SERIOUS.
I'M TOTALLY SERIOUS.
WHY ARE YOU LAUGHING? BECAU...
BECAUSE I JUST HEARD IT.
I HEARD IT AND IT'S RIDICULOUS!
I MEAN... YOU'RE MARRIED.
YOU'RE MARRIED AND IT'S JUST RIDICULOUS
AND IT'S, LIKE... IT'S, LIKE, WHEN I SAID IT
I JUST SORT OF, LIKE, I FLOATED UP OUT OF MY BODY, YOU KNOW
AN AND, THEN... AND, THEN, I HEARD MYSELF SAY IT
AND, THEN, THE FLOATING RACHEL...
WAS, LIKE, "YOU ARE SUCH AN IDIOT!"
WELL... WELL, I AM MARRIED...
I KNOW.
EVEN THOUGH I HAVEN'T SPOKEN TO MY WIFE SINCE THE WEDDING.
I'M SORRY, THAT'S NOT FUNNY.
ACTUALLY, IT IT KIND OF IS.
MY WIFE WON'T RETURN MY CALLS.
I DON'T KNOW WHERE MY WIFE IS.
OH, DARN.
"HEY, ROSS, WHERE'S THE MISSUS?"
"DON'T KNOW."
OH... GOD.
OH...
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
DO YOU THINK... UH, DO YOU THINK YOU COULD
JUST KIND OF FORGET THAT I TOLD YOU THIS?
WELL, I KIND OF HAVE TO, I MEAN, BECAUSE THE THING IS...
WELL, THE THING IS...
THAT... YOU KNOW, THAT YOU'RE MARRIED TO EMILY.
THAT IS WHAT THE THING IS.
OH, GOD.
THING... ROSS...
THINGS AREN'T GOING TO BE WEIRD BETWEEN US, RIGHT?
I MEAN, WAS THAT JUST THE STUPIDEST THING, ME TELLING YOU THAT?
NO, NO, NO.
GOD, I MEAN, I'M GLAD YOU DID.
LOOK, IF IF NOTHING ELSE, IT'S IT'S ALWAYS GREAT
WHEN SOMEONE TELLS YOU THEY LOVE YOU.
R... THAT'S WHAT I SAID!
ROSS, THANK YOU FOR BEING SO NICE.
NO, THANK YOU FOR...
THANK YOU.
OH, GOD. I'M JUST GLAD
I DIDN'T GIVE YOU THE CASSETTE I MADE
OF ALL OF OUR SONGS.
WHAT? WHAT, UH, WHAT SONGS?
OH, YOU KNOW, "WITH OR WITHOUT YOU."
OH, YEAH.
"EVERYBODY HURTS."
OH... YEAH.
"RHIANNON."
WH... WHY "RHIANNON"?
COME ON, YOU REMEMBER
IN THE LIVING ROOM...
ON MONICA'S LAUNDRY?
NOT ME.
REALLY?
SO, WHAT HAPPENED?
UH, WELL, IT WAS REALLY HARD
BUT I'M GLAD I DID IT.
SO, WAS I RIGHT OR WRONG?
OH, COME ON, HONEY, DOES IT REALLY MATTER?
NO.
RIGHT?
YES. I NEED IT FOR MY SCORE BOOK.
DIARY.
OKAY, LET'S GO!
YEAH, ATLANTIC CITY!
COME ON.
ATLANTIC CITY, BABY.
OOH, LET'S ROLL SOME BONES.
HEY, JOEY
HIGH FIVE FOR ROLLING BONES.
OW!
OH!
UH, PHEEBS, YOU'RE LEAKING.
OH, MY GOD, YOUR WATER BROKE.
OH... OKAY. OH...
ALL RIGHT, WELL, DON'T WORRY.
I CALL SHOTGUN.
PHEEBS!
WE HAVE TO TAKE YOU TO THE HOSPITAL NOW.
OKAY. YEAH, WELL
THERE'S PROBABLY ONE ON THE WAY TO ATLANTIC CITY.
PHEEBS, THE BABIES ARE COMING NOW.
HONEY, HIGH FIVE, THE BABIES ARE COMING.
HEY, WAIT...
REMEMBER WHEN MY WATER BROKE?
I CAN'T BELIEVE
PHOEBE'S GOING TO HAVE HER BABIES.
I KNOW, IT'S... BEAUTIFUL AND AMAZING.
YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE I CAN'T BELIEVE?
I HAD TO KISS PHOEBE AND RACHEL EVERY TIME I LEFT THE ROOM.
I MEAN, IT'S TOO BAD THEY DIDN'T SEE US HAVING SEX.
DO YOU KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT WOMEN?
NO.
IT'S ALL RIGHT. OKAY.