I'M GOING TO GET SOME MORE COFFEE TO GO.
DO YOU WANT ANYTHING, BABY DOLL?
I'M FINE. THANKS.
YEAH, SEE, I CAN'T PULL OFF "BABY DOLL," CAN I?
NO. I THINK WE LEARNED THAT
FROM THE "SUGAR LIPS" INCIDENT.
I'M GOING TO GET SOME TEA.
HOW YOU DOING, PUNKIN?
NOPE.
SO, IT LOOKS LIKE IT'S GOING REALLY WELL FOR YOU TWO, HUH?
I KNOW, REALLY WELL. IN FACT...
I'M GOING TO ASK PHOEBE TO MOVE IN WITH ME.
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I THINK THAT IS SO GREAT.
WHEN ARE YOU GOING TO ASK HER?
TONIGHT, BUT DON'T SAY ANYTHING, OKAY?
I SWEAR. I PROMISE , I PROMISE.
MY GOD, I'M SO EXCITED.
ALL RIGHT, BUT LISTEN, LET ME TELL YOU:
DO NOT GET HER FLOWERS, OKAY?
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, SHE CRIES WHEN THEY DIE
AND THEN THERE'S THE WHOLE FUNERAL...
I'LL SEE YOU AFTER WORK, SWEETIE.
OKAY. BYE.
SO, WHAT MOVIE SHOULD WE SEE?
GARY'S GOING TO ASK YOU TO MOVE IN WITH HIM!
WHAT? REALLY?
HE JUST TOLD ME AT THE COUNTER.
HE MADE ME PROMISE NOT TO TELL
BUT I COULDN'T HOLD IT IN ANY LONGER.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
RIGHT, BUT BECAUSE IT'S FAST.
BECAUSE IT'S SO FAST. IT'S FAST.
RELAX. IT'S PHOEBE , NOT YOU.
OH. GOOD FOR YOU, PHEEBS. WAY TO GO.
BUT IT IS FAST, ISN'T IT?
OH...
I LIKE HIM A LOT, BUT I DON'T THINK I'M READY FOR THIS.
SO, WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
I DON'T KNOW. I'LL JUST HANDLE IT.
I'LL ASK YOU TO TALK TO HIM.
ME? WHY ME?
BECAUSE YOU ARE SO AFRAID OF COMMITMENT.
YOU TALK TO HIM.
MAKE HIM SCARED LIKE YOU.
MAKE HIM A MAN.
I'LL TRY, BUT I'M NOT SURE
WHAT GOOD IT WOULD DO, YOU KNOW
BECAUSE I'M A LOT LESS AFRAID OF COMMITMENT
THAN I USED TO BE.
OH, THAT IS SO SWEET.
STILL TERRIFIED.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF IT. NO PROBLEM.
HEY, ROSS, IS, UH...
IS STATEN ISLAND REALLY AN ISLAND?
UH HUH.
THAT'S WHY THEY CALL IT STATEN ISLAND.
OH. I THOUGHT IT WAS LIKE LONG ISLAND.
ALSO AN ISLAND.
HEY, WHAT TIME IS IT?
2:17.
WOW, YOU REALIZE WE'VE BEEN THROWING THIS BALL
WITHOUT DROPPING IT FOR, LIKE, AN HOUR?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
I REALIZED IT A HALF HOUR AGO, BUT DIDN'T WANT TO SAY ANYTHING
BECAUSE I DIDN'T WANT TO JINX IT.
OH.
WOW, WE ARE PRETTY GOOD AT THIS.
YEAH.
HEY... WE TOTALLY FORGOT ABOUT LUNCH.
OH. I THINK THAT'S THE FIRST TIME I'VE EVER MISSED A MEAL.
YEAH?
YEAH. I THINK MY PANTS ARE A LITTLE LOOSE.
HEY, YOU GUYS, UH... IS MONICA HERE?
NO. NO. ALL RIGHT, LISTEN
I JUST BOUGHT SOMETHING.
I'M NOT SURE SHE'S GOING TO LIKE IT
AND IT'S GOING TO SEEM A LITTLE CRAZY
BUT THIS IS SOMETHING I'VE WANTED
SINCE I WAS A LITTLE GIRL.
YOU BOUGHT SHAUN CASSIDY!
NO. I WISH.
OKAY... YOU READY?
YEAH. YEAH.
OKAY.
CHECK IT OUT.
OH, MY GOD! WHAT WHAT IS...
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
IT'S IT'S A CAT.
THAT IS NOT A CAT.
YES, IT IS.
WHY IS IT INSIDE OUT?
EXCUSE ME
BUT THIS IS A PUREBRED, SHOW QUALITY SPHINX CAT.
HOW MUCH DID YOU PAY FOR THAT?
IT WAS EXTRAVAGANT, BUT I GOT A PRETTY GOOD DEAL.
YEAH? HOW MUCH?
A THOUSAND BUCKS.
ON A CAT?!
IT'S NOT A CAT.
FOR $1,000, YOU'D THINK
AT LEAST IT WOULD COME WITH HAIR.
OR SOMETHING.
ALL RIGHT, LISTEN, BALL BOYS.
MY GRANDMOTHER HAD ONE OF THESE WHEN I WAS A LITTLE GIRL
AND IT WAS THE SWEETEST THING.
I MEAN, IT WAS SO CUTE.
IT WOULD SIT IN MY LAP AND JUST PURR ALL DAY LONG
AND I WOULD DRAG A SHOESTRING ON THE GROUND
AND IT WOULD CHASE IT.
FREE CATS DO THAT, TOO, YOU KNOW.
IT'S NOT A CAT!
LOOK, YOU GUYS, I'M REALLY EXCITED ABOUT THIS, OKAY?
I DON'T CARE WHAT YOU THINK.
I'M GOING TO GO SET UP A LITTER BOX FOR MRS. WHISKERSON.
WELL, WHAT AM I GOING TO CALL HER-- FLUFFY?
YOU WANT TO GET SOMETHING TO EAT
OR DO YOU WANT TO SEE HOW LONG
WE CAN THROW THIS BALL BACK AND FORTH, HUH?
UH... THE BALL THING.
YEAH?
HEY, ROSS, WOULDN'T IT BE GREAT
IF WE COULD GO FOR, LIKE, TWO STRAIGHT HOURS
WITHOUT DROPPING IT?
UH... YEAH, IT WOULD.
LET'S DO IT.
OKAY.
UH OH.
WHAT?
I HAVE TO PEE
AND RACHEL'S IN THE BATHROOM.
MAN, I DIDN'T THINK WE WERE GOING TO MAKE IT.
I KNOW.
DON'T SWITCH HANDS, OKAY?
HEY, LADIES, WHAT ARE YOU IN HERE FOR?
HEY, CHANDLER, WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
GARY, I AM HERE
TO REPORT A CRIME.
YEAH? IT IS A CRIME THAT YOU AND I DON'T SPEND MORE TIME TOGETHER.
WHAT'S UP?
UH, WELL, I HEARD THAT YOU WERE THINKING ABOUT
ASKING PHOEBE TO MOVE IN WITH YOU
AND I THOUGHT MAYBE WE SHOULD HAVE A TALK
YOU KNOW, MAN TO... WELL, ME.
SURE. OKAY.
OKAY.
UM, ARE YOU CRAZY?
ARE YOU INSANE?
IF YOU LIVE WITH PHOEBE
YOU TWO ARE GOING TO BE, YOU KNOW, L LIVING TOGETHER.
YEAH. I CONSIDERED THAT.
I JUST KNOW IT'D MAKE ME HAPPY.
YOU MEAN SCARED.
NO, I MEAN HAPPY.
WELL, "SCARED HAPPY.2
CHANDLER, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I AM TRYING TO OPEN YOUR EYES, MY MAN.
DON'T YOU SEE?
IF YOU LIVE WITH PHOEBE
SHE'S ALWAYS GOING TO BE THERE.
YOU'RE GOING TO GET HOME-- SHE'S THERE
YOU GO TO BED- - SHE'S THERE.
YOU WAKE UP, AND, OH, YES-- SHE'S THERE.
I KNOW. I CAN'T WAIT.
WERE YOUR PARENTS HAPPY OR SOMETHING?
LISTEN, CHANDLER, THE WAY I SEE IT IS
I WAS LUCKY ENOUGH TO FIND SOMEONE THAT I REALLY LOVE.
I JUST... I WANT TO BE AROUND HER AS MUCH AS I CAN.
WOW, YOU KNOW, WHEN YOU SAY IT
IT DOESN'T SOUND SO SCARY.
SEE, YOU KNOW WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT, RIGHT?
YEAH, I THINK I DO.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU MOVE IN WITH HER.
YOU MOVE IN WITH HER RIGHT NOW.
MAYBE I SHOULD MOVE IN WITH MONICA.
NO, IT'S TOO SOON FOR YOU GUYS.
YOU'RE RIGHT ABOUT THAT.
NOW, WHEN THEY FOUND THE REMAINS
OF THE MESOZOIC MASTODON
THEY DISCOVERED WHAT APPEARED TO BE
THE REMAINS OF A PALEOZOIC AMPHIBIAN IN ITS JAWS.
HOW DID IT GET THERE?
MAYBE THIS SHOULD BE MORE OF A QUIET GAME.
HEY, GUYS.
HEY.
I LEFT MY WATCH ON THE COUNTER LAST NIGHT.
IT WAS RIGHT HERE. WHERE IS IT?
I DON'T KNOW.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, COME ON. I'M LATE FOR WORK.
HOW DO YOU KNOW? YOU DON'T HAVE A WATCH
GUYS, COULD YOU PLEASE JUST STOP THROWING THE BALL FOR ONE MINUTE
AND JUST HELP ME FIND IT?
OH, I DON'T KNOW.
YEAH, CAN'T DO IT.
NO! D...
AAH! AAH!
WHAT?
MONICA, WHATEVER YOU DO, DO NOT DROP THAT BALL.
YEAH. WE HAVEN'T DROPPED IT IN...
TWO HOURS, 27 MINUTES.
REALLY?
I'M NOT GOING TO BE ABLE TO MAKE IT IN TO WORK TODAY.
UM, I DON'T FEEL VERY GOOD.
YES!
WOW, UH, FOR A SECOND THERE
I THOUGHT I WAS FEELING BETTER, BUT I'M NOT.
BYE.
HEY, RACH.
HEY.
CHECK IT OUT--
ALMOST THREE HOURS WITHOUT DROPPING IT.
WHOO.
OH, WOW. CONGRATULATIONS.
THAT'S QUITE A WASTE OF TIME.
RACH? YEAH?
YOU HAVE SCRATCHES ALL OVER. WHAT HAPPENED?
WELL, IT'S MY CAT.
WHAT?
OH, YEAH. I GOT A CAT.
I DON'T WANT A CAT.
OH, DON'T WORRY. IT'S NOT A CAT.
YEAH.
YOU GUYS
THIS CAT IS NOTHING LIKE MY GRANDMOTHER'S CAT.
I MEAN, IT'S NOT SWEET; IT'S NOT CUTE.
I EVEN DRAGGED THAT LITTLE STRING ON THE GROUND
AND IT J JUST FLIPPED OUT AND SCRATCHED THE HELL OUT OF ME...
AND I SWEAR-- I KNOW THIS SOUNDS CRAZY--
BUT EVERY TIME THIS CAT HISSES AT ME
I KNOW IT'S SAYING:
"RACHEL."
DOESN'T SOUND AS CRAZY AS PAYING 1,000 DOLLARS FOR A CAT.
WHA...! YOU PAID 1,000 DOLLARS FOR A CAT
WHEN YOU OWE ME 300 DOLLARS
WELL, I... I WAS GOING TO LET YOU PLAY WITH IT.
HEY.
MM... DID YOU TALK
TO GARY ABOUT THE MOVING IN THING?
YES, I DID, AND I THINK YOU SHOULD DO IT.
WHAT?
HE'S A GREAT GUY, YOU KNOW
AND HE LOVES YOU A LOT.
YOU ARE A VERY LUCKY LADY.
YOU ARE USELESS.
FREAKING OUT ABOUT COMMITMENT IS THE ONE THING YOU CAN DO--
THE ONE THING-- AND YOU CAN'T EVEN DO THAT RIGHT.
GOD. I'M SORRY.
IF HE ASKED ME, I'D MOVE IN WITH HIM.
OH!
GOD.
OOH, GET OUT OF HERE, YOU GOOD FOR NOTHING.
HEY, CHANDLER.
HEY, GAR.
HEY, SWEETIE.
HI. CAN I TALK TO YOU FOR A SECOND?
YEAH... OKAY.
YOU LOOK VERY PRETTY TODAY.
THANKS. OKAY.
HERE'S THE THING-- YEAH?
I REALLY WANT THIS RELATIONSHIP TO MOVE FORWARD. MM HMM.
BECAUSE IF YOU'RE NOT MOVING FORWARD
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE JUST MOVING BACKWARDS.
NOW, THAT'S NOT TRUE.
IF YOU'RE NOT MOVING FORWARD, YOU'RE JUST STAYING STILL
AND STAYING STILL IS GOOD.
WATCH THIS.
PHOEBE?
YEAH?
I WANT YOU TO MOVE IN WITH ME.
THAT IS SO SWEET
BUT DON'T YOU THINK THAT IT'S A LITTLE TOO SOON?
THERE'S JUST SO MUCH
THAT WE DON'T KNOW ABOUT EACH OTHER.
OH.
OH, OKAY, I GET IT.
I JUST... I DON'T WANT US TO JUMP INTO SOMETHING
YOU KNOW, THAT WE'RE NOT... READY FOR.
YOU KNOW? UH HUH.
I REALLY DON'T WANT TO MESS UP WHAT WE HAVE.
I'M JUST... I'M WORRIED IT'S GOING TO BE A BIG MISTAKE.
HUH.
WHICH IS WHY MY ANSWER IS YES!
REALLY?
UH HUH.
OH, YOU'RE SO HAPPY.
MONICA, STOP THROWING IT SO HARD!
WE'RE ON THE SAME TEAM.
FOUR HOURS?
YOU GUYS HAVE BEEN DOING THIS FOR FOUR HOURS?
THAT'S RIGHT, BABY.
ALL RIGHT, I'M IN.
NO, NO! DON'T DO IT!
DON'T!
WHAT?
HE'S A DROPPER.
OH, YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT!
I'M NOT A DROPPER!
IT'S REALLY A A A... THREE PERSON GAME, YOU KNOW?
IT'S THROWING AND CATCHING.
ALL RIGHT.
OH, OH, IT'S SO HARD.
DON'T WORRY, GUYS. IT'S NOT A CAT.
OH, MY... OH, GOOD GOD.
I GIVE UP, YOU GUYS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M GOING TO DO WITH THIS THING.
BAKING IT DIDN'T HELP, HUH?
SO WHY DON'T YOU
JUST TAKE IT BACK TO WHERE YOU GOT IT?
I TRIED. THEY WON'T TAKE HER BACK.
MAYBE THAT'S BECAUSE SHE'S A MINION OF THE ANTICHRIST.
RACH...
WHY WON'T THEY TAKE IT BACK?
WELL, THEY SAID THEY WOULD
BUT THEY WOULD ONLY GIVE ME STORE CREDIT
AND, I MEAN, WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?
GET A THOUSAND REGULAR CATS?
YOU SAID IT WAS A SHOW CAT.
WHY DON'T YOU SHOW IT?
WIN SOME PRIZE MONEY?
THOSE SHOWS COST, LIKE, 100 BUCKS TO ENTER
AND ALL YOU WIN ARE THESE RIBBONS
WHICH, TECHNICALLY, BELONG TO THE DAMN CAT.
LOOK, IF YOU WANT, YOU CAN KEEP IT AT OUR PLACE
UNTIL YOU FIND OUT WHAT TO DO WITH IT.
NO, MON, THAT'S NOT THE POINT.
I AM OUT 1,000 DOLLARS I AM ALL SCRATCHED UP
AND I'M STUCK WITH THIS STUPID CAT THAT LOOKS LIKE A HAND.
OH, MY GOD.
THE CAT'S MADE MY EYES WATER.
DON'T DON'T THROW IT TO ME!
MY VISION'S BEEN COMPROMISED!
OH, GOD. OKAY, OKAY...
IT'S OKAY.
MAN, THAT WAS CLOSE.
YEAH. YOU ALMOST OVERREACTED TO SOMETHING.
HEY. HEY.
WE HAVE GREAT NEWS.
WE'RE MOVING IN TOGETHER!
ISN'T IT GREAT? YAY!
YAY!
CONGRATULATIONS. THAT'S GREAT.
I KNOW. I'M SO EXCITED.
SO AM I.
WELL, YOU'RE NOT MORE EXCITED THAN I AM.
NO WAY. I'M THE MOST EXCITED.
OKAY, I'LL SEE YOU AT THE STATION LATER.
YEAH, I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
DON'T FORGET ABOUT THE MOVING IN.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU'RE MOVING IN WITH HIM? WHAT HAPPENED?
I COULDN'T TELL HIM NO-- HE GOT SO SAD.
BUT MAYBE IT'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
I DO REALLY LIKE HIM A LOT
AND WOULD PROBABLY DO IT EVENTUALLY ANYWAY...
AND, PLUS, THINK OF ALL THE MONEY I'LL SAVE ON STAMPS.
WHY? DO YOU WRITE HIM A LOT?
NO. I JUST HEARD WHEN PEOPLE LIVE TOGETHER
THEY SPLIT THE COST OF STAMPS, DON'T THEY?
YEAH.
THAT'S RIGHT. YEAH, YEAH.
OH!
OH... I'M SORRY.
THE OVEN MITTS REALLY FREAKED ME OUT.
HI, HONEY. HEY, HONEY.
DID YOU FIND ANY APARTMENTS IN BROOKLYN HEIGHTS?
NO. NOTHING.
OH. REALLY? YEAH.
NOTHING AT ALL? NO.
AS SOON AS SOMETHING OPENS UP, WE'LL MOVE RIGHT IN.
UNLESS IT DOESN'T HAVE A POOL; I NEED A POOL.
PHOEBE, CAN I TALK TO YOU FOR A SECOND?
UH HUH.
TAKE A SEAT.
ALL RIGHT.
YOU OKAY?
YOU FEEL ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, I FEEL GREAT, BECAUSE WE'RE MOVING IN TOGETHER.
SO YOU, UH...
YOU CHECKED THE PAPER FOR LISTINGS
IN BROOKLYN HEIGHTS, RIGHT?
YOU YOU CHECKED THE POST?
YEAH. UH HUH. THERE WAS NOTHING.
COULD I GET SOME WATER?
IN A MINUTE.
YOU YOU CHECKED TODAY'S POST?
UM, YEAH. TODAY'S. MM HMM.
HMM...
BECAUSE, UH, THIS IS TODAY'S POST
AND, UH, THESE ARE THE LISTINGS I FOUND.
"BROOKLYN HEIGHTS, TWO BEDROOMS."
"BROOKLYN HEIGHTS, ONE BEDROOM."
"BROOKLYN HEIGHTS," "BROOKLYN HEIGHTS," "BROOKLYN HEIGHTS."
OH, ARE THESE FOR RENT?
I THOUGHT PEOPLE WERE JUST BRAGGING.
LET ME TELL YOU WHAT I THINK MIGHT BE GOING ON HERE.
NO, NO. DON'T LOOK AT THE TABLE.
LOOK AT ME.
OKAY?
I THINK SOMEBODY ASKED SOMEONE TO MOVE IN WITH HIM
AND I THINK SOMEONE SAID YES
BUT NOW SHE'S HAVING DOUBTS BECAUSE
MAYBE THINGS ARE MOVING TOO FAST FOR SOMEONE.
DOES THAT SOUND AT ALL
POSSIBLE TO YOU?
YES, YES, YES, FINE!
I AM SOMEONE!
YOU WANT ME TO SAY IT?
I HAVE DOUBTS.
I'M SORRY!
PHOEBE?
YEAH?
PHOEBE, IT'S OKAY THAT YOU FEEL THIS WAY.
I MEAN, IT IS SOON
AND THERE'S A LOT OF THINGS WE DON'T KNOW ABOUT EACH OTHER.
I FIGURED EVERYTHING I KNOW ABOUT YOU, I REALLY LIKE;
AND THE THINGS I DON'T KNOW, I'D GET TO LEARN ABOUT
IN A PLACE WITH BOTH OUR NAMES ON THE MAILBOX.
THAT'S SO SWEET.
SWEETHEART
BUT NONE OF THAT MATTERS IF IT'S TOO SOON FOR YOU
IT'S FINE. WE DON'T HAVE TO MOVE IN TOGETHER.
I JUST... I WANT YOU TO BE HAPPY.
LIVING WITH YOU WOULD MAKE ME HAPPY.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO SAY THAT.
NO, I REALLY WANT TO LIVE WITH YOU.
I WANT TO MOVE IN WITH YOU.
ARE YOU SURE?
YES. DEFINITELY, YES.
LET'S LIVE IN AN APARTMENT THAT WE BOTH LIVE IN.
OH, THAT'S GREAT!
OH, WAIT. ONE SEC, ONE SEC.
HEY, YOU-- BEHIND THE GLASS-- WHO ARE YOU LOOKING AT?!
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED TO SAY THAT
EVERY TIME I WAS IN ONE OF THESE ROOMS
WHICH WAS NEVER.
SHOW CAT!
QUALITY SHOW CAT!
OH, MY GOD!
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOUR BABY?
THAT'S NOT A BABY.
THAT'S A CAT.
EWW! IT'S CREEPY LOOKING.
OH, NO.
ACTUALLY, IT'S VERY SWEET.
IT'S VERY SWEET. LOOK.
YEAH. DO YOU WANT IT?
NO. I HATE CATS.
WELL, SO, THEN WHAT ARE YOU DOING TO ME? OKAY?
JUST GET OUT OF HERE, ALL RIGHT? MOVE ON
SHEESH.
WOW, WHAT AN UNUSUAL CAT.
YES. THANK YOU. EXACTLY.
YOU WANT IT?
MAYBE.
I WAS THINKING ABOUT GETTING A CAT.
I WAS JUST GOING TO  GO TO THE SHELTER, BUT...
OKAY, WHY NOT?
OH, TERRIFIC.
THAT'LL BE 2,000 DOLLARS.
WHAT?
OKAY, 1,000 DOLLARS.
I THOUGHT YOU WANTED ME TO ADOPT YOUR CAT.
WELL, I DO
BUT YOU'RE JUST GOING TO HAVE TO ACTUALLY LOOK AT THIS
AS MORE OF AN INVESTMENT THAN A CAT.
OKAY, YEAH. I JUST WANTED A CAT.
YEAH. OKAY, OKAY...
OBVIOUSLY, YOU KNOW HOW TO HAGGLE
SO I'M NOT GOING TO TRY AND TAKE YOU ON, OKAY?
SO $800 AND I DON'T CALL THE COPS, WHICH I SHOULD
BECAUSE YOU ARE ROBBING ME BLIND! BLIND!
JUST TAKE THE CAT, LEAVE THE MONEY AND RUN AWAY.
JUST RUN AWAY.
DAMN IT!
CAN'T YOU AT LEAST SMILE OR SOMETHING?
OKAY, DID ANYBODY JUST HEAR THAT?
ANYBODY?
I'M STARVING.
COME ON, GUYS, SUCK IT UP.
WE'RE CLOSING IN ON TEN HOURS.
IT'S GUT CHECK TIME.
I DON'T KNOW WHO MADE YOU THE BOSS, ALL RIGHT?
WE INVENTED THIS GAME.
PLEASE
I MADE THIS GAME WHAT IT IS.
NOT FUN ANYMORE?
I'M STILL HUNGRY.
ALL RIGHT, THERE'S SOME PIZZA AT MY PLACE.
WE CAN ALL EAT WITH ONE HAND, RIGHT?
ARE YOU WITH ME?
I AM.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO! COME ON! COME ON!
LET'S GO, TEAM MONICA!
WE CAN WORK OUT THAT NAME LATER.
RACHEL...
WHAT IS YOUR CAT DOING IN ONE OF MY BOWLS?
IT'S NOT. I'M DEFROSTING A CHICKEN.
OH, I SOLD MRS. WHISKERSON.
OH, THANK GOD.
DID YOU GET YOUR MONEY BACK?
YEAH. 1,500 DOLLARS.
YOU MADE A PROFIT?
I JUST CAME FOR THE RED VELVET PILLOW.
OH, YEAH.
THERE YOU GO.
THANKS, RACHEL, AND, UH, DON'T FORGET
YOU CAN COME VISIT HER ANYTIME YOU WANT.
OH, GOOD. GREAT.
I I'LL KEEP THAT IN MIND.
HEY.
SO WHAT IS THIS, SOME KIND OF SNAKE OR SOMETHING?
I REALLY LIKE WAKING UP WITH YOU.
I LIKE WAKING UP WITH YOU, TOO.
OH, IT'S SUCH A BEAUTIFUL MORNING.
I COULD STAY HERE ALL DAY
THAT WOULD BE GREAT.
WE COULD HAVE BREAKFAST IN BED...
JUST A SECOND.
OKAY.
OH!
OH, NO.
ALL RIGHT, COME ON, MONICA!
LOOK ALIVE.
COME ON, LOOK ALIVE.
ROSS!
OH, I WAS HAVING THE BEST DREAM.
WHAT?
I DREAMED I WAS DROWNING
AND NOT THROWING THIS BALL.
OH, GOOD. YOU'RE ALL UP.
HEY. HEY.
PHOEBE, IT'S 6 AM IN THE MORNING .
WHY AREN'T YOU AT GARY'S?
OH, YEAH. THAT'S OVER. WHAT? WHAT?
GARY'S SUCH A GREAT GUY.
WHATEVER THE PROBLEM IS, YOU CAN WORK IT OUT.
HE SHOT A BIRD. OH, THAT IS OVER.
OH, HONEY, I'M SORRY.
THAT'S TERRIBLE.
PHOEBE, ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH, YEAH, I'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
WELL, HEY, HERE, PHEEBS.
OH. NAH, I DON'T FEEL LIKE PLAYING.
IT'S OKAY.
IT'S OKAY, OKAY?
LOOK...
JUST PRETEND THAT IT DIDN'T HAPPEN, OKAY?
NO ONE NEEDS TO KNOW.
PHOEBE... PHOEBE'S NOT AN OFFICIAL BALLPLAYER.
I MEAN, ONLY OFFICIAL BALLPLAYERS CAN DROP THE BALL.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO. OKAY.
OKAY.
PHOEBE, WANT TO GET SOME BREAKFAST?
YEAH. OKAY.
OKAY, LET'S RACE.
FIRST ONE THERE WINS.
HA HA!
YOU GUYS WANT TO EAT HERE?
YEAH. YEAH. YEAH.
OH, MAN, THAT WAS GREAT, HUH?
CAN YOU BELIEVE HOW LONG
WE THREW THAT BALL AROUND?
IT IS AMAZING IT LASTED THAT LONG.
I KNOW. MY A RM IS KILLING ME.
NO. I MEANT WITH THE DROPPER OVER HERE.
OH, YEAH.
HOW DID I GET THIS REPUTATION AS A DROPPER, OKAY?
I'M ANYTHING BUT A DROPPER.
ROSS.