WHAT'S GOING ON?
HUH? WELL, MY EYE IS A LITTLE ITCHY.
UH... MINE, TOO. YEAH.
WOW, IT'S REALLY RED.
YOU SHOULD GO SEE MY EYE DOCTOR.
RICHARD? I'M NOT GOING  TO GO SEE YOUR EX BOYFRIEND.
RICHARD-- THAT'S ALL I EVER HEAR.
RICHARD, RICHARD, RICHARD.
SINCE WE'VE BEEN GOING OUT
I THINK I'VE MENTIONED HIS NAME TWICE.
OKAY, SO RICHARD, RICHARD.
IT'S NOT RICHARD, OKAY?
IT'S THIS NEW GUY, AND HE'S REALLY GOOD.
WELL, I'M SORRY, I'M NOT GOING TO AN EYE DOCTOR.
OH, GOD, HERE WE GO. WHAT?
ANYTIME ANYTHING COMES CLOSE TO TOUCHING HER EYE
OR ANYONE ELSE'S, SHE, LIKE, FREAKS OUT.
WATCH. WATCH.
ROSS! COME ON. THAT'S... ALL RIGHT, FINE, OKAY
I HAVE A WEIRD THING WITH MY EYE.
CAN WE JUST NOT TALK ABOUT IT, PLEASE?
ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT.
HEY, RACH, YOU KNOW THAT GREAT SONG
UM, "ME, MYSELF AND...EYE"?
AAH! MONICA! COME ON.
HEY, DOES ANYONE WANT TO GET SOME LUNCH?
ALL THOSE IN FAVOR, SAY "EYE."
ROSS! STOP IT! COME ON.
HOW MUCH DID EYE LOVE
THE KING ANDEYE?
CHANDLER. ALL RIGHT...
ME, TOO! ME, TOO! ME, TOO!
ALL RIGHT, JUST STOP IT!
THAT'S ENOUGH! COME ON.
YOU OKAY THERE, MAN?
YEAH. I GOT TOO EXCITED.
ALL RIGHT, I GOT TO GO.
I'M TAKING BEN TO THE PARK.
OH, GIVE HIM A KISS FOR ME.
ALL RIGHT. BYE.
BYE. BYE.
LATER.
I AM SO SORRY YOU GOT CAUGHT IN THE MIDDLE OF THAT.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO BE SO OUT THERE
BUT I AM FURIOUS WITH HIM.
WOW. UM...
CALM DOWN?
I'M TRYING, BUT, MAN, THAT GUY CAN PUSH MY BUTTONS.
WHY ARE YOU SO MAD AT HIM?
LOOK, I DON'T WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT, OKAY?
IT JUST SEEMS... YOU WANT
TO BE ON MY LIST, TOO?
KEEP TALKING.
HAS ANYONE SEEN MY LIST, BY THE WAY?
UH, NO, PHEEBS. WHAT'S IT LOOK LIKE?
IT'S A PIECE OF PAPER, AND IT SAYS "ROSS" ON IT.
I SEE.
HI. HEY. HEY.
I JUST GOT OFF THE PHONE WITH ESTELLE, AND GUESS WHAT?
I GOT THE LEAD IN A MOVIE!
CONGRATULATIONS! THAT'S AMAZING.
WHAT'S THE MOVIE ABOUT?
OH, UH, IT'S CALLED SHUTTER SPEED.
IT'S REALLY COOL. YEAH.
UM, WELL, I MEET THIS GIRL ON THE SUBWAY
AND WE FALL IN LOVE IN, LIKE, A DAY, RIGHT?
AND THEN, SHE DISAPPEARS
BUT I FIND OUT WHERE SHE LIVES, AND WHEN I GET THERE
THIS, LIKE, OLD LADY ANSWERS THE DOOR
AND I SAY, "WHERE'S BETSY?"
RIGHT? AND SHE SAYS, "BETSY'S BEEN DEAD FOR TEN YEARS."
OOH... CHILLING.
YEAH.
OH, AND THE BEST PART IS
WE'RE FILMING IN THE DESERT OUTSIDE OF VEGAS.
YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS, BUDDY? I KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS, BUDDY.
ROAD TRIP! YEAH. WE CAN RENT A CAR.
I JUST HAVE TO BE THERE BY TUESDAY.
OOH, WAIT, MY GRANDMOTHER'S DEAD.
WELL, UH... WE CAN TALK ABOUT THAT, TOO, PHEEBS.
NO, NO.
HER CAB-- SHE PROBABLY WON'T BE USING IT.
YOU COULD DRIVE IT TO LAS VEGAS.
ALL RIGHT! THANKS, PHEEBS.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO ABOUT MY JOB?
OH, UH, NOT GO.
ALL RIGHT! GREAT! ROAD TRIP, BABY!
IS THIS OKAY WITH YOU?
CHANDLER, YOU DON'T HAVE TO ASK FOR MY PERMISSION.
YOU CAN GO. THANK YOU.
HEY, RACH, COME ON.
YOU'RE GOING TO BE LATE FOR THE EYE DOCTOR APPOINTMENT.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET THIS OVER WITH.
OH... NO.
LOOK WHAT I DID.
OH...
I MEAN, LOOK AT THIS MESS.
I MEAN, WE'RE GOING TO PROBABLY HAVE TO CLEAN THIS UP, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO RESCHEDULE.
IF YOU THOUGHT THAT THIS MESS WAS GOING TO BOTHER ME
YOU ARE WRONG.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO, BLINKY. ALL RIGHT.
CHANDLER...
OH, HEY, JOEY.
HEY. WHAT'S UP?
WELL, I CAN'T DECIDE WHICH ROUTE TO TAKE TO VEGAS.
HEY... YOU'VE TRAVELED A LOT, RIGHT?
YEAH, I'VE BEEN AROUND. OKAY...
SO... SO WHICH ROUTE SHOULD I TAKE
THE NORTHERN ROUTE OR THE SOUTHERN ROUTE?
OOH, IF YOU TAKE THE NORTHERN ROUTE
THERE'S A MAN IN ILLINOIS WITH A BEARD OF BEES.
GREAT! PROBLEM SOLVED.
BUT ON THE SOUTHERN ROUTE
THERE'S A CHICKEN THAT PLAYS TIC TAC TOE.
WELL, BACK TO SQUARE ONE.
OH, I KNOW A WAY THAT YOU CAN DECIDE.
ALL RIGHT, I'M GOING TO ASK YOU A SERIES OF QUESTIONS
AND YOU ANSWER AS QUICKLY AS YOU CAN.
YES.
GOOD, BUT WAIT.
OKAY... ALL RIGHT
HERE WE GO. NOW, I WANT YOU TO RELAX...
TAKE A DEEP BREATH , CLEAR YOUR MIND...
WHICH DO YOU LIKE BETTER
PEANUT BUTTER OR EGG WHITES? PEANUT BUTTER.
WOULD YOU RATHER BE A FIREMAN OR A SWIMMER? A SWIMMER.
WOULD YOU RATHER SLEEP WITH MONICA OR RACHEL? MONICA. OH...
HUH. I ALWAYS THOUGHT IT'D BE RACHEL.
NO THINKING, NO THINKING.
TIE OR ASCOT? ASCOT.
NORTH ROUTE OR SOUTH ROUTE? NORTH ROUTE.
BAM! THERE YOU GO, HUH?
WOW.
THAT WAS INCREDIBLE.
BEARD OF BEES, HERE I COME.
HEY.
OH, THIS GUY AGAIN.
HEY, MAN, WHAT'S UP?
UH, NOT MUCH.
YOU GUYS WANT TO SEE A MOVIE TONIGHT?
SURE. WHAT DO YOU WANT TO SEE?
I DON'T KNOW. UM...
I KNOW HOW WE CAN DECIDE.
PHOEBE, SHOW HIM YOUR GAME.
UM, NO, THANK YOU.
WHAT'S WITH HER?
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT, HEY, I KNOW HOW WE CAN DECIDE.
OKAY, I'M GOING TO ASK YOU QUESTIONS
AND YOU ANSWER REAL QUICK, OKAY?
OKAY.
WHAT DO YOU LIKE BETTER, ACTION OR COMEDY? ACTION.
WHO WOULD YOU RATHER SLEEP WITH, MONICA OR RACHEL?
DUDE, YOU ARE SICK.
OH, RIGHT, I'M SORRY.
I FORGOT YOU HAD THAT WHOLE RACHEL THING.
I'M SORRY.
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT DOES THAT THING DO?
HMM. THAT'S AN EYE REMOVAL MACHINE.
ALL RIGHT, I'M OUT OF HERE.
I'M KIDDING, I'M KIDDING.
UH OH. HI, RACHEL.
I'M DR. MILLER.
MONICA TOLD ME YOU WERE A LITTLE NERVOUS
BUT EVERYTHING'S GOING TO BE JUST FINE.
SO, WE'RE DONE THEN.
ALMOST, BUT FIRST, WE GOT TO START. OKAY.
THIS IS THE GLAUCOMA TEST.
UH HUH.
SIT DOWN.
OKAY.
PUT YOUR CHIN HERE.
MM HMM.
NOW, YOU'RE GOING TO FEEL
A SMALL PUFF OF AIR IN EACH EYE.
W WH WHAT?
A SMALL PUFF OF AIR.
NOW, COME ON!
HERE WE GO.
ALL RIGHT.
ONE, TWO, THREE.
WHOOPS! SORRY.
ALL RIGHT, JUST...
I'M STAYING HERE THIS TIME.
OKAY.
READY? UH HUH.
ONE, TWO, TH...
I'M SORRY.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M GOING TO HOLD HER HEAD.
THAT'S OKAY.
OKAY. OKAY.
OKAY.
ONE... UH HUH.
TWO...
I'M SORRY.
YOU KNOW WHAT? YOU'RE YOUNG
YOU PROBABLY DON'T
HAVE GLAUCOMA.
OKAY, SO...
IT'S WAS VERY, VERY NICE TO MEET YOU, SIR.
OH, HEY... WHAT... ARE YOU CRAZY?
OKAY, YOU HAVE A SMALL , MINOR INFECTION
IN THAT LEFT EYE.
I WANT YOU TO TAKE THESE DROPS
THREE TIMES  A DAY FOR A WEEK
AND YOU'LL BE AS GOOD AS NEW.
NO, I DON'T PUT THINGS IN MY EYE.
OKAY, THEN, I GUESS WE'LL SEE YOU
BACK HERE IN THREE MONTHS
GREAT. AND I'LL FIT YOU FOR A GLASS EYE.
OKAY, JUST GIVE ME THE DAMN DROPS.
DR. MILLER...
P E C F D.
VERY GOOD, MONICA.
YOU KNOW WHERE THEY ARE.
I SURE DO.
AND YOU DON'T GET ONE
YOU KNOW, I GOT TO TELL YOU
THOSE EYE DROPS ARE A MIRACLE.
MY EYE IS 100% BETTER.
THEY'RE STILL IN MY COAT.
DAMN.
HEY.
HEY, YOU READY TO GO?
YEAH. LISTEN, HOW COLD IS IT GOING TO BE THERE?
DO I NEED A COAT OR WILL ALL THESE SWEATER VESTS BE ENOUGH.
WHAT?
I LOVE YOU.
MAN, I WISH ROSS WAS COMING WITH US, YOU KNOW?
I'M GOING TO MISS HIM.
THANKS A LOT.
I JUST GOT THAT JERK OUT OF MY MIND.
HEY, SO WHERE ARE WE STAYING?
IS THE MOVIE PUTTING US UP
IN A BIG HOTEL SUITE?
NO, NOT REALLY.
IT'S AN INDEPENDENT FILM
SO WE DON'T HAVE A REAL BIG BUDGET.
I FIGURED I'D JUST STAY IN YOUR ROOM.
I SEE, BUT ONCE YOU GET YOUR FIRST PAYCHECK
YOU'LL BE SPRINGING FOR A BIG HOTEL SUITE, RIGHT?
I MEAN, LEAD IN A MOVIE--
THEY MUST BE PAYING YOU A LOT.
OH, YEAH. CHECK THIS OUT--
FOR EVERY DOLLAR SHUTTER SPEED MAKES
ONE PENNY OF IT GOES RIGHT IN JOEY'S POCKET.
SO YOU DON'T GET PAID
UNLESS THE MOVIE MAKES MONEY?
DID YOU NOT HEAR THE PLOT OF THE MOVIE?
SHE'S BEEN DEAD FOR TEN YEARS.
I'M GOING TO BE A MILLIONAIRE!
HEY. HEY. HEY.
JUST WANTED TO SAY GOOD BYE TO YOU GUYS
AND TO SEE IF MAYBE YOU GUYS
WILL PLACE A LITTLE BET FOR ME, HUH?
20 BUCKS ON BLACK 15.
YOU GOT IT. ALL RIGHT.
YOU REMEMBER THE NUMBER, RIGHT?
YEAH. BLACK 13.
BLACK 15!
YOU GOT IT.
BYE BYE, NOW.
BYE, YOU GUYS. BYE.
I'LL SAY GOOD BYE AT THE CAR. OKAY.
OH, ANYBODY WANT TO SAY GOOD BYE TO ME AT THE CAR?
OH, HONEY, I'LL SAY GOOD BYE TO YOU AT THE CAR
IF YOU DON'T MIND THE PUS.
SEE YA.
NO, WAIT A MINUTE.
THE PUS IS GOOD.
IT MEANS IT'S HEALING.
HEY, PHEEBS, WHATCHA READING?
PHEEBS?
HELLO.
PHOEBE?
PHEE... PHEE... PHOEBE.
PHOEBE, COME ON.
OH, I'M SORRY. I DIDN'T SEE YOU THERE.
PHEEBS, ARE YOU MAD AT ME OR SOMETHING?
BECAUSE IF YOU ARE
PLEASE TELL ME WHAT IT IS I DID.
WELL, IF YOU DON'T KNOW, I CAN'T HELP YOU.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW.
WELL, I CAN'T HELP YOU.
OKAY, WELL, WHATEVER IT IS
I AM VERY, VERY SORRY, OKAY?
APOLOGY ACCEPTED.
OKAY.
SO WE'RE... WE'RE GOOD?
UH HUH.
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER, OKAY?
BYE, FAT ASS.
ALL RIGHT!
PHOEBE, NOW, COME ON.
WOULD YOU PLEASE TELL ME WHAT IT IS
THAT MADE YOU SO MAD AT ME?!
I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T REMEMBER.
WHAT? WHAT DO YOU MEAN, YOU CAN'T REMEMBER?
I WAS SO FOCUSED ON BEING MAD AT YOU
THAT I FORGOT WHAT IT WAS I WAS MAD ABOUT.
WELL, IF YOU CAN'T REMEMBER
CAN'T WE JUST FORGET ABOUT THIS?
OH, NO. I AM MAD AT YOU.
I KNOW THAT MUCH.
BUT I AM SORRY ABOUT THE "FAT ASS" THING
BECAUSE YOU ACTUALLY HAVE A VERY SWEET LITTLE HEINIE.
MAN, I'M GETTING PRETTY TIRED.
YOU MIGHT HAVE TO TAKE OVER SOON.
WE'VE BEEN DRIVING FOR A HALF HOUR...
AND YOU HAVEN'T LOOKED AT THE ROAD ONCE.
DON'T WORRY. IT'S OUT THERE.
MAYBE I JUST NEED LUNCH.
YEAH.
YOU WANT TO EAT?
MY TREAT.
ISN'T THAT ROSS' MONEY?
YEAH, OKAY, ROSS' TREAT.
WHERE DO YOU WANT TO EAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
OH, HEY.
I KNOW HOW WE CAN DECIDE.
I'M GOING TO ASK YOU A BUNCH OF QUESTIONS
AND THEN YOU HAVE TO ANSWER REAL FAST, OKAY?
SO, CLEAR YOUR MIND.
CLEAR IT RIGHT OUT. CLEAR IT OUT. CLEAR.
OKAY.
OKAY, IT'S ALL CLEAR
EXCEPT FOR THIS IMAGE OF A SMALL, PURPLE LAMP.
IS IT ALL RIGHT IF THAT STAYS IN THERE?
I DON'T SEE WHY NOT.
YEAH, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, YOU HAVE TO ANSWER.
THE FIRST THING THAT POPS INTO YOUR HEAD.
OKAY, WOULD YOU RATHER BE TOO WET OR TOO DRY? TOO DRY.
DO YOU BELIEVE IN GHOSTS? YES OR NO. NO.
IS THE MOVIE GOING TO BE MY BIG BREAK? NO.
WHAT?
YES.
DUDE, YOU SAID NO.
WELL, I ALSO SAID YES.
WELL, YOU DON'T THINK
THIS IS GOING TO BE A BIG BREAK FOR ME?
NO...
I DON'T BELIEVE THIS.
LOOK, JOE, I JUST...
I JUST DON'T WANT YOU
TO GET YOUR HOPES UP TOO HIGH, YOU KNOW?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I'M THE LEAD IN A MOVIE.
THEY'RE NOT EVEN PAYING YOU.
THIS DOESN'T EVEN SOUND LIKE A REAL MOVIE.
YOU KNOW WHAT? I DON'T NEED THIS, OKAY?
I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU'RE DUMPING ALL OVER MY BIG BREAK.
BECAUSE, JOE, I DON'T THINK THIS IS GOING TO BE YOUR BIG BREAK.
IS THAT WHY YOU'RE ON THIS TRIP, HUH?
TO MAKE ME FEEL LIKE A LOSER?
BECAUSE IF IT IS, I'LL TELL YOU, I'D RATHER BE ALONE.
OH, YOU DON'T WANT ME ON THE TRIP.
NOT IF YOU'RE GOING TO BE LIKE THIS.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
THE NEXT TIME YOU ASK ME A QUESTION LIKE THAT, I'LL LIE.
YEAH, I DON'T WANT YOU ON THE TRIP.
ALL RIGHT, FINE, FINE.
WHY DON'T YOU PULL OVER? I'LL GET OUT RIGHT NOW.
FINE.
GET OUT.
YOU'RE NOT ACTUALLY SUPPOSED TO STOP ON A BRIDGE.
GET OUT!
ALL RIGHT!
WAIT! WAIT! THERE'S NO SIDEWALK!
YEAH, I'M GOING TO DIE HERE.
OKAY, ARE YOU MADE AT ME BECAUSE MY HAIR GEL SMELLS?
NO.
ARE YOU ANGRY WITH ME BECAUSE I SAID
YOUR HANDWRITING IS CHILD LIKE?
NO. THAT MADE ME FEEL PRECIOUS.
OH, I KNOW.
IS IT BECAUSE HE'S ALWAYS CORRECTING PEOPLE'S GRAMMAR?
"WHOM. WHOM."
SOMETIMES IT'S "WHO."
YEAH? SOMETIMES IT'S...
OH, DID YOU BEAT HIM AT A BOARD GAME?
HE TURNS INTO SUCH A BABY WHEN HE STARTS TO LOSE.
OH, YEAH, I'M THE BABY.
HEY, STOP IT!
HEY.
CHANDLER, WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
JOEY KICKED ME OUT OF THE CAR
ON THE GEORGE WASHINGTON BRIDGE.
WHY? WHY?
HE WENT CRAZY.
WE WERE PLAYING THAT GAME WHERE YOU ASK A QUESTION
AND YOU HAVE TO ANSWER REALLY FAST.
OH, THAT GAME SHOULD NOT BE PLAYED WITHOUT MY SUPERVISION.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW WHAT MADE HIM SO MAD.
ALL I SAID WAS THAT I DIDN'T THINK
THIS WAS GOING TO BE HIS BIG BREAK.
THAT THIS MOVIE WASN'T GOING TO DO ANYTHING FOR HIM
AND THAT IT DIDN'T SOUND LIKE A REAL MOVIE.
OKAY, HE SHOULD HAVE PUSHED ME OFF THE BRIDGE.
WHAT'S IN THE BAG?
OH, I FIGURED YOU GUYS WOULD ALL BE MAD AT ME
SO I GOT YOU SOME GIFTS THAT I FOUND ON THE SIDE OF THE ROAD.
WHO WANTS THE TEDDY BEAR WITH ONE LEG?
I DO.
OKAY...
NOT EVEN CLOSE.
OKAY, THEN YOU KNOW WHAT? HELP ME. I NEED HELP.
I CAN'T DO THIS.
OKAY, COME ON, LET'S DO IT.
ALL RIGHT.
SIT DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, PUT YOUR HEAD BACK.
YES.
ALL RIGHT, NOW OPEN YOUR EYES.
OKAY, THEY ARE.
HOW MANY FINGERS AM I HOLDING UP?
FOUR.
OH, MY GOD, I WAS THINKING FOUR.
REALLY?
YES!
YOU KNOW WHAT?
WHY DON'T WE START WITH A PRACTICE ONE, OKAY?
NO DROPS.
GREAT.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT, ON THREE.
ONE... TWO... THREE.
MY PILLOW'S ALL WET.
WELL, YOU SAID IT WAS PRACTICE.
THEN WHY DID YOU MOVE?
BECAUSE I KNEW YOU WERE LYING.
ALL RIGHT, COME HERE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
GET... JUST GET...
MONICA, STOP IT!
OH, MY GOD! STOP IT!
I AM GOING...
TURN IT OVER!
NO!
I AM... I AM GOING TO GET...
GET THESE DROPS IN YOUR EYES.
OH, MY GOD!
YOU REALLY ARE FREAKISHLY STRONG.
MONICA, STOP IT!
DAMN! IT'S EMPTY!
WELL, IF JOEY AND CHANDLER WALKED IN RIGHT NOW
WE COULD MAKE A FORTUNE.
OH, THAT IS DEFINITELY CHANDLER, JOEY OR ROSS...
OR RACHEL.
HELLO. IT'S JOEY.
I'M SO GLAD YOU CALLED.
CHANDLER TOLD ME WHAT HAPPENED.
YOU KNOW, HE'S REALLY UPSET ABOUT IT.
NOT AS UPSET AS HE'S GOING TO BE WHEN HE FINDS OUT WHAT I DID
WITH HIS SWEATER VESTS.
WHAT DID YOU DO TO HIS SWEATER VESTS?
LET'S JUST SAY THERE'S A WELL DRESSED PACK OF DOGS
in Ohio.
Hey, Monica, is Phoebe there?
I GOT TO ASK HER SOMETHING ABOUT THE CAR.
Yeah, she's here. Hold on one second.
HEY, DUDE.
Hey, Pheebs.
THIS BOX KEEPS SLIDING OUT FROM UNDER THE SEAT.
WHAT IS IT?
OH, THAT'S MY GRANDMA.
AND THANKS, JOEY.
SHE'S HAVING A REALLY GREAT TIME.
IS THAT JOEY? IS THAT JOEY?
LET ME TALK TO HIM.
OKAY, JOEY, CHANDLER'S HERE.
HE WAS WONDERING IF...
OKAY, I GUESS HE RAN OUT OF CHANGE.
YOU KNOW, HE WON'T EVEN TALK TO ME.
HOW AM I GOING TO APOLOGIZE TO HIM.
IF HE WON'T EVEN TALK TO ME?
MAYBE YOU SHOULD SEND HIM SOMETHING.
SO WHEN HE GETS TO LAS VEGAS
HE'LL KNOW THAT YOU'RE SORRY.
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
I WONDER WHERE I COULD GET A BASKET OF PORN?
OH, NO, NO, DON'T SAY "I'M SORRY" WITH PORN.
NO?
YOU KNOW WHAT YOU SHOULD SEND HIM--
A CARTON OF CIGARETTES.
BECAUSE THAT WAY HE CAN TRADE IT FOR PROTECTION...
NO, THAT'S PRISON.
OKAY, PHEEBS, I KNOW HOW WE'RE GOING TO FIGURE THIS OUT.
OKAY, CLEAR YOUR MIND
AND ANSWER THE FIRST THING THAT COMES INTO YOUR HEAD, OKAY?
MM HMM.
WHAT DO YOU LIKE BETTER, FLORA OR FAUNA?
FAUNA. WHO WOULD YOU RATHER BE, SIMON OR GARFUNKEL?
GARFUNKEL.
WHY ARE YOU MAD AT ME?
YOU SAID I WAS BORING.
OH.
WHEN DID I SAY YOU WERE BORING?
OH, MY GOD! I REMEMBER NOW!
WE WERE PLAYING CHESS.
PHOEBE, YOU AND I HAVE NEVER PLAYED CHESS.
OH, COME ON, YES.
REMEMBER THAT TIME ON THE FROZEN LAKE
WE WERE PLAYING CHESS.
YOU SAID I WAS BORING
AND THEN YOU TOOK OFF YOUR ENERGY MASK
AND YOU WERE CAMERON DIAZ.
OKAY, THERE'S A CHANCE THIS MAY HAVE BEEN A DREAM.
SO, THIS ENTIRE TIME, YOU'VE BEEN ANGRY WITH ME
BECAUSE OF A DREAM?
WELL, GUESS WHAT, PHOEBE.
NOW I'M MAD AT YOU.
OW!
I WANTED TO MAKE SURE THAT THIS WASN'T A DREAM.
OTHERWISE WE'RE JUST WASTING EACH OTHER'S TIME.
?? I'VE BEEN THROUGH THE DESERT ON A HORSE WITH NO NAME ??
?? IT FELT GOOD TO BE OUT OF THE RAIN ??
?? IN THE DESERT ??
??
?? YOU CAN'T REMEMBER YOUR NAME
?? BECAUSE THERE AIN'T NO ONE FOR TO GIVE YOU NO PAIN ??
?
?? LA LA LA LA LA LA LA... ?
HEY.
STANLEY!
HEY HEY!
YOUR LEADING MAN IS HERE.
LET'S GET TO WORK.
UM... SLIGHT CHANGE OF PLANS.
WE'VE SHUT DOWN.
WHA... WHAT?
WHY?
IT'S A MONEY THING.
WE DON'T HAVE ANY.
YOU'RE KIDDING, RIGHT?
WHAT? NO.
IT'S PROBABLY JUST TEMPORARY.
WE'RE HOPING TO GET SOME MORE MONEY SOON.
SO IF YOU COULD JUST HANG OUT.
HANG OUT?
HOW LONG?
I DON'T KNOW-- A WEEK, MAYBE TWO.
THE MONEY WILL TURN UP.
PEOPLE ALWAYS WANT TO INVEST IN MOVIES.
HEY, YOU'RE NOT RICH, ARE YOU?
NO.
WORTH A SHOT.
LOOK, JOEY, LET ME KNOW WHERE YOU'RE STAYING, OKAY?
HEY, PAL.
ARE YOU JOEY TRIBBIANI?
YEAH.
THESE GOT LEFT FOR YOU.
THANKS.
"CONGRATULATIONS ON YOUR BIG BREAK."
?? LA LA ??
?
?? SEE, I'VE BEEN THROUGH TH DESERT ON A HORSE WITH NO NAME ?
?? IT FELT GOOD TO BE OUT OF THE RAIN ??
?? IN THE DESERT ??
??
?? YOU CAN'T REMEMBER YOUR NAME
?? BECAUSE THERE AIN'T NO ONE FOR TO GIVE YOU NO PAIN ??
?
?? LA LA LA LA LA LA LA LA ?
?? LA LA LA LA LA. ??
HELLO.
Hey, Monica, it's Joey.
HEY, JOEY.
OH, YOU REMEMBER ME EVEN THOUGH YOU'RE A BIG STAR.
Oh, come on.
It'll be years before I forget you.
JOEY, WHAT'S IT LIKE ON A MOVIE SET, HUH?
DO YOU HAVE A DRESSING ROOM?
DO YOU HAVE A CHAIR WITH YOUR NAME ON IT?
Yeah, yeah, I got all that going on, yeah.
Listen, I want you to make sure you tell Chandler
that he couldn't have been more wrong.
Uh-oh. I got to go, Monica.
My... my sushi's here.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
THANKS FOR WAITING.
OKAY.
EVERYBODY SMILE.
THANKS A LOT.
ENJOY YOUR STAY AT CAESARS.
WE HOPE IT'S TOGA RIFIC.
KILL ME. KILL ME NOW.
RACH, CAN YOU PA SS ME THE TV GUIDE?
YEAH.
GO!
WHAT?!
GET AWAY!
OH, MY GOD!
HOLD HER. OKAY.
WE'LL SEE YOU IN ABOUT THREE OR FOUR HOURS.