OKAY, PICK A CARD. OKAY.
ALL RIGHT. NOW... MEMORIZE IT.
YOU GOT IT?
OH, YES.
OKAY. IS THAT YOUR CARD?
YES.
YEAH, IT IS.
HEY, GUYS.
HI, THERE!  HI!
GUESS WHAT. BEN IS GOING TO BE  IN A TV COMMERCIAL.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
WELL, IT'S NOT FOR SURE
BUT, UH, WE MET THIS GUY IN THE PARK
WHO THOUGHT BEN WAS REALLY CUTE, YOU KNOW...
WHICH HE IS.
UM, ANYHOO, HE, UH, HE GAVE US HIS CARD
AND TOLD US TO BRING HIM DOWN
FOR THIS COMMERCIAL HE'S AUDITIONING.
WHOA. THIS GUY'S, LIKE
THE BIGGEST COMMERCIAL CASTING DIRECTOR IN TOWN!
BEN TAKES ONE LOUSY WALK IN THE PARK
AND GETS AN AUDITION?!
I MEAN, "WAY TO GO, BEN!"
MAN, I'VE BEEN IN THAT PARK A MILLION TIMES.
NO ONE'S EVER OFFERED ME AN AUDITION.
I KNOW. IT'S CRAZY-- WE WERE JUST PUSHING BEN ON THE SWINGS...
I'M ALWAYS ON THE SWINGS!
WHAT AM I DOING WRONG?
THAT.
OKAY, GOT TO GO. WISH ME LUCK.
HEY, RACH, NOW THAT YOU'RE WORKING AT RALPH LAUREN
CAN YOU BRING ME BACK SOME OF THOSE POLO SHIRTS?
UH, WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I DON'T KNOW IF I'D FEEL COMFORTABLE
STEALING ON MY VERY FIRST DAY.
UNWILLING TO STEAL FROM WORK... INTERESTING.
BESIDES, IF ANYBODY'S GOING TO GET FREE STUFF
IT'S GOING TO BE ME.
OKAY, GUYS, WAY TO WISH ME LUCK.
GOOD LUCK. HAVE A GOOD DAY.
BYE.
OKAY, LET'S DISCUSS RACHEL'S BIRTHDAY.
I SAY WE THROW HER A SURPRISE PARTY THIS WEEKEND.
WHOA, BUT HER BIRTHDAY'S NOT FOR, LIKE, ANOTHER MONTH.
OKAY, BUT IF WE THROW HER A PARTY ON HER BIRTHDAY
THEN IT'S NOT A SURPRISE.
I THINK THAT'S A GREAT IDEA.
WE CAN HAVE A DINNER PARTY
AND JUST INVITE HER CLOSE FRIENDS.
ROSS! WE'RE HAVING A SURPRISE PARTY FOR RACHEL!
OKAY!
DONE.
OKAY, GREAT. SO DO YOU WANT TO DO IT TOGETHER?
I WOULD LOVE TO DO IT TOGETHER.
OOH!
THEY'RE GOING TO DO IT TOGETHER.
DUDE, THAT'S MY GIRLFRIEND.
OH, SO I GOT TO SHUT IT DOWN NOW?
ALL RIGHT. I GOT TO TAKE OFF.
I'M PICKING UP BEN , AND THEN WE'RE OFF
TO THE BIG AUDITION.
I BET IT'S GOING TO BE WEIRD
SEEING SOME ACTOR
PRETENDING  TO BE BEN'S DAD.
YEAH.
WEIRDER THAN SEEING
HIS TWO MOMS MAKE OUT?
WHOA, WHOA. "DAD"?
THERE'S A DAD IN THE COMMERCIAL?
YEAH. THE DAD AND BEN EAT SOUP
AND PRETEND TO ENJOY IT.
WHOA, HEY, WELL, MAYBE I'LL GO DOWN THERE WITH YOU
AND SEE IF I CAN GET AN AUDITION AS THE DAD.
I MEAN, WHO BETTER THAN TO PLAY BEN'S FATHER THAN HIS GODFATHER?
YOU'RE NOT HIS GODFATHER.
WHAT?!
ARE YOU KIDDING?!
OF COURSE I AM.
OKAY, LET'S GO , GODFATHER.
ALL RIGHT! WHOA.
HEY! I'M IN.
THEY'RE GOING TO LET ME AUDITION.
REALLY? THAT'S GREAT.
IT TURNS OUT ONE OF THE CASTING LADIES
HAS ACTUALLY SEEN ME IN A PLAY
SO I STEERED CLEAR OF HER.
AND THE OTHER ONE
I KNOW FROM... WELL, YOU KNOW.
HEY, THAT KID LOOKS FAMILIAR.
OH, YEAH, YEAH . HE'S DONE TONS OF COMMERCIALS.
I'VE SEEN HIM IN, LIKE , SUGAR SMACKS, PLAYSTATION
AND THAT ONE FOR THE PHONE COMPANY.
IN FACT, HE WAS SO GOOD IN THAT ONE
HE ACTUALLY CONVINCED ME TO SWITCH PHONE COMPANIES.
CHANDLER WAS MAD...
YEAH, WELL, HE'S NOT GOING TO GET THIS ONE, ALL RIGHT?
BEN IS WAY CUTER THAN THAT KID.
I MEAN, LOOK AT HIM-- LOOK AT YOU!
THAT'S... GREAT.
LISTEN, WOULDN'T IT BE GREAT, THOUGH
IF I GOT TO PLAY BEN'S DAD?
JOEY, YOU LOOK NOTHING LIKE BEN.
I LOOK MORE LIKE HIM THAN YOU DO.
YOU KNOW, I REALLY DON'T KNOW YOU WELL ENOUGH
FOR YOU TO DO THAT.
SO, IT'S DOWN TO THESE TWO.
NANCY, I KNOW YOU LIKE THIS ONE, AND I THINK I AGREE.
RACHEL, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WELL, UM, I MEAN, THAT ONE IS PRETTY
BUT, OH, I JUST... I JUST LOVE THIS FABRIC.
SORRY.
OH, DON'T BE SORRY.
THAT'S PART OF YOUR JOB HERE TO GIVE YOUR OPINIONS
AND THEN I TAKE CREDIT FOR THEM. I'M KIDDING.
SHE IS KIDDING...
BUT DON'T EVER DISAGREE WITH HER AGAIN.
OKAY, NOW I'M KIDDING.
OH, WHAT A FUN OFFICE.
I DON'T KNOW WHICH ONE, BUT I DO KNOW I NEED A CIGARETTE
SO WHAT DO YOU SAY WE TAKE A BREAK, WE GO OUTSIDE
AND WE'LL FIGURE THIS THING OUT WHEN WE COME BACK?
RACHEL?
YEAH?
YOU SMOKE?
OH, NO. MY DAD'S A DOCTOR
AND HE WOULD ALWAYS TELL ME JUST HORROR STORIES...
ABOUT, UH, GHOSTS AND GOBLINS...
WHO... TOTALLY SUPPORTED THE PRINCESS' RIGHT TO SMOKE.
AND THEN THEY CAME BACK FROM SMOKING
AND THEY HAD MADE ALL OF THE DECISIONS WITHOUT ME.
THAT DOESN'T SEEM FAIR.
I KNOW. IT'S LIKE I'M BEING PUNISHED
FOR NOT HAVING THIS DISGUSTING, POISONOUS HABIT.
YEAH, IT IS THE BEST.
I MEAN
I MEAN, WHAT IF THIS KEEPS HAPPENING, YOU KNOW?
THEY'LL THEY'LL BE OUTSIDE SMOKING
MAKING ALL THE DECISIONS, AND I'LL JUST BE UP IN MY OFFICE
BREATHING IN MY STUPID CLEAN AIR, YOU KNOW?
AND THEN, WHEN THE DAY COMES
WHEN KIM WANTS TO PROMOTE ONE OF US
WHO DO YOU THINK SHE'S GOING TO PICK-- ME OR SMOKEY SMOKERSON?
WE USED TO HAVE A SMOKING AREA AT WORK.
IT WAS GREAT.
THERE WAS THIS BIG FLOWER POT WITH DIRT IN IT
AND WE USED TO PUT, LIKE, OUR CIGARETTES OUT IN IT.
ONE OF THE OLD TIMERS TOLD ME
THERE USED TO BE A LITTLE TREE IN THERE.
RACHEL, YOU CAN GO DOWN THERE.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO SMOKE.
JUST SAY YOU WANT TO GET SOME... FRESH AIR.
YEAH, I COULD DO THAT.
YEAH, OR IF YOU JUST DO THE EASY THING AND SMOKE.
YOU KNOW, TAKE LONG, DEEP DRAGS...
WOW. I STILL DON'T HAVE MY LUNG CAPACITY BACK YET.
HEY.
OH, HEY, RACH, DO YOU WANT TO GO GET COFFEE?
OH, I WOULD LOVE TO.
OH, GOOD!
I'M GOING TO GO, TOO, BABE.
OH, GOOD.
YAY. YAY. YAH.
OH, I CHANGED MY MIND.
OKAY.
OKAY, LET'S TALK ABOUT THE PARTY.
I HAVE SO MANY IDEAS.
ME, TOO!
OH!
YEAH!
OH, LOOK AT THAT.
ALL RIGHT.
HERE'S A LITTLE SKETCH OF THE CAKE.
UH HUH. SEE?
UM, SOME SAMPLE MENUS, UM...
YOU KNOW, I THOUGHT WE'D START OUT
WITH TUSCAN STYLE FINGER FOOD, OKAY?
AND, FOR MUSIC, HERE'S AN ALPHABETIZED LIST OF ALL OF MY CDs.
I'VE HIGHLIGHTED THE ONES
THAT'LL GO REALLY GOOD WITH THE FOOD.
WHAT HAPPENED TO THE INTIMATE DINNER PARTY?
YOU KNOW, WE'RE NOT DOING THAT, OKAY?
WOW. ALL RIGHT.
LOOKS LIKE YOU TOOK CARE OF EVERYTHING.
THANKS A LOT, COHOST.
WAIT A MINUTE.
I DIDN'T TAKE CARE OF EVERYTHING.
THERE'S PLENTY OF THINGS FOR YOU TO DO.
UH HUH. LIKE WHAT?
CUPS!
CUPS? YOU'RE GIVING ME CUPS?
AND ICE.
CUPS AND ICE?
OH, I GET TO BE IN CHARGE OF CUPS AND ICE?
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
OKAY, I WILL BE IN CHARGE OF CUPS AND ICE.
WAIT A MINUTE.
I CAN GET ICE AT THE RESTAURANT.
I GOT IT! MINE!
HEY. HI.
HOW'D THE AUDITION GO?
NOT SO GOOD.
NOW, WAIT A MINUTE.
ARE YOU DOING JOEY'S...
"THE AUDITION DIDN'T GO SO WELL...
YEAH, IT DID!"?
YEAH, I AM!
YEAH, BEN GOT A SECOND AUDITION!
GREAT!
YEAH, I HAD TO TEACH ROSS MY BIT
BECAUSE I ACTUALLY DIDN'T GET A CALLBACK.
YOU GOT A CALLBACK , TOO, DIDN'T YOU?
YEAH, I DID!
HEY, RACHEL, WHAT  ARE YOU DOING OUT HERE?
WELL, YOU KNOW, IT GOT KIND OF LONELY UP THERE
SO I JUST THOUGHT I WOULD COME OUT HERE AND...
GET SOME FRESH AIR.
NANCY AND I WE RE TALKING ABOUT  THE FALL COLLECTION.
OH, GREAT.
SO, ANYWAY...
HONEY, I'M SORRY. WE'RE SMOKING ALL OVER YOU.
OH, THAT'S OKAY.
WE'LL MOVE. YOU STAY RIGHT HERE.
YOU KNOW, I SENT THE DESIGNS OVER TO RALPH
AND HE WAS VERY EXCITED ABOUT THE LOOK.
OH, THAT'S GREAT.
YOU ARE THE BEST.
EXCUSE ME, CAN  I BUM ONE OF THOSE?
YEAH, YOU KNOW, ACTUALLY...
OKAY, OKAY, WHAT'S SO FUNNY OVER HERE?
I THOUGHT  YOU DIDN'T SMOKE.
OH, YOU KNOW, I I THOUGHT
YOU GUYS MEANT MARIJUANA CIGARETTES, YOU KNOW?
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
LIKE, DOOBIES?
ACTUALLY, I THOUGHT TO MYSELF, "WOW, THOSE GUYS ARE CRAZY!"
BUT, NO, ACTUALLY, I SMOKE THE REGULAR ONES
ALL... ALL THE TIME.
WE GET HIGH.
ME, TOO.
I'M KIDDING.
OH!
ME, TOO.
OH, GOD, THIS IS SO NERVE RACKING.
HOW HOW DO YOU DO THIS?
WELL, FORTUNATELY, I DON'T GET MANY CALLBACKS.
IS IT A GOOD SIGN
THAT THEY ASKED US TO HANG AROUND AFTER THE AUDITION?
WHO KNOWS?
OKAY, UH, WE HAVE NARROWED IT DOWN TO RAYMOND, BEN
KYLE AND JOEY.
THE REST OF YOU, THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
YES! I KNEW IT!
BYE BYE...
SO LONG...
LATER.
I'M NOT MARRIED TO HIM ANYMORE.
HE'S MY EX HUSBAND.
I'M TOTALLY GAY.
ROSS, THIS IS GREAT.
I MIGHT ACTUALLY GET TO PLAY BEN'S DAD.
ACTUALLY, THAT CAN'T HAPPEN.
BECAUSE YOU ALL HAVE SUCH DIFFERENT LOOKS
WE'RE PUTTING  YOU WITH RAYMOND
AND KYLE WITH BEN.
SO IT'LL EITHER BE YOU TWO OR YOU TWO.
OH, MAN...
THIS IS GOING TO BE KIND OF WEIRD, HUH?
YEAH, IT IS.
YEAH. IT'S GOING TO BE WEIRD.
NO, WE'RE WE'RE, LIKE, BEST FRIENDS.
THAT'S THAT'S WHY IT'S WEIRD.
OH, OH.
I I THOUGHT WE WERE JUST... TALKING.
HEY, ROSS, IF BEN GETS THIS COMMERCIAL
DO YOU THINK HE CAN GET ME SOME FREE SOUP?
CHANDLER, A CAN OF SOUP IS, LIKE, 60 CENTS.
YEAH, OKAY, BUT I HAVE BEEN SUPPORTING
A 29 YEAR OLD ITALIAN FOR FIVE YEARS.
HEY.
IS IT OKAY IF I LEAVE THIS STUFF HERE
TILL RACHEL'S BIRTHDAY PARTY?
SURE. WHAT'S IN THEM?
UM, CUPS.
OH, GOOD, BECAUSE WE GOT RACHEL 800 GALLONS OF WATER.
SERIOUSLY, THAT'S A LOT OF CUPS.
YEAH, WELL, THAT'S BECAUSE I'M IN CHARGE OF CUPS AND ICE
AND MONICA IS GOING TO RUE THE DAY
THAT SHE PUT ME IN CHARGE OF CUPS AND ICE.
YOU KNOW, I RUED THE DAY ONCE.
DIDN'T GET A WHOLE LOT ELSE DONE.
OKAY, TIME TO BRING UP THE REST OF THE CUPS.
OH, HEY, JOEY.
HEY, PHEEBS.
HEY.
ROSS, GOOD. I'M, UH, GLAD YOU'RE HERE.
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT SOMETHING.
OH? WHAT'S UP?
WELL, I'VE BEEN THINKING ABOUT THIS WHOLE COMMERCIAL THING.
YOU KNOW, ME GOING UP AGAINST BEN
THE TWO OF US COMPETING, AND...
WELL, THAT CAN'T LEAD TO ANYTHING GOOD
SO... I THINK I'M JUST GOING TO STEP ASIDE.
I'M GOING TO TELL THEM THAT I WON'T AUDITION.
WOW, UH... JOEY, THAT'S... THAT'S GREAT.
THANKS, MAN.
THAT'S IT?
YOU YOU'RE GOING TO LET ME DO THIS?
THIS IS MY CAREER WE'RE TALKING ABOUT HERE.
BUT... BUT YOU JUST...
I JUST SAID THAT SO YOU WOULDN'T
LET BEN DO IT.
LOOK, ROSS, IF ANYONE SHOULD STEP ASIDE, IT SHOULD BE BEN.
WHAT?
WHAT?! CHANDLER, TELL HIM.
WELL, LET ME... LET ME GET THE DOOR FIRST.
OH, HI, NO ONE.
WHY SHOULD BEN STEP ASIDE?
IT WAS HIS AUDITION IN THE FIRST PLACE.
YOU JUST TAGGED ALONG.
YOU'RE LIKE THE... THE TAG ALONG DAD.
AT LEAST I CARE ABOUT HIS FEELINGS.
WH WH WHAT?
DO YOU KNOW HOW HARD THIS IS GOING TO BE ON HIM
WHEN HE DOESN'T GET IT?
AND WHY WOULDN'T HE GET IT?
OH, COME ON.
HAVE YOU SEEN WHAT MY KID CAN DO?
HUH?
I MEAN, HE DIALS PHONES
HE HE EATS TORTILLA CHIPS.
HE HE PLAYS SOCCER WITH THE CARTOON TIGER.
ARE YOU SAYING YOUR KID EATS SOUP BETTER THAN MY KID?
YOU JUST GIVE  HIM A SPOON, BABY.
OH, YEAH? I GUESS WE'LL SEE.
YEAH
BECAUSE THIS COMMERCIAL BELONGS TO ME AND MITCH.
YOUR KID'S NAME IS RAYMOND.
YEAH? SO'S YOURS!
HOW DID WORK GO? OH, IT WAS GREAT.
I WENT DOWN THERE JUST LIKE YOU SAID
YOU KNOW, AND WE TALKED BUSINESS
AND KIM TOTALLY TOOK MY OPINIONS.
YOU STINK.
THANKS.
NO, I'M I'M SERIOUS.
WELL, THAT THAT'S JUST BECAUSE I WENT DOWN THERE
AND THEY WERE ALL SMOKING.
THIS IS ACTUALLY THE SMELL OF SUCCESS.
OKAY, BUT THERE'S SOMETHING DIFFERENT, THOUGH.
OH, MY GOD. YOU SMOKED.
I DID NOT.
YES, YOU DID.
YOU LOOK HAPPY AND SICK-- YOU SMOKED!
ALL RIGHT, FINE, BUT I HAD TO.
I HAD TO DO  IT FOR MY CAREER.
I WISH I HAD TO SMOKE FOR MY CAREER.
BUT IT'S SO GROSS.
DON'T... NO, WELL, NO, IT'S NOT THAT BAD, YOU KNOW.
IT'S... I MEAN, YEAH, MY TONGUE FEELS A LITTLE FUZZY
AND MY FINGERS SORT OF SMELL.
I ACTUALLY FEEL LIKE I COULD THROW UP.
CAN YOU HEAR YOURSELF?
I KNOW. I'M SORRY. I'M SORRY.
I... I'M NOT MYSELF.
I SMOKED, LIKE, HALF A PACK.
I FEEL A LITTLE SHAKY
AND A LITTLE WEIRD.
OKAY, BUT YOU GOT TO PUSH PAST THIS, OKAY?
BECAUSE IT'S ABOUT TO GET SO GOOD.
CHANDLER.
OH, I GOT TO TELL YOU, YOU SMELL SO SMOKY
I GOT... I I GOT TO GET UP.
WHAT?
I'M NOT KIDDING.
I THINK YOU SMELL GREAT.
SO WE'RE DECIDED-- NO ON PLAID, YES ON PINK.
ABSOLUTELY.
I'M SO ON BOARD.
MM HMM.
RACHEL, DIDN'T YOU JUST LIGHT THAT?
YEAH, BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M JUST REALLY, REALLY TRYING TO CUT BACK, YOU KNOW.
GOOD LUCK, RACH.
I'VE ACTUALLY BEEN THINKING ABOUT QUITTING LATELY.
OH, WELL, SURE-- EVERY SUNDAY NIGHT
I TELL MYSELF I'M QUITTING.
EVERY MONDAY MORNING, IT'S LIKE...
TELL ME ABOUT IT.
WELL, LET'S JUST QUIT.
WE'LL JUST QUIT. LET'S ALL QUIT.
IT DOES SOUND APPEALING.
I NEVER COULD DO IT.
OH, BUT YOU COULD. YOU CAN. ABSOLUTELY.
WE CAN HELP EACH OTHER OUT.
YOU KNOW, WE COULD GET-- WHAT? WHAT?-- THOSE PATCHES.
WE COULD BE LIKE THE PATCH SISTERS.
WELL, YOU KNOW, WE REALLY SHOULD QUIT.
OKAY, LET'S QUIT.
YES. GREAT. GIVE ME THOSE CIGS.
COME ON, GIVE IT. GIVE IT.
OUT, DONE. QUIT. WHOO!
MY LATE HUSBAND GAVE ME THAT LIGHTER.
SHE'S FUNNY.
I'M NOT KIDDING.
OKAY, THEN. OKAY.
MMM... SOUP.
MMM, SOUP.
D. JOEY, ROSS IS GOING TO BE HERE ANY SECON
WOULD YOU MIND WATCHING BEN FOR ME
WHILE I USE THE LADIES' ROOM?
OH, YEAH. NO PROBLEM.
MMM, SOUP.
HI, BEN.
SO YOU WANT TO BE AN ACTOR, HUH?
WELL, I GOT TO TELL YOU, IT'S NO PICNIC.
THERE'S TONS OF REJECTION.
NO STABILITY.
I MEAN, ONE DAY YOU'RE DR. DRAKE RAMORAY.
THE NEXT DAY, YOU'RE EATING KETCHUP
RIGHT OUT OF THE BOTTLE.
IT'S A TOUGH LIFE.
I MEAN, SURE, OKAY
YOU CAN GET UP WHENEVER YOU WANT
WATCH TV ALL DAY
MEET TONS OF WOMEN IN ACTING CLASS...
WHO AM I KIDDING?
I CAN'T TALK YOU OUT OF THIS.
IT'S A GREAT LIFE.
JOEY.
ROSS.
BEN.
I MEAN, BEN, BEN.
OKAY.
RAYMOND, JOEY, YOU'RE UP.
SO HERE'S WHAT, UH...
ARE YOU SURE THAT I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU SOMEWHERE BEFORE?
NO. I HAVEN'T BEEN IN ANY PLAYS.
ALL RIGHT. WELL, LET'S... LET'S TRY ONE.
WHENEVER YOU GUYS ARE READY.
UH OH.
IS THERE A PROBLEM?
WELL, THIS IS NOODLE SO UP
AND I'VE BEEN WORKING WITH TOMATO.
SO... BUT THAT'S OKAY.
NO PROBLEM, NO PROBLEM.
MMM, NOODLE SOUP.
YEAH.
YOU KNOW, THAT THAT'S FINE
BUT THE LINE IS, "MMM, SOUP."
OH. WHAT DID I SAY?
"MMM, NOODLE SOUP."
HOW'S THAT DIFFERENT?
OH! I SEE, YEAH.
ALL RIGHT?
LET'S TRY ONE.
MMM, NOODLE SO UP.
OKAY.
LET'S... DO IT AGAIN.
MMM, SOUP.
I MEAN NOODLE SOUP.
I MEAN SOUP.
COME ON!
YOU KNOW WHAT?
WE NEED TO MOVE ON.
NO, I COULD DO IT ONE MORE TIME.
SEE, LOOK.
MMM, NOODLE SOUP.
DAMN IT!
SO, I THINK THAT IF WE GET THESE SAMPLES IN
TO THE MAGAZINE BY MONDAY, WE'RE GOING TO BE FINE.
SOUNDS GOOD. SO, RACH, HOW YOU DOING?
I'M GREAT.
NO, WITH THE NOT SMOKING THING.
OH. WELL.. KILL... ME... NOW.
LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING.
I ATE
40 MALLOMARS TODAY.
I HAVE... I HAVE PATCHES ALL OVER MY BODY, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, I HAVEN'T SLEPT IN TWO DAYS.
WE QUIT YESTERDAY.
THAT'S COUNTING TODAY.
BUT, ANYWAY
SO THESE SAMPLES, I THINK...
OH, MY GOD!
OH, I'M SO SORRY. I FORGOT.
I HAVE TO GO  TO THE MAIL ROOM
AND MAIL SOME PROOFS.
OH, WELL, GO AHEAD.
RACHEL AND I WILL JUST SIT HERE AND KEEP BRAINSTORMING.
UM... ALSO
VOGUE CALLED
AND THEY WERE WONDERING IF...
YOU KNOW WHAT? I'M A LITTLE HUNGRY.
I'M JUST GOING TO RUN DOWN TO THE VENDING MACHINES.
OH. ALL RIGHT.
HEY.
UH OH. BUSTED.
COME ON, YOU GUYS.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I THOUGHT WE WERE THE PATCH SISTERS.
YEAH. THAT DIDN'T WORK OUT.
WAIT A MINUTE. WHAT ABOUT ALL WE TALKED ABOUT?
YOU KNOW, THE DISGUSTING PLACE.
THE UGLY PEOPLE.
HEY, HOW YOU DOING?
RACHEL, WE TRIED TO QUIT, BUT IT WAS TOO HARD.
WELL, YOU KNOW, IF YOU STARTED SMOKING AGAIN
YOU COULD HAVE AT LEAST TOLD ME.
COME ON. GIVE ME ONE OF THOSE.
WHAT ARE WE TALKING ABOUT?
NO, NO. YOU'RE DOING GREAT. DON'T YOU GIVE UP.
THAT'S WHY WE DIDN'T TELL YOU
AND WE ARE NOT GOING TO DRAG YOU DOWN WITH US.
WAIT. NO, NO, NO. DRAG ME DOWN. DRAG DRAG ME DOWN.
FORGET IT, RACHEL.
WE'RE BOTH SO PROUD OF HOW WELL YOU'RE DOING.
I'M NOT GOING TO LET YOU BLOW IT.
IN FACT, IF I CATCH YOU WITH A CIGARETTE, YOU'RE FIRED.
GO ON. I DON'T WANT YOU BREATHING THIS STUFF. GO ON.
ALL RIGHT.
SO YOU'LL COME WITH  ME ON THE PARIS TRIP?
OH, MAN!
HEY.
HEY, CHECK IT OUT.
UM, CUP HAT, CUP BANNER, CUP CHANDELIER
AND THE THING THAT STARTED IT ALL--
THE CUP.
GREAT JOB WITH THE CUPS, PHEEBS.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST GO OUT WITH HER?
AND DID YOU NOTICE THE ICE?
LOOK, WE HAVE IT ALL--
WE HAVE CRUSHED, CUBED AND DRY.
WATCH.
AHH... MYSTICAL.
OH, YES.
CHANDLER...
IF IT WEREN'T...
NO ONE'S EATING MY TUSCAN FINGER FOOD
BECAUSE THEY'RE ALL FILLING UP ON PHOEBE'S SNO CONES.
THERE ARE SNO CONES?
SNO CONES?
YECH!
YOU KNOW, GO, GO.
THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
PHOEBE.
HMM?
YOU REALLY DID DO A NICE JOB.
THANK YOU FOR STATING THE OBVIOUS.
I DESERVE THAT.
I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW THAT
IF WE EVER COHOST A PARTY TOGETHER AGAIN
YOU CAN DO WHATEVER YOU WANT.
YOU KNOW, JOEY'S GOT A BIRTHDAY COMING UP.
REALLY? WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
OKAY, I'D LIKE TO BE IN CHARGE OF BEER.
WELL, THEN THERE'S NOTHING LEFT FOR ME.
OH, LOOK, LOOK!
SURPRISE!
WHAT?!
MY BIRTHDAY IS NOT FOR ANOTHER MONTH.
THAT'S THE SURPRISE.
OH, MY GOD.
YOU GUYS, THIS IS SO GREAT.
IT'S SO UNEXPECTED.
I MEAN, CHANDLER'S BIRTHDAY'S EVEN BEFORE MINE.
SURPRISE.
WOW! THIS IS SO GREAT.
LOOK AT ALL THESE... CUPS.
THIS IS SO WEIRD.
I WAS IN CHARGE OF CUPS.
OH, OKAY. NOT SO WEIRD.
CHANDLER, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
NOTHING.
WHAT'S IN YOUR HAND?
MONEY. I'M STEALING ALL THE MONEY.
CHANDLER...
OKAY, BUT JUST ONE, OKAY?
BECAUSE NOBODY KNOWS WHEN MY BIRTHDAY IS.
LET ME MAKE THIS CLEAR TO YOU, OKAY?
IT'S EITHER THAT OR THIS.
IS THERE A MENTHOL?
HEY.
LISTEN, MAN, UH... I'M SORRY THE AUDITION DIDN'T GO WELL.
YEAH, RIGHT.
NO, REALLY, I AM, JOEY.
I FEEL BAD.
YEAH, WELL , LOOK, ROSS...
YOU DON'T HAVE TO, OKAY.
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT I SUCK.
I MEAN, WHAT KIND OF ACTOR CAN'T EVEN SAY, "MMM! NOODLE SOUP"?
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
MAYBE... MAYBE YOU DIDN'T MESS UP
THE AUDITION BECAUSE YOU SUCK.
MAYBE YOU MESSED UP BECAUSE YOU CARE MORE ABOUT YOUR GODSON.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I THINK, SUBCONSCIOUSLY...
WHOA. YOU LOST ME.
I THINK, ON SOME LEVEL
YOU YOU SABOTAGED YOUR OWN AUDITION
SO BEN WOULD GET THE PAID.
WELL, YOUR WAY SOUNDS A LOT BETTER THAN MINE.
YEAH. YEAH. IT'S NOT THAT I'M A BAD ACTOR...
NO.
NO, IT'S JUST THAT, UH, I CARE SO DAMN MUCH ABOUT LITTLE BEN
THAT, UH, IT WAS MORE IMPORTANT FOR ME TO SEE HIM SUCCEED.
THERE YOU GO. YEAH.
THANK YOU. THANK YOU.
SO, DID HE GET IT? NO.
AW, WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
OH, HI. EXCUSE ME. IS RACHEL GREEN HERE?
I'M SUPPOSED TO MEET HER FOR LUNCH.
SHE DOESN'T COME DOWN HERE ANYMORE.
YOU CAN FIND HER UP ON TEN.
OKAY, GREAT.
WE TALKED ABOUT THE WHOLE PRESENTATION
YESTERDAY AT LUNCH.
HE WONDERED IF ONE PERSON
WOULD BE ENOUGH TO TAKE ON THE TRIP
AND I SAID, YEAH, ABSOLUTELY.
I'LL CATCH YOU GUYS LATER.