ARE YOU LOOKING  AT NAKED TRIBES WOMEN?
NO. LOOK.
THAT'S A PIG.
I KNOW, I KNOW, BUT LOOK AT THE KNOBS ON IT.
HEY.
HEY. HEY.
EMILY'S COUSIN KICKED ME OUT.
WHAT? WHY?
WELL, WHEN YOU'RE SUBLETTING AN APARTMENT
FROM YOUR WIFE'S COUSIN, AND THEN YOU GET A DIVORCE
SOMETIMES THE COUSIN SUDDENLY WANTS HIS APARTMENT BACK.
HOW CAN HE DO THAT? DIDN'T YOU SIGN A LEASE?
WHO NEEDS A LEASE WHEN IT'S FAMILY?
HEY, YOU COULD STAY WITH US.
WE'LL TAKE CARE OF YOU.
ANYTHING YOU NEED, MAN
BUT YOU HAVE TO PROMISE ME
YOU WILL LET US KNOW
THE SECOND YOU ARE FEELING BETTER
SO WE CAN MAKE FUN
OF YOUR HAIR.
YOU GOT IT.
OKAY.
THANKS, YOU GUYS, I REALLY APPRECIATE THIS.
I'M GOING TO GET PACKING AGAIN.
I'VE BEEN MOVING AROUND SO MUCH LATELY
I'M BEGINNING TO FEEL LIKE A NOMAD.
WHAT?
HE THOUGHT YOU SAID "GONAD."
WOW, MONICA. IF EVERY RESTAURANT WERE AS CLEAN AS YOURS
IT'D BE A TOUGH TIME MAKING A LIVING.
OH, LARRY.
SO, UM, DO HEALTH INSPECTORS
WORK ON COMMISSION?
NO. BRIBES.
IT'S OKAY TO LAUGH, RIGHT?
YEAH. I WAS JUST KIDDING.
OKAY.
I'M GOING TO CHECK THE KITCHEN FLOOR.
OKAY. KNOCK YOURSELF OUT, LARRY.
I DON'T GET VIOLATIONS.
YOU COULD EAT BEANS OFF THAT FLOOR.
BUT DON'T, BECAUSE THAT'D BE A VIOLATION.
YUMMY.
WHAT? LARRY?
OH, YEAH. I'D LET  HIM
CHECK OUT MY KITCHEN FLOOR.
A 98.
I DEDUCTED TWO POINTS BECAUSE
YOU'RE NOT WEARING YOUR CHEF'S HAT
AND THAT IS A SECTION FIVE VIOLATION.
LOOK, LARRY, HONEY
UM... I WROTE THE BOOK ON SECTION FIVE
AND I KNOW THAT YOU DON'T HAVE TO WEAR YOUR HAT
UNLESS YOU'RE IN THE KITCHEN.
WHERE IS YOUR HAT?
IT'S IN THE KITCHEN. I'LL GO GET IT.
THERE'S THE TWO POINTS.
HEY, YOU SHOULD REALLY READ THAT BOOK YOU WROTE.
WOW.
YOU SAW THE HAT IN THE KITCHEN
AND YOU KNEW SHE'D HAVE TO GO
IN THERE HATLESS TO GET IT.
YOU COULD HAVE YOUR OWN, YOU KNOW
HEALTH INSPECTOR DETECTIVE SHOW.
WELL, I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT.
YEAH, BUT THEN I COULD BE YOUR SIDEKICK, VUNDA.
MAYBE VUNDA COULD GIVE ME HER NUMBER
AND I COULD ASK HER TO DINNER SOMETIME.
OKAY, SHE WOULD LOVE THAT, YOU KNOW
SINCE YOU KNOW ALL THE CLEAN PLACES TO EAT.
I'LL CALL YOU.
OKAY.
HE'S SO FUNNY. WHOA. OH.
THANKS.
THANK YOU.
MON, HOW'S ROSS DOING
YOU KNOW, SINCE ALL THE EMILY STUFF?
HE'S NOT GREAT , BUT, UM...
HE'S DEALING WITH IT.
OH, WAIT A MINUTE, YOU'RE NOT GOING TO...?
OH, HONEY, PLEASE, NO.
I CAN'T GET STARTED WITH ALL THAT ROSS STUFF AGAIN.
HE'S GOING TO BE SCREWED UP FOR A LONG TIME.
AND BESIDES, YOU KNOW
I DON'T GO FOR GUYS RIGHT AFTER THEY GET DIVORCED.
RIGHT. YOU ONLY GO FOR THEM
FIVE MINUTES BEFORE THEY GET MARRIED.
TWO POUNDS OF MOCHA JAVA, PLEASE.
IT'S DANNY.
ARE YOU GUYS EVER GOING OUT AGAIN?
I DON'T KNOW. HE HASN'T CALLED ME
SINCE THAT ONE TIME WE WENT OUT.
I SEE HIM IN THE HALLWAY, WE FLIRT.
I'M ALL...
... AND NOTHING.
HEY.
HI, DANNY.
WOW. THIRSTY, HUH?
ACTUALLY, I'M HAVING A PARTY AT MY PLACE ON SATURDAY--
SORT OF A HOUSEWARMING THING.
OH, FUN. OH, GREAT.
I'M REALLY LOOKING FORWARD TO IT.
OKAY, SEE YOU.
WELL, I GUESS WE WON'T BE WARMING HIS HOUSE.
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
I SEE WHAT HE'S DOING.
HE'S NOT ASKING ME OUT
BECAUSE HE WANTS ME TO ASK HIM OUT.
AND YOU'RE NOT GOING TO DO THAT.
THAT'S RIGHT.
BECAUSE THAT WOULD GIVE HIM THE CONTROL.
SO NOW HE'S ALL, OOH, COMING UP WITH THIS
"I'VE GOT A PARTY" THING--
YOU KNOW, TRYING TO GET ME
TO HINT AROUND FOR AN INVITATION.
BLEW UP IN HIS FACE, DIDN'T IT?
SO THERE IS NO PARTY?
OH, NO.
THERE'S A PARTY.
THERE'S A PARTY, BUT THE POWER--
THAT IS STILL UP FOR GRABS.
YOU FOLLOW ME?
I THINK SO.
SO HE'S NOT INVITING YOU TO HIS PARTY
BECAUSE HE LIKES YOU.
EXACTLY.
THEN WHY DIDN'T HE INVITE ME?
OH! TO THROW ME OFF.
ROSS?
HEY, ROOMIES.
HEY.
LOVE WHAT YOU'VE DONE WITH THE PLACE.
YEAH, I KNOW, I KNOW, IT'S A LOT OF BOXES
BUT AGAIN, I REALLY APPRECIATE YOU GUYS LETTING ME STAY HERE.
NOT A PROBLEM.
AND LISTEN, HEY-- SINCE YOU'RE GOING TO BE HERE FOR A WHILE
I WAS THINKING WE'D PUT YOUR NAME ON THE ANSWERING MACHINE.
OH. I, UH, HOPE YOU DON'T MIND
BUT I KIND OF ALREADY JAZZED IT UP A LITTLE.
CHECK IT OUT.
?? We will, we will call you back. ??
HEY.
ALL RIGHT.
PRETTY COOL, HUH?
YOU'RE FAKE LAUGHING, TOO, RIGHT?
OH, THE TEARS ARE REAL.
YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL THIS EVENING.
SHOW ME THE BADGE AGAIN.
SHINY.
YOU MIND IF I WASH UP?
I CAME STRAIGHT FROM WORK
AND WHO KNOWS WHERE THESE BABIES HAVE BEEN?
YOU ARE JUST NONSTOP.
WE'RE OUT OF HERE.
WHY?
JUST WALKING PAST THE KITCHEN
I SAW TEN VIOLATIONS.
I AM SHUTTING THIS PLACE DOWN.
YOU HAVE THE POWER TO DO THAT?
THIS DOES.
SHUT IT DOWN.
HEY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
NOTHING.
YOU BUILT A FORT, DIDN'T YOU?
KIND OF.
OH, MY GOD, THE AIR PURIFIER.
ROSS'S AIR PURIFIER.
ALL I HEARD FOR FOUR YEARS THROUGH COLLEGE WAS...
DUDE, YOU SHOULD HAVE GONE OUT ONCE IN A WHILE.
I HATE THIS THING.
COME ON, CHANDLER.
ROSS IS OUR FRIEND.
HE NEEDS US RIGHT NOW.
SO, WHY DON'T YOU BE A GROWNUP
AND COME WATCH SOME TV IN THE FORT?
I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT LARRY CLOSED DOWN CHERMIN'S.
I LOVE THAT PLACE.
YEAH, I KNOW
BUT YOU SHOULD'VE HEARD ABOUT ALL THEIR VIOLATIONS.
LARRY SAID THAT THEY SHOULD CALL IT VERMIN'S.
THAT GUY JUST PLAIN KILLS ME.
OH, HI, DANNY.
HEY, GUYS, UH, I JUST WANTED TO INVITE YOU
TO THE PARTY TOMORROW NIGHT.
OH, THANKS.
I'LL TRY TO STOP BY.
YEAH, ACTUALLY, I THINK... I'M GOING TO BE BUSY.
YOU ARE?
YEAH. REMEMBER?
I'VE GOT THAT, UH... GALA.
WHAT'S THE GALA FOR?
UH, IT'S A, UM...
IT'S A, IT'S  A REGATTA GALA.
REALLY? YOU SAIL?
NO. NO, BUT I SUPPORT IT.
OKAY. WELL, HOPE I SEE YOU TOMORROW NIGHT.
OKAY.
TAKE CARE.
WALKED RIGHT INTO THAT ONE, DIDN'T HE?
WHAT ONE?
YOU WANTED HIM TO INVITE YOU.
TO THE PARTY AND HE DID.
YEAH, BUT HE WAITED UNTIL THE LAST MINUTE.
SO IF I SAID YES, HE WOULD KNOW
THAT I HAD NOTHING BETTER TO DO THAN WAIT AROUND
FOR AN INVITATION TO HIS STUPID PARTY.
I SAID NO, WHICH PUTS ME
RIGHT BACK IN THE DRIVER'S SEAT.
SO, THE BALL IS  IN HIS COURT?
BALL?
NO, THERE'S NO BALL.
HEY, PHEEBS, YOU WANT TO JOIN US?
OH, SURE, YEAH. WHERE'S THIS FROM?
IT'S FROM SUN LING'S.
OOH!
LARRY JUST TOLD ME SOMETHING ABOUT SUN LING...
OH, NO, THANK YOU.
JOEY, PLEASE.
SORRY.
HELLO, CHILDREN.
HEY.
WANT TO PLAY SOME FOOSBALL?
PLEASE?
OKAY.
NO, NO. NO.
WE HAD TO MOVE THE TABLE INTO MY ROOM
BECAUSE OF ALL THE BOXES.
COME ON.
ALL RIGHT, I HAVE ONE QUESTION.
WHAT IS THE DEAL WITH THIS?
BYE BYE, LITTLE PUPPET JOEY HAND?
NO, NO, THE "QUIET DOWN" THING.
OH, YOU MEAN THIS.
MM! MM!
LOOK, I DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH MORE OF THIS I CAN TAKE.
DID YOU KNOW HE TAPED OVER MY BAYWATCH TAPE
WITH SOME SHOW ABOUT BUGS?
MY GOD.
WHAT IF THAT HAD BEEN PORN, HUH?
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, YOU KNOW
THIS MAY BE TOUGH, BUT COME ON, IT'S ROSS.
I SURVIVED COLLEGE WITH HIM.
ALL RIGHT. I GUESS I CAN HOLD OUT A LITTLE LONGER.
LET'S HAVE A GAME.
OKAY.
NO, NO, NO.
YES!
UH, FELLAS?
OKAY, SO HE'S OUT OF HERE.
HEY. HEY.
YOU GUYS GOT ANYTHING TO EAT?
I JUST WENT DOWN TO JOHN O's
FOR SOME CHICKEN, AND IT WAS CLOSED.
I TOOK LARRY THERE TO EAT, BUT IT WAS ALL VIOLATED
SO WE SHUT IT DOWN.
PHEEBS, IF THIS GUY KEEPS CLOSING DOWN
ALL OUR FAVORITE PLACES, WHERE WE GOING TO EAT?
I DON'T KNOW; CLEAN PLACES?
MMM. YUM.
IT'S DANNY.
DON'T LET HIM IN. I'M SUPPOSED TO BE AT A REGATTA GALA.
WE'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
CAN'T YOU JUST SAY IT STARTS LATER?
WHAT KIND OF A REGATTA GALA STARTS AT NIGHT?
THE FAKE KIND.
HEY, UM, I NEED A LADLE.
YOU GOT A LADLE?
WE HAVE A LADLE.
THANKS. SEE YOU AT THE PARTY.
OKAY. GREAT.
HEY, YOU GUYS.
YOU KNOW WHAT LARRY WOULD SAY?
HE'D SAY, "SEE YOU LADLE."
WELL, I'M DONE WITH THIS.
YOU WANT ANYTHING, ROSS?
UH, SPORTS? INTERNATIONAL?
APARTMENT LISTINGS?
UH, I'LL TAKE SPORTS.
MINE.
ALL RIGHT.
UH, INTERNATIONAL.
THAT'S MINE, TOO.
I'M ITALIAN.
I GUESS I COULD CHECK OUT THOSE APARTMENT LISTINGS
EVEN THOUGH THERE'S NEVER ANYTHING IN HERE.
NOT EVEN ON PAGE SEVEN?
OH, YEAH. YOU'RE RIGHT.
OH, HERE'S AN AFFORDABLE PLACE.
TWO BEDROOM, CLOSE TO WORK.
OOH, IT'S AVAILABLE IN FIVE WEEKS.
WHAT ABOUT THAT CIRCLED ONE?
OH, I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S KIND OF EXPENSIVE FOR A STUDIO.
BUT IT'S AVAILABLE NOW...
ISN'T IT?
YES, IT IS.
LET'S GO LOOK AT IT.
OKAY, LET'S GO.
HERE WE GO. HEY, HEY.
OH, OH, OH , HEY, GUYS.
I WAS WONDERING IF YOU WOULD, UH...
MAYBE CHIP IN FOR SOME NEW AIR FILTERS
FOR THE PURIFIER?
I MEAN, AFTER ALL, WE ARE ALL USING IT.
LET'S GO QUICKER.
OH, MY GOD.
MMM.
LOOK AT THIS KITCHEN...
SLASH BATHROOM.
THAT'S GREAT, YOU KNOW
SO YOU CAN COOK WHILE IN THE TUB.
SOMEBODY WAS USING HIS HEAD.
HEY, LET'S CHECK OUT THE REST OF THE PLACE.
I THINK THIS IS IT.
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE WE SHOULD KEEP LOOKING.
BUT, HEY, ROSS, THIS PLACE IS AVAILABLE NOW.
YOU DON'T WANT TO BE STUCK WITH US
FOR THE NEXT FIVE WEEKS.
YEAH.
SO YOU THINK I SHOULD GO AHEAD
AND TAKE THIS PLACE?
IT'S PERFECT.
HOW ABOUT YOU?
KITCHEN SLASH BATHROOM.
UH, I SEE WHAT YOU GUYS ARE SAYING.
I'LL, UH... I'LL GO DOWNSTAIRS
FILL OUT AN APPLICATION.
WE ARE BAD PEOPLE.
HE KNEW WE WERE TRYING TO GET RID OF HIM.
HE KNEW.
YOU THINK WE COULD GET A BATHTUB IN OUR KITCHEN?
HEY, YOU READY FOR DINNER?
OOH, ABSOLUTELY.
GREAT.
YOU WANT TO GO  TO THE ITALIAN PLACE
DOWN ON BLEECKER STREET, RIGHT?
OOH, I LOVE THAT PLACE.
SO... NO.
OH, HOW ABOUT MAMA LEZOTTI'S?
UGH.
SURE.
I WONDER HOW LONG THAT MILK HAS BEEN SITTING OUT.
OH, NO. THIS PLACE
IS TOTALLY HEALTHY.
THIS MILK IS MINE.
I BOUGHT THIS TODAY BECAUSE I WAS THIRSTY FOR MILK, YOU KNOW.
OKAY, LET'S GO.
HEY, BUDDY.
YOU FAMILIAR WITH SECTION 11 B
OF THE HEALTH CODE
THAT REQUIRES ALL REFUSE MATERIAL
TO BE TAKEN OUT OF THE BACK EXIT?
BUT THEN I HAVE TO GO
ALL THE WAY AROUND THE DRY CLEANER.
OH, SO YOU'RE SAYING YOU CHOOSE CONVENIENCE OVER HEALTH?
WOULD YOU BE INTERESTED IN A... FREE COFFEE?
OKAY, STOP
LARRY... OKAY, CAN'T YOU JUST BE LARRY
AND NOT LARRY THE HEALTH INSPECTOR GUY?
YOU KNOW, I MEAN, IT WAS REALLY EXCITING
AT FIRST, BUT NOW, IT'S LIKE, OKAY-
SO WHERE ARE WE GOING TO EAT EVER?
WELL, I SUPPOSE I COULD
GIVE HIM A WARNING.
THANK YOU.
OKAY,  GO, GO, GO.
NOW, IF, AFTER DINNER
YOU STILL, LIKE, REALLY NEED TO BUST SOMEONE
I KNOW A HOT DOG VENDOR WHO PICKS HIS NOSE.
MAYBE... MAYBE  WE DID A GOOD THING
HELPING ROSS GET BACK ON HIS FEET.
YES, THAT WAS A NICE PLACE. YEAH.
NOT A LOT OF CLOSET SPACE
BUT HE COULD JUST HANG HIS STUFF
OUT THE WINDOW IN A BAG.
YEAH!
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE PIZZA?
ABOUT ROSS.
OH.
HELLO?
OH, YEAH.
IT'S THE APARTMENT MANAGER.
ROSS PUT US DOWN AS REFERENCES.
ROSS IS THE GREATEST GUY YOU'LL EVER MEET.
YEAH, HE'S VERY RELIABLE.
OF COURSE, HE  HAS A BIG, HUGE DOG
THAT, UH, BARKS INTO THE NIGHT.
WELL, WHO DOESN'T LOVE DOGS?
UH, HE'S A TAP DANCER.
YES, SOME WOULD SAY THAT IS A LOST ART.
HE'S A PIMP.
THERE YOU GO. YES, HE'S A PIMP.
HE'S A BIG, TAP DANCING PIMP.
HELLO?
OH.
OKAY, HONEY, I'M READY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I AM GOING TO WANDER INTO THE PARTY
AND I WILL BE ALL, YOU KNOW, "OOH, I DON'T NEED THIS.
I'M COMING FROM A REGATTA GALA."
DID YOU PICK THIS OUT OF A BOOK?
MONICA, HONEY, THIS IS AS REAL AS IT GETS.
?? WATCHIN' ??
?? FOR A SOUND TO LEAD ME TO ??
?? WHEREVER YOU GO WALKIN'...??
THIS IS NEVER GOING TO WORK.
HE'S RIGHT THERE.
JUST GO OVER AND SAY HI.
I HAVE TO GO DOWNSTAIRS, COME BACK UP
AS IF I'M COMING HOME FROM THE REGATTA GALA.
OKAY? SO JUST GO DISTRACT HIM.
BUT DON'T BE SEXY.
HEY, DANNY.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
IT'S A GREAT PARTY.
GREAT FOOD.
UH HUH.
YOU KNOW, MOST PARTIES
IT'S ALL CHIPS AND SALSA, CHIPS AND SALSA.
SO, UH...
WHAT'S THIS?
SALAD.
OH.
AND, UH, WHAT'S THIS?
BREAD.
AREN'T YOU A CHEF?
OH.
HEY, RACHEL.
HEY. OH, RIGHT.
TONIGHT WAS YOUR PARTY.
YOU LOOK GREAT. I'M GLAD YOU COULD MAKE IT.
OH, YEAH, WELL, YOU KNOW, THE GALA HAD TO END SOMETIME.
DON'T GO ANYWHERE.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK, ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, SURE.
ALL RIGHT, WHOSE COURT'S THE BALL IN NOW?
I THOUGHT THERE WASN'T A BALL.
OH, COME ON.
HE'S GLAD THAT I CAME.
HE DOESN'T WANT ME TO GO ANYWHERE.
BALLS FLYING ALL OVER THE PLACE.
RACHEL, THIS IS MY FRIEND, TOM.
THIS IS THE GIRL I TOLD YOU ABOUT.
OH, COME ON, YOU'RE TELLING PEOPLE ABOUT ME?
I THINK YOU TWO
COULD REALLY HIT IT OFF.
I'M GOING TO GO MINGLE.
SO, YOU WORK AT BLOOMINGDALE'S, HUH?
MY MOM CALLS IT "BLOOMIES."
OH... YEAH.
OKAY. AT EASE, SOLDIER.
I'M SORRY?
NO, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
YOU CAN JUST DROP THE ACT, TOMMY.
I KNOW WHAT'S GOING ON HERE.
YOU'RE DANNY'S WINGMAN, RIGHT?
YOU GUYS ARE BEST BUDS.
FRAT BROS.
I'M GOING TO GO TALK TO A FRIEND.
YEAH, YEAH. YOU GO TALK TO YOUR FRIEND.
YOU GO TELL HIM, "NICE TRY."
MAN, YOU KNOW, HE JUST KEEPS LOBBING THEM UP AND I JUST KEEP
KNOCKING THEM RIGHT OUT OF THE PARK.
I THINK I NEED A DRINK.
YEAH.
98... 99...
ONE... HUNDRED.
OKAY. GO.
DUDE, I'M TELLING YOU, I'M FINE.
HERE WE GO, HERE WE GO.
HEY.
SO, I, UH... I DIDN'T GET THAT APARTMENT.
SOME PROBLEM WITH MY APPLICATION.
YOU'RE KIDDING!
YEAH, BUT THE GOOD NEWS IS
PHOEBE SAID I COULD STAY
AT HER PLACE FOR A WHILE, SO...
WELL, YOU CAN'T STAY WITH PHOEBE, ROSS.
WE'RE ROOMIES.
LOOK, YOU GUYS DON'T NEED ME HERE
TAKING UP ALL YOUR SPACE.
WE GOT PLENTY OF SPACE.
THERE'S STILL SOME OVER THERE BY THAT SPEAKER.
PLEASE, JUST STAY.
YEAH.
ARE YOU GUYS SURE ABOUT THIS?
DEFINITELY, YES.
YES. ROSS, YOU HAVE TO STAY.
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, BUDDY.
HEY.
SO I'M A PIMP, HUH?
IT'S OKAY.
LOOK, I KNOW SOMETIMES I CAN BE A PAIN IN THE ASS
BUT YOU JUST HAVE TO TALK TO ME.
TELL ME IF SOMETHING'S BOTHERING YOU, OKAY?
AND FOR MY PART, I'LL REALLY DO EVERYTHING I CAN
TO KEEP MY ANNOYING HABITS YOU KNOW, JUST...
WELL, I SEE YOU'VE HAD A VERY PRODUCTIVE DAY.
DON'T YOU THINK THE COWBOY HAT'S A LITTLE MUCH?
COME ON, IT'S FUN.
ALL RIGHT.
ISN'T THIS A WOMAN'S HAT?
DUDE, STOP TALKING CRAZY AND MAKE US SOME TEA.