HI.
HI, YEAH, HI.
I'M, UM, PHOEBE BUFFAY
AND I HAVE BABIES COMING OUT OF ME.
OKAY. HAVE YOU STARTED HAVING CONTRACTIONS?
NOT YET. I HEARD THEY REALLY RT.
DO THEY HURT?
OH. WELL...
OH, MY GOD.
NOW, WHICH OF YOU IS THE FATHER?
NO, NONE OF THEM ARE THE FATHER.
THE FATHER IS MY BROTHER.
OKAY.
I AM SO GOING TO MISS
WATCHING YOU FREAK PEOPLE OUT LIKE THAT.
PHEEBS, THIS IS FOR THE BABIES TO LOOK AT SOMEDAY
SO IS THERE ANYTHING YOU WANT TO SAY--
YOU KNOW, BEFORE IT ALL STARTS?
OH, OKAY.
UM... HI, KIDS.
UM, IT'S ME, AUNT PHOEBE.
CAN'T WAIT TO SEE YOU.
PLEASE DON'T HURT ME.
HEY, WHAT TOOK YOU GUYS SO LONG?
YOUR CAB LEFT WHEN OURS DID.
WELL, WE HAD TO GO BACK BECAUSE I FORGOT MY JACKET.
THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU... YOU'RE NOT WEARING A JACKET.
OH, MAN. I DID IT AGAIN.
OKAY, SO SOMEONE HAS TO CALL FRANK AND ALICE
AND THEN MY MOM...
JOEY, WHAT A RE YOU DOING?
WELL, I GOT TO GET THE "BEFORE" SHOT.
HI. PHEEBS?
OKAY, SO WE JUST SPOKE TO THE NURSE
AND THE REASON THAT YOUR DOCTOR IS LATE
IS BECAUSE, UH, SHE'S NOT COMING.
WHAT?! APPARENTLY, SHE FELL IN THE SHOWER AND HIT HER HEAD.
OH, MY GOD.
SHE'S SO STUPID.
PHEEBS. PHEEBS, IT'S GOING TO BE OKAY.
THAT'S EASY FOR YOU TO SAY.
I DON'T SEE THREE KIDS COMING OUT OF YOUR VAGINA.
HONEY, LISTEN, YOU KNOW WHAT?
THE NURSE SAID
THAT THE DOCTOR IS WONDERFUL.
YEAH, HE'S THE HEAD OF THE DEPARTMENT.
ALL RIGHT.
OOH. OH, DEAR GOD, SAVE ME. WHAT?
I'M HAVING MY FIRST CONTRACTION.
OH, IT'S NOT BAD. OKAY.
AND SO THE MIRACLE
OF BIRTH BEGINS AND...
HEY, ARE YOU OKAY?
OOH. SOMETHING HURTS.
OOH, IT'S SYMPATHY PAINS.
OH, THAT'S SO SWEET.
I DIDN'T KNOW I CARED THAT MUCH.
HELLO.
HI. HI.
PHOEBE, I'M DR. HARAD.
I'M GOING TO BE
DELIVERING YOUR BABY.
I WANT YOU TO KNOW YOU'RE GOING TO BE IN GOOD HANDS.
I'VE BEEN DOING THIS FOR A LONG TIME.
I'LL BE BACK IN A MINUTE TO DO YOUR INTERNAL.
IN THE MEANTIME, JUST RELAX
BECAUSE EVERYTHING HERE LOOKS GREAT.
AND, ALSO, I LOVE FONZIE.
DID HE JUST SAY HE LOVES FONZIE?
THAT'S WHAT IT SOUNDED LIKE.
ALL RIGHT.
HEY!
HEY, AM I LATE? AM I LATE?
NOBODY CAME OUT YET, RIGHT?
NO, NO, NO, WE HAVEN'T STARTED YET.
WHERE'S ALICE?
UH, DELAWARE. SHE'S ON HER WAY, THOUGH.
SO UNTIL SHE GETS HERE, I'M GOING TO BE YOUR COACH.
BUT DON'T WORRY-- SHE TOLD ME ABOUT THE "LA MAZDA" STUFF.
YEAH, THAT'S WHEN, IF YOU GET THE BABIES
OUT BY THE END OF THE MONTH
THEY GIVE YOU TWO PERCENT FINANCING.
YEAH.
MONICA, YOU'RE GOING TO BE VERY PROUD OF ME.
I JUST GOT US DATES WITH TWO UNBELIEVABLY CUTE NURSES.
OH, MY.
THEY ARE MALE NURSES.
NOT IN MY HEAD.
ANYWAY, THEY WANT TO TAKE US OUT SATURDAY NIGHT.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
UM...
I DON'T THINK SO.
WHAT? WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO'S BEEN TELLING ME
TO GET OVER ROSS AND MOVE ON.
I'M MOVING ON, AND YOU'RE MOVING ON WITH ME.
COME ON. GIVE ME ONE GOOD REASON WHY YOU DON'T WANT TO GO.
WELL, UM...
WHY DON'T YOU GIVE ME SOMETHING THAT WOULD BE A GOOD REASON
AND THEN I'LL TELL YOU IF IT'S TRUE?
WHAT?
HARDER THAN IT SOUNDS, ISN'T IT?
OKAY, YOU'RE COMING WITH ME
AND I ALSO TOLD THEM IF WE'RE STILL HERE WHEN THEY GET OFF
WE'LL GO DOWN TO THE CAFETERIA AND GET SOME JELL O WITH THEM.
YEP.
THERE'S ALWAYS ROOM FOR JELL O.
JOEY, HOW DO YOU MAKE THAT DIRTY?
AH, IT'S EASY.
YEAH, I CAN DO  IT WITH ANYTHING.
WATCH. UH...
GRANDMA'S CHICKEN SALAD...
ROSS! COME HERE.
GET A SHOT OF THIS.
HEY, BABIES--
THESE ARE THE HEADLINES ON THE DAY YOU WERE BORN.
OKAY, NOW, GIRL BABY, TURN AWAY
AND, BOY BABIES... CHECK IT OUT, HUH?
THIS IS WHAT NAKED WOMEN LOOKED LIKE
THE MONTH YOU WERE BORN.
ALL RIGHT, NOW LET'S DIVE RIGHT INTO THE GOOD STUFF.
OKAY, I'M HAVING ANOTHER ONE.
THIS ONE DOESN'T HURT EITHER.
OOH, YES, IT DOES. OW! OW!
OW! OW!
OOH!
NOTHING.
OOH, I WAS KIND OF HOPING THAT WAS IT.
HEY, WHERE ARE MONICA AND RACHEL ANYWAY?
A COUPLE OF NURSES ASKED THEM OUT; MAYBE THEY'RE WITH THEM.
REALLY? MALE NURSES?
YEAH. I WAS BUMMED, TOO.
SO THEY'RE GOING ON DATES?
WHEN?
I THINK SATURDAY.
WHAT'S WITH HIM?
UM, SYMPATHY PAINS.
I THOUGHT IT WAS REALLY SWEET AT FIRST
BUT NOW I THINK HE'S JUST TRYING TO STEAL MY THUNDER.
OKAY.
LET'S SEE WHAT
WE GOT HERE.
OH, YOU KNOW, FONZIE DATED TRIPLETS.
YOU KNOW, THIS FONZIE PERSON
YOU KEEP REFERRING TO-
IS THAT, UH... IS THAT ANOTHER DOCTOR?
OH, NO, NO.
FONZIE IS THE NICKNAME OF ARTHUR FONZARELLI.
THE FONZ.
ALL RIGHT.
IT'S NOT THAT WEIRD, IS IT?
IT'S VERY WEIRD.
I DON'T WANT SOME GUY DOWN THERE TELLING ME I'M
YOU KNOW, "DILATED AMUNDO."
TO BE FAIR HE DOESN'T SEEM TO BE IMPERSONATING FONZIE...
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
WHY ARE YOU DEFENDING HIM?
JUST GET ME ANOTHER DOCTOR--
ONE WHO IS NOT CRAZY AND DOES NOT "FONZIE."
AGAIN, IT'S NOT THAT HE...
OH! OH!
OH, HEY, THERE THERE YOU ARE.
LISTEN, I I THINK THAT THERE IS SOMETHING
THAT YOU SHOULD KNOW.
OH, IS THIS ABOUT YOU... YOU DATING THE NURSE?
YEAH. JOEY ALREADY TOLD ME, AND I AMSO,SO FINE.
I MEAN, YOU AND I--
WE'RE JUST, YOU KNOW, WE'RE NOTHING.
WE'RE JUST... EH, GOOFING AROUND.
UM, ACTUALLY I WAS ABOUT TO TELL YOU
THAT I WAS I WAS GOING TO GET OUT OF IT
BUT, HEY, IF WE'RE JUST GOOFING AROUND
THEN, UH, MAYBE I WILL GO OUT WITH HIM.
FINE. MAYBE I WILL, TOO.
HEY. YOU GUYS.
LOOK WHAT I FOUND IN THE... GIIIFT SHOP!
OH! OW!
GET UP! GET UP!
OKAY, PHEEBS? YEAH.
THIS IS DR. OBERMAN.
HE HAS NO STRONG FEELINGS ABOUT FONZIE
OR ANY OF THE HAPPY DAYS GANG.
HI. AND YOU'RE GOING INTO WHAT GRADE?
I'M ACTUALLY A FIRST YEAR RESIDENT
BUT I GET THAT A LOT.
YOU SEE, I GRADUATED EARLY...
UH HUH, ME, TOO.
ROSS, MAYBE I SHOULD HAVE SPECIFIED
THAT I'D BE NEEDING A GROWN UP DOCTOR.
OH, NO, REALLY, I'M FULLY QUALIFIED TO...
SHH! DOOGIE, SHH!
DOESN'T ANYBODY UNDERSTAND THAT I'M
GOING TO BE HAVING BABIES SOON? HUH?!
GO!
GO, LITTLE BOY, GO!
OH, YOU MADE HIM CRY.
MR. TRIBBIANI, I'M AFRAID
YOU'VE GOT KIDNEY STONES.
UH... WELL, WHAT ELSE COULD IT BE?
IT'S KIDNEY STONES.
OR...
KIDNEY STONES.
WELL, IF IT WAS SOMETHING ELSE...
THEN THAT WOULD  BE KIDNEY STONES.
ALL RIGHT, YOU'RE GETTING THERE.
OH, AND, YOU KNOW
THESE BABIES ARE VERY, VERY LUCKY.
THEY ARE? WHY?
THEY HAVE THE HONOR OF BEING BORN
ON THE FONZ'S HALF BIRTHDAY.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
JUST TO CLARIFY...
I'M NOT FONZIE.
HONEY, YOU KNOW, I JUST GOT TO TELL YOU.
I THINK THIS IS SUCH A TERRIFIC THING
THAT YOU'RE HAVING THESE BABIES FOR FRANK AND ALICE.
I KNOW IT IS.
CAN I TELL YOU A LITTLE SECRET?
YEAH, WHAT?
I WANT TO KEEP ONE.
OH, I'M GOING TO BE ON THE NEWS.
OKAY, PHOEBE
HONEY, YOU'VE  GOT TO BE KIDDING.
YOU KNOW YOU CAN'T KEEP ONE OF THESE BABIES.
WHY NOT? MAYBE I CAN; YOU DON'T KNOW.
YES, YES, I DO KNOW-- FRANK AND ALICE ARE GOING
TO WANT TO KEEP ALL OF THEIR CHILDREN.
MAYBE NOT, YOU KNOW?
SERIOUSLY-- THREE BABIES ARE A HANDFUL.
MAYBE THEY'RE, YOU KNOW, LOOKING FOR A CHANCE
TO UNLOAD ONE OF THEM.
LISTEN, I'D HATE TO MISS AN OPPORTUNITY
JUST BECAUSE I DIDN'T ASK.
PHOEBE, NO. THIS IS. .. THIS IS INSANE.
OH, JUST ASK HIM.
WHA...? ME?
I CAN'T ASK HIM.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA HOW INAPPROPRIATE THAT WOULD BE?
ALL I'M SAYING IS
JUST TALK TO FRANK, OKAY?
JUST... YOU KN OW, FEEL HIM OUT.
NO. FORGET IT. I AM NOT GOING TO ASK FRANK
TO GIVE YOU ONE OF HIS KIDS.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
OH.
TELL HIM IT'S FOR YOU.
FEELING A LITTLE BETTER, SWEETIE?
WELL, MAYBE A LITTLE.
I WISH YOU HADN'T SEEN ME THROW UP.
ME, TOO.
HEY. I JUST HEARD.
WHAT'S UP?
KIDNEY STONES.
NOW, ORDINARILY, MR. TRIBBIANI
WE TRY TO BREAK THE STONES UP WITH SHOCK WAVES
BUT THEY'RE TOO CLOSE TO THE BLADDER NOW
WHICH MEANS WE CAN EITHER WAIT FOR YOU TO PASS THEM
OR ELSE GO UP THE URETHRA.
WHOA HO!
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
NOTHING IS GOING UP,OKAY?
"UP"-- "UP"  IS NOT AN OPTION.
WHAT'S A URETHRA?
ARE YOU CRAZY?!
SO DID YOU ASK HIM?
NO. I HAVEN'T HAD A CHANCE TO BE ALONE WITH HIM YET.
WELL, I'M KIND OF ON A CLOCK HERE.
OH, FONZIE.
YOU KNOW WHO I ALWAYS LIKED? MORK.
UNDO IT, UNDO IT, UNDO IT.
FONZIE MET MORK.
MORKFROZEFONZIE.
YEAH. UM...
YES, BUT...
FONZIE WAS ALREADY COOL...
SO HE WASN'T HURT, RIGHT?
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
HEY.
HI.
HOW YOU DOING?
OKAY. THE DOCTOR SAYS ANY MINUTE NOW.
HEY, YOU KNOW
ALICE IS GOING TO BE HERE SO SOON.
YOU COULDN'T JUST, LIKE, DO ME A FAVOR AND, LIKE...
LIKE LIKE HOLD THEM IN?
SORRY, FRANK. I'M KIND OF IN THE MIDDLE OF THE LAST FAVOR
YOU ASKED ME TO DO.
HEY.
HI.
RACHEL...
UH, MONICA, THIS IS DAN, ONE OF THE GUYS WE'RE GOING
TO BE GOING OUT WITH ON SATURDAY.
UH, DAN, MONICA.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
HELLO, DAN.
I'M REALLY LOOKING FORWARD TO SATURDAY NIGHT--
REALLY, REALLY!
SO, DAN...
NURSE, NOT A DOCTOR, HUH?
KIND OF GIRLIE, ISN'T IT?
CHANDLER...
NO, THAT'S OKAY; I'M JUST DOING THIS
TO PUT MYSELF THRO UGH MEDICAL SCHOOL.
OH.
AND IT DIDN'T FEEL
SO GIRLIE DURING THE GULF WAR.
SURE.
AND, LISTEN, THANKS FOR DOING THAT FOR US BY THE WAY.
SO WHY WAIT TILL SATURDAY?
ARE YOU FREE TOMORROW?
SURE. I'LL GET SOMEBODY TO COVER MY SHIFT.
AW, GREAT.
HEY, UH, HOW ABOUT IT-- YOU AND ME, SATURDAY NIGHT?
NO.
ALL RIGHT. VERY GOOD.
OOH, THIS IS A BIG ONE.
OH! GET THESE THINGS OUT OF ME!
BREATHE... BREATHE...
BREATHE THROUGH THE PAIN.
I WANT THE DRUGS, ROSS!
I WANT THE DRUGS!
I DO, TOO! I DO, TOO!
YEAH, I LOVE YOU.
OKAY. BYE.
HI.
THAT WAS ALICE'S MOM.
SHE SAID THAT SHE LEFT FIVE HOURS AGO.
SHE SHOULD BE HERE BY NOW.
OH, HONEY, DON'T WORRY. SHE'S GOING TO MAKE IT ON TIME.
YEAH. YEAH.
SO, FRANK... THREE BABIES.
WHOO! THAT JUST SEEMS LIKE A LOT, HUH?
NOT TO ME.
YEAH, FAIR ENOUGH.
OKAY, YOU'RE TEN CENTIMETERS.
TIME TO START HAVING SOME BABIES.
I WANT ONLY THE FATHER IN HERE, PLEASE.
WE LOVE YOU. GOOD LUCK. LOVE YOU.
BYE, DAN.
UH, BYE, MONICA.
UH... BYE .
ALL RIGHT.
I NEED A CLAMP, A STERILE TOWEL AND CHANNEL 31.
WHAT IS THAT?
?? Sunday, Monday, Happy Days ??
?? Tuesday, Wednesday, Happy Days... ??
OH, MY GOD! OH, NO, NO, NO.
IT'S A GOOD ONE.
FONZIE PLAYS THE BONGOS.
ALL RIGHT, YOU READY? IT'S TIME TO TRY PUSHING.
ARE YOU READY? IT'S TIME TO TRY PEEING.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT!
WAIT! WAIT!
IT'SALMOSTTIME TO TRY PEEING.
NOW, PUSH.
NOW, JUST CONCENTRATE ON PUSHING.
YEAH, HERE WE  GO. I SEE THE HEAD.
YES! IT HAS A HEAD!
ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S IT. KEEP PUSHING.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THERE'S SOMEBODY COMING OUT OF YOU.
THERE'S SOMEBODY COMING OUT OF YOU, AND HE'S, HE'S...
THAT'S MY SON!
HERE'S YOUR FIRST BABY.
YES!
YES! WE GOT A BABY BOY!
FRANK, JR., JR.!
OH! HOW DOES HE LOOK? HOW DOES HE LOOK?
SO GROSS!
OKAY, YOU READY TO PUSH AGAIN?
OH, I ALREADY HAD A BABY-- LEAVE ME ALONE.
OKAY, OKAY, COME ON.
YOU CAN DO IT.
YEAH! HA HA!
LITTLE LESLIE'S HERE!
WE GOT ANOTHER ONE!
OH, MY GOD.
I CAN'T BELIEVE I HAVE... TWO CHILDREN.
HOW SCARY IS THAT?
COME ON, LITTLE CHANDLER, IT'S TIME TO BE BORN.
COME ON, LITTLE CHANDLER.
YEP. ALL RIGHT, HE'S COMING.
YEP. HE'S COMING. HE'S COMING.
HEY, WHERE'S HIS THING?
CHANDLER IS A GIRL!
OH, GOD, KINDERGAR TEN FLASHBACK.
WELL, THEY MUST HAVE READ THE SONOGRAM WRONG
BECAUSE THEY BECAUSE THEY THOUGHT IT WAS A BOY
BUT CHANDLER'S A GIRL; CHANDLER'S A GIRL!
OKAY! KEEP SAYING IT!
AM I TOO LATE?
NO, NO. EVERYTHING'S OKAY; EVERYBODY'S HEALTHY.
THERE'S 30 FINGE RS AND 30 TOES.
WE HAVE OUR BABIES?
YEAH...
OH. WE HAVE OUR BABIES.
OH, MY GOD.
YOU DID IT, MAN.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO SEE THEM?
THEY'RE SO SMALL...
SO I'LL CALL YOU TOMORROW.
GREAT.
SO ARE YOU REALLY GOING TO GO OUT WITH THAT NURSE MAN?
WELL, YOU AND I ARE JUST "GOOFING AROUND"
AND I THOUGHT, "WHY NOT JUST GOOF AROUND WITH HIM?"
YOU KNOW, I DON'T KNOW IF YOU'VE EVER LOOKED UP
THE TERM "GOOFING AROUND" IN THE DICTIONARY.
WELL, I HAVE.
AND THE TECHNICAL DEFINITION IS...
TWO FRIENDS WHO CARE A LOT ABOUT EACH OTHER
AND HAVE... AMAZING SEX...
AND JUST WANT
TO SPEND MORE TIME TOGETHER, YOU KNOW?
BUT IF YOU HAVE THIS NEWFANGLED DICTIONARY
THAT GETS YOU MAD AT ME, THEN WE HAVE TO
YOU KNOW, GET YOU, MY ORIGINAL DICTIONARY.
I AM SO BAD AT THIS.
I THINK YOU'RE BETTER THAN YOU THINK YOU ARE.
REALLY?
OKAY. SO IF...
KNOW WHEN TO STOP.
YOU KNOW, I SENSED THAT I SHOULD STOP.
MM HMM.
SO, WE'RE OKAY?
YEAH. ALL RIGHT, I'M GOING TO GO TELL DAN
THAT IT'S NOT GOING TO HAPPEN.
DON'T DO THE DANCE.
RIGHT.
I THINK YOU'RE MY FAVORITE.
WHICH ONE DO YOU HAVE?
I DON'T CARE.
HI.
HEY.
SO FRANK AND ALICE WANTED ME TO TELL YOU
THEY'RE STILL OUTSIDE, MAKING PHONE CALLS.
OH. BUT, UM, I MEAN
DID YOU TALK TO THEM ABOUT... YOU KNOW?
YEAH.
UM...
NO, HONEY.
OH, OKAY.
IT WAS A LONG SHOT.
HEY, YOU GUYS, CAN I JUST HAVE
LIKE, A SECOND ALONE WITH THE BABIES?
OH, YEAH, SURE.
YEAH.
THANKS.
SO HERE YOU ARE.
SEEMS LIKE YESTERDAY
I WAS TALKING TO YOU IN THAT LITTLE PETRI DISH.
EVERYONE SAID LABOR WAS THE HARDEST THING
I'D EVER HAVE TO DO, BUT THEY WERE WRONG.
THIS IS.
WELL, I HAD THE MOST FUN WITH YOU GUYS...
AND I WISH I COULD TAKE YOU HOME AND SEE YOU EVERY DAY, BUT...
OKAY, I'LL SETTLE FOR BEING YOUR FAVORITE AUNT.
I KNOW ALICE'S SISTER HAS A POOL, BUT YOU LIVED INME.
OKAY, SO WE'RE COOL.
YEAH, WE'RE GOING TO BE GREAT.
OKAY?
LITTLE HIGH FIVES?
HI! HI! HI!
OH...
WELL, IF YOU'RE GOING TO CRY...
PHOEBE, WE ARE SO PROUD OF YOU.
YOU'RE AMAZING.
I KNOW.
DOES IT REALLY HURT AS BAD AS THEY SAY?
YEAH. YOU WON'T BE ABLE TO TAKE IT.
SO, NOW THAT LITTLE CHANDLER TURNED OUT TO BE A GIRL
WHAT ARE THEY GOING TO NAME HER?
THEY'RE GOING TO CALL HER CHANDLER.
THAT'S KIND OF A MASCULI NE NAME, DON'T YOU THINK?
WORKS ON YOU.
WELL, MAYBE THEY CAN GIRLIE IT UP A LITTLE BIT
LIKE, UH, CHANDLERETTE.
I THINK I HEARD ALICE CALL HER, UM, CHANNY FANNY.
HA HA-- CHANNY FANNY.